Chapter 201

Mixed Bath (1)

◆

The center of the Imperial City.

The Academy's walls rise high in the center of the bridge over the gently flowing waterway.

The bridge is quiet at dawn. There are few passersby along the usually bustling streets, only a few hardworking individuals who have started their day early.

Vikir crosses the bridge and makes his way to the Academy.

Slowly, slowly.

He was in worse shape than he thought.

The blood from his back had congealed and stopped bleeding, but the energy that had been drained from him was slow to return.

'Even with the resilience I gained by changing into a dog's body, I'll barely be able to survive this... in a human body.'

Perhaps in a human body, he would have passed out already.

With that, Vikir dragged his crumbling body and barely made it to the outer walls of the academy.

Hack.

A black puppy walking with its tongue hanging out.

The guards patrolling the Academy's outer walls spotted Vikir like that.

“What a cute little puppy, and he's so tiny.”

“Hey, hey, don't touch him. It looks like a sick dog. What if it gets something dirty?”

“It's dirty, let's get rid of it.”

One of the guards tried to pet Vikir, but the other guard next to him stopped him.

Pow!

The other guard walked out with a sullen look on his face and kicked Vikir.

Getting his ass handed to him, Vikir was forced to walk away.

The guards giggled at Vikir and then walked away without looking back.

'...What a pitiful stray dog.'

It's not like I hadn't been on the streets before, so I knew that life on the streets was hard.

However, the feeling of the streets for humans and the feeling of the streets for dogs were worlds apart.

Vikir gritted his teeth and stuck to the outside of the wall.

He walked as close to the wall as he could without being seen.

Even a casual passerby would be wary and move away.

He didn't know when he would be attacked again.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, look!”

A drunken passerby pulls a sausage out of his pocket and throws it at him, but of course he doesn't eat it.

In fact, it only makes him move further away from the dangerous creature.

“What a stubborn dog.”

The drunk shakes the sausage a few times before dropping it on the ground and walking away.

'....'

Vikir walks silently against the wall.

His eyes scanning his surroundings, but his mind replaying the previous battle with the Eight Corpse.

Snake Morgue should have been the Corpse King long ago.

Cindywendy had given him a progress report not long ago, and so far he hasn't shown any signs of disturbance.

'Looks like he's still human.'

And at that point, the Corpse Queen appeared. What does this mean?

The corpse of Geronto and Ah'Heman.

And the last thing she said was....

There was more to think about.

When it came down to it, the main reason he couldn't end the Corpse Queen's life was his lack of swordsmanship.

Vikir remembered Hugo's performance against Andromalius.

The seven teeth he had created with a single blow, the upper and lower jaws that had closed like the gills of a monster, the way he had split the sky in seven.

They were the same Baskerville seven, but Vikir's seven and Hugo's seven were different.

That would be the gap between Graduotor and Swordmaster.

However, there was a moment when Vikir crossed the gap and reached the level of Master.

It was against Dantalian, when he received the buff from Saintess Dolores.

For a brief moment, Vikir's power rivaled Hugo's, and he was able to turn Dantalian's back on him.

The problem is, even without the saintess's help, you need to be able to summon that much power to survive the fight ahead.

If you want to reach the peak of your powers as soon as possible, you need to............

'...I've lost too much blood, and my thoughts keep getting interrupted.'

I have a lot to think about, but my concentration is slipping.

He needed to find a safe place to rest before he could formulate his next plan and take action.

'Let's get back to the academy. I need to get to my dorm or the infirmary and get some sleep....'

Vikir dug his forepaws into the ground and made a burrow.

The opening beneath the rampart-like wall had been filled with softened soil and fallen leaves, making it easy to dig back in.

Vikir had just dug a hole under the wall and entered the academy.

He heard the sound of laughter from the bushes.

“Ugh, I've been drinking too much, I'm getting sleepy.”

“Let's just burn this one and get back inside.”

“It's almost dawn.”

Three boys and three girls were leaning against the fence, flirting.

They reeked of alcohol and cigarettes and hadn't slept until this hour.

Vikir saw the scars that still marked their foreheads.

X

The scars are familiar.

Because they were all made by Vikir himself.

'...The sophomores who used to bully Pigi.'

A bunch of low-life scumbags who thought it was the beginning of the school year and picked on Pigi because he was nervous.

So Vikir had followed them, masked, and once dragged them into a back alley to give them a good beating when they went outside the academy.

At that point, Vikir pulled out a sword and carved a cross-shaped scar into the bullies' foreheads.

'If you ever make a nuisance of yourselves inside the academy again, I will not only kill you, but also your father and mother,' he said.

The murderous threat was a bonus.

Ever since they'd been beaten to a pulp by the masked Vikir, the six had been living like rats in the academy.

They usually insulted and bullied not only their juniors, but also their classmates, even their seniors, if they seemed a little weak.

However, if they think they are stronger or have a higher status than them, they are despicable servants who will fart and grovel, regardless of whether they are a junior, classmate, or senior.

But after being exposed to overwhelming violence and fear, they barely breathe inside the academy.

Who? Who had paid for the assault? And then to harm their parents?

There were too many people to pinpoint the culprits.

All they could do was grit their teeth and relive the karma they had accumulated, not knowing when or where retribution would strike again.

Once the bullies were silenced, there were fewer problems in the academy.

...But, did I mention that people are not meant to be fixed?

They were hiding in fear of being watched, but their caution didn't extend to the puppy, who had nowhere to go.

“Huh? What the fuck, asshole.”

One of the boys, who had been drinking from a bottle, spotted Vikir emerging from the bushes.

Vikir turned his head to look away. The dog's body had recovered quickly, but the wounds on his body still hadn't fully healed.

The six sophomores giggled and surrounded Vikir.

“Hey, is it okay for stray dogs to roam around the academy like this?”

“They'll spread disease. Let's clean it up. It's a nice thing to do, picking up trash.”

“I've been under a lot of stress lately. Let's tie him up somewhere.”

“Shall we burn it alive?”

“Awww, poor thing, just throw him in the sewer over there and be done with it.”

“Ah, I suddenly remember that masked bastard. Next time I see him, I'm going to carve a knife mark in his skull just like that. Let's practice first and carve it into that bastard's body.”

The six bullies giggle, holding cigarette butts and daggers in their hands.

Several throw lit cigarette butts at Vikir, and a few throw liquor bottles at him, shattering them.

Spitting and kicking were commonplace.

Vikir thought for a moment.

'Maybe I should just kill them.'

It takes strength to endure, and when you're in such bad shape, it's hard to endure.

No matter how badly he was injured, if he were back in his human form, he could probably make six heads roll on the floor in a second, or even half a second.

In fact, I could probably do it in a dog's body.

But that would mean a big headline in the Academy's morning paper tomorrow.

.

It'll set other dogs and cats on fire.

I don't have a place to dispose of the body, and I don't have the stamina to do so.

Especially since my eyelids kept trying to close earlier.

[Growl...]

A small cry came from above, barely audible to Vikir's ears.

He looked up to see the cub perched on the wall, its fur standing upright, looking down at him.

It looked like it might jump at any moment.

But Vikir shook his head.

The second-year students at Colosseo Academy are strong in their own way.

Six of them together would be a formidable foe for a young cub.

'I can't help it, I have to take on a human form for a while....'

Vikir was mulling over the various ways to dispose of a corpse without leaving a trace in his head.

“Cold Warrior, second year, class B.”

An extremely dry and cold voice came from somewhere.

“Attendance No. 8, Pal Uspear, No. 29, Betty Realbelt, No. 58, Houser Yellop, No. 63, Seaweed Aimecom, No. 66, Bison Redmin, No. 71, Oiler Southmiddle.”

A voice calling out the attendance numbers and names of the six scumbags, letter by letter.

“...What do you guys think you're doing?”

An unexpected source appeared.

A female student holding a bowl of food in one hand and a bowl of water in the other.

It was the student council president, Dolores L. Quovadis.

Chapter 203

Mixed Bath (3)

◆

Vikir was a little, well, a lot, embarrassed.

“Choco, your sister is here, too. Let's wash together!”

Saintess Dolores came into the bathroom.

Dolores L. Quovadis, who is she?

A saintess of the former world who appeared during the Age of Destruction.

A hero of the ages, healing the wounded and slaying evil.

During the Warring States Period, when many small countries were proliferating, she was evaluated as much more than Saint Joan de Arc or Saint Helena, the classical saints whose names were widely known across the continent.

The authority and sanctity of Dolores' name in the Age of Destruction, when blood flowed like rivers and corpses made mountains, was comparable to that of a goddess.

...And?

I never thought I'd see Dolores with my own eyes as she entered the bathroom to bathe.

Vikir closed his eyes tightly and swallowed hard.

'Of course I don't have any unholy feelings of lust or anything.'

'...But regardless of that, if my comrades saw this, they would try to kill me.'

For those comrades who shared the battle against the Demon World, Dolores was an object of worship.

In those days, everyone owed her their lives at one time or another, great or small.

So, knowing that Vikir is now sharing a bathroom with Dolores in the form of a dog would certainly raise eyebrows.

Especially those of the Paladin class, who would surely draw their swords at the blasphemy.

'I apologize, comrades. I'll get out of here as soon as I can.'

Vikir felt a surge of guilt and quickly tried to get out of the bathtub.

Of course.

“Choco, where are you going, you should be bathing with your sister!”

Dolores smiled brightly and grabbed Vikir's body, pulling him back into the tub.

Dolores then began to scrub Vikir's body with a light lather of soap.

“What are you, a little kid, with all these scars, did you get into a fight with the other kids?”

“....”

Vikir closed his eyes and tried to stay as still as possible.

But there was no way to escape the gentle touch as it ravaged every inch of his body.

'It is said that the Rune Gods are manipulators of cause and effect. If so, the god of this world must be a delusional man with a grim ego.'

Vikir gritted his teeth in internal blasphemy.

Dolores, meanwhile, pulled Vikir into her arms and soaked in the herbal bath.

“Ah, it's warm. Choco, right?”

“....”

“I work so hard to clean you, and you don't clean me? It's a little unfair, isn't it?”

“....”

Meanwhile, Vikir was forced to blaspheme once more.

Regardless, Vikir felt his body recovering.

The wounds inflicted by the Lich and the Ragged Golem, two high-ranking undead, were healing quickly.

Internal wounds that were not easily healed, even with the resilience of a dog's flesh, were healing, and his depleted mana was rapidly replenishing.

When Vikir closed his eyes and remained motionless, Dolores said curiously.

“What? You closed your eyes, that feels good, my choco, huh? Ooooooo~”

“....”

But Vikir was thinking of something else entirely.

'If I want to reach Swordmaster, I need to change my training methods a bit.'

A good idea... no, a thought for the Path of salvation.

Vikir began to closely analyze his mana and sword skills.

His current aura was at the level of a sticky liquid, the highest level of the Graduator.

My swordsmanship is at the level of a Baskerville Sixth Form Master, barely scratching the surface of the Seventh Form.

To reach the level of Swordmaster, you must be able to solidify the density of your aura to the level of a solid, and you must also master the Seventh Form.

'...Baskerville 7th Form.'

Currently, the only person who has mastered the Seventh Form is the head of the family, Hugo Le Baskerville.

Considering the prowess he displayed when he slaughtered Andromalius, there was a huge gap between Hugo's 7th and Vikir's 7th.

'Baskerville's teeth are used for biting, chewing, cutting, crushing, and mincing prey. The sword itself resembles the upper and lower jaws of a hunting dog. The seventh tooth, in particular, is crucial in its connection to the sixth, and to fully realize the look of this 'ambush horizontal bicuspid canine'....'

Vikir is deliberately and diligently rolling his hair.

But Vikir's preconceptions are quickly shattered.

“Wow – look at the pink jelly on his paws.”

Dolores lifted Vikir's front paw and kissed the pads.

She stroked his head, pressed his cheeks, touched his chin, and rubbed his belly, and Vikir couldn't think straight.

Finally, Dolores wiped the foam from the tip of Vikir's nose with the tip of her own and said.

“Dogs usually kiss often.”

“....”

“You don't give me kisses. It's a shame.”

“....”

“Are you sure you're a dog? This is suspicious.”

Dolores cupped Vikir's cheeks and laughed.

And the moment he heard the words.

The words-

Vikir's heart sank.

'If she's found out I'm not a dog, it's over.'

He couldn't imagine what terrible things would happen then.

Perhaps I'd have to wage a bloody slaughter against the entire Inquisition of Quovadis, who would be enraged....

'If that were to happen, Baskerville might be moved.'

The Baskervilles and the Quovadis are the backbone of the Empire.

If war were to break out between these two families, it would be on a scale as large as any of the nation-state wars of the Warring States period before the unification of the Empire.

In that case, it might be better to close your eyes once and for all.

We can't afford to cause internal strife among mankind in the face of an annihilation war with the demons.

...In many ways, I can't help it.

'I'm sorry, comrades.'

Vikir closed his eyes and did something he had never done before in his entire life: deviate.

Jjog-

He ran his tongue across Dolores's cheek once.

And Dolores, who was kissed by Vikir, said.

“Awww, how cute!”

She hugged Vikir tightly and bombarded him with kisses.

This was also an unexpected accident.

◆

The long but short bath was over.

Dolores stepped out of the bathroom, dried herself off, and went straight to bed.

In the third year, everyone is in a single-occupancy room, and the bed is narrow for a single person.

Dolores pulled the blankets over her and hugged Vikir tightly.

“It's good to have someone to talk to and fall asleep with tonight.”

Vikir did not escape her lips on his nose again.

After a while, Dolores lay down with Vikir in her arms and opened her mouth.

“Many people come to me for counseling, confessing their vices and misdeeds, seeking indulgence and repentance.”

“....”

“But I have no one to whom I can confide my troubles or misdeeds. Where can I go to confess?”

Vikir closed his eyes and thought.

Once, while fighting Dantalian, Vikir had experienced a strong connection with her spirit when the Awakened Dolores had buffed him.

Dolores' words from that time came back to her now.

'Everyone in the world confesses their sins and pours out their troubles to me,... but to whom do I confess my sins and pour out my troubles?'

Sometimes it's not enough to talk to God. There are moments when you want to talk to a fellow human being.

Coincidentally, Dolores was confiding in the Night Hound about the same thing.

Although she doesn't recognize them as the same person.

Dolores' relationship with her father, who was divided between the Old and New Testaments. Tired of always being the model student, the one who is expected to do well. Always having to be good, always having to perform well, and only being good enough. A life where one slip-up is met with consternation and undue criticism....

All of this pressure weighs heavily on Dolores' shoulders.

Dolores looked at Vikir and said.

“It's strange that I'm saying all this to you, it feels strangely familiar.”

“....”

Vikir closed his eyes wordlessly.

Hadn't she been told once that she could read the souls of her subjects?

Her ability, though still faint, seems to be growing.

Is that why?

Dolores confided to Vikir one of the biggest questions that had been on her mind lately.

“Am I going to die a virgin, never having held a man's hand in my life?”

At the same time, Dolores squeezed Vikir's front paw.

She closed her eyes and whispered in Vikir's ear.

“Actually, there's a guy who's been bothering me a bit lately.”

The words came as a surprise. Vikir perked up one ear.

What kind of man could be on the mind of Dolores of all people?

'I don't know who it is, but... must be the enemy of many men.'

Vikir thought quietly to himself.

If Dolores had spoken these words during the Age of Destruction, many men would have been outraged.

After all, she was the idol of the age.

Meanwhile.

Dolores held Vikir tightly in her arms and pictured a nameless, faceless man in her mind.

The Night Hound.

A man who had saved her from a terrifying demon, who had kept a terrible plague at bay, who had taken her under his wing when she felt unappreciated and unwanted.

If he wasn't that kind of man, was there any man in the world who could handle herself?

Dolores thought so.

An unknown, but good man. A handsome man.

A man with enough power to defeat a mighty demon, but who would still help the sick and poor, covered in filth and profanity, and who understood their pain.

'And... then the demon said he was handsome, too.'

Dolores blushed for a moment.

She didn't think a person's appearance was important, but... well, it couldn't hurt to be good-looking, could it? She decided to think so.

After taking a bath and lying naked on the fluffy bedding, she drifted off to sleep.

'Oh well. I still have some work to do today. I need to write to the Pope and ask him about the phenomena of 'awakening' and 'resonance' in saints....'

But at dawn, when the weight of her eyelids was the heaviest in the world, Dolores finally fell asleep.

She fell into a deep sleep, her face glowing.

And.

“....”

A hound stares down at her sleeping face.

And then.

Beep-.

The window opened.

“I owe you ....”

The hound, now fully recovered, began to melt into the darkness once more.

Chapter 204

Festival Night (1)

◆

The day has dawned.

The exam period was over, and there was a holiday over the weekend, a perfect time to relax.

And the students of the Academy were using this time to discuss the upcoming festival.

The festival planning committee decided that each class or club should come up with a concept for the festival, which was also the case for the students of the newspaper club Ryukeion.

Dolores, the student council president and the club's leader, nodded.

“Our club is doing a haunted house and a bar, right?”

Halloween in the Empire falls in late summer.

It was the perfect excuse to celebrate, especially since they had just been released from a grueling exam.

“Well, then, let's decide in advance which ghost you're going to dress up as.”

At Tudor's words, the first, second, and third years all nodded.

Then. Bianca spoke up.

“But 'the tradition', is it still in effect this time?”

Bianca's words brought everyone's eyes together.

There was no one who didn't understand what she was saying.

At the Academy, men always disguise themselves as women and women as men during festivals.

It's a time-honored tradition that even the professors can't escape.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and all the other members of the class had an idea.

“So we'll have the men dress up as female ghosts and the women as male ghosts.”

“Right. That's right, we'll dress up as ghosts and switch genders.”

“But are there separate female ghosts and male ghosts?”

“No, there's no such thing as a female ghost and a male ghost, you just switch genders while wearing the ghost costume. For example, there are female zombies and male zombies.”

“And then we can serve drinks or meals as them!”

“Okay, so let's draw lots for which ghost we'll each dress up as.”

“Okay, let's draw lots for freshmen, sophomores, juniors, and seniors.”

“That's a good idea, since each grade has a different number and gender ratio.”

Next, the members drew a lot from the box.

Tudor was the first to draw a lot.

Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.

The scraps of paper in the box brushed against his fingertips.

He had to be careful, because if he picked the wrong lot, he could be stuffed into black history.

“Please give me the one that's okay....”

Tudor closed his eyes, prayed, and grabbed the scrap of paper.

He unfolded the tightly folded lot to reveal the concept of the ghost.

.

“Ah, this will do, and I don't particularly care what gender.”

With black armor and a bloody sword, anyone can dress up as a Death Knight, regardless of gender.

Tudor had kept his blue eyes and blond hair intact, and he'd simply added long hair.

It was a handsome look, but as with his previous cross-dressing trials, the lines were bold and the look didn't quite work.

Next, Sancho drew his lot.

As a warrior who grew up on the frozen soil of the north, Sancho got the concept of a ghost with a cold image.

“Ugh. I don't like this role.”

Unlike roles such as zombies and vampires, the Snow Maiden is a role that definitely requires cross-dressing, which is not good for men.

When the makeup was applied to his muscular body, Tudor burst out laughing.

“Isn't it an ice golem, not a snow maiden?”

“Hahahaha- Let It Go, buddy.”

Everyone laughed hilariously at Sancho's unsuccessful attempt at cross-dressing.

Fortunately, Sancho didn't seem to mind cross-dressing.

After all, he firmly believes that cross-dressing is something that only men can do, so it's a manly act.

After that, Pigi also drew a lot.

Pigi is now able to show off his tiny, cute appearance to the fullest.

With the wings on his back, he looks like a real fairy.

Next up was Bianca.

Bianca has stitches all over her body and nails in her hair.

Her mustache was a bonus.

She was naturally tall and attractive and androgynous, so this makeup suited her perfectly.

“Okay, next up is....”

Bianca turned her head to see Sinclaire standing there.

However, Sinclaire seemed to have something else in mind.

“You know, I've been working on a costume.”

“Really? What is it?”

Bianca's eyes widened. She hadn't expected Sinclaire to be so enthusiastic about dressing up for Halloween.

Next, Sinclaire opened her bag and pulled out the costume she'd brought.

It was a single, giant spider with clumsy sewing.

On top of her head was a tiny crown.

“Ta-da- It's the Spider Queen. How is it?”

“Ohhh. I didn't realize you liked spiders so much. By the way, didn't you scream like crazy the other day when a spider came out of the bathroom?”

“Yeah, did I? I remember it well... Anyway, I love spiders!”

Bianca can only shake her head at Sinclaire's almost apologetic tone.

And then.

Everyone's eyes moved toward the same spot.

The one person whose turn it was to draw lots.

“....”

A tired-looking Vikir stood up from his seat.

Drat.

Everyone swallowed hard from the tension as Vikir's chair was pushed back.

For some reason, what Vikir would choose was of considerable interest to the entire academy.

There were already reporters from the Cold Class with cameras ready to capture the mana screen.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi murmured with envious glances.

“I heard there was a line from first years to fourth years lined up to take part in dressing up Vikir?”

“I heard that even the Imperial Palace's makeup artists have formally applied to the Academy.”

“Apparently, the Empire's most prestigious magazines are paying big bucks for Vikir's cross-dressing photos.”

Of course, all of these outside approaches were dismissed out of hand in the interest of protecting the Academy's students.

Professor Banshee Morgue, in a fit of irritation, rejected all applications and requests for interviews.

Next. Vikir's lot was revealed.

A ghost with a perfect female concept. It is a role that requires a delicate and complete makeup like the Snow Queen.

If any male student had picked this lot, the audience would have burst into laughter.

Just like Sancho did once.

But.

“....”

“....”

“....”

No one in the room laughed at Vikir's role.

Instead, there was a strange sense of unidentifiable anticipation in the room.

Soon, a witch's costume was thrust in front of Vikir.

A black hat, a black cloak, a tattered broom, and long, black false nails.

It was a witchy look, ready to cast forbidden black magic at a moment's notice.

But the quality of the witch's outfit was already the focus of attention.

The girls who had been assigned to make up Vikir's face had a blank look on their faces.

“Wow, it's really a waste to watch it alone.”

“...Is he really a guy, right?”

“This mana screen is going to be a big hit in tomorrow's newspaper.”

Amidst the chatter, Vikir's brow furrowed slightly.

White skin, a sharp nose, blood-red lips, and eyelashes so long they could have fallen as snow.

With makeup on, Vikir looked pretty, like a face not of this world.

So much so that the boys watching were confused about his gender identity.

It's no wonder that the native tribes of the Depth Black Mountain started a war of aggression after learning of Vikir's appearance.

...However, Vikir himself was uncomfortable with these reactions.

'This never happened in my previous life.'

Before his regression, Vikir was more used to being looked at with disdain.

He was much shorter and thinner-boned than he is now, and a childhood injury had left him with a limp.

His face was scarred with knife marks and burns from his various missions.

The sight of Vikir's face made girls his own age, as well as younger and older women, cry or run away.

Of course, the younger, prettier ladies of the academy wouldn't even deal with him.

They would give him disdainful glances or even spit on him. They would throw away anything he happened to touch.

They even avoided being in the same room together, not wanting to breathe the same air.

Of course, as a hunting dog, Vikir was trained to be completely emotionless, so he wasn't hurt by any of this.

However.

In this life, he ate well, grew taller, and didn't have a single scar on his face.

This was quite a change from what he had expected, and it was not easy for Vikir to adjust.

“...Hmm.”

Vikir furrowed his brow once, and the room erupted into an uproar.

“Vikir, why, what's wrong, just tell me!”

“Are you thirsty? Are you hungry? Are you stuffy? Are you uncomfortable somewhere? Can I get you something to drink?”

“Are your clothes too tight? Should I loosen the corset on your back? Are your high heels the right size? Are your toes hurting?”

“Are the eyelashes too heavy? Are these your original eyelashes? Is the makeup too dark? Are you feeling stuffy? Should I lighten the makeup and make sure your skin doesn't have any blemishes? Ugh....”

“Isn't it too sunny by the window? I'll cover it with my back!”

“By the way, do you have a sister, does she look like you, and if so, can I call you brother-in-law?”

“Hey, this is a big deal. Everyone, block behind me, If this face leaks, it will at least be stampede!”

“But are you a witch or an angel? You look like one.”

“Oh, Rune, this is the face I'll be wearing to confession tonight... Please forgive this lustful lamb....”

Just then.

“Huh!”

A startled whistling noise was heard from the other side of the club room.

Everyone, who had been focusing on Vikir's face, turned their heads to see a third year student holding a box of lots, his face white as a sheet.

Standing there was Dolores, who had just plucked a lot.

“....”

She looked at the lot in her hand with a thoughtful expression.

The part Dolores was to play at this festival.

The words were written inside the swallow.

Chapter 205

Festival Night (2)

◆

The festival has begun.

Numerous stalls were set up inside the academy.

Lively music echoed here and there, and colorful lights lit up the night.

Huge stacks of food were piled high and overflowing, with men and women coming and going in colorful costumes.

Everyone enjoying the festival was dressed as a ghost.

Most were zombies or skeletons, with the occasional vampire or mummy.

The same was true for Ryukeion, the newspaper club that opened the bar.

“Welcome to a ghostly bar with romance and chivalry!”

“The snacks are friendly and the boss is delicious! Come on in!”

“Sancho! The snacks and the boss have changed!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi are hard at work hawking their wares.

Tudor, dressed in black armor and a Death Knight costume, was wooing female customers with talk of chivalry and romance.

“Beautiful lady, why don't you join me in Ryukeion's bar to discuss drink and poetry?”

“Kaaaak- okay!”

“You look like a wandering knight!”

Sancho, dressed as a Snow Maiden, was a favorite among his fellow muscular macho men.

“Wahahaha- come to Ryukeion's bar! If you stay until 9pm, I'll serve you blood stew as hot as a warrior's boiling blood!”

“Ho-ho, that must be a hunk of protein and iron, I can make up for my muscle loss, I can aim for three tons!”

“Cross-dressing, you're dressed quite manly, aren't you, hahaha- go now!”

Pigi, dressed as a fairy, is also attracting quite a bit of attention among the women.

“Hey, hey, hey. Over here, I need a flyer!”

“What? Look at this cute kid. Are you a student at the academy too?”

“If it's a concept that stimulates maternal love, it's a success, huh, ho-ho-ho- come on, my sisters will buy it for you.”

As a result, the front of Ryukeion's bar was bustling with people.

Meanwhile.

“Hey, this is such a blasphemous outfit, won't it cause a controversy? Who wears a swallow like this....”

Saintess Dolores hesitated in the back of the bar.

Black leather gloves, black cloak, boots, and a plague doctor's mask covering his entire face.

It was the look of a Night Hound.

Tudor walked by and laughed at Dolores.

“A bit of a social controversy, the Night Hound.”

“ ... Is that true?”

“Still, the plague doctor mask isn't the only trademark of the Night Hound, is it? It's a look that's often seen on Halloween, and it's always been a part of the festivities. Wouldn't it be weird if we banned a certain costume because of the Night Hounds?”

If you look at the bar next door to us, there are often people wearing plague doctor masks.

It's been a staple of Halloween celebrations since the beginning of the Empire, so I don't think it's something that should be enforced.

“....”

Dolores was conflicted.

Only she knew that the Night Hound was innocent.

But that didn't mean she shouldn't be dressed in a way that might make some people uncomfortable.

Dolores was just deciding whether or not to step out in front of the tent.

“What is that outfit?”

As expected, there's someone who doesn't like Dolores' outfit.

Professor Banshee Morgue. In addition to being the professor of the Hot Class, he was also the advisor to Ryukeion of the newspaper department.

“President Dolores. I didn't expect you to dress so inconsiderately.”

“....”

“Even though it's a festival you enjoy without thinking about, you wouldn't say you didn't think about the social repercussions your outfit would cause, right? How can you possibly imitate such an irredeemable trash criminal?”

Professor Banshee's criticism was harsh.

His words were well within the realm of rational understanding, but the last line cut deeply into Dolores's emotions.

'He is not a criminal, but rather a holy and sublime...!'

But Dolores couldn't shout that.

It would be against the will of the Night Hound, who did not want to reveal his identity.

So Dolores decided to be bold.

“I like this outfit.”

“...What?”

“I'll be serving like this.”

Professor Banshee's mouth dropped open in disbelief as Dolores bit her lip tightly.

“I'm disappointed in you, Ms. Dolores. I thought you were a smart student, even if you are young.”

“....”

“Well, you'll have to take responsibility for your own behavior. Even though I'm your advisor, I have no right to interfere with your attire, so do whatever you want.”

Professor Banshee clicked her tongue in frustration and returned to the tent.

Meanwhile, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi, who had been watching, were gossiping amongst themselves.

“What's going on? Professor Banshee is here. Why is he here?”

“Professor Banshee isn't the only one. There are other professors.”

“Usually, during the festival, the professors go around to the bars in each division and class to make sales.”

That's right. Professors enjoy the festival too.

It was an unspoken custom among professors to visit the bars of the students they were responsible for and sell them alcohol and snacks, giving them compliments and attracting other customers.

Thus, Professor Banshee Morgue had come to the bar here in Ryukeion today.

But.

None of the students working in the bar welcomed Professor Banshee's visit.

That's right....

“Tsk!”

Professor Banshee took a bite of the food Tudor had brought him and spit it right back out on the floor.

“This chicken is so undercooked that if a skilled veterinarian treats it, it could be saved.”

That wasn't all.

Professor Banshee continued to lash out at the food that followed.

“It's a good thing the empire is united, because if there were still many other nations on the continent, they'd surely be greedy for oil and invade these pork chops.”

“You'd better keep this beef separate from the salad, it's so undercooked I think it's still alive, and it's still trying to eat the salad next to it.”

“What a fine mace. It's hard and heavy, so I can crush the head of my enemy at any time. Oh, and by the way, is the bread I ordered still here?”

“If I had to choose the most delicious thing on this table, I would choose this water without hesitation. Of course, even this water is dry and hard.”

“These beans are so undercooked that if they do well, I might plant them and hope for another year.”

“This pork isn't cooked at all, can't you hear the Hakuna Matata that this pork is singing.”

Professor Banshee is known for having an incredibly picky palate.

The students working in the kitchen began to resent his relentless taste assessments.

Dolores, who was less than impressed, stepped forward.

“If you're going to make so many complaints, why did you bother visiting?”

“I don't want to visit either. But it's customary among professors to go to the bars of their students and give them a boost in sales, which is why I'm sitting here in this dirty chair, eating low-quality ingredients, poor hygiene, and condiment-laden food served by workers who don't pay taxes and don't have health certificates, even though the food isn't cheap and they only take cash, so it's not tax deductible and I don't get a cash receipt.”

Not even Dolores can argue with Banshee's point.

Professor Banshee looks down at the fried potatoes and chicken dish in front of him in disgust.

“But if it had any flavor, I wouldn't be complaining about it. Taste is the most important thing, and the absence of it makes the bad stuff seem even more pronounced, doesn't it? There's nothing to see here, this snack probably tastes like waste....”

However. After scooping up a spoonful of chicken and potatoes, Professor Banshee couldn't finish his sentence.

Tasty.

Delicious.

It was definitely delicious.

“...What is it? Why is it delicious?”

The subtle flavor of fire, the richness of the bone broth from the shredded chicken, the savory flavor from the soft crunch of Morgue's specialty potatoes, and the tangy, salty taste from the mysterious red sauce.

“Holy... this is definitely a flavor I've had before, but only in the most prestigious restaurants in the Imperial City, not in a bar at an academy festival like this?”

Professor Banshee scooped up a few more spoonfuls of chicken stew and looked up.

“Who made this? Did they bring in a professional chef from out of town?”

“I doubt it.”

Dolores looks a little puzzled, too.

Just then, a passing Tudor turned his head.

“Ah, so it's to your liking? By the way, I just replaced the chef in charge of the kitchen.”

“Replacing the chef? With who?”

“Well, there's this one guy who's an unusually good cook, and he decided to take over the entire kitchen, and there-”

Tudor pointed a finger, and the heads of Professor Banshee and President Dolores turned.

Then, beyond their feet in the kitchen, they saw a face holding a large frying pan to the flames.

Kurrrk...

A sharp nose, dark eyebrows, flawless white skin, and eyes like a lake of blood.

A schoolgirl in a black hat and cloak stirs a wok with mystical flames.

A slight frown, beads of sweat on her forehead.

But her face, bathed in firelight, is mesmerizing.

It was like watching a witch possess and control her victims with her flavor.

Both Professor Banshee and Dolores are stunned by the sight.

“Was there a girl like that in our class?”

The scene was so magical that even the great Professor Banshee was mesmerized for a moment.

But then Tudor's voice interrupted their reverie.

“Professor. Have you forgotten the traditions of our academy?”

“...?”

Professor Banshee shook his head, unable to understand Tudor's words.

Then an exclamation point appeared above his head.

“...!”

That's right.

There is a long-standing tradition at the Academy.

It's called TS.

Men to women, women to men.

In other words, the bewitched witch in the kitchen is a boy dressed as a girl.

And the boy's identity was obvious.

“Order! Three plates of Vikir's special chicken stew, two plates of Vikir's special seafood, six plates of Vikir's special sausage vegetable stir-fry, five plates of Vikir's special meatball rice balls, and another Vikir's special....”

“Uh-huh! Look guys! Another new menu! How in the world did you manage to make such delicious snacks out of leftover ingredients? What's the name of this? What? Nothing? It's just made with leftover ingredients? Let's put this on the menu as soon as possible! This is the 32nd special new menu!”

“Ugh! Ever since we opened the kitchen to the public, we've been getting too many male customers! At this rate, we'd better reveal that this is a guy!”

“Oh no! This time it's the girls! Get more number tags!”

“No! The number of male customers hasn't decreased at all! In fact, they've increased! What's going on?”

The staff is silently taking in the rush of orders.

He's a student, but he's incredibly skilled at creating simple, practical, and delicious dishes.

It was Vikir.

Chapter 206

Festival Night (3)

◆

Vikir, dressed as a witch, was stir-frying vegetables and meat.

A limited amount and quality of ingredients.

But the number of dishes that could be made from their combination is endless.

'Memories. I used to eat this a lot in the field.'

Vikir dipped a piece of dry bread into the milk, reminiscing about the past before the regression.

As the Age of Destruction dragged on, the more food ran out.

Most of the supplies brought to the front lines were burned by demon raids, and what little did arrive was stolen or embezzled by the higher-ups.

What did eventually fall into the hands of officers and soldiers at the end of the line withered, rotted, or spoiled.

Aside from their anger, the men on the front lines had to make the most of this extremely limited food supply.

Along the way, Vikir learned a lot from his comrades.

How to prepare inedible ingredients to make them edible, what parts of poisonous vegetables to remove, how to restore freshness to meat that has lost its flavor, how to make astringent, bitter, or sour vegetables palatable, how to kill the individuality of spices that are too intense to be liked or disliked, how to make them taste universally acceptable, how to boil, how to stew, how to bake, how to grill, how to steam, how to stir-fry....

Now, Vikir was using his experience to make the most of the limited space and limited ingredients.

'A few simple snack menus will definitely be better than the chefs at the moment.'

After decades on the battlefield, a few of the old soldier's signature dishes were enough to overwhelm most chefs.

This, of course, is due to the advanced recipes of previous eras, and the taste of time spent in the field.

'The potatoes developed by Morgue are earthy and tasteless, and the texture is like chewing sand....'

But Vikir chopped up the potatoes, seasoned them with salt and vinegar, and added mandrake leaves and sabac berries to the wok and fried them over high heat.

'This will completely remove the earthy flavor and bring out the sweetness and texture,'

Come to think of it, I had done this to potatoes once before.

'You don't have anything like this at home, do you?'

Suddenly, a clear face flashed before Vikir's eyes and then it was disappeared.

“....”

He stared at it with teary eyes.

'Hey. Why don't you come over and cook for me? I'll take you in.'

'Speaking of which, when do you get into the academy? Let's see. I'm probably going to get in early by a year or two. It would be so much fun if we were in first grade together....'

And then, as if on cue, they tangled, planning their future together.

'...Where you are now and what you're doing.'

Vikir thought briefly.

Then he surprised himself.

That he still had time to think of others.

'I wonder if I have any sensitivity left.'

Vikir shook his head to clear his thoughts.

He turned his attention back to the reality.

'I'll see you soon enough.'

It's always a good idea to keep your hands busy when your mind wanders.

Cluck.

The chicken and potatoes are stir-fried, and the red soup seasoning is poured over the top.

This nameless dish, once eaten by mercenaries on the front lines in the Age of Destruction over the carcasses of demons, has been transported back in time and created in the Academy's festival bar and has become a very popular new menu item.

“....”

Vikir gripped the wok and turned his head.

Outside the kitchen, on the tables, he could see people drinking and eating snacks.

Good food makes people happy. Everyone was eating Vikir's food with a smile on their faces.

'...It was the same way back then, my comrades-in-arms, who are now dead, also enjoyed my cooking.'

The people who made it, the people who ate it, and the scenery in which it was enjoyed have changed dramatically, but the flavor is timeless.

And although it is a slightly different view,... the comrades-in-arms who are dead and gone are still alive in this era.

The comrades who ate rough food together and crossed rough lines together are still alive with young and innocent faces.

Kwok.

Vikir tightened his grip on the wok.

For their sake, he had to live this day, this moment, as best he could.

There would be more demons to kill, more lines of fire to cross, more strength to grow.

With that resolve, that sense of mission, Vikir turned his attention to the food in front of him.

Vikir put aside his personal thoughts and focused on the small tasks at hand.

Meanwhile.

“....”

Dolores stared blankly at Vikir in the kitchen.

“...Wah.”

Dolores's lips parted, even though she was holding it together. It's a very admirable look.

She had always thought of herself as the type of person who looked at the inside rather than the outside, but... that didn't mean she didn't look at the outside at all.

It wasn't that she didn't care about a man's face, it was just that she hadn't ever seen one that really impressed her.

It was only now that Dolores realized the significance of this.

“I can't believe he's wearing such a blasphemous outfit with a face like that. Why is he dressed like a witch....?”

She stumbled back to her senses and looked away.

A witch is the opposite of a saint, so it was natural for Dolores to be offended by the outfit.

But the other girls behind her had a different opinion.

“ ... He's so fucking handsome.”

The voice of the heart, unfiltered.

Dolores gasped, wondering if she'd said it out loud, but she hadn't.

Turning her head, she spotted a group of schoolgirls who hadn't made it inside the crowded bar, but had gathered at the fence outside to watch the kitchen.

Most of them were dressed as zombies, so the scene was quite apocalyptic.

“How can a man be so pretty, this is a scam!”

“Vikir, I love you! I love you! Can you please take a look at this place? Please! Don't just take my word for it, it's steamed!”

“Oh really, it looks like our Vikir is going to win all the 20th Golden Sexiest Newcomer awards this year~ Do you remember how when I was giving my acceptance speech, the entire audience was in tears, so I boiled and ate bear soup with it?”

“In the real world, all the sexiest creatures looked at our Vikir's breathtaking figure and retreated, retreating and disappearing even outside the empire, so they were all turned into barbarians. There's nothing we can do about it. Vikir is responsible for this. Vikir, the sexiness that has disappeared in this world from everyone but himself, let's eat it all. Ha really...”

“Vikir is so sexy that he beat up all the walls and broke the old border fence of the Warring States Period with his fists to unify the country, can he win the Imperial Peace Prize? Yes!”

“Ha wait a minute. I gave up on people who thought Vikir was sexy, and the empire was cut in half, so I came here high-fiving my friend from the Northern Varangian.”

A large crowd of zombie cosplayers crowded around the bar's perimeter fence to get a glimpse of Vikir.

The sight of them, clinging to the fence and shaking the fence stakes to gain access to the kitchen, was apocalyptic.

“Yay, sales are exploding!”

“You're the best!”

Tudor and Sinclaire excitedly began handing out numbered tags to customers outside the fence.

Despite the extra zeros added to the prices of the food on the menu, Vikir's creations are selling like crazy.

Most of the customers were from the nobility, so they weren't afraid to open their wallets despite the high prices.

“Huh! Look, guys, there's a new menu again! How in the world did you manage to make such a delicious snack out of leftover ingredients? What's the name of this thing? What? Nothing? It's just leftover ingredients? Let's put it on the menu as soon as possible! It's Vikir's special new menu!”

After revealing the fact that Vikir was actually a man, the number of female customers began to increase dramatically.

Surprisingly, the number of male customers didn't decrease at all, but actually increased.

“Wow, look at all the guys. Men just need to be pretty.”

“Hey! It's a big deal! She's a guy!”

“I thought it was all about being really pretty~”

“Girls just need to be pretty, too, eek!”

“Did my school have a girl like that?”

“He's a freshman in this year's Cold Class. He's famous for doing a Colosseo Naphtali.”

“I heard this place is a good restaurant.”

“Take my order, please! I'll pay for my meal here in advance. Oh, and could you please put the drinks and food away, they're distracting from the view?”

Ugh. Professors and students, a crowd.

“Excuse me, Vikir, I'm sorry you're so busy, but do these come with extra toppings, and I'd like to try one of the new items you just added.”

Even Prof. Banshee had taken up a table and was sitting down, placing one order after another.

Just then.

Bianca walked into the kitchen, fresh from a publicity stint.

When she saw Vikir holding the pots and ladles, she exclaimed in surprise.

“What the hell, why are you in the kitchen? Get out there and sell! Why are you rotting in the kitchen with that face!”

Hearing that, Vikir nodded and let go of the ladle.

At that very moment.

“No! The kitchen is ruined without Vikir's touch!”

Tudor rushes over and stops Vikir.

Soon, Tudor, the chef, and Bianca, the hustler, were arguing.

“Vikir is an asset to the kitchen, don't you dare take him away from us! How many lonely gourmets have fallen in love with Vikir's taste right now!”

“Are you kidding me, you want him to stew in that perfect witch costume? Every time he steps outside, sales go through the roof!”

Suddenly, a group of kitchen students swarmed behind Tudor, and a group of charmers behind Bianca, and they began to argue.

“Don't disrespect the kitchen!”

“The flower of a festival is attracting customers!”

Students from both positions, including Tudor and Bianca, began to fight for Vikir's position.

Just then.

“They shouldn't be fighting.”

There was one person pulling Vikir to his feet.

A moment.

“?”

Vikir's expression turned slightly blank.

A familiar face.

......Why is this person who should be on the far western border now here in the Imperial Capital?

Chapter 207

Festival Night (4)

◆

“Vikir should be in the kitchen!”

“What's the point of having a kitchen if you don't have a pimp!”

An extreme case of PIMPY (Please In My Front Yard) as each side tries to get Vikir to join their side.

In this gap between the kitchen faction and the pimping faction, local egoism blossoms beautifully.

“We shouldn't fight.”

A man hugged Vikir.

“?”

Vikir frowned.

...Why is this person here now?

A familiar face. He was wearing a vampire costume and a mask, but Vikir could tell by the momentum.

Who else could be of this size and age and exude this much intimidation?

Osiris. Osiris Le Baskerville.

The head of Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman, Hugo's legitimate successor.

He is now hugging Vikir in his witch disguise.

For a moment, Vikir's mind raced with thoughts.

The first thing that came to mind was the cryptic message that Cindywendy had sent him the other day.

1. The Ten Corpse. Information obtained. Need time to analyze. One month.

2. Night Hound. Two copycats emerge. One for praise. The other, purpose unknown.

3. Osiris of the House of Baskerville. Family crest emptied. Supposedly headed for the Imperial City.

The third entry apparently states that Osiris, the head of the Baskerville family, has emptied his household and is headed for the Imperial City.

Although the exact purpose was unknown.

Meanwhile. Public opinion is up in arms about the masked man who appears out of nowhere and takes Vikir away.

“Who is he? He's very tall.”

“Is it Vikir's family?”

“I can't see his face because of the mask.”

Most people are curious about Osiris' identity.

However, Osiris took Vikir with him and quickly left the scene.

As if he had no intention of making a scene.

And then. Back behind the tent, Osiris set Vikir down.

“You've gotten a lot prettier since I last saw you, little brother (dongsaeng).”

He said, with a hint of gravity in his voice.

But Vikir's expression remained cold.

“What brings you here, hyung-nim?”

“Hyung-nim? Wouldn't it be more appropriate to call me oppa?”

“...According to the traditions of the Academy, it would be correct to call you Unnie.”

“It was a joke.”

“So was I.”

Vikir asked again.

“What brings you here, brother.”

“It is the duty of an older brother to come to the rescue when his younger brother is in trouble.”

Just then.

“Samchuun!”

A hand shot out from Osiris's back.

Vikir's eyes widened slightly.

He could see the Pomeranian being carried by Osiris. Osiris's broad shoulders and back had been hidden until now.

“Ying-ying-ying-I miss you, Samchun! Why aren't you coming?”

Pomeranian has a sorrowful look on her face as she hugs Vikir and rubs her face.

When Vikir lifted his head, feeling the dampness around his belly, Osiris revealed his purpose for coming.

“Pomeranian has missed you so much. My father has granted me a special vacation. To take Pomeranian to the Academy.”

At the words, Vikir doubted his ears. A vacation? Hugo?

Seeing Vikir's puzzled expression, Osiris laughed softly beneath his mask.

“He's got a tight grip on the reins of the family these days.”

Osiris's words were surprising.

Mention the Pomeranian's fondness for blood bean chocolate, and the marshland along the Western Front is turned to mush, and cacao plantations take its place.

If the Pomeranian says he wants to spend his summers by the river, the lands along the Southern Front are swept away by silt and rapids and turned into rivers.

The Baskervilles even raided the ruby mines of their ally Morgue when Pomeranian showed an interest in jewelry making.

Pomeranian protested that she missed Vikir, and after a long hunger strike that lasted two meals, Hugo granted her a visit.

Of course, this was done in the utmost secrecy, so as not to reveal Vikir's relationship with the family.

And Pomeranian was escorted by Osiris Le Baskerville himself!

'...What a world.'

Vikir rubbed his forehead at the butterfly effect of the storm he had created.

But at the center of the storm, Pomeranian is just hugging his legs and whimpering for Vikir's amusement.

“Hahaha, our princess is finally showing her smile. Pomeranian has been quite depressed since you disappeared, and the atmosphere in the house hasn't been right for a while. Your father has been so worried about you....”

Osiris looks at Pomeranian with a gentle expression, his expression is also softer than I've ever seen before.

It's as if Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman, is changing a little bit due to Pomeranian's appearance.

On the other hand, Osiris was also looking around the Academy's bars as if he had a new appreciation for them.

“ ... It's been a long time since I've been here, too. I was once a student at the Academy, and I was in charge of many things as student council president, but now that I've graduated, it's all just a memory.”

Muttering to himself, Osiris looked back at Vikir as if suddenly remembering.

“Oh, by the way. On the way here, I saw a pretty girl inside the bar's tent, and she was staring at you. What's your relationship?”

A pretty girl. Osiris would say.

“You mean Student Council President Dolores?”

Vikir asked without thinking.

At that very moment.

...Hwadeuljjag!

The area beyond the tent suddenly shook.

Vikir turned to see what it was, and saw the back of Dolores' figure scurrying away.

Dolores hadn't made a move until we started talking about her family, so it's possible she was just passing by and overheard our conversation.

...But why are those ears red?

'Well, it doesn't matter.'

I hadn't said anything bad, I'd just been caught saying something nice, so I didn't think anything would come of it.

Maybe she was offended that I was judging her appearance, but I don't think I need to think about it because it's not going to happen again.

“As for Ms. Dolores, we're not in a relationship, we're just senior and junior.”

Vikir cut to the chase, and Osiris cocked his head.

“...Dolores? You mean the lady of the Quovadis? If she is, I recognize her face. I didn't mean Dolores.”

“Hmm? Then who were you referring to?”

“I don't know her name, but she was dressed as a yeti.”

“....”

“It's a joke.”

Clearly, Osiris's personality had changed a lot since I'd last seen him.

Vikir was silent for a moment, wondering if this was another Pomeranian influence.

'Perhaps...... In the face of a wall at the top of the Graduator, regaining one's emotions may be more advantageous for growth. I don't know about Osiris himself, but it must be good for him.'

I had no idea that having a younger sister (actually a niece) in a house full of brothers would have such a profound effect.

Well, aside from that, Osiris gave Vikir a lot of information.

A general overview of what was going on in the family.

“The trade deal you arranged is well underway. It's been in the works since our alliance with Messinadnaro.”

The three-way trade between Ballak, Baskerville, and Cindywendy was finally on track.

However, there was one strange thing.

Vikir turned to Osiris.

“House Messinadnaro?”

“That's right. The same family that was outlawed by the Baskervilles.”

Osiris seemed to already know about Cindywendy's past.

Vikir is left to wonder why Cindywendy, who has a grudge against the Baskervilles, would join forces with them.

Osiris explained again.

“Do you remember the truth commission we created before you entered the Academy? I've been chairing it ever since, and we've re-investigated everything that happened in the past.”

Seven families involved in the club burning suspension were disowned.

The misunderstandings and misdeeds between the Baskervilles and the Messinadnaro were also brought to light.

As a result, the Baskervilles have formally apologized to the Messinadnaro and have made restitution.

It was a win-win situation, as many of the old Baskervilles who had participated in the conspiracy were forced to give their heads, and Osiris was able to reorganize the family's order and power structure once more.

In the end, Hugo and Osiris completely overpowered the Senate, led by the Seventh Count, and seized control of the House.

It seemed that Cindywendy had also been somewhat relieved by this series of events and had joined forces with the Baskervilles.

'Well, that's her own mind.'

...Whether she had truly forgiven Baskerville or not, only she would know the exact details.

“Indeed.”

Osiris turned to Vikir, as if remembering something.

“I have come to see you today not only to tell you these things.”

He pulled something out of his pocket and held it out to Vikir.

“Is this ...?”

Vikir's eyes sparkled as he examined the object.

Osiris tilted his head and said.

“It's an artifact that fell from the spot where Seth died. I don't know what it can be used for, so I brought it to you.”

When demons die, they drop their artifacts.

Just as Dantalian had dropped the Picaresque Mask, Andromalius would have done the same.

It was a shame I couldn't keep it, but now I have it.

...Sparkle!

A black strange ring appeared in Vikir's hand, shining brightly.

/ Ring

-Finit hic Deus -Off

-Finit hic Deus, the realm of the gods ends here.

It's an orb that contains the skills that Andromalius used to specialize in when he was alive.

It was a covenant-forming ring with the ability to create spaces so secretive that even the eyes of the Rune Gods could not see into it.

The moment he held it in his hand, Vikir couldn't help but think of a clichéd line.

'...You're lucky.'

Chapter 208

Festival Night (5)

◆

Usher Pou Bianca. 18 years old. Originally from Usher, the Divine Bow Palace. Early admission to the Colosseo Academy.

As a member of the festival organizing committee, she found herself in the middle of another annoyance.

“Hey, there... I've been watching you all this time, and I like you!”

The boy standing in front of her, holding out the letter, was someone she remembered seeing a few times in her joint class with Hot Class.

Bianca frowned. She stroked the fake mustache at the base of her nose.

Bianca studied the face of the boy in front of her again.

Her sharp eyes sparkled as she fired a needle from a hundred paces away.

“Caked-on makeup -13 points, flaky skin -11 points, unkempt eyebrows -12 points, incongruous lip tone -14 points, cuts from shaving -4 points, untrimmed nail cuticles -4 points, mismatch of personal color and clothing -5 points, split ends of hair from excessive bleaching -8 points, awkward cross-dressing -22 points, total score of 7 out of 100.”

The boy in front of her was quite handsome, but he didn't reach Bianca's aesthetic threshold.

The cross-dressing was an additional point deduction, as it looked very sloppy.

'If you were dressed as a woman, you need to be pretty. It's not even pretty. I don't need anything that isn't pretty.'

From a young age, she loved pretty things.

Pretty clothes, pretty food, of course.

Pretty dolls, pretty weapons, pretty men, pretty women, pretty horses, pretty saddles, pretty horseshoes, pretty carpets, pretty carpet cleaning brooms, pretty carpet cleaning broom holders....

As such, Bianca was known for her demanding aesthetic, even within the Usher family.

So much so, in fact, that she handpicked her nannies as babies.

Maybe that's why? Bianca wasn't interested in men.

Men are basically ugly. They don't dress up or take care of themselves as much as women do.

If they happen to wear makeup to look pretty, they're called unmanly even amongst themselves.

So Bianca's entire life has been about getting attention from men.

To her, men were basically ugly creatures, people she had nothing to do with in her life.

That's why, since the beginning of the semester, she's been asked out countless times by seniors and classmates alike, but she's always turned them down.

'Bianca! Would you like to go see the newly released play 'Worn Out Newbie 2'?

'I've seen all three.'

“Bianca, have you had dinner? If not, would you like to join us?”

'I already ate lunch for tomorrow.'

'Bianca, let's go worship at the temple this weekend!'

'I'm a heretic, I believe in voodoo.'

'Hey, Bianca, when are you free this weekend? Try to find some time.'

'I don't have a weekend.'

'Bianca, why don't you go to.... this Christmas?'

'No.'

I'd rather hang out with pretty girls, but I never felt like hanging out with ugly guys.

The only exception would be Tudor, the little bully I grew up bickering with?

'...But I can't help but like pretty people.'

I blamed myself for this personality and tried to change it, but I couldn't change my taste.

How can I change the fact that I've been insisting on pretty women since I was a baby, even for my nanny and maids?

If I could find a guy who could score at least 20 out of 100, I'd be happy, but there weren't many of them in the academy.

And even if there were men who barely met the physical requirements, none of them were of such great ability or status that she, the eldest daughter of the Usher family and head of the Cold Class, would dare to approach her first.

'Yeah. I'm me, and I don't have to change who I am to fit in.'

So Bianca had given up on meeting and socializing with men since she started school.

...But.

Now, her resolve has long since been shattered.

'100 points. One hundred points!'

Vikir is in the kitchen, stirring a pot full of stew with a ladle.

Bianca's gaze half unraveled at the sight of him.

Crazy. Giddy. Ecstatic. Dreamy and Decadent.

She had never seen such dangerously beautiful things, not even among her own kind.

Where the hell did that nonsense come from?

It's like a character ripped off the page and popped out of one of those cringe-worthy 19th-century doujinshi comics I read as a kid.

And not just any character, but the decadent heroine of the story itself.

Bianca was grateful to her parents at this point.

They had given her the eyesight to see a needle in a haystack from a hundred paces away, so of course she should be grateful.

'Wow... how can a man be so pretty, there's nothing to see.'

Even from a very long distance, if you energize your eyes with mana, you can see things as if they were right in front of you.

So Bianca continued to marvel as she handed out flyers for a bar from miles away.

Skin as white and smooth as ivory, without a single blemish, eyelashes so long and luxuriant they seemed to fall and pile up, eyebrows so dark and straight, and eyes as red as a lake of blood beneath them.

I always knew he was good-looking, but the makeup made him even more insane.

No wonder onlookers were swarming around him with mana screenshot cameras.

'Should I take a mana screenshot too?'

Despite the bustling crowd of people dressed as zombies, skeletons, ghouls, vampires, death knights, witches, werewolves, and more, Bianca couldn't take her eyes off Vikir.

Just then.

...Bam!

Bianca's shoulders shook once.

Palalag-

A few flyers in her hand fell to the ground.

Her shoulders bumped together in the bustling crowd.

“Oh really, where are your eyes....”

Bianca turned her head with an annoyed expression.

But then a face caught her eye.

Bones. A skull mask, and a pair of glowing, bloodshot eyes.

“Huh!”

Bianca gulped down the wind.

[....]

A woman dressed as a skeleton was staring at them.

A chill ran down her spine that was almost indescribable.

The skull mask and armor were too elaborate for a Halloween costume.

'..., She looks real.'

Bianca swallowed dryly.

She'd never been pushed in a energy fight before, but for some reason, she couldn't use her energy against the skull-masked woman in front of her.

There was an overwhelming aura emanating from her, not mana or aura, but a presence, a class apart.

Then, a hoarse voice came from within the skull mask.

[Be careful].

It said. It sounded as if it was giving the insignificant bug a pass for once.

“....”

Bianca couldn't say anything in response to that, though, and could only lower her gaze.

'Keep your mouth shut and your eyes down.'

Instinctive warnings screamed in her head.

It was the creepiest thing I've ever experienced in my 18 years of life.

None of my classmates, not the skinny kids, not the weight-lifting seniors, not even my professors, had ever given me the creeps.

...No.

If I had to pick one, it would be Prof. Sadi, the only one with the same level of creepiness.

The hairs on my body stood on end, and my back was damp with sweat.

Feeling like a hedgehog in front of a giant pit, Bianca backed away, forgetting to pick up the flyers that had fallen to the floor.

[...Ung].

The skull-masked woman snorted and turned away as if she wasn't worth dealing with.

Judging by the condition of her skin, body shape, and voice that occasionally peeked out of her mask or armor, she was around the same age.

But the presence she exudes overwhelms Bianca, the Usher family prodigy and top enrollee in the Cold Warrior Class.

“ ... Who the hell is that?”

She must be a student at the Academy if she's taken the trouble to dress up in a Halloween costume like that, and if she is, there's no way Bianca wouldn't know it.

“Maybe he's from Magic Tower or Varangian, but I don't think there's anyone of her caliber there. ...Maybe a returning student?”

Bianca broke out in a cold sweat and backed away, moving at a shuffling pace, heading for the newspaper publisher's bar.

The solicitation stops here.

Her legs were shaking from the terror she'd just endured.

'I'll go back to the bar and ask Vikir for a shift. Honestly, I think he'll do a better job of bringing in customers than I will.....'

Bianca was somewhat confident in her cooking, so it was a more efficient decision.

And she needed to get away from that murderous woman as soon as possible.

'...What's wrong?'

Bianca quickened her pace.

The kitchen of the newspaper's bar.

Toward where Vikir was.

Chapter 209

Festival Night (6)

◆

[Be careful].

The Corpse Queen opened her mouth in an irritated tone.

Her irritation rose in her voice from the depths of her lungs, the source of which contained the heat of the infernal fires simmering in the depths of the Black Demon World.

“............”

Naturally, the female student whose shoulder was bumped could only shudder and didn't say anything in response.

[... Hah.]

The corpse queen snorted and turned her attention away.

The girl who had just bumped into her shoulder seemed to be from the Academy.

Judging by the look on her face, she might be a new student, maybe even an early enrollee.

The corpse queen suddenly felt uncomfortable as she thought about it.

Maybe. Really, just maybe.

What if she hadn't become a corpse queen?

What if she hadn't been admitted to the Academy, like so many other girls her age?

She knew full well that there were no ifs in history, but just this once, just this one time, if she could put on an age-appropriate act, she might think so.

'...With him.'

The Corpse Queen saw a face in her thoughts.

The waves of time would slowly sweep everything away until eventually nothing remained, but they would never erase this one face.

The gaze, always expressionless, always looking so far away that it was impossible to tell where it was looking.

The face she could still remember so clearly and distinctly.

At the same time, she remembers the conversations she had with him before she became the corpse queen.

'Hey. Do you want to come to my house and cook?'

'....'

“Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll just take you in.”

'....'

'So, when are you getting into the academy? Let's match it up with me. I'm probably going to get in a year or two early. It would be so much fun if we could be first years together....'

Then.

There was a presence that scattered the Corpse Queen's thoughts.

...Nod!

A small woman beside her tugged on the collar of the Corpse Queen's cloak.

Geronto. A red-haired mage with bandages covering her entire body, including her face and neck.

She was a Lich, a high-ranking undead who had been brought back to life by the Corpse Queen.

The Corpse Queen listened to Geronto's unspoken report and nodded.

[Yes, Rosie, the Night Hound, his scent seems to be leading this way].

The Corpse Queen naturally couldn't help but recall the events of the previous night.

The disruptor who appeared out of nowhere. It was only recently that she realized he was an unprecedented villain who had been terrorizing the nights of the Imperial City recently.

'Certainly no ordinary man.'

The barbarian's archery, his swordplay, all too familiar.

At the crucial moment, however, the blinding light from the tip of his blade prevented me from reading its exact trajectory.

However, the Corpse Queen had witnessed a sun-like aura like this once before.

[...Madam Eight-Legs, in that night's battle].

The Corpse Queen felt her heart beat for the first time in a very long time.

She hadn't felt her heart beat in a very long time, ever since she had forced herself to peer into the Abyss of Magic in an attempt to leap to a higher realm during her Closed training and suffered a mana backflow that killed half of her body.

Since then, her heart has been beating again, even though it hadn't beaten properly since then.

What does this mean?

[No way. No way. No way. That can't be possible. ...... but. But.]

Even she couldn't pinpoint what she was hoping for, what she expected, what she wanted to see.

And so the Corpse Queen had come to the Academy in a state of confusion.

To meet the Night Hound she had met the night before.

Next, Geronto led her to a dormitory.

[A dormitory? This place looks like it's for students. Surely the Night Hound that's been wreaking havoc across the Imperial City isn't a student at the Academy?]

The Corpse Queen shook her head in disbelief.

She fumbled with the lock on the back door of her dormitory.

Chiiiig...

At the Corpse Queen's touch, the lock instantly melted into molten iron, like ice dumped on a stove.

The corridors inside the dormitory were dark and empty.

It was the festive season, and everyone seemed to have gone out to play.

After melting down a few more locks in her way, the Corpse Queen broke into one of the rooms in the dormitory and swallowed a small gulp.

[...This looks like a girl's room, doesn't it?]

A plainly decorated single occupancy room.

However, judging from the decorative items and the smell in the room, this is definitely a girl's room.

The room was empty, as I had guessed based on the atmosphere in the hallway.

What's unusual is that there are a few small paw prints on the window sill that appear to belong to a dog.

[You have a dog? Let's get it off your hands].

The Corpse Queen muttered hoarsely.

How many animals had she cut and pasted as experiments in order to reach the pinnacle of black magic?

Naturally, there were many dogs among them.

Therefore, the Corpse Queen harbored a vague feeling of guilt or indebtedness for having pets, including dogs.

Meanwhile.

...Bam!

Geronto stood there and shook his head.

It was a sign that the scent had stopped.

The corpse queen was forced to leave the dormitory without much of a payoff.

[...Well, at this point, the only thing we can do is capture and interrogate the owner of this room].

Following the trail of the room's owner, the corpse queen emerged into the festival streets once again.

Moment.

[...!]

There was a scene in front of her.

Countless cherry blossom petals. Those pink waves.

The skull mask's eyes widened at the sight of a cherry blossom rain on an epic scale.

Even if they were just fake petals created by magic, it was still spectacular.

[....]

As she stares at the festival petals fluttering in the night sky.

“Wow, you did a great job with your costume!”

A group of schoolboys said to the corpse queen, grinning broadly.

[...?]

Before the corpse queen can turn her head, the boys walk past, laughing amongst themselves.

“Wow, I thought her helmet and armor were made of real bones.”

“She must have put a lot of work into her costume.”

“Did you see that? Didn't he have a nice jawline under that skull mask?”

“Ugh, the proportions and the lines are so graceful, you should walk a horse.”

Small talk.

The Corpse Queen found it quite refreshing to be the subject of such small talk.

Compared to the atmosphere of her previous groups, or her current one, it was hard to imagine.

But he didn't feel any new feelings of offense or anger.

'It was Halloween, after all.'

Halloween, which symbolizes the Academy's summer festival, is more passionate and open, unlike Halloween in the winter.

It's a festival where even strangers pass by and exchange greetings and hugs.

The Corpse Queen watched the crowd of passersby come and go with newfound emotion.

Students dressed as zombies, skeletons, ghouls, vampires, death knights, ghosts, mummies, and more.

Outsiders enjoying the students' costumes and imitating them in their own ways.

Then.

“Hey pretty girls, buy a skewer, it's half price because you're pretty!”

A female student started hawking the corpse queen.

“Wow, your costume is really tight, you must be looking forward to the festival!”

[....]

“Awww, I feel great, you're enjoying the festival so much, I'll give you one more as a service!”

The corpse queen was taken aback by the skewer that was suddenly thrust in front of her, and was immediately subjected to a hard sell.

[...Delicious?]

...Nod!

The corpse queen walks down the street with her sugared fruit skewers and Geronto with his ice cream waffles.

For the first time since her heart stopped beating, the Corpse Queen felt a little bit, just a little bit, good about this situation, even if it was only for a moment.

Following the scent from her room, Geronto walked from tavern to bar, from passerby to passerby.

Up and down the street, right and left, back and forth, left and right, everywhere.

Handsome bards busking, dance troupes performing, water balloon tosses and whack-a-mole games with all sorts of prizes....

The corpse queen looked suspiciously at Geronto, who was carrying water balloons, ice cream, whirling potatoes, and a giant teddy bear.

[Are we on the right track, Rosie?]

...Nod!

Geronto flinches slightly, but then nods and points to a spot.

A bar came into the Corpse Queen's view.

A ghost bar run by a newspaper club.

Students dressed as ghosts were hawking, serving, and cooking, welcoming customers to the bar.

On a large stage opposite, guest dancers dressed as skeletons were performing to loud music.

Flames roared and heart-pounding drums pounded.

A melting pot of chaos and revelry, with crowds of people weeping and laughing and stomping their feet.

And there, the Corpse Queen could see one familiar face again.

[...Isn't that the woman who bumped shoulders with me earlier?]

The woman she bumped shoulders with earlier is standing here again, looking dazed.

I'd warned her to be careful in the future, but here she was again, looking so stupid.

The Corpse Queen clicked her tongue.

[You haven't woken up yet, stupid girl, you won't live long].

This is puzzling, since she seems to have pretty good instincts, given that her eyes immediately snapped shut.

Suddenly, the Corpse Queen stopped clicking her tongue and turned her head to the side.

She was curious as to what it was that had so mesmerized the pretty girl.

And.

[...!?]

The corpse queen's eyes, which had been turned away without a second thought, soon opened wide enough to tear.

It was a person cooking in the bar's kitchen.

Upon seeing that face, the Corpse Queen couldn't help but freeze in place, shocked as if struck by lightning.

Then, she stuttered and opened her mouth.

[...He, did he have a sister?]

Chapter 210

Festival Night (7)

◆

[...He, did he have a sister?]

Not likely.

There are no women in his family. No daughters are born.

Daughters have been rare in their family ever since the disappearance of their only daughter a long time ago, as if a curse had been placed on them.

But what is this woman in front of her?

A schoolgirl dressed as a witch and cooking.

Pale skin, a sharp nose, a veil-like jawline, deep eyes and thick lashes. Add to that a slight frown and you have the ultimate in decadence.

Add to that hair as black as the night sky and red eyes that shine like rubies, and it's like he's come back to life.

...If it hadn't been for the woman, I might have actually believed it.

[Blood? But that doesn't explain it, what the hell happened after that night in the depth....]

The corpse queen muttered softly.

She had apparently cut herself off from everything in the world after 'that one day'.

She didn't know, because in order to plunge into the depths of the Black Magic, she would have to cut all her ties to the world, and weigh herself down.

So she did not know. Any information beyond the 'one day' that involved him.

Moreover.

'No more thinking.'

Or the existence of 'it' that was preventing the Corpse Queen from thinking clearly.

...Jist!

The Corpse Queen was momentarily thrown off balance by the impact of a large, thick awl piercing her skull.

Her brain is immediately restricted from deep thought.

A terrible headache was kicking her half-dead, half-alive brain.

'Stop thinking about your headache, I'll take care of all that for you.'

The demonic whisper in my ear. It tempts you to let go of your complicated thoughts and woes and respond to the simple stimulus in front of you.

Ugh!

The Corpse Queen gritted her teeth.

[...I'm not a corpse, I'm capable of independent thought and judgment, not a puppet that moves only at your will].

The voice in her ear paused at those words. The 'it' closed its mouth.

'....'

The Corpse Queen clenched her teeth and covered her ears.

[I told you, I'm only giving you half the day].

'....'

[And to fulfill the part of the contract, I must go to that bar now. Don't forget why I made the contract with you].

Then 'it' whispered in a sweet voice once again.

'Of course, that's why I found your sister, with my 'powers'.'

The Corpse Queen turned her head at those words and looked to the side.

Geronto. The mage turned lich. The girl who would have been sixteen this year had she lived.

The Corpse Queen opened her mouth.

[I know, your ability, the mystical one that lets you 'meet the person you want to meet,' but... you know there's one other person I've been looking for besides my sister, right?]

'....'

[The main reason I accepted your contract offer was to find his body, but you never did, even after two years of scouring every inch of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain].

'....'

[And now, I don't know if it's because of your powers or if this is my destiny, but I've once again gotten a lead on him. Somehow I feel like if I go there, I'll know everything].

'....'

[So don't stop me].

The corpse queen was the first to resist the voice of 'it'.

This was because the corpse queen and 'It' were not in a master-servant or one-sided contractual relationship, but rather a mutually beneficial one, which was quite different from the way most demons would enter into a contract with a dying human to take over their body completely.

But 'it' continued to speak to the corpse queen.

'It's dangerous. I smell danger.'

[...What?]

'I sense something sinister in that bar. It reeks of the disgusting odor of demon hunters.'

Geronto, next to the Corpse Queen, seems to sense it as well.

The Corpse Queen saw Geronto nod in agreement and thought for a moment.

'But why now, Demon Hunter, and what on earth is going on while I sleep half the day?'

'It' was still pestering the Corpse Queen.

While the corpse queen was living half the day, 'It' was also living half the day.

The Corpse Queen gritted her teeth.

[I have come prepared, and the identity of your uneasiness is probably the Night Hound, and I will meet him and unmask him myself. And that woman's identity as well].

Then the thing shut up and was silent for a long time.

The Corpse Queen is about to take a step forward when It gives up.

'We don't have much time left.'

'It' opened its mouth.

'It's midnight, and after midnight, this body is mine....'

[...That's enough].

The corpse queen stopped talking.

It was silent, as if it too had decided that further conversation was pointless.

Caw-.

A crow cawed ominously and flew through the rain of festival cherry blossoms.

[....]

The corpse queen's eyes immediately calm down.

She stopped thinking and let her instincts guide her.

It was time to clear up the confusion.

The Corpse Queen was about to take a step forward.

“Waaaaaaah! You're so pretty!”

“Who the hell is that witch!”

“It's not my sister, it's my brother!”

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Big sister, please take a look at this!”

“Witch, please cast a spell on me too!”

“I love you, just give me a drink!”

A huge crowd suddenly rushed into the newspaper club bar.

...Click! ...Click! ...Click! ...Click! ...Click!

Screenshot flashes of mana exploding everywhere.

The corpse queen was pinned down by a crowd of people.

She was crushed so hard that her cheeks bulged out of her skull mask.

[... These, these].

The Corpse Queen slowly drew up her mana.

She was going to clear her mind of everything that bothered her and move forward.

As she had always done.

But.

...Jaw!

Had she sensed a change of plans? A footstep blocked the corpse queen's path.

“Stop.”

Bianca. It was her.

'Stop.'

The corpse queen's eyebrows moved.

'The bitch who couldn't even keep her mouth shut earlier?'

What the hell was she doing standing in her way now?

But Bianca stood firmly in front of the corpse queen, her body trembling slightly.

“I understand your feelings, but that's it.”

[?]

Understand your feelings? How dare the bitch say she understands?

The Corpse Queen was just about to open her mouth to say something.

Bianca opened her mouth first.

“So much for fandom, you have to stay in line.”

[??]

“No matter how pretty that kid is. You can't do that by raising your mana? Are you doing this because we're not mana users?”

[????]

The Corpse Queen stared blankly behind her mask for a moment.

Then another face popped out from beside Bianca's.

A girl with gray hair and sleepy eyes. It was Sinclaire.

“That's right. Only our staff is allowed to see our witch.”

The Corpse Queen had no idea what these chicks were talking about.

[... Are these bloodsuckers crazy].

“Mmmmmmmm- blood, you look like you're about our age, but you sound like you've just come out of the grave.”

“Sisters, if you'll excuse me, I'd like you to step aside, or take your number and wait.”

Bianca and Sinclaire worked together to keep the Corpse Queen at a distance.

Eventually, the corpse queen was forced to reveal her power.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Bianca and Sinclaire's expressions changed as she drew on her dark mana and emitted a sinister aura.

'Black mage!'

Even the Empire classified them as Class 1 dangerous people.

The black mages under their care are usually identified as those who feed on the rust of the state and move only under its control.

But the skull-masked woman in front of them looks suspicious.

Maybe... maybe all those bones on her face and body aren't just cosplay.

“...!”

“...!”

Bianca and Sinclaire's faces go white.

There's no way they, the elite of the Cold and Hot Class, a newcomer who had just finished her first-year midterms, could have withstood the momentum of the Corpse Queen.

And then.

...Teog!

Bianca and Sinclaire weren't the only ones blocking the Corpse Queen's path.

Black coat, gilded boots, chains and daggers dangling from her body.

And, crucially, a plague doctor's mask covering his face.

“...Who are you and what are you doing on someone else's property?”

It was the Night Hound.

Chapter 211

Festival Night (8)

◆

...Boom!

The sound of loud firecrackers echoes through the air.

A fireworks festival colorfully decorates the night sky.

Music blasts from the ground, and dancers dressed as skeletons and zombies put on enthusiastic performances.

A specialty of the Imperial Capital.

A concert where academy insiders and outsiders stomp their feet and cheer in unison.

...And in front of him, in the newspaper club's bar, something strange was happening right now.

◆

The corpse queen put her hands in her bosom and stretched them out.

Huddle, huddle, huddle!

A large amount of skeletal fragments fly out from under her black cloak and scatter on the ground.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

At the same time, the black mana that emanated from the Corpse Queen's body enveloped each and every one of the bones.

Germination. Evil roots and sinister shoots sprouted from the bony seeds.

Thud! Thud!

A black magic circle formed on the ground where the bones touched, and skeletal soldiers were summoned.

<Skeleton

Danger Rating: C

Size: 1.7 meters

Found in: All continents

-Name: 'The Bone Man'.

A common sight in graveyards, battlefields, abandoned houses, and sewers.

In rural areas and run-down cities, they're almost as common as street rats.

Skeletons (骸骨兵). The most basic form of the dead.

All they need is a piece of bone, and they can use it as a seed to root and sprout a magic circle, drawing from it an unlimited amount of power.

It is much more portable than zombie, which can be summoned through flesh, or wraith, which can be summoned through a fragment of the soul.

Flesh, even if dried and made into jerky, will eventually decay and disappear, and souls, no matter how well sealed in a vial, will eventually evaporate.

On the other hand, a high-level warlock who has attained a certain level of mastery can produce an endless supply of skull vials simply by scattering tiny bits of bone that are close to bone powder.

Woody, woody, woody, woody!

Bianca and Sinclaire's faces hardened as they watched the skeletal soldiers rise from the ground.

As the elite of the Academy, there was no way they couldn't feel these ominous waves of mana.

'Undead soldiers? Here?'

The two female students' mouths dropped open.

This skull-masked woman in front of them was definitely one of them.

Either she's a child who doesn't realize how terrifying it is to break the taboo of black magic, which is strictly controlled by the empire... or she's an absolute powerhouse who knows it and has the guts to do it.

But judging by the thick, strong, bony creatures in front of them now, it was overwhelmingly the first.

“Uh, where did these monsters come from, is she one of those 'Night Hounds' or something?”

“That's not the point, we need to get the professors here now!”

Bianca and Sinclaire didn't even dare to stand up to the powerful black magic in front of them.

Then.

“Wow! The performance is starting!”

“Awesome! A real performance!”

“Huh? But what's behind the concert?”

“Wow! There are skeleton backup dancers in the back!”

“But they really came out of the shadows! Who are they? What are they doing?”

“Boom! New face dance team! Their costumes are real, brothers!”

The crowd around them had a different reaction.

Maybe it's because it's a Halloween party where everyone is dressed up as skeletons and zombies, but no one thinks it's weird to see the skeleton soldiers summoned by the Corpse Queen.

Who says humans are animals of atmosphere?

Even if there's a fire or smoke in the room, if the person next to you is sitting calmly, it makes you feel uneasy, but if you sit still, you may suffocate to death.

That was exactly what was happening here at the academy's festival.

Although an Academy student who is sensitive to Mana, but in fact, 99% of the party people gathered here are outsiders, illiterate in Mana, and probably because they're intoxicated by alcohol and the excitement of the party, so even standing next to the Skeleton Soldiers, you don't feel anything other than a little eerie.

But of course, there are those who can recognize anomalies even in these situations.

“...Black mage? What are you doing! If you're in the Imperial Army, please state your rank!”

Saint Dolores, dressed as a Night Hound, stepped forward.

The holy aura she emanated stopped the skeleton soldiers crawling up from the abyss.

Crackle – Crackle – Crackle

The corpse queen's aura was so powerful that the skeleton soldiers were not killed, but they were still frozen in place by the holy power of Dolores, who had been somewhat awakened since the Battle of Dantalian.

The saintess's protection also properly blocked the balack mage's negative emotions, such as the fear that his powerful aura caused in those around him.

Also, the way the skeleton soldiers flailed about made the audience think that this was some sort of dance troupe performance.

“Oh, it's performance art.”

“Is that a flash mob or something?”

“Uh-huh, a performance where an unspecified number of people gather in a specific space at a specific time and do the same thing for no purpose? I heard it's the latest trend in the Imperial Capital!”

“Wow, now that I see it, it looks real!”

Even the guest singers and dancers on stage began to mimic the behavior.

“Who are they? When were they booked? I've never seen them before.”

“I don't know, but they're pretty hip. The quality of their costumes and props is amazing.”

“They seem to have a good crowd.”

“...Should we try it?”

As professional dancers dressed as zombies and skeletons mimic the stumbling movements of the skeleton soldiers, the cheers become more frenzied.

Firecrackers popped everywhere, and the music got louder.

The crowd's attention now shifts back to center stage.

...But all the while, Dolores's expression was hardening.

'Ugh, so strong. What is this person, or is she even a person at all?'

The skull-masked woman in front of Dolores was a terrifying force that even her holy power couldn't handle.

She thought she'd become much more skilled since her battle with Quilt, or rather Dantalian, but she was still far from it.

The black mage woman in front of her appeared to be her age, but she possessed an incredibly powerful mana that was incomparable to her own.

This kind of ominous and dangerous mana was something she had only ever felt when dealing with a demon of Dantalian's level.

No wonder Dolores' strength alone was insufficient.

'...The Night Hound was with me then.'

Dolores broke out in a cold sweat.

It reminded Dolores of the terrifying enemies she had fought, and the weight of her mission and burden.

Meanwhile, the Corpse Queen had known all along that the Night Hound before her was a fake.

She also recognized Dolores as the owner of the girls' dormitory room she had visited earlier.

The Corpse Queen growled and asked.

[Where have you taken the Night Hound?]

“...What?”

Dolores asked with a frown.

The Night Hound's whereabouts were something Dolores had been wondering about herself.

But the skull-masked woman in front of her almost seemed to assume that Dolores knew the whereabouts of the Night Hound.

[The Night Hound's tracks were found in your room, and I'm already on my way to check them out].

Dolores's expression hardened even more.

'No one has ever been in my room.'

Dolores, who values her privacy, doesn't allow anyone to enter her space.

Not only does she clean up after herself, but she also fixes her own furniture and equipment when it breaks.

This is true whether she's in her home in Quovadis or in her dormitory at the Academy.

Dolores couldn't figure out why the enemy in front of her was making such an outrageous misunderstanding, but she decided it wasn't important right now.

“I don't know what you mean, but it doesn't sound like you're looking for him with good intentions. If you're not a black mage in the Imperial Army, then you're clearly an enemy! If you are, then I can't tell you anything.”

[...Him? What are you related to him?]

The Corpse Queen asked in a sharp tone.

Dolores answered after some thought.

“Soul mate.”

And.

...Boom!

After hearing Dolores' answer, the Corpse Queen exploded.

[Really? In that case, I'll tear that soul to pieces and turn it into a disease of the dead!]

A fierce rage that even the Corpse Queen herself couldn't understand the source of caused her black mana to boil over even more.

A fiery night of roaring flames, earth-shattering music, and partying.

In the midst of it all, a witch and a saint stand in sharp opposition.

...And.

“Stop.”

A voice intervened in the middle of the two women's nervous battle.

Thick and low, like nails scraping across vocal cords.

“...!”

[...!]

Both the Corpse Queen and Dolores took half a step back, startled by the appearance of a new figure.

A man wearing the mask of a plague doctor and a black cloak wrapped around his entire body.

Vikir.

It was the moment when the true Night Hound appeared.

Chapter 212

Festival Night (9)

◆

Vikir. The Night Hound stood before his prey.

Moments ago, Vikir had been cooking in the kitchen when a familiar sensation caused him to throw down the wok and run out of the bar.

This was no time to be stir-frying potatoes, judging by the fierce shivering of the Demon Sword Beelzebub lurking in his arteries.

'Is this aura...?'

The smell of the demon. How can I forget the hateful scent of blood?

From the looks of it, the entity that invaded the academy was the Corpse Queen.

I had fought her once before in the ruins of House Indulgentia.

It is unknown why she is inside the academy, or for what purpose she has entered the chaos of the festival.

But it was a crisis, and it was certainly an opportunity.

'Take this opportunity to eliminate one of them once and for all.'

But you want to make sure that as few people as possible get caught in the crossfire.

Especially if it's a classmate you care about.

“Back off. Unless you want to die.”

Vikir warned briefly from beneath his Night Hound mask.

“...!”

“...!”

Bianca and Sinclaire shuddered slightly at the words.

This was the first time they'd ever seen the Night Hound in person. Nor have they ever heard its voice.

For Bianca and Sinclaire, who have only ever read about the Night Hound in newspapers, he's just another villain.

So Vikir purposely spoke in a cold voice without a single ounce of warmth, filled with mana, so that Bianca and Sinclaire would be terrified simply by hearing the warning.

“Is that really the Night Hound? I've never heard such a horrible voice in my life.”

“I'm sure the face behind the mask is just as terrifying as that voice!”

But Dolores had a different reaction.

“...Guys, let's stay back.”

She knows the Night Hound.

That his inner self is sublime and holy, and that he is the only one who can stand up to the demon at this point.

At the same time, Dolores sent some of her juniors to inform the professors of the current situation.

'We cannot summon too many professors, or even the Night Hound will be in danger.'

We need a saving grace, someone who can calm things down a bit.

One or two academy professors would be just the right number.

Dolores adjusted the power of the Salvation Army while simultaneously radiating divine power to control the undead around her.

Next. The Night Hound and the Corpse Queen faced off once more.

Vikir murmured low.

“This time, I won't miss.”

But the corpse queen's reaction was slightly different.

[Take it off.]

...?

Vikir shook his head, and the corpse queen made herself clear once more.

[Take off your mask. Reveal your face].

The corpse queen makes strange demands out of nowhere, but there is no reason for Vikir to comply.

“Die.”

Vikir draws his black bow, Anubis.

Boom!

Five trajectories of Ballak's archery tear the atmosphere into pieces.

Seeing this, the Corpse Queen's aura exploded.

Thud!

The skeleton soldiers rose up and formed a wall to block the arrows, followed by a vague inferno as a topping.

...Pow!

Vikir quickly stepped back.

A fireball fell from the spot where he had just stood, engulfing everything in its path.

Meanwhile. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, who had watched the Night Hound and the Corpse Queen clash, each said something.

“Is this villain versus villain?”

“I don't know what these villains are fighting about, but it would be perfect if they both died.”

“We need to get the professors!”

“This is one of those moments when the phrase 'Stop poisoning by poison', and 'fight against one another'.”

“Let's get out of the way, we might end up in a whale fight....”

The Night Hounds are an Evil defined by the Empire that must be eradicated.

Black mages outside of the Empire's control are also dangerous, and their power and harm are not far behind the Night Hounds.

Therefore, everyone who could see the situation wanted the Night Hound and the Corpse Queen to be exterminated here and now.

...Only one. Except for Dolores, who knew what was going on.

'Please don't get hurt.'

She was cheering on the Night Hound with a piteous expression.

A pilgrim on a path of sacrifice and hardship. A great being who sacrifices for the sake of all, yet never shows any sign of regret.

I can't help but cast a pitying glance at him, who must be bearing all the blood, wounds, and pain alone at this very moment.

[....]

And the corpse queen, noticing the same gaze from Dolores, became even more uncomfortable.

[...Soul mate? You're kidding!]

A veil of pitch-black fire formed around her, and sharp iron skewers began to protrude from it.

[Remove your mask and reveal your identity, Night Hound!]

It's the corpse queen, still obsessed with the face in the mask from earlier.

But.

“Death to the demon.”

Vikir doesn't answer, only sending arrows flying.

The corpse queen's fire grows hotter and hotter as she continues to make demands.

[...Really? You don't have any intention of speaking, do you?]

She momentarily sidetracks the dead soldiers' advance.

[Then I will force you to speak].

Suddenly, the hordes of skeletons change direction and spread out.

Intent on inflicting AoE damage on an unspecified number of people.

The first targets were the crowd near the bar: Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, among others.

“Ouch! They're coming this way! We'll stop them!”

“We can't let the civilians get hurt!”

“Ooh, do you think we can stop it from our line?”

“We have to try!”

“We have to hold on!”

This is where my experience with midterms at the Academy comes in handy.

Defense Test. A defense against an onslaught of monsters.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire had already been through this before and were able to hold off the skeleton soldiers.

But practice isn't the same as the real thing.

The students were overwhelmed by the momentum of the creatures as they clung to them, baring their teeth and nails.

“Ouch! We're breached!”

“We're in danger!”

“Hey, is there anyone who can help! I'm pierced!”

“We're breached too!”

“W, wrong, there's no way we can do this!”

Even if you're in the mood for a party, you can't help but notice what's going on at this point.

Slowly, the crowd at the very back of the concert began to realize what was happening.

The dead, with their unconditional hatred of the living, descend upon the students.

Catastrophe was inevitable.

...Then.

Quack, quack, quack!

The storm raged, sweeping away the skeletons in its wake.

A black cloak fluttered before the eyes of the exhausted students.

“Professor!”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire shouted together, their faces flushed with color.

The man who had reduced countless skeleton soldiers to bone dust with a single blow.

It was Professor Banshee Morgue.

“What the hell is going on here, why are there undead on campus...?”

It didn't take him long to realize what was happening.

This was a crisis of the first order.

Wake-up call.

The skeleton soldiers are on the move, targeting students and spectators at the academy.

But not a single one of them managed to break through Professor Banshee's defenses.

“You will not be able to harm my students by a hair's breadth.”

Professor Banshee stood in the way of his students with his usual stern and sarcastic demeanor.

Whoosh!

Hellfire and iron skewers flew, but Professor Banshee blocked them all with a wall of wind and ice.

Woohoo!

But even Professor Banshee's storm windows and ice walls couldn't completely block the Corpse Queen's attack.

Taking advantage of Professor Banshee's distraction, the Legion of the Dead broke ranks and attempted to cross over to the concert hall beyond the bar.

“...Professor Sadi!”

Professor Banshee opened his mouth to call out, but a high-pitched chuckle came from the other side.

“Ho ho ho – I told you not to call me by my first name, grim old man.”

A stalk of whip flew out like a snake, crushing the skeleton soldiers on the other side.

Thud!

Kill Hill's heel pierced the crown of a skeleton rolling across the floor.

Then, a tall, slender woman in killer heels, Professor Sadi, appeared.

Puff, puff, puff!

The whip she wielded devastated a radius of several dozen meters, sweeping the dead away like garbage.

Professor Banshee glared at Sadi in an annoyed tone.

“How unlucky for you to be on duty at a festival.”

“I don't care who's on call, it's ridiculous.”

But aside from her work attitude, Sadi's skills are the real deal.

She quickly subdues every single one of the dead who make their way toward the crowd.

Professor Banshee, meanwhile, had multicast several great spells of fire, ice, and earth and was aiming for the back of the bar.

“The other professors who were contacted should be here soon, and it's time to hunt down the bad guys.”

Professor Banshee was confident of victory.

As the Night Hound and the Corpse Queen bared their teeth at each other, he was ready to ambush them.

But beside him, Professor Sadi had no answer.

“....”

She just glances around, her unreadable eyes scanning the area for any sign of backup.

Just then.

...Kurrrr!

A strange phenomenon was detected.

A black curtain suddenly descended around them.

A shield made of an unknown, eerie aura, dark mana, descended like a curtain marking the end of the stage.

The curtain was composed of a demonic energy so powerful and strange that even Professor Banshee, who was well versed in magic, had never seen it before.

“.....Barrier?”

Professor Banshee hurriedly cast a series of spells that had been created.

“Hohoho-what is this? Is it a barrier? Who hit it?”

Professor Sadi cracked his whip, but couldn't pierce the black curtain.

Soon, the barrier disappeared in an instant, hiding its presence.

“ ... It didn't run away, it's still in this space. We just can't see it.”

Professor Banshee scanned his surroundings with a sharp gaze.

The Night Hound and the Corpse Queen, who had disappeared into the subspace of the barrier, were still out there somewhere.

Knowing that, both Professor Banshee and Sadi remained alert and on guard.

...But they did not know it.

/ Ring

-Finit hic Deus -On

-Finit hic Deus, the realm of God ends here.

This ring is the product of the power of Andromalius, one of the Ten, and it is the most powerful ring of all, so powerful that anyone but a monster or a child under the age of 8 cannot even look into it.

...And.

“You will die here.”

In a subspace void that no one can peek into.

The Night Hound and the Corpse Queen were about to begin their fight, once again alone.

Chapter 215

My Neck Will Be Your Sheath (2)

◆

[...?]

Camus looked stunned for a moment.

A metal skewer extended from her hand and pierced Vikir's stomach.

[It's midnight, little one].

An unpleasant voice emanated from the crack in the mist that had been torn open like a mouth.

The eighth demon, Seere.

At midnight, it began forcibly controlling Camus's body.

[Oh, no! No...!?]

Camus cried out in desperation.

But the heaviest thing in the world is an eyelid.

For a moment, Camus's head snapped open like a marionette with a broken thread. And soon a completely different expression appeared on her face.

Her eyes loosened slightly, and she smiled bewitchingly.

The demon king Seere, who ruled over the herds of corpses and bones, was there.

“...!”

Vikir recognized Camus at once.

How could he forget those sticky eyes that held so many of his companions in the line of fire?

[Hohoho- you're the same Vikir, I've heard so much about you from my 'roommate'].

Seere said as she looked at the Vikir in front of her.

Unlike other Ten Commandments, which usually referred to their original owner as the 'host', Seere was referring to Camus's consciousness as a roommate.

'A form of roommate rather than ...host? A strange relationship.'

Vikir stepped back, covering the hole in his stomach with his hand.

Certainly the corpse queen before him was different from the other Ten Commandments.

She's half Camus, half Seere, and they've come to an arrangement where they share the day by mutual agreement.

Perhaps this is why the demonic aura didn't seem so strong when I first met her.

Vikir regenerated the wound on his stomach using the power of the bog salamander.

Tsutsutsuts...

The speed of healing was lower than before. It wasn't because her regeneration power had decreased, but because the damage from the magic had become more powerful.

The dark mana floating in the air had also become much thicker since the body's controller had changed from Camus to Seere.

'Is this 100% of her?'

Vikir swallowed hard and looked up.

In front of him, Seere, who had begged for Camus's body, was walking towards him.

[I almost ruined the job in the end because of one trivial emotion. This is why all humans are thrown away. They don't understand the greater good.]

Demons generally have no concept of gender, but they still vaguely distinguish between male and female bodies.

Seere was technically a female, and as such, her voice, gestures, facial expressions, and everything else was tinged with deadly color.

And when it manifested in the body of Camus, the impact was enormous.

But fortunately, there were no males around here that could be charmed within Andromalius's barrier.

With a strong will, Vikir cleared his mind of Seere's disturbing aura.

He asked in a calm tone.

“How long has it been in your body?”

[I don't know? It's been a while, I guess, because it was around the time she was mastering the Art of Complete Revival...]

Vikir's eyebrows twitched at that.

The veteran who had lived through the Age of Destruction had eaten not only sword rice, but also quite a bit of magic rice.

As such, he had a vague idea of what Seere was referring to as a 'art of complete revival'.

Seere spoke in a mixed voice.

[If you're a swordsman and don't know, the 'Art of Complete Revival' is a magic that drains the caster's life and brings the target back to life completely. In short, it's like giving away one's life].

However, to cast this spell, the caster must have the remains of the target.

A certain amount of the target's body parts, such as ashes, blood, nails, and hair, must be present for the spell to be complete.

Vikir asked briefly.

“But that foreign magic is considered taboo even among black mage, right? The rebound penalty in case of failure is too large compared to the slim possibility of success.”

The 'rebound penalty' refers to the strain placed on the veins of the entire body, including the brain, by the explosive backflow of mana if the spell fails halfway through.

At that, Seere laughed out loud.

[Hohoho! That's right, you're admitting your stupidity right after you've had an affair. But hey, I am gratefu, because I got this body thanks to this stupid bitch doing something like that].

“...?”

Vikir frowned. Seere grinned from ear to ear.

[This kid had dabbled in all sorts of black magic that was forbidden even by his own family, and had a mana surge].

“...!”

Mana Surge is the most burdensome of the rebound penalties, and is the most feared by all mana users.

Simply put, the mana in your veins bursts and spurts out of your veins, wreaking havoc on your body, and the danger is nothing short of a stroke or cerebral hemorrhage.

Most will die instantly, but there is a small chance that they will go berserk, rampage, or turn vegetative.

In some cases, the accumulated mana is released all at once through the sweat pores of the body, causing an explosion of terrifying proportions.

This seemed to be the case with Camus.

[She was a fearless brat who relied on her talent and determination. Hohoho- there's a guy she'd love to see again? What kind of fool risks her life for that?]

Seere sneered as she looked down at Camus's body.

[If I had a face like this and a body like this, I would never have lived like that... I would have been able to easily beat up young males and become stronger by draining their blood... Ahhh, the world is so hard].

Camus practiced black magic, which was considered too dangerous even by the Morgue, the Mage Family.

Only one reason. One day, when she finds Vikir's remains, she intends to share her lifeblood to bring him back to life.

But taboo magic is taboo for a reason.

Outer magic is powerful and fascinating.

Many geniuses who could have made their mark on human history had they lived have fallen under its spell and been destroyed by it, and the number of people who have been buried in the dust of history is countless.

The stronger and smarter you are, the easier it is to fall into the trap, and it makes everyone think that they are different.

And the end result is the same for everyone.

Crippled or dead.

The mana surge causes the veins in the body to shut down.

Camus experienced a mana surge at the last moment before completing her spell, leaving her teetering on the edge.

With half of her brain dead. She was half dead, half alive, not really dead and not really alive.

And then, as a living corpse, a figure appeared in front of her.

[Little girl, why don't you make a contract with me?]

The fall of a noble idealist. A being who had fallen in the most dramatic trajectory from top to bottom.

At the end of the fall, at the bottom, lurking with its mouth open, was the grim demon Seere.

[Well, a normal mage would have died a hundred times over, so this girl's talent for surviving in a vegetative body in such a situation is truly remarkable. Hohoho- I have one good eye, don't I?]

Seere said in a pleased tone, as if she was quite fond of the body she was occupying.

[Maybe if she didn't have that... longing and desperation for a man, she would have been a little less impatient, and with a little more time to mature and grow stronger, she would have been able to perfect the 'Art of Complete Revival'].

“....”

[Hohoho- well, that's all wrong now].

Finished speaking, Seere raised her head and looked at Vikir.

Kurrrrr!

His aura boiled like asphalt.

Only now did the demonic scent begin to flow at a 100% intensity.

Puff-puff-puff!

Black flames and iron skewers flew out, aimed at Vikir.

The magic power, which had never been stronger than before, pressed down on the entire field within the formation and tightened.

“....”

Vikir stepped back and raised his black bow, Anubis.

The hunter's focus remained firmly fixed on the bull's-eye even in these extreme conditions.

Pop! Pop! Pow!

A hole opened up at the base of the flames, and the iron skewers were struck by the arrow and sent flying in a shower of sparks.

Seere chuckled.

[Indeed, the hunter who killed Andromalius and Dantalian, but you can't catch me like that... huh?]

But the demon's laughter didn't last long.

Kirik-.

An unpleasant sensation washed over her face.

Seere frowned and waved her hand.

[...What is this?]

Something like a thin thread is pressing against her face, preventing her from moving forward.

It was thin enough to not be easily observed by the naked eye, but it was quite tough.

It was like a wire.

Karak-

There were countless such threads in the air.

[Hack hack hack]]

Little Madam. The creature had set a trap of spider webs around Seere's body.

[What? Isn't that a spider from the Euphoric Hell? Why is it here?]

Seere tried to break the threads with her strength, as if they were a nuisance.

Taeae-ae-ang – Gee-gee-.

Surprisingly, it didn't break even with the strength of a demon king class demon.

Of course, Seere wasn't the type to show off his physical strength, but it was still quite unexpected.

[How dare this bugger...!?]

Seere breathed out flames and tried to incinerate the web.

But there was no way a veteran demon hunter like Vikir would miss a moment of distraction.

Puff-puff-puck!

Arrow after arrow flew, piercing Seere's limbs. None of them were critical, but all were likely to affect her movements.

[Gah!]

Seere screamed, and the hound of death bared its teeth in front of her.

...Whoosh!

The sword's aura burned like the sun.

Vikir unleashed a long black aura blade.

In an instant, Seere shouted in panic.

[If you kill me, you'll also kill this girl!]

The human mind is a fragile thing, easy to play with. From a demon's perspective, it is.

Especially when they're as deceptive as she was.

...But.

“No.”

Vikir's grip on the sword was firm, unwavering.

“Only you will die.”

Chapter 219

That Day, Him and Me (2)

◆

Time is like flowing water, so easily it passes by even if you don't hold on to it.

And so it seems all the more swift to those who have nothing to hold on to.

-The Dark Hall of Morgue-

This place, always immersed in shadow, takes the form of a tall tower.

Towers that rise sharply under a gloomy sky where crows fly in flocks.

And on the highest of them, on the throne of the Great Council, sat a man.

Skinny and tall, with a sinister aura radiating from his back.

A grim-looking man with black hair and black eyes stared down at the ground below.

Snake Morgue.

Responsible for the Mage Master Morgue's Dark Hall and considered the third in rank within the family.

After Raspane Morgue, the head of the family, and Adolf Morgue, the representative of the Light Hall, he is the most powerful man in the House of Morgue.

However, unlike Raspane and Adolf, who are close siblings, they had a good friendship, but Snake, who was a bit distant, was different from them.

And Dark Hall also gives the impression that he is somehow distant within the family, in keeping with Snake's personality.

Whatever. The Dark Hall lurks in the shadows, conducting secret research and experiments, and the fruits of their labor are the spear and shield of the Morgue, so Snake, who oversees all things Dark Hall, is clearly indispensable to the Morgue.

“....”

Such was Snake, now frowning and looking down at the tower.

There was a girl standing there, looking up at him with a chubby face.

Camus Morgue. A member of the Light Hall and the future owner of Morgue House.

Snake spoke in a low voice.

“ ..., A member of the Light Hall, what are you doing here?”

There was little reason for a Morgue from the Light Hall to come to the Dark Hall.

Except for the quarterly exchange of skills.

Even then, it's only between established practitioners, so there's even less reason for the recently turned seventeen-year-old Camus to come here.

But.

“I left the Light Hall.”

Snake's eyes widened a little at Camus's words.

His eyebrows wiggled at the next words.

“I wish to join the Order.”

The bombshell. It's not normal to switch factions.

Especially not from the position of young master, the man responsible for Morgue's future.

Snake was dumbfounded and speechless for a moment.

Only after a long moment did he finally speak.

“...Why?”

“Because I'm tired of struggling.”

Camus answered immediately, and Snake fell silent again.

Snake knew from reports that Camus had been searching the Black Mountain depths for Vikir for years.

He also knew from reports that Camus had not only been unsuccessful in his search, but that there had been no small harvest in recent years.

“...I guess you didn't find it after all.”

“Yeah.”

Camus nodded coolly, admitting her failure.

They had spent the last hour frantically searching the depths, but in the end, they hadn't found Vikir's remains.

A bond at age eight. And reunited at fifteen.

Those few days at the Red Fang Castle were the happiest of Camus's life.

She wondered if it would be the same if she were to get married and go through the honeymoon period. At the time, she believed the happiness would last a lifetime.

But it was shattered. Hated by the natives of the jungle! Torn to shreds by a demonic creature!

Camus gritted her teeth and searched the depths.

And the more she searched, the more she had to admit.

Vikir was no more. He was dead. Not even his bones.

Is that why? Camus had been blackened.

“I want to learn black magic and bring him back to life.”

“...How can you do that when you can't even find his body?”

“I'm sure his spirit still wanders the Netherworld, or maybe he's already turned into a ghost. Either way, I plan to summon it and bring him back to life. If we can find his remains later, so much the better.”

At that, Snake put a hand to his forehead.

“Young lady. You're taking it too easy to switch factions, aren't you? You're going to leave the Light Hall, enter the Dark Hall, and walk the path of the Black Magic. What does this mean....?”

“It means that I will abandon my mother, my uncle, and all my authority as young lady, and live in the shadows for the rest of my life.”

Camus cuts off Snake's words like a knife.

Snake's mouth hung half open, at a loss for words.

His expression doesn't change as much as his younger cousin Banshee Morgue, who is a professor at the Colosseo Academy in the distance, but he seems really surprised this time.

With a grunt, Snake straightened his posture.

“ ...What on earth do you want from me, Young lady?”

“As I said before, I have someone I want to learn black magic from and bring back to life.”

“At best, you can animate a ghost, or a corpse.”

“I thought there was a way to imbue them with the spirituality of the living.”

“!”

Snake's expression twitched once more.

The kind of black magic that Camus was talking about was a dangerous kind of ancient black magic, the kind that required the sacrifice of one's own life in exchange for a “art of complete revival” that would bring the dead back to near full life.

It is, of course, strictly taboo, both in Morgue, and in the Empire.

“...It is not only difficult to learn, but the chances of success are extremely slim, and even if you succeed in saving your victim after ten thousand attempts, there is a high probability that they will corrupt or run amok afterward.”

“The soul of the person I'm trying to save is strong. Once I succeed, I don't have to worry about anything else-if I can succeed.”

Camus's faith was firm and steadfast.

Seeing the look in her eyes, Snake paused for a moment.

After a long moment, he cut her off.

“I refuse.”

A black folding screen then unfolded, closing the distance between Snake and Camouflage.

A clear sign of good luck.

But Camus didn't leave. Instead, she stood there, unmoving, and spoke.

“Marquis Snake. I know you love my mother.”

Suddenly, the unfolding folding screens stopped.

Camus turned to Snake on the other side of the folding screen and continued.

“Love between close relatives is also an affair. You hid in the shadows of the Morgue, saying you had no reason to look at the sky. Even now, because of your genius talent, you were forced to become the head of the dark hall, and you still love the head of the family.”

There was no answer.

Only.

...Drrrr!

The black folding screens blocking my view were cleared away.

Snake, his face set in a stern expression, had slid down from his throne and was now standing in front of Camus.

“Did Adolf tell you that I'm a filthy human being? Did he tell you to go and mock me with those words?”

But Camus was unfazed.

“My mother and uncle never told me that, I only knew it from the rumors that circulated among the elders.”

“Bullshit. The elders are all old and dead already.”

“The will of the dead. Even the dead talk a lot.”

With that, Camus drew up her mana.

A black aura formed behind her, and the spirits of old men with graying beards began to float around.

They were the ghosts of the elders.

Seeing that she had already learned to use black magic, Snake asked in surprise.

“What is this black magic! Who taught you this?”

“I'm self taught.”

“...What, what?”

Snake was speechless.

Self-taught black magic? Was that even possible?

It's not an exaggeration to say that she broke new ground by herself. A truly remarkable talent, if true.

“...I'm not kidding. So it's true that you're a once-in-a-hundred-years talent.”

Snake stroked his chin.

But that didn't change his demeanor.

“But that is irrelevant. I cannot allow young lady to enter the Dark Hall.”

“Is that because you don't want to offend my mother? Because you still love her?”

Camus's retort left Snake momentarily speechless.

And Camus's next move was even more baffling.

She untied her clothes and walked forward.

Suddenly, all of her clothes fell to the ground and she was naked without a single thread.

Camus said to Snake

“I looked just like my mother when she was young. And if I were to take you into my body, would that change the story?”

She stepped up to stand directly in front of Snake.

Camus's eyes glowed with desire, a desire so strong and so hot that it would do anything to reach its goal.

And Snake's pupils shake when he sees those eyes.

“ ...Get dressed.”

“....”

“Get dressed, young lady.”

Snake turned his head and gestured.

...Charak!

The clothes rose up like a snake and wrapped around Camus's entire body.

In front of Camus, who suddenly looked like he was dressed casually.

“Don't you ever insult my feelings for her again.”

The Marquis of Snake Morgue shook his head.

For a moment, she stared at him in silence.

Then her mouth opened.

“Thank you for the favor. Master.”

Chapter 220

That Day, Him and Me (3)

◆

Snake Morgue.

In addition to being a member of the Morgue family, he was also a licensed Black Mage registered with the Imperial Army.

12-73062191, which was his military number. This meant that he was a soldier with a guaranteed identity and was under the control and surveillance of the Empire.

But even he had a secret place.

The basement of the Dark Hall's headquarters. A deep underground space that stretched for over 600 floors.

-Level 666 of the Crypt.

It was a place beyond the reach of the Empire, beyond the gaze of the Morgue, and known only to the delegates of the Dark Hall.

Walking directly down the spiral staircase that seemed to have no end in sight, Snake spoke to Camus as she followed.

“Young Lady.”

“Yes. Master.”

“Do you know the origins of the 'Morgue'?”

Snake was still using a distant tone.

Camus shook her head, saying nothing in response.

Snake lifted his lantern, illuminating the darkness of the underground.

“The Morgue began as a mortuary, a morgue.”

“...!”

“It was a small family that specialized in such things, keeping only unidentified corpses.”

“Morgue” is a name for a very old bloodline that has been passed down since before humans established the concept of family or nation. The main job of those who inherited this lineage was collecting unidentified corpses and finding relatives.

They would collect bodies that had been mutilated beyond recognition, find the relatives, hand them over, and get compensated.

As a result, they naturally found themselves in the company of the dead, and over time, people who could communicate with the dead gradually appeared.

Whether it was once a power on par with a nation, or decades after its fall, when it was once again called a House of Mage, there was a steady stream of people with this uncanny ability.

Just like the current camel.

“So, technically, the Morgue's origins are very close to the dead. From their earliest beginnings, they spoke to the dead and called upon them.”

“...So you've been in touch with the black magic since birth.”

“Exactly.”

Snake lifted the lantern.

The room was silent and gloomy, like a stone chamber in a deep tomb.

Even the air was chilly against the skin.

Snake's mumbling voice was drowned out by his footsteps, forcing Camus to strain her ears even further.

“And so it is that the Black Mages of Morgue know that the truth that a man can seek and understand in a lifetime is but a handful of sand picked up from the shore.”

“Then where is most truth?”

“Behind death. Beyond the gates.”

It is only by crossing the gates of death that man becomes completely free and eternal.

The infinite truth behind it can be explored.

“Knowing this, magical geniuses who have surpassed the limits of human endeavor will eventually turn to black magic. The more intelligent and accomplished they are, the more easily they are swayed by temptation.”

“I suppose I need to familiarize myself with death.”

“No. Before that, you must first be wary of death.”

“?”

Camus shook her head.

Then Snake turned to her, a serious look on his face.

“Remember, Young lady. A black mage is the one who has the least regard for death.”

“Why is that, Master?”

“Because one must first understand and familiarize oneself with life before one can understand and familiarize oneself with death.”

Snake's words were grim but sincere.

He turned toward Camus.

“Life. Feelings for others. Love. Friendship. Trust. Organic relationship with all that is in the world. Gratitude for being alive. The preciousness of life. Understand these things first, and only then can you truly understand death, for everything is two-sided.”

“Can't we get acquainted with death first?”

“That would be like a bunch of drunken fools imitating a black mage.”

“ ...That's hard.”

“It's hard, very hard.”

Contrary to popular belief, a true black mage must be able to love and understand the living more deeply than anyone else.

It is one who loves all things living and pities all things dying.

It's more like an archmage or a saint, as the world calls them.

'So this is what it means to be polar opposites.'

Camus was becoming increasingly interested in black magic.

Not as a means to an end, but as a pure end in itself.

◆

Some time passed.

Under Snake's guidance, Camus gained knowledge at an incredible rate.

Soon, her skills were beyond recognition.

...Pow!

Black air currents swirled, and a woman with nothing but bones and skin rose from them.

Rosie Morgue. She was Camus's third cousin, who had been killed in battle against the barbarians.

Camus had used Rosie's remains, found while searching the depths, to turn her into a undead soldier.

“Rosie!”

Camus and Rosie embraced each other.

Because she had been resurrected by high-level black magic, she had only a very low level of intelligence.

Even her magic level was higher than when she was alive.

Meanwhile, Snake, who was watching the scene from the side, was overwhelmed with admiration.

“To think that you've already been able to create a undead soldier, that's quite an accomplishment.”

How long had it been since she'd turned to the Black Mage?

It wasn't an exaggeration to say that Camus had already mastered almost every aspect of Black Magic that humans had discovered.

The rest was just something she could conquer as she grew older.

'Maybe this child will be the one to see the end of the black magic discovered by humans.'

Snake thought to himself.

...But.

Camus was looking at something more than just the obvious laying down of the law.

“It's not good enough.”

She looked sadly at Rosie, then shook her head.

Then she turned to Snake.

“What I'm looking for is a way to fully revive the dead.”

“ ...That's the realm of humans, and after that, it's the realm of gods.”

“The distinction between human and god is meaningless in the face of what must be done.”

At the same time, Camus unfolded a large piece of paper in front of Snake.

It was a drawing of incredibly intricate and detailed shapes.

Snake's eyes widened as if they were about to tear apart.

“What is this?”

“The Magic Circle of Full Revival. The result of my own research.”

Hearing Camus's calm words, a chill ran down Snake's spine.

It was several steps more advanced than the one that had resurrected Rosie just a moment ago. No matter how many times he opened it, it still looked perfect.

Snake turned his head towards the young genius in front of him.

A mixture of emotions sprouted in him. Pride, jealousy, fear, affection, and sadness.

What was he looking for in that face that looked so much like 'her' from the past?

Snake has been in and out of the depths of the Abyss of Magic, but he's never been inside his own mind, so he doesn't know.

He could only ask questions.

“Is a man named Vikir that good?”

“....”

Camus didn't answer. It just nodded slowly.

Snake nodded as well.

“Very well, if that's what you want.”

He hadn't expected to say the words he'd spoken to 'a woman' so long ago, when he'd ascended to the Master of the Dark Hall, to her child so many decades later.

The two genius black mages put their heads together at the table.

“Since we have no remains of the person we wish to save, what do you propose to do about that?”

“We've enlisted the cooperation of the Baskervilles to gather some blood and hair. There may also be fragments of his soul mixed in with the unspecified number of spirits we summoned from the depths.”

“I see, if there are fragments of his body, then there will be fragments of his soul as well, so we can sort them out then.”

Not just a corpse that moved at will, but a corpse with memories and a personality.

No, at that point it was no longer a corpse.

Snake opened his mouth.

“Do you know the paradox of 'Ship of Theseus'? Even if he regains his body, memories, and personality, it is a question that needs to be considered.”

“It's never too late to ponder such existential questions after success, Master.”

With that, Camus and Snake began to imbue their drinks and ingredients with mana.

The circle of magic fired up.

Countless complex shapes glowed.

The ingredients at their center.

35 liters of water, 20 kilograms of carbon, 4 liters of ammonia, 1.5 kilograms of lime, 800 grams of phosphorus, 250 grams of salt, 100 grams of potassium nitrate, 80 grams of sulfur, 7.5 grams of fluorine, 5 grams of iron, 3 grams of silicon, 15 other trace elements, and memories of blood and flesh... All of which began to emit a foul stench, heat, and smoke.

...Wait, stench?

Camus's expression stiffened for a moment.

According to the theory, it was supposed to smell like human flesh at this time.

But now it smelled like rotting flesh, a horrible stench.

'Failure!'

Camus knew in her gut. She didn't know what had gone wrong, or how, but she knew the result.

But there was nothing she could do about the circle that had already been activated.

Then, from the center of the circle, something strange began to rise.

...! ...! ...! ...! ...!

I couldn't tell what it was, but at least it wasn't Vikir.

That thing must not be allowed to leave the circle.

Camus gritted her teeth and gathered her mana, trying to catch the spilled water again.

But it wasn't enough.

...Boom!

The magic circle shattered and the mana flowed back.

“Young lady!”

Snake's shout rang in my ears.

The price of failure is death. What else could it be?

Camus felt the power of her entire body release.

She sees a door in front of her. Wide open.

Camus's body was being pulled through it of its own accord. Beyond, into a vast abyss of stars and gas clouds. Like dust.

'Is this death.'

Camus surrendered herself to the flowing water with a blank expression.

She didn't know why the spell had failed. Was it because the fragments of Vikir's flesh were too old? Or was his spirit absent from the depths?

Perhaps he has already turned his back on this world and attained Buddhahood?

Then I felt pity for myself. The person who remained in this world, suffering and struggling alone.

Maybe it would be easier to follow him through that gate at this point.

...Right then.

Flutter!

A figure stood in Camus's way.

A figure stood in the door, his black cloak flapping. Snake Morgue.

Without looking back, he spoke to Camus.

“Go back.”

Camus looked up.

Snake spoke again.

“Your picnic is not over yet, so go back and say it was beautiful.”

Snake took a step without hesitation toward the other side of the door called by the dawn, dew, sunset, and clouds in the abyss.

'I hope you become a black mage who can love life.'

That was it.

At the same time.

...Bang!

As soon as Snake disappeared beyond the door, it closed.

He went in and closed the door.

Poof!

The abyss stopped pulling Camus in.

Boom!

With a loud explosion, Camus rolled across the floor.

“Cough!”

Blood spewed from her mouth.

Camus came to his senses.

“...Master!?”

But her head doesn't turn. His entire body is as stiff as stone.

Then something came into view.

It was Snake, sitting on the ground with his eyes closed.

To my astonishment, his skin, which had been so vibrant just moments before, had turned to dry parchment.

In an instant, his body was reduced to bone and flesh. All of his life force had been drained.

“....”

Camus felt tears well up in her eyes.

She could see nothing through her cloudy, wet vision.

Snake was dead.

He had taken most of the rebound penalty for his mana rampage to keep him alive.

Camus sobs slightly, remembering all the years she spent learning magic from her master.

But she couldn't sob at will.

Even Snake hadn't been able to bear the full impact.

That alone had killed half her brain and half her body.

She had lost her sister, her lover, and her teacher. Was this the result of turning her back on her mother and uncle?

She lost all her loved ones around her. She went from the highest to the lowest. A doll who can do nothing but cry and regret the past.

An underground cave that is now deserted. A tomb so deep and lonely that the only person left in it was a dead girl who hadn't died yet, sobbing her heart out.

...Just then.

An unidentifiable voice called out.

[Little girl, why don't you make a contract with me?]

It was a temptation as sweet as the first taste of honey.

She tried to move to see what it was, but her semi-immobilized body wouldn't budge.

[I can give you power].

Instead, it manifested itself into her consciousness.

A giant hand stretched out toward her.

[The power to reunite you with your loved ones.]

It was a hand that the drowning Camus had no choice but to face.

Chapter 221

That Day, Him and Me (4)

◆

[I can give you power].

It was a trick of the demon. It was literally a ploy from the demon.

But Camus couldn't refuse. She had no other choice.

Whatever it took to starve to death on a cold stone floor at the bottom of a pitch-black abyss, she had to make a deal.

“Okay, what's the deal?”

[Simple, after you die, I will take over your body, and I will carry out your wishes].

'Okay. I'll do it, contract.'

[Oh? So soon? You're a good negotiator. You're smart. It's worth watching].

The demon smiled softly at Camus.

The demon then revealed her true name.

[My name is Seere, and by the power of the 8th demon who crossed over from the demon world to the human world, I have made a contract with the human Camus Morgue....]

Seere, the demon. She made a contract with Camus to take over her body after her death and fulfill Camus wishes while she was still alive.

Camus made the deal before the spark of life she carried was extinguished.

And now.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The demon Seere inhabited Camus's body.

And as soon as Seere took control of Camus's body, the first thing she did was....

[Uh!? What is this!? You're not dead yet!?]

Was to freak out.

Camus's eyes narrowed as she felt the other personality inhabiting her body.

'Did the Master arrange this?'

At the last moment, Snake oxidized all the damage that was supposed to be directed at Camus in his embrace.

The result was that Camus was only half dead.

According to the contract, the demon Seere can only claim the body after Camus is dead, so in this case, only half of the body would be Seere.

The demon Seere, now in possession of half of Camus body, began to jump up and down.

[This is ridiculous! It was a shock she couldn't have survived! If you're a human, you should have been dead by now, but how are you still alive!]

Seere turned and looked at Snake's body, which was now sitting upright in front of Camus eyes.

[Aaaah! It's the mage's doing, damn it, I should've taken what was his, even if it was just a little bit of a physical disparity].

'Take away?'

[Oh, no, I didn't take it away, I just meant that I should have made a fair contract and taken it.]

'Take it away. Did you mean to trick me into taking your body for nothing?'

[No! It's not like that...!]

Seere blurted out.

Camus ignores it, and pushes herself up.

It moved. It's not what it used to be, but her body listens.

However, her body doesn't feel quite as balanced as it used to, with Seere controlling one part of her body and Camus controlling the other.

In the end, Camus and Seere had to compromise.

[Damn, it's twisted, but it's twisted tight, so here's the deal. You use this body for half the day, and I'll use this body for the other half of the day].

'What do I get in return for doing that?'

[You're so shameless, you should have been dead and gone by now if it weren't for me. Oh, shit, I'll just wait a little longer until you starve to death].

'Quick, tell me, what can you do for me in return for me lending you my body.'

Finally giving in to Camus's prodding, Seere replied irritably.

[I have the ability to find hidden treasure, including when it's human, and I'm good at killing livestock and beasts, which makes me a good match for a black mage whose job it is to resurrect the dead].

But Camus didn't seem too interested in the latter ability.

'Good at finding people?'

That was enough for him.

And that's how Camus entered into a two-way contract with Seere.

They would wake up when each other fell asleep.

◆

Camus then held Snake's funeral and searched the Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain again.

However, she had informed Morgue that she and Snake would be practicing their closed training together.

Adolf was worried, but Raspane let it slide.

'Sister, Marquis Snake, how can you trust him!'

'He is not a man who would do any harm to Camus.'

'But the Marquis of Snake is a delegate of the Dark Hall! Besides, we have heard nothing of him as yet!'

'...Say no more about it.'

There was no way anyone could have been more disgusted by the words of Lord Raspane of Morgue.

So, officially, the Marquis of Snake, a delegate of the Dark Hall, and his apprentice, Camus, went into seclusion deep within the family home.

As time went on, the prying eyes slowly faded away.

In the meantime, Camus continued to search the jungle alone, with little success.

Until, that is, he picked up a strange object from the depths of the forest.

“...This bone?”

The bones of a black mage with a powerful grudge and magic were lying on the ground.

'Why is a black mage of this caliber lying dead here?'

Camus immediately channeled her mana to create a lich.

The high-ranking undead named Ah'Heman became her faithful servant.

...A little more time passed.

It was after several undead pieces she had painstakingly created were lost. Camus, who had been concentrating on searching and researching in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, decided to come out into the world.

[What? The undead you sent to the city disappeared?]

Seere was also annoyed.

[That must have been Dantalian, that bastard. He's got bad taste in his mouth and likes to take what belongs to others. He must have seen some well-made undead running around the city and stolen them for his own, it's obvious].

Seere and Dantalian had crossed over to the human world together, but they didn't seem to get along very well.

“I don't know about the other undead, but we need to get Rosie back.”

I felt like I had been out of the world for too long, so I sent them to find out the latest news about the city, which was a problem.

Camus immediately left the forest and headed for the city.

On her way to Indulgentia's orphanage where Dantalian was supposed to be.

She heard that there was a festival going on at the Colosseo Academy in the distance.

'It has nothing to do with me now.'

Since Vikir's death, she hadn't thought about the academy.

Camus passed the Academy by and headed straight for Indulgentia.

And then.

“...!”

Camus could see the ruins that had been left behind.

Who could have left Dantalian's lair in this state?

Camus quickly scanned her mana.

Fortunately, Rosie's soul and body were here.

Though it was shattered and scattered, Camus' powerful black magic could bring it back to life.

“Dantalian, you lowly thief. How dare you....”

Camus pushed the others aside and resurrected only Rosie.

Tsutsutsuts...

When she had just reclaimed her third cousin.

“...Who's there?”

Camus sensed something was watching her.

A figure in black robes and a plague doctor's mask.

An ominous aura radiated from him.

[Eight Corpse Seere. 'King of the Dead'. You are my copycat].

An eerie voice modulation came from his mouth.

Camus shook her head, not sure who was imitating whom.

“Who are you?”

[Don't you know me?]

“I do not know. Not like you.”

[You don't seem interested in what's going on in the world. Don't you even read the newspaper?]

Camus snorted lightly at his question.

“...Newspaper? Why would I read such a thing, I have nothing to lose in this world.”

After Vikir's death, Camus turned her back on the world, even if it was a family affair.

Afterward, the mysterious man said.

[The Demon Kills].

“If you can, do it.”

It was Camus's first battle against an opponent of her caliber since becoming a black mage.

◆

“...Ugh!?”

Camus opened his eyes.

The battle with the Night Hound had been intense.

His aura, especially at the end, was like the sun, almost blinding.

“What was that?”

Camus thought as she ran a hand through her greasy hair.

The first time the Night Hound had drawn his bow, he had momentarily let go of the leash of reason.

The barbarian archery that had killed Vikir could never be spared, not after seeing the man who wielded it.

But as the battle continued, something was off.

The Night Hound, whom I knew only as an archer, drew his sword and emitted an aura.

It was too dazzling to see clearly, but I knew I'd seen it before.

'What?'

A million thoughts raced through Camus mind.

Could it be that Vikir was still alive?

What if he had survived his grave wounds and found his way into barbarian society, where he healed and learned the art of archery?

'Come to think of it, that bow wasn't even an ordinary bow. It was obviously carved from a spider's exoskeleton.

What if Vikir eventually came back to life and took revenge on Madam Eight-Legs?

The fact that he didn't return once he was healed could be due to something like amnesia.

'...Of course, it's all wishful thinking, but you never know, right?'

In the first place, Camus had risked his life on the tenuous hope that she could find Vikir's remains and bring him back to life.

There was a possibility that Vikir had been lucky enough to survive that night.

That he might have been accepted as a member of the tribe instead of being killed by savage barbarians.

He might have learned to be an excellent archer from them.

The possibility that they had killed the Madam Eight-Legs, a depths nightmare.

And the possibility that all these possibilities overlapped and overlapped.

But that slim chance subconsciously tugged at Camus's emotions, and even in his stunned state, he forced Rosie to track down the Night Hound without killing it.

“...Okay, I'll go check it out right away.”

As soon as she recovered, Camus created an underground chamber beneath the ruins that no one knew about.

In addition, she kept a “life vessel” there, just in case.

A life vessel was a container of highly concentrated black mana, a warlock's second heart.

Camus had arranged for Rosie to be able to teleport here if her life was in danger.

“Do you understand, Rosie? If I collapse, you must bring me right here, because that's the only way I'll survive.”

Rosie nodded slowly as she listened to Camus's conviction.

It couldn't hurt to have the insurance, if only for the sake of coming here in the first place.

'Time to find out.'

If Seere really did have the ability to 'bring you into contact with those you wish to meet', then it was worth a shot.

Camus clenched her teeth.

She followed the trail of the Night Hound's escape to the darkened Imperial City.

Pow, pow, pow!

Fireworks lit up the night sky.

Toward the Colosseo Academy, where a festival was in full swing.

Chapter 225

Tuition (3)

◆

The Hunter's Guild “Sherpa,” an outsourced dispatcher of hunters and guides for monster hunting.

This guild was not known for its mercenaries, but it was known for having many guides who were familiar with the ecology and geography of monsters.

These guides, all of whom were native to the area for at least three generations, knew the ins and outs of where rare monsters lurked and swarmed.

Not to mention they know all the shortcuts and stealthy escape routes.

However, with only a few classes available to send out, such as guides and porters, guilds have always been at a disadvantage.

This is because they're often treated unfairly, with no credit for their work and reduced pay at the end of the quest.

However.

The presence of the Sherpa Guild's leader has been a constant source of support for the guild's members, even in these difficult times.

Kkigigigig-

The guild gates opened.

The guild members who were practicing in the training center looked back at the front door of the guild office and shouted in unison.

“The Guild Leader is coming to work!”

“Attention! Salute!”

“Good morning!”

A man who commanded the respect of all the guild members.

He stood at least 2 meters tall and 30 centimeters wide, and weighed close to 180 kilograms.

A tightly cropped sporting haircut, scars running horizontally and vertically across his face, heavy armor-like muscles covering his entire body, and even the martial arts skills on the graduator.

The name of this man, who looks like a huge beast of prey, is 'Miniature Pinscher', also known as 'MiniPin'!

How many people could punch out labor costs based on his appearance?

As long as MiniPin reigns supreme as Guild Leader, the Sherpa Guild will continue to survive, as he is both terrifying in appearance and terrifying in skill.

He's even known to be relentless when it comes to training his guild members, as he's a strict meritocrat.

“The more you sweat in training, the less you bleed in battle!”

MiniPin's thunderous words made the guildsmen in the barracks stiffen once more.

It was all thanks to him that the Sherpa Guild's porters and guides were armed with the physical and mental strength of steel.

What's more, MiniPin's rank was Graduator. He could be a member of any of the top mercenary guilds.

Even the Imperial Army was sending scouts to train him as an officer.

But MiniPin had rejected all of these offers.

'I love hunting. Fighting monsters is my calling.'

These were MiniPin's beliefs.

There was a small part of him that hoped to one day join the Baskervilles on the Western Front, but that was out of the question, as they wouldn't be the first to send him a scouting offer.

So MiniPin's main goal is to preserve and protect his current guild.

“And to do that, I need to keep my employers in check.”

MiniPin walked into his office and scanned through the new requests.

“Let's see, this is a request for a courier from another mercenary guild. They want to capture a Venompion for research... but they have too few people. If we get involved, the couriers will die. Dismissed. Is this a request for directions to a merchant? Hmm, but the mercenaries escorting them are too underpowered. We may lose them. Dismiss this one....”

We do not accept requests from strangers.

I've weeded out nearly 90% of their requests.

MiniPin clicked his tongue.

“ ... I wonder how many of them will be alive next year.”

There were too many who didn't know their place and wanted to slay powerful monsters.

Attaching porters or guides to such creatures would almost always result in their annihilation.

“They are weaker and slower to escape, so they are the first to be used as shields in a crisis, and we cannot afford to lose members of our own guild.”

So MiniPin interviewed and thoroughly weeded out weak or reckless clients.

Only clients with a mercenary plaque or mercenary credentials, or who have served in the military, are accepted, and those with lesser credentials are rejected, no matter how insignificant.

...This is exactly what happened.

“What, an academy student, even a first year?”

MiniPin reviewed the last request in front of him.

A newcomer to the Academy had requested to hire a guide.

<Request

Name: Vikir

Affiliation: Colosseo Academy

Request: Hire a guide

Purpose: Defeating monsters

Students from the academy don't usually visit places like this. They're all rich kids, after all.

However, every once in a while, an oddball will come here, mostly out of mere curiosity and a desire to experience the low life.

And for the hunting guilds, if they allowed themselves to be entertained by the children of the rich, they would lose some of their most valued members, some of whom had been with them for decades.

“Hmph. What's an Academy young master doing in a place like this? Did he feel like having some fun?”

It doesn't even say what monsters you'll be hunting. He just wanted to hire a guide.

Of course, it wasn't even worth thinking about.

MiniPin crumpled up the request and tossed it in the trash.

“Give him a glass of milk and send him on his way. You little brat, you think this quest is for kids?”

MiniPin shrugged off Vikir's request.

....

...And that was the beginning of all the tragedies that followed that night.

◆

The night. A moonless night.

Mr. MiniPin returned home from his night shift.

When he got home, he found his bunny like wife and bear like child already asleep in bed.

Passing through the living room and into the kitchen, MiniPin was hungry and rummaged through the storage room. He was going to boil some potatoes for a late-night snack.

Then.

MiniPin spotted the midnight meal on the kitchen table.

There were eggs, bacon, and toasted cornbread. It was cold, but it still looked delicious.

“...Honey.”

MiniPin muttered softly as he looked over at his sleeping wife.

He was always grateful and sorry for her, for all the trouble he'd put her through when she was younger, for the daughter he'd never done anything for, but who was growing up so well.

“Just be patient. One day, I'll solve a big client and treat you well.”

MiniPin went into the bedroom, determined to work even harder as the head of the household.

My wife seems to have fallen asleep while putting my daughter to sleep, so today I have the large bed to myself.

Eventually, when MiniPin put on his arm pillow and closed his eyes.

A rustle.

A small noise started coming from the second floor window of the bedroom.

“...What is that?”

MiniPin yawned and stretched.

Then he saw a silhouette crash through the window.

A man in a black mask opened a second-floor window and stepped inside.

MiniPin's heart sank.

He must be a burglar because he doesn't have a knife in his hand.

But he's really an unlucky burglar.

“Even if you do come in....”

The Guildmaster of the Sherpa Guild, the leader of all the guides, a man with a rank of Graduator, and even the imperial army and prominent mercenary guilds send him love calls, so why would he come to rob his house?

“I guess I'll have to take some care of it. After subduing him, should I report to Tyler and discipline him, or should I hand him over to the Imperial Guard?”

In fact, MiniPin had done this a few times.

He'd scolded thieves who'd climbed over the fence out of hunger and turned them into siblings and subordinates.

So this time, after listening to their excuses for coming in to steal after being subdued, he was willing to look the other way.

“Hey, hey, hey. Wait, stop there. If you surrender now, I might let you off the hook....”

However, it was MiniPin who really had his eyes closed.

Boom!

The black-clad man threw a fist with lightning speed.

It grazed the tip of MiniPin's ear, severing a few strands of hair before shooting off to the side.

As MiniPin gulped it down, a hole appeared in the wall next to him.

...Boom!

A fist-shaped hole was punched into the wall made of solid wood.

“This is a warning.”

An eerie voice emanated from the masked man's mouth.

A cold bead of sweat trickled down MiniPin's spine.

'If I got hit....'

If that fist had hit him straight in the face, his skull would have shattered like a grain of sand.

A level beyond human strength. Does he use mana? It doesn't make sense otherwise.

“You! How dare you think you know who I am!”

MiniPin realized that this was no ordinary opponent and immediately raised his mana.

MiniPin's fist pulsed with the whitish energy of a low-grade Graduator, something between gas and liquid.

But.

...Snap.

His opponent raised his fist as well. Surprisingly, his fist didn't contain a single handful of mana.

Only then did MiniPin realize that the opponent's fist that had flown out just a moment ago had been driven by pure muscle power.

'What kind of strength....'

A chill ran down my spine. If his body could exude such power without using mana, what would happen if he did use mana?

'I'm glad he's not using mana.'

It had been years since I had shuddered at the pure physical power of another.

MiniPin breathes a sigh of relief.

Pfft!

To his surprise, the intruder's two fists began to erupt with mana.

...!?

But MiniPin's surprise was short-lived.

Bam!

This is because my memory was cut off from the moment I thought the other person's fist was flying under my chin.

Chapter 226

Tuition (4)

◆

The next day.

MiniPin opened his eyes.

“...Is this a dream?”

But it couldn't be.

He woke up face-down on the cold floor, and his jaw was swollen shut.

There was nothing but a blanket covering him.

Suddenly, an ominous intuition flashed through his mind.

“Oh, no, honey, baby girl!”

MiniPin kicked the floor and ran down the stairs to the second floor.

But.

“Are you up?”

“Daddy, good morning!”

MiniPin was greeted by his wife and daughter, both in good spirits.

“...?”

MiniPin looked dazed.

The fire was warm in the fireplace, and sweet potatoes, potatoes, and corn were cooking.

The kitchen was bubbling and smelling like chicken stew.

Flower petals floated in the teacups, and outside the window, white laundry was drying in the sun and wind.

“?”

MiniPin was dumbfounded by the way everything looked.

His wife and daughter's attitude toward him was no different than usual.

The house was no different from yesterday.

“Why were you sleeping on the floor? You're so heavy, I couldn't even move you. What's wrong with your sleeping habits?”

“Uh, uh, me on the floor?”

“Yeah. You were sleeping soundly on the floor. I woke you up a few times, but you didn't wake up, so I just put a blanket over you. Is your neck stiff?”

She slaps MiniPin on the back.

“Uh, no. Did everything go well last night? Did a burglar get in?”

“What? A burglar? How can I hear something like that when you're here? Some big guy with a big liver....”

“Oh, no. I had a bad dream.”

“Ew, that's because you sleep in a weird position! By the way, get the sweet potatoes and corn out of the fireplace – they should be ready. Oh, and leave the potatoes, I put them in a little late!”

His wife didn't know what to say.

MiniPin sat down at the table and ate his wife's breakfast in disbelief.

Then, as usual, he left the house on time and headed for the guild office.

The streets were just as normal and routine as ever.

Neighbors greeting me as I left the fence, subordinates bowing to me on my way to work.

“...Was this a dream?”

But no.

My jaw was definitely knocked out and the hole in the wooden wall was still there.

So some crazy person broke into the house, punched MiniPin in the jaw, and left.

He didn't even rob anything!

“What the hell was he doing?”

MiniPin shook his head in disbelief.

He vowed to be extra careful with the door tonight.

◆

That night.

Lying in bed, MiniPin closed his eyes only when he saw that his wife was safely asleep.

Bushluck.

If only it hadn't been for another small noise from the window.

“Whoa, no way!”

MiniPin looked to the window.

The madman from yesterday was standing there again.

The intruder had picked the lock and stepped over the threshold without a sound.

He was even crumpling a piece of paper in his hand, deliberately making noise to show off his ghostly presence.

Rushing- Rushing-

The scene is so eerie that it sends chills down your spine.

“...Won't let me this time.”

MiniPin had hidden his favorite sword under his bedside table, just in case.

Sigh.

It's a good thing my wife is the type of person who won't notice if I go to bed with her once she's asleep.

For this great sword unleashes terrifying lethal force just by being pulled out of its sheath.

“Die!”

MiniPin charged at the intruder, swinging his greatsword.

But.

No.

The unthinkable happened.

The Graduator's aura, spinning at high speed and cutting through everything in its path, intercepted the greatsword.

And with the intruder's bare hands!

Kwagigigig! Pow! Pow! Pow!

Gradualtor's sword and aura were blocked. It was even crumbling into pieces by the second.

'This is no way...!'

MiniPin was horrified at what was happening in front of him.

But even his astonishment was not enough.

Puck!

Another fist to the jaw cut off his consciousness.

◆

“You've been a bad sleeper lately, haven't you?”

His wife asks him nonchalantly when he wakes up in the morning.

“....”

MiniPin woke up this morning still on the floor, unable to answer.

What can I say, he's been knocked out repeatedly by nightly intruders.

It's a heartbreaking story that he can't tell not only to his wife, but also to his friends, colleagues, and subordinates.

'I can't do this. I'll have to call the Imperial Guard tonight.

For the first time in his life, he leans on the power of the authorities.

MiniPin prepared to leave for work, making an important decision.

◆

The night passed, and the next morning.

“Mr. MiniPin. Is your report accurate?”

An investigator from the Imperial Guard asked, rubbing his sleepy eyes.

MiniPin had no answer.

The intruder did not come last night.

The Imperial Guard investigators looked up at MiniPin's massive body and said.

“Common sense dictates that no burglar could rob Mr. MiniPin's house.”

“Besides, to be able to capture a Graduator-class aura with just bare hands, what kind of vain... would someone with such skill be doing as a thief in the first place?”

“You said you haven't held a grudge against anyone recently. Hmm, after all, it's stalking driven by passion?”

“Whatever. We're not exactly idle either, so we're not going to be able to stand guard all night.”

“Well, it's a bit of a stretch to call it a substitute, but I'll be sure to patrol this area a bit more in the future, so goodbye.”

In the end, MiniPin had to bow his head a few times to dismiss the investigators of the Imperial Guard.

◆

And bizarrely, that night.

Bushluck-.

An intruder came to visit.

“Aaahhhh, you bastard, what do you think you're doing!”

MiniPin, wearing two helmets, ran out swinging the sword in both hands, and the result was the same as usual.

Puck-puck!

The two helmets shattered, and so did the two swords.

MiniPin was stunned by another punch to the jaw.

◆

The next day, too.

And the day after that.

And the day after that.

The midnight visits continued.

When morning dawned and it was clear that nothing had been stolen from his house this time, MiniPin sat down on the couch in the guild office with a sinking feeling.

He had already sent his wife and daughter to live with relatives, just in case,

From that day forward, MiniPin became a man afraid of the night.

How could he not be scared when some madman kept climbing through his window, hitting him once and then disappearing?

It was a very effective and violent natural sleeping pill.

“I've been suffering from stressful insomnia lately, is... some new fad insomnia treatment?”

Of course not.

But I can't mention this to the guild leader, so I just groan.

“If I told the Imperial Guard, I'd be laughed at. Ha, that clever bastard. You only come after me when I'm alone, so what's this....”

Who in the world would believe that a man over six feet tall was constantly stalking and assaulting me?

For the first time in his life, MiniPin could only feel frustrated.

Just then.

“Guildmaster. Your request has arrived.”

The adjutant waved a stack of papers in front of him.

There were fewer this time. Only one sheet.

MiniPin narrowed his eyes.

“It's the off-season and we still get requests?”

“Uh, yeah. They've been sending me statements for days. It's the same person every time.”

Then.

MiniPin realized something was wrong.

Each time, the new statement was in bad shape.

It must have been written on new paper, and it was badly wrinkled.

“What's wrong? Isn't this a new order? Why is it crumpled?”

“I don't know, he always comes in and leaves with a crumpled one. He's a student at the academy I told you about.”

“...Academy? Who is that?”

“You know who it is, a young man from the Colosseo. The one the guild leader sent back with a glass of milk.”

“Ah~”

I suddenly remember. I remembered the outrageous client who came and chased me away.

“Whatever. I have no intention of joining in the fun of the rich and famous....”

This time, MiniPin didn't think much of it and just crumpled it up.

Bushluck.

At that moment.

MiniPin stiffened as if struck by lightning.

He'd heard that crumpling sound before.

“...!?”

MiniPin quickly moved his hands, unfolded the request form he had just crumpled, and crumpled it again.

Bushluck.

This paper is made of a special material, so its crinkling sound is slightly different from other papers.

It was definitely the unpleasant noise of a nighttime intruder.

So why was the request form, which he always crumpled up and threw in the trash in his office, back here?

MiniPin looked back at the adjutant and stammered.

“Are you, are you... cleaning my room these days?”

“What? Yes, I do, all the time.”

“And the trash can in your room, do you empty it?”

“I haven't emptied it, because it's always empty.”

The adjutant's words shocked MiniPin.

He'd thrown the request form in the guild office trash a few days ago.

“Then....”

Some lunatic sends a request and then picks it up from the trash and puts it back again and again.

And it's been raiding in the night, fumbling with it!

“What the hell, what kind of crazy person does this...!”

MiniPin's face turned blue as he opened the request fully.

<Request Form

Name: Vikir

Affiliation: Colosseo Academy

Request: Hire a guide

Purpose: Defeating monsters

The paper is crumpled and barely recognizable.

MiniPin is staring at it with a blank expression.

“...When?”

An unfamiliar voice came from behind the adjutant.

Behind the adjutant who was expressing his disapproval that he was not allowed to come in here, MiniPin had a blank expression on his face.

'This is a warning.'

A first-year student at Colosseo Academy. Vikir.

“Do you feel like taking on a request now?”

He was speaking in the same voice as the intruder from last night.

Chapter 227

Tuition (5)

◆

A night with a bright moon.

Vikir silently stepped out into the wilderness of the Imperial City.

Beside him, MiniPin drove the carriage.

“It's me, Mr. .... What monster are you trying to catch?”

MiniPin had gotten a taste of Vikir's power and temper, and was treating him with great caution.

That was why he had personally responded to Vikir's request for a guide.

He knew that if he offended the madman, he would lose a valuable member of his guild.

But Vikir didn't care much for MiniPin's intentions.

“Considering that I'm a student at the academy, it's not too strange that I caught so many of them.”

“Aha.”

MiniPin nodded at Vikir's words.

Certainly, Vikir's strength was far beyond that of a normal academy student.

'Where did this monster come from?'

MiniPin let out a small sigh.

Meanwhile. Vikir was thinking about something else.

'...MiniPin, this is one of the people I need to have on my side.'

He's one of the best guides, one of the heroes who contributed so much to the Allied Forces of Humanity during the Age of Destruction.

Most of the monster encyclopedias that Vikir knows of were created by him, and later, the research field called 'monster ecogeography' was also founded based on his research.

However, MiniPin died early in the war against the demons because he had no background to fall back on.

A wild man who belonged nowhere. What does that mean?

'The person who picks it up first is the owner.'

In this life, MiniPin's life will be much longer.

He'll have the Baskervilles behind him, who will one day be swallowed up by Vikir.

'...Although I did reveal some of my power because I was planning to reap it as a vassal.'

Vikir briefly tested MiniPin, who would later rise to the ranks of heroes and soon become his confidant.

“What monsters do you know that would be suitable for a student to catch and still provide a decent income?”

“Hmm. The only monster that's not too strong and provides a decent income... is Gnoll.”

Gnoll. A grotesque creature with the head of a hyena and the body of a dwarf.

They are lowly creatures that walk on two legs and are covered in filthy fur and stink.

They inhabit the high mountains outside the Capital in packs, and their burrows are so deep underground that they cause the ground to collapse.

Not only do they get in the way of civil engineering projects, but they also attack workers, making them increasingly dangerous.

MiniPin was indeed very knowledgeable about monsters.

He generously shared his knowledge of gnolls with Vikir.

“Gnolls are weak in combat, so even a first-year academy student can capture many of them. Their fur is surprisingly tough and hard, and they're also good at keeping warm, so they're often used as rugs and covers. Their bones and organs can also be sold for medicinal purposes.”

“But selling them isn't as good as catching one of those powerful big monsters, is it?”

“You don't understand! Gnolls are an ecosystem disrupter, as defined by the Imperial Family. There's a bounty for simply killing them.”

Well, that's a different story.

Not only does killing them bring in a certain amount of bounty per animal, but if you can sell their hides, meat, and bones, you can kill two birds with one stone and make a decent income.

“So. How do you catch gnolls?”

“Hmm. Gnolls have a habit of collecting shiny objects. When encountered, it's most common to dazzle and kill them by scattering glass or something like that....”

But Vikir shook his head.

“That's only for the few gnolls you encounter.”

“Yes, I suppose that's true.”

“I will use another method.”

“...?”

Vikir's chosen method was simple.

“Gnolls are drawn to the fresh blood of a freshly killed animal. They have a great sense of smell, and they can smell it from miles away.”

“That's right, how do you know that so well, do they teach that in the academy these days?”

MiniPin looked quite surprised, for what Vikir had just said was something only experienced hunters would know.

They are the first to swarm and coil around a wounded, blood-scented prey.

Like sharks in the ocean, they play a role on land.

Vikir caught a boar, cut open its throat, and dragged its carcass from place to place.

Its blood soaks into the soil, its fishy smell wafting across the forest on the night breeze.

Vikir roamed the mountains, smearing the boar's fur and blood on the ground.

Of course, MiniPin, who had to follow, was horrified.

“You're provoking the gnolls! It's suicidal! They're only a C+ danger individually, but in a group, they're up to an A!”

The sight of all the gnolls within a few kilometers swarming toward this place would be a sight any hunter would hate to see.

But Vikir merely nods with a nonchalant expression.

“Don't worry. I'll just lure them in and hide.”

MiniPin is slightly relieved.

“Ah, hiding, that's good to hear. Certainly, they're less focused when they're eating, and if there's a competition for food among the herd, the weaker ones will surely be left behind, which will make it easier for us to pick out the easier ones to hunt. Then we can catch them one by one as they fall to the back of the pack....”

Vikir's next words, however, made MiniPin flinch once more.

“No, we're chasing the lead. We will follow them wherever they lead their prey.”

“What? Why is that....”

“To locate the main pack's dens.”

Vikir was targeting not one or two gnolls, not a pack, but an entire colony.

Gnoll hunting at the colony level, something not even the Empire's marauding armies could do.

MiniPin's mouth dropped halfway open at the ease with which Vikir brought it up.

“Why, why would you go to such lengths...?”

And then, to MiniPin, Vikir said something short.

“It's good to make money.”

◆

Then a group of gnolls came and tore apart the boar's carcass.

They cut open the boar's belly and scraped out the still-hot, steaming entrails, then dragged the rest of the carcass down a low path through the underbrush.

Vikir and MiniPin followed quietly behind.

Soon, they came upon a large earthen cave hidden in a low hillside.

MiniPin climbed onto a high branch and looked around.

'Do you really think this will work?'

But the scene in front of them proved once again that Vikir's plan was hopeless.

Swarms of gnolls.

MiniPin was horrified at the sheer number of gnolls roaming around.

“Boss. I think this is a bit much. The swarm is quite large. All of the gnolls that have been causing trouble in the Imperial Capital have gathered here. If we mess with this place, they'll flood the nearby villages.”

Monster Wave.

If you make a mistake, there is a high possibility that you will end up committing the mistake of overthrowing.

But.

“We should look for other entrances to this cave.”

Vikir remained nonchalant.

Within a few hours, Vikir had found several other entrances that he believed connected to the first one.

MiniPin was impressed with Vikir's skillful search, but he still had no idea what to do with all these gnolls.

Then.

Vikir loaded up on mana and slammed his fist into the dirt wall.

...Boom, boom, boom!

The piles of dried earth that made up the cliff collapsed, blocking the entrance to several private burrows.

Vikir laughed bitterly, remembering popping champagne glasses at the club.

“Now move to the topmost cave.”

MiniPin did as he was told and drove the carriage toward the topmost entrance.

Boom!

A few of the gnolls leapt out to play, only to be decapitated by MiniPin's greatsword.

“Mr. Boss. What are you going to do now... huck!?”

MiniPin swallowed hard.

Vikir pulled out all the items he had loaded into the wagon.

It was oil.

With all the money he had left, Vikir had bought all the waste oil that the Academy had been hoarding to throw away when it reached its expiration date, and now he was pouring it into the very top of the gnoll's den.

Gurgling, gurgling, gurgling...

The bluish oil, squeezed from the sabik berries, thickens in the den.

Kungkung-

Grrrr...

Hmm?

From the bottom of the cave, the sounds of chattering rang out.

A few gnolls rise to the top of the cave, only to be sent back down by MiniPin's greatsword.

When dozens of barrels were empty, Vikir kicked all the remaining barrels down into the den.

And then.

Grumble!

He tossed the torch he was carrying into the depths as well.

...BOOM!

A loud booming sound.

At the same time, the sabic tree oil, which is highly flammable and has a low boiling point, began to heat up with a loud noise.

Washishishishisik- jijijik-popjik!

The sound of the oil frying the gnolls that hadn't yet escaped the den.

The boiling oil continues to flow down the hole, and the gnolls below are fried alive, unable to escape.

Crackle!

Kaeng!

Chiiiing...

The gnolls in the upper tier are fried in oil, and even the gnolls in the middle tier are choking on soot and dying.

The gnolls in the lower levels scramble to escape, leaving the bodies of their comrades behind.

However, the entrances to most of the tunnels are already blocked by piles of earth, and suffocation is inevitable.

Oxygen concentration drops rapidly, and smoke and odor rise.

The air also heated up rapidly, and the survivors steamed to death at the entrances of the blocked tunnels.

“...! ...! ...! ...!”

MiniPin could only agape.

He'd never seen anyone hunt colony monsters like this before.

However, Vikir remained calm under the circumstances.

“This kind of loud tactic works well to scare away monsters with low intelligence.”

In fact, pouring boiling oil over the entrance of the upper level cavern was more of a performance.

In reality, it couldn't cause that much damage.

The real purpose is to frighten and confuse the prey.

...Udeug! ...Ppudeudeug!

The burned gnolls are terrified and scramble to the bottom of the cave.

Younger and smaller gnolls and older and slower gnolls are trampled to death by their peers.

It's also not uncommon for mates to bite each other to death as they try to get through the narrow tunnel first.

When the pack is disrupted, only the strongest and fastest survive.

And those who survived ran towards the entrance of the cave on the lowest level.

“...Come out now.”

Toward where the last hound's eyes shone.

Chapter 228

Tuition (6)

◆

There was chaos in the forest that had been quiet just a moment ago.

Ppajijijijig! Ppusisisisig! Wasasasasasa...

The screams of frying gnolls tore through the night sky.

The foul stench of burning wild beasts wafted out of the den.

Even those who had barely survived were covered in hot oil.

[Grrrr! Grrrr!]

[Crackle!]

[Gah!]

The gnolls scrambled out of the den in agony, each baring their teeth and nails.

The wounded beast's vision is narrowed. That means it can't see anything.

Although it was only a C+ ranked monster, the killing power it unleashed while struggling was comparable to that of a higher rank monster.

However.

...Poof!

All of its viciousness was meaningless in Vikir's hands.

A crude iron skewer quickly pierced the gnoll's neck.

[Huh?]

The gnoll who was just coming out of the cave felt a stinging sensation on the side of his neck, but he was so helpless that he ran straight ahead without even thinking about looking to the side.

But of course, he couldn't take more than a few steps before his neck was punctured and he stumbled to a halt.

Thud.

A fountain of red blood gushes from his neck, and for a few seconds, the gnoll lies motionless, blurry-eyed and breathless.

Vikir stays close to the side of the cave, continuing to stab the gnolls in the neck as they leap out of the cave.

...Pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug! ...pug!

There's not much to stab. Just once. I strain my arm, extend it, withdraw it.

Every time the iron skewer monotonously moves back and forth, the gnolls that jump out of the cave fall down and pile up in front.

Soon, every single one of the gnolls that jumped out of the cave turned into cold corpses and piled up in the empty space in front of the cave.

Vikir roughly wiped the blood from his face and ran a hand through his hair.

“Looks like we're done here.”

A grisly scene of slaughter.

MiniPin couldn't help but cluck his tongue as he watched the killing spree unfold with such skill and precision.

“ ...What in the world are you doing?”

“What, you've never seen someone catch a gnoll before?”

“Of course, it's my first time seeing you. Where is the person who catches gnolls like this?”

By the time MiniPin had finished speaking, more than a dozen gnolls had been flipped out of the den.

MiniPin collected the bodies of the gnolls that kept piling up in a certain spot and loaded them into the cart.

There were so many of them that the cart would never be able to carry them. They would have to ask the local government or guild to help them.

And even now, Vikir was waiting by the den.

Dipping a skewer in and out of the throats of leaping gnolls with lightning dexterity.

Just then.

[Grrrr...]

An unpleasant sound came from the den.

As soon as MiniPin heard it, she called out.

“Gah, Mr. Boss! Dodge! There's something else coming!”

Next thing you know, something big pops out of the hole.

It was a gnoll, three times larger than a normal gnoll, but unusually, it had black-green fur all over its body.

Its fur was needle-sharp, and sticky oil dripped from its bloodshot eyes like tears.

MiniPin cried out in horror.

“It's a poison gnoll, a variant of gnolls! It's ranked A in danger, and its strength and speed are dozens of times that of normal gnolls! Plus, its teeth, nails, and fur have a poisonous venom that can drive a person insane...!”

But there was no time for explanations. The poison gnoll suddenly burst out, smashing through the narrow cave entrance.

“Eiss!”

MiniPin raised his greatsword and rushed toward Vikir.

He hoped to buy his client time to duck for cover.

But.

[Aang!]

A cloud of dust fell from above, stopping MiniPin's life-threatening lunge in its tracks.

“...?”

MiniPin froze in place, dumbfounded.

That's because this small lump that looked like a butterfly that fell from the sky immediately rushed to the Poison Gnoll in front of it as soon as it hit the ground.

And what's even more amazing is that as soon as the vicious Poison Gnoll was bitten on the nape of the neck by the tiny speck of dust, it immediately rolled its eyes, foamed at the mouth, and fainted.

[Grrrrr!]

Poison Gnoll rolled over on its back, spewing whatever was inside of it out of its mouth and anus, and then stretched out completely.

“Huh?”

MiniPin looked back and forth between Vikir's and Poison Gnoll's corpses, dumbfounded.

What kind of monster was a Poison Gnoll? Once it appears, a small village in the mountains is wiped out for the day.

A named monster that even a few small and medium-sized hunting guilds couldn't defeat with all their might.

It even travels around with its minions, so large guilds must mobilize their elite forces to take it down.

...But.

“Well done, come back.”

Vikir waved his hand, and the dust balls quickly jumped up and crawled into the hem of Vikir's sleeve.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

The hatchling stuck out its tongue and gave him a look that seemed to ask for praise.

Meanwhile.

MiniPin was just blinking as if he couldn't believe that the small furball in front of him, which he couldn't even tell was a living thing, had killed the poison gnoll in one bite(?).

“Haha, I thought these past few days at the hands of my boss were a nightmare... but now it's more like a dream, is this even possible?”

“It's real, just think about the reward money and the sale price of the byproducts.”

MiniPin nodded at Vikir's natural command.

And MiniPin had to hold his tongue as he counted the gnoll and poison gnoll corpses piled up in front of him.

“If you count the ones that died in the den, the number must be staggering, and I'm afraid I can't even begin to count them; we'll have to go out to the big city and get them appraised by several experts.”

“If there's a reward per head, we'll have to get all the bodies.”

“Yes. The ones that were choked to death or had their throats slit can be skinned and sold, and the ones that were fried in oil should be fine to sell for their bones, but I'll have to go in later, when the heat in the den has cooled down.”

The gnolls' den was still burning hot, so Vikir and MiniPin sat outside the den for a while, collecting the gnoll corpses.

During this time, a few surviving gnolls sometimes crawled out on notice and were sorted out at the cub madam line.

Eventually, when the heat in the den had cooled down enough, MiniPin grabbed a torch and crawled inside.

As he dug, he made small incremental steps forward, until he saw an amazing sight in the depths of the tunnel.

“Sah, boss, you have to see this for yourself!”

Hearing MiniPin's exclamation, Vikir followed suit.

What awaited them inside was quite unexpected, even for the ever-calm Vikir.

A gold coin. Piles and piles of gold coins, dipped in oil and glowing with golden light.

In the flickering light of the torches, they cast eerie lights and shadows on both sides.

It's fitting that a man would freeze when suddenly exposed to so much wealth.

“ ... What's all this?”

MiniPin looked back at Vikir with a slightly frightened expression.

But Vikir remained nonchalant.

“Apparently, someone's been using this place as a safe.”

“What? That's a safe... ah!”

MiniPin exclaimed, then gasped.

As I've said before, gnolls have a habit of collecting shiny things and hoarding them in their burrows.

It was possible that someone had taken advantage of this behavior and was storing black money here.

“With so many gnolls, it would be hard for anyone to steal it. They're natural safekeepers.”

“Ha, but what kind of big man would keep his money in a gnoll's nest?”

“I don't know. But at least one thing is certain.”

At Vikir's words, MiniPin tilts his head, puzzled.

Then his face turns white at Vikir's next words.

“He must be confident enough to kill all these gnolls and retrieve the gold.”

Someone who could kill all the gnolls in this place as easily as opening a vault door.

What's more, this is a large enough colony that even poison gnolls are lurking.

“....”

MiniPin shuddered slightly as he looked at the gold coins in front of him.

A huge pile of gold coins.

Rattling-

Vikir picked up a gold coin lying randomly on the dirt floor.

“...No serial number.”

A gold coin without a serial number yet.

This means that it is an unregistered coin that has been created in a currency-producing country but has not yet been officially distributed to banks.

“Damian Bourgeois, the director of the Department of Money Manufacturing, enacted a law requiring unique serial numbers to be engraved on banknotes and coins. It looks like these coins were stolen before the law was enacted, or just before serial numbers were engraved.”

“Are you saying that these are all the result of a bank robbery?”

“That doesn't explain it.”

Vikir thought about whether there had been any recent articles about banks being robbed.

...There was. There had been.

A being is said to have been destroying major facilities in the Imperial Capital as of late.

[Exclusive] The Night Hound, and its viciousness...

-The Night Hound's evil deeds have crossed the line... The Night Hound's assault on the Academy was... anti-human and anti-national... Meanwhile, the Night Hound's destruction of key facilities in the system during the festivities was... The Imperial Bank...

Vikir remembered the article well, as it was written by Vikir himself.

The villain had recently raided the Imperial Bank and stripped it of all its riches.

A mysterious terrorist who mimicked the crimes of the Night Hound, only to commit even greater crimes.

A name pops into Vikir's head.

“...!”

It casts an ominous shadow over reality.

Vikir and MiniPin quickly scrambled out of the cave, and something long and large fell in front of them.

Kwa-kwa-kwa-kwa-kwak!

Vikir stumbled back from the sudden explosion.

When the dust settled, he saw a long, winding scar on the ground.

It looked as if a giant snake had slithered across it.

It was a mark made by the strange man who was currently standing on a bare tree branch and looking down.

[Hohohoho – rats crawled into my piggy bank?]

A modulated high-pitched voice is heard through the air hole in the mouth of the mask.

The color drains from MiniPin's face as he hears the voice.

He looked even more horrified than when he'd seen countless gnolls.

“Mi-Ms. Ouroboros!”

He encountered the worst villain who was terrorizing the night of the Imperial Capital.

Chapter 230

Tuition (8)

◆

Vikir had gotten satisfying answers from the various appraisers MiniPin had referred to him.

“Most of them are low-ranked, I see. A lot of the bodies have been burned or mangled by boiling oil.”

“But there are quite a few high grade ones, as there are so many of them.”

“As the price of playing is expensive these days, the total sales price is likely to be quite high.”

“Do you have any distributors in mind? If not, we can introduce you to some good ones.”

Appraisers appraised the corpses of gnolls piled up like a mountain in an empty lot and set prices based on the condition of their skin, bones, internal organs, meat, etc.

1. The best quality is the one with the skin, meat, internal organs, and bones intact.

2. As long as the skin is in good condition, it is a premium product.

3. Even if the skin is damaged, if the meat or internal organs are intact, it is intermediate grade.

4. The skin, meat, and internal organs are damaged, but the bones can still be removed.

Gnoll corpses are welcomed with open arms by all magic labs in the Imperial City.

Even taxidermists sometimes buy them when a large gnoll comes in. This is because they make great teaching tools for beginners.

The skin is in high demand for its durability and softness to the touch, and the meat and organs are also used for food, feed, and fertilizer.

Some specialty cuts of gnoll meat are prized by gourmets because they taste similar to the finest beef.

Scattering gnoll organs in fish ponds and orchards will produce more abundant results than any artificial feed or fertilizer.

The bones were also heavily processed for medicinal and spiritual uses.

Because Vikir fried them with boiling oil, the skin, meat, and internal organs of the dead gnolls were mostly damaged.

However, due to their large numbers, many gnolls remained intact, and even the most mangled corpses still had intact bones, teeth, and claws that could be sold for a decent amount of money.

Of course, it was a small amount of money compared to the price they would receive once they were processed, but it was quite generous considering that they could skip the process of collecting, transporting, and sorting them all together, as well as dealing with retailers who would try to haggle over the price.

“What's more, it's even better that the government has even given us a reward. That's awesome!”

That was the general consensus of MiniPin, who had been glued to Vikir's side ever since that night.

He was so impressed with Vikir's efficiency during the extermination of the gnoll horde that he took care of all the menial tasks, from selling the gnoll corpses to collecting the reward money.

Vikir had seen MiniPin's loyalty during the battle with Ms. Ouroboros, so he knew he could trust him with everything.

As MiniPin loaded the gnoll skins into Vikir's cart, he said.

“You can sell all the gnoll byproducts to the Guild, but I suggest you find a market for the skins. Especially in the case of the skins of the Poison Gnolls, I'd rather you put them up for auction privately, though...”

“Then I suppose we'd better take it to the Academy.”

Vikir replied with a nod.

The academy in Colosseo rents out warehouse space enchanted with preservation magic to students at a low rent.

And the bazaar, held on the last day of every month, held various auctions, so it was the perfect place to sell things.

“It's a 'bargain' bazaar, not a large-scale auction officially sanctioned by the Empire, so it should be easy to dispose of the gnoll skins.”

“Hmm. A bazaar in the Colosseo. Sounds like a good idea.”

Gnoll skins have many uses.

Its warmth and texture make it a great addition to armor in winter, and its toughness and elasticity make it useful for knots and decorations on scabbards.

It could also be used as a reagent because it changes color when it comes into contact with poison.

“And I belong to a newspaper club, so maybe I can place an ad in the back of the paper.”

Vikir returned to the academy to sell both the gnoll and poison gnoll skins.

Meanwhile, MiniPin looked disappointed.

“You're going back to the Academy?”

Vikir's skill in this hunt was beyond belief for a first-year undergraduate at the Academy.

Was that why? MiniPin must have realized that he wanted to continue working with Vikir.

...But he had no idea.

Vikir had no intention of letting him go.

“Hey, MiniPin.”

Vikir called to MiniPin in a soft voice.

When MiniPin looked away, Vikir asked bluntly.

“Your home doesn't look like it's in very good shape. How are your wife and daughter?”

Vikir asked. MiniPin's expression darkened slightly at Vikir's words.

“That's right, it's actually quite difficult to run a guild these days due to lack of funds, and I can't afford to let go of my longtime family members....”

“Why would a guild of your caliber have such a problem? From the looks of it, there are plenty of skilled guides and porters in the guild.”

“All hunting guilds are like that these days. The big mercenary guilds have a lot to look out for, and it's a shame to be without a backup.”

After speaking, MiniPin smiled bitterly.

“Huh, this is all my fault. If I hadn't made a mistake when I was younger, I wouldn't be in such a tight spot financially.”

“Mistakes?”

Vikir asked, and MiniPin hesitated a bit before nodding.

“When I was younger, I was pretty ambitious, so I made some contacts with brokers to fulfill my dreams... until I got scammed and lost all my savings.”

“You got scammed by brokers?”

“Yes. I'm ashamed to say, but yes, I did, and I put my wife through a lot of trouble, and I still feel guilty about it, and I feel guilty about my daughter, By the way. She's going to school next year, and I'm already worried about the cost of her education.”

“What was your dream that made you try to get through brokers?”

Vikir asked, and MiniPin scratched the back of his head and answered in a rueful little voice.

“I guess it was... Actually, I wanted to join Baskerville House.”

Vikir's eyes narrowed slightly at the unexpected words.

MiniPin continued.

“A family that slays monsters on the Western Front. Iron-blooded swordsmen, how cool is that? And when you join the Baskervilles, you're taught the invincible Baskerville style of swordsmanship. They give you a house, they give you land, and they give you a wife, so I figured that was the only way to go. Of course, it all went down the drain when I got scammed by the brokers.”

“Hmm- yeah?”

Vikir stroked his chin with a finger.

The thoughts I had from the beginning became even stronger.

Vikir asked one last time.

“Hey.”

“What?”

“Are you familiar with the ecology of monsters? Their habits, the location of their nests?”

“Of course, I've traveled all over the continent with the Exploration Guild in the past.”

“Are you familiar with the monsters of the Western Front?”

“Of course. I can recognize every subspecies, variant, subordinate, and superspecies.”

Vikir nodded in satisfaction at MiniPin's answer.

“I'm sure I'll need to call on you again sooner or later.”

◆

Colosseo Academy's admissions office and scholarship foundation.

Professor Banshee was filling out some papers with an annoyed look on his face.

“ ...It seems like I'm the only one doing all the work for the academy.”

The mountain of papers in front of him were all related to scholarships and tuition.

Then.

A knock.

There was a knock on the office door.

“Come in.”

A familiar face appeared at the same time as Professor Banshee's voice.

It was Dolores, the student council president.

Professor Banshee hated her because she always showed up when it was time to allocate the scholarship budget.

“ ... What else are you here to nag me about?”

“It's an agenda for students who have been neglected by scholarships.”

Dolores slid a new set of documents in front of Professor Banshee's eyes.

Students who cannot attend next semester due to disadvantaged family circumstances.

They were filled with stories of students who had to work part-time to pay their tuition and couldn't keep their grades up, or who couldn't keep their grades up to qualify for scholarships.

The students who worked part-time ended up not being able to save up enough money in time, and the students who studied ended up not getting scholarships because their grades weren't good enough.

There were also students who had complicated family situations and were actually disadvantaged, but were not eligible for scholarships on paper.

Dolores says calmly.

“Some of the students who didn't get the scholarships need to be re-evaluated. On the other hand, there are students who have received scholarships who need to be reevaluated.”

The number of people who fraudulently obtained scholarships by pretending to be from poor families on paper when in reality they were from well-to-do families and living well was considerable, Dolores said.

She was now reporting this same fact.

However.

The documents Dolores submitted were all neat and well-presented forms, but to Professor Banshee, they were just luggage that needed to be handled while working extra nights.

“ ... Scholarships are awarded according to school rules. The same ones you're supposed to uphold and defend as student council president.”

“I'm asking you to take a second look at the needy students that those rules miss.”

“Are you asking me to do my job twice?”

“As a 'student council president,' I have an obligation to be a voice for student grievances.”

“And who's going to take care of my grievances about having to work twice, and you're going to double my salary?”

“Professor Banshee Morgue. Today is the deadline for tuition payments. Please listen to your students one more time.”

“What does the school rules say I'm supposed to do about that?”

Professor Banshee and Dolores continue to argue, neither of them backing down.

However, as time passed, Dolores's spirit was gradually weakened by Professor Banshee's ironclad attitude.

...Just then.

BANG!

The door burst open without a knock.

Vikir. He strode into Professor Banshee's office.

Naturally, Professor Banshee, who hated Vikir, frowned.

“Vikir-kun, now you're slamming through the door without knocking? I guess your father didn't give you a good home education, did he?”

“Yes.”

“...?”

It was a defeat for Professor Banshee, who hadn't realized that Vikir had a fairly strong immunity to parent abuse.

Professor Banshee crossed his arms in frustration.

“I know. Did you know that today is the deadline for tuition payments?”

Deep down, he knew Vikir wouldn't be able to come up with the money.

He'd heard that Vikir had brought back a lot of gnoll skins from somewhere.

But Professor Banshee had heard other rumors as well.

'Two groups of students, one noble and one royal, have declared that they will keep Vikir's arm in check.'

There are two major factions in the bazaar of the Colosseo Academy.

The Noble Faction, made up of elites from the nobility, and the Royalist Faction, made up of elites from the royalty.

As long as these two groups are determined to keep Vikir in check, there is no way that the goods at the bazaar will fetch a fair price.

So Professor Banshee knew deep down that Vikir would have a hard time paying his tuition.

'I don't know where he got that many skins to play with,... but if it's not cash, it's not money if you can't sell it.'

...But.

Professor Banshee's prediction went spectacularly wrong.

Thud!

Vikir placed a heavy sack on Professor Banshee's desk.

The large sack was surprisingly full of banknotes and gold coins.

It was a staggering amount of money, enough to pay for 4 years of tuition in one fell swoop.

“!?”

Professor Banshee and Dolores stared at the pile of gold coins on the desk in amazement.

Standing in front of them, Vikir opened his mouth with his characteristic expressionless face.

“It's for all my friends who couldn't pay their tuition.”

Chapter 231

Tuition (9)

◆

Colosseo Academy's Thrifty Bazaar boasts a huge scale that belies its cute name.

Students auction off their used items at bargain prices, and occasionally some students bring in items they've crafted or foraged, or unidentified antiques from their respective families.

The size of the bazaar is such that it is considered one of the top ten auctions in the empire, and the fact that people from outside the academy are allowed to bid at the bazaar attracts a lot of attention and foot traffic.

It is also one of the largest bazaars in the empire, and attracts many people from outside the academy.

The “aristocracy” and the “nobility”.

The Aristocracy was formed by students from prominent aristocratic families. The elite, including the Seven Families, their relatives, and their families, held real power.

On the other hand, the nobility faction, which was formed by elites from noble families, was just as powerful as the aristocracy faction.

While the Aristocracy was a small elite, exclusive league of its own, the Nobility was made up of members of the Toho family, who were renowned for their agriculture and commerce, the heirs of famous mercenary guilds, or the heirs of large mines and shipyards.

They were the real power in the academy and continued to grow in size and power by recruiting talented juniors under their wing.

This power structure would continue after graduation, becoming a network of connections and systems that would eventually encompass the political and financial circles of the empire.

And it was Vikir who was the first first-year to be predicted by the aristocracy and the nobility, the two groups that secretly dominate the Academy.

Although it wasn't when he entered Academy, he was a talented person who stood out in the midterm exam over time. Since he is a single person with no backbone behind him, he is perfect for flirting.

The aristocracy and the nobility had been plotting to take this talented first year under their wing for a very long time.

But Vikir has never lived up to their expectations.

At best, their letters were chewed up rather than read, and no matter how many times they tried to visit and talk to him, they never saw his face.

Even when the second and third years tried to make a show of force by dispatching a group of beautiful girls and a group of fierce fighters, it didn't work, so both the aristocrats and the nobility were left with their heads in the sand.

'Whoa, Vikir, I think we need to give this cocky junior a good punch in the nose.'

'Let's give him a good slap in the face before he gets under our skin.'

Ironically, the aristocrats and the nobility joined hands to suppress each other.

In the short term, Vikir became a public enemy.

Just as the aristocrats and the nobles were plotting to take him down, Vikir showed up at a bazaar.

'I hear he's trying to raise money for tuition.'

'Gnoll skins. I've been needing it for a while now, so I thought I'd give him a good price.'

'I'm sure he got a good deal from the hunting guild, but I'm not sure he knows the market price.'

'Yeah, I heard they don't take clients from just any hunting guild.'

The aristocratic and noble students were eager to use the auction to flatten Vikir's nose.

And when the auction began, no one really wanted to buy Vikir's gnoll skin.

The aristocrats and nobles had outbid the other students.

The aristocrats and nobles giggled in the back of the silent auction room, imagining Vikir's soon-to-be dead face.

...But.

'I thought there would be a lot of people who covet gnoll skin because it is a useful item. It's not as popular as I thought.'

Vikir shrugged and turned his head to look back at the pile of gnoll hides on the auction house stage.

'Aha. Is it because there are so many?'

At the same time, Vikir did something that made both the aristocrats and the nobles jump out of their skin.

...Hiss!

As if he was going to light a torch on the spot, he ignited the gnoll skin on the stage.

Everyone jumped to their feet in horror, but Vikir continued to burn every gnoll skin in sight.

Crackle! Crackle! Hiss!

More than half of the gnoll skins on the stage had burned to nothing.

....

A strange silence descended upon the auction hall.

In this frozen atmosphere, Vikir spoke briefly.

'Is it still too much?'

At the same time, Vikir pulled on the fire once more.

He did not extinguish the flame until the remaining gnoll skins were once again halved.

At this point, the students began to get agitated.

The students were upset because they needed the gnoll skins for their research.

But Vikir was relentless.

When no one came forward to buy it, Vikir raised the torch once more.

There was no hesitation in his gesture, as if he intended to burn them all to the ground.

Instead, the onlookers rushed to stop him.

'That's for the next class! I, I want to keep it! I'm not prepared yet!'

'I needed some extra armor for my cold-weather performance evaluation, too! There's not much left for sale....'

'Buy! I'll take it! Outbid!'

'I'll buy it! I'll buy it! Stop burning it!'

In such a situation, Vikir said firmly.

'The minimum bid is four times the first auction price.'

Vikir was determined to get his money's worth.

In the end, the students had no choice but to cry and eat mustard to Vikir, blaming the aristocrats and the nobles.

Of course, the students of the aristocratic faction and the noble faction were dumbfounded.

◆

“...So. That's how the auction ended?”

Professor Banshee asked in disbelief.

Vikir nodded nonchalantly.

“Yep. I was able to get all of my tuition paid for.”

I'm afraid those words will end.

...Thud, thud, thud!

The tough leather bag placed on the desk tore with a loud noise.

The bills and gold coins inside began to fall to the floor with a loud clatter.

Clink, clink, clink, clink.

Professor Banshee's desk was quickly covered in money.

He looked down at the large, sturdy leather sack bursting at the seams and muttered quietly.

“ ... You'll need some change.”

Professor Banshee pulled a pair of reading glasses from his pocket and placed them on the tip of his nose, and with a delicate snap of his fingers, he extracted a handful of large gold coins.

“That covers your tuition, ah, all four years at once, all in one lump sum.”

Professor Banshee just shrugged his shoulders, as if he didn't know what to do with the rest of the money.

But Vikir didn't seem to be in the mood to collect the change.

“The rest is for tuition, too.”

“...There's too much money left over to be called tuition. Are you planning to buy a lecture hall, if you're going to be a professor and not a student?”

“Please use the rest for the students who can't afford tuition.”

Professor Banshee was stunned by Vikir's words. And even Dolores, who was standing next to him.

“Surely I'm not mishearing you?”

“Yes.”

“Are you saying that you're going to donate all of this money to the Foundation, in the name of scholarships?”

“Yes. But with a condition.”

At Vikir's words, Professor Banshee's mouth twisted into a 'then so be it' expression.

It happens often. People with deep pockets donate large sums of money to scholarship foundations and then take advantage of them.

Usually it's about tax deductions (donations are far more tax-deductible than any other expense), expanding their influence within the academy by creating a positive image, or even creating a political group or building power.

...But Vikir's conditions were again outside of Professor Banshee's expectations.

“The condition is that in order to receive this money, you must fulfill a certain number of volunteer hours at the orphanage.”

“Orphanage?”

Professor Banshee furrowed his brow as if he didn't understand.

If you can get a scholarship by volunteering at a orphanage, that's a great deal.

This is a very grateful offer for Academy students who have to focus on part-time jobs and scholarships.

In other words, it was no different from saying that they would just pay the tuition for free. For the next ten years or so!

'What the hell is he up to?'

Professor Banshee scanned Vikir's entire body with a questioning look.

But no matter how hard he stared, Vikir didn't respond, so Professor Banshee raised his hands.

“Okay. I see. We'll create an award on Academy and award scholarships in its name. Do you have anything in mind for the name of the award?”

Vikir was silent for a moment at Professor Banshee's question.

Then Professor Banshee waved his hand as if he didn't want to hear more.

“I see you don't, so we'll just call it the Vikir Award. I'm sure the students who receive it will be very grateful to you, since they're lucky enough to have a wealthy sponsor and get their tuition paid for free. You must be a celebrity.”

Then.

Vikir held up a hand to stop Professor Banshee.

“The donor's name shall remain anonymous, and the prize shall be named something else.”

“?”

Professor Banshee adjusts his glasses and looks up.

“You mean to tell me you're going to donate a large sum of money and be anonymous, so you get no tax deduction and no fame?”

Professor Banshee's belief that all humans are driven by self-interest was being denied in front of him.

But whether Professor Banshee was confused or not, Vikir spoke up, still with the same expressionless face, but in a slightly lowered voice.

“The name of the award shall be 'Nymphet'.”

Hearing that, Professor Banshee furrowed his brow in confusion.

Only.

“....”

Dolores, who had been listening to this entire conversation from the side, could only twitch her eyelids.

Chapter 233

Suspicion (2)

◆

The next morning. Early hours before the first period classes started.

Dolores found herself in the newspaper club room.

She had dark circles under her eyes from being up all night last night dealing with the student council agenda.

“I have a lot of work to do for the National Collegiate League next week. Should I hold a vigil again today....”

Colosseo. Magic Tower. Varangian. Temisquira.

All of the official organizations of the Colosseo Academy were busy, as the annual competition between the four most prestigious academies in the empire was approaching.

Including, of course, the student council, of which Dolores was the president.

But despite the night's work, her eyes were alight with enthusiasm.

“I'll finish my club work in the morning, then I'll go to lecture, and then I'll have a free period until afternoon, so in the meantime, I'll go find Vikir and get ...!”

Dolores pushed open the door to the club room with a flourish.

“Good morning, everyone!”

Dolores' usual cheerful greeting.

But it's odd how her classmates, who would normally greet her with a cheerful smile, are so quiet.

All of them are looking at her with a strange expression on their faces.

“Spring is coming to our dear Dolores.”

“A romance with a younger man, that's great.”

“She's younger~ Our Dolores is in a higher grade, but she's younger!”

“Whatever. My junior and her are a campus couple, I'm jealous, I'm jealous!”

“You don't even tell us! It's really too much! Do I need to know about my best friend's love life through a newspaper article?”

...?

Dolores can only roll her big eyes at the comments from her third-year classmates.

Then. Dolores saw a newspaper article being held out in front of her.

It was a newspaper from outside the academy, and it was the exclusive report of a reporter from another newspaper who had infiltrated the academy.

[Exclusive] Springtime for the Student Council President of the Colosseo Academy?

-Ms. Dolores L. Quovadis, known as the student council president of Colosseo Academy, has recently been found to be in a relationship...

Ms. Dolores has been the center of attention since the beginning of her enrollment, not only for her literary skills, but also for her beauty...

Her partner, surprisingly, is Mr. V, a freshman two years below her...

Mr. V, who had attracted attention from the beginning of his enrollment due to his outstanding appearance, grades, and athleticism...

The feelings between the two, which are believed to have sprouted during the volunteer work,...

After an ardent courtship on both sides of Dolores part, the relationship appears to have been successful...

The Quovadis family is yet to comment on the matter...

Meanwhile, the citizens of the Imperial Capital, upon learning of Ms. Dolores love life, reacted to the news with comments such as, “It's nice to see,” “She's a good girl,” and “I'm jealous, but as long as she's happy, it's okay.”...

“..., What is this?”

Dolores's mouth dropped open.

I thought there had been a lot of paparazzi coming in from the outside recently, but was it really about me?

A group of third-year students gathered around Dolores as she stood dumbfounded.

“Hey, hey, hey. Here's the guy who's supposed to be 'student council president' and 'the guy the saint has a crush on'. Isn't that him from the first year? Naphtali man! Why did he dress up as a woman at the festival?”

“If it's Vikir, we can send our own Dolores! He's quiet, sincere, and most of all, he's handsome!”

“What a pity! You should have listened to us, then we could have helped you long ago!”

“My dear Dolores~ we've always thought you seemed strangely uninterested in men~ but it turns out you have high eyes, doesn't it?”

“I heard that a well-behaved cat goes up to the stove first~ Ugh! How dare you put this sister aside!”

The girl talk began. It was a conversation that Dolores was having a hard time adjusting to.

“It's not that, it's just that there's something about Vikir that's bothering me...! There's more than one thing about him that seems suspicious!”

But Dolores's excuses only served to reinforce the misunderstanding.

“Yeah, yeah~ That's how it all starts~ with a little something bothering you.”

“I've had enough of the prologue~ Now for the main story?”

“What, is Vikir a suspicious? I mean, he's suspiciously handsome, I mean, his eyes are suspicious, his nose is suspicious, his mouth is suspicious, his skin is suspicious~ I wonder if it's a human being!”

“That's right, I was intimidated by his witch costume at the festival the other day, even though I'm a girl. We need to be more like Dolores!”

That's all anyone who's ever seen Vikir dressed as a woman at a festival is still talking about.

Realizing that all excuses were useless against this tide, Dolores stormed out of the gathering spot.

“Ugh... If this happens, it becomes more difficult to find it.”

It seemed like I would have to refrain from meeting Vikir for a while.

I didn't want to spur on the gossip.

Just then.

“...!”

As she exited the lecture hall and turned onto the trail, something caught her eye.

“Ugh! This crazy dog ??again!?”

“Die, die, die!”

“Ouch! I'm bitten! It hurts!”

The familiar voices were coming from behind the building.

Dolores walked over to where the voices were coming from and saw an amazing sight.

Yousphere, Realbelt, Yellowlove, Aimcom, Redmin, and Southmiddle.

A group of sophomores from the Cold Warriors' B class.

This group of three boys and three girls were making a ruckus among themselves.

And in the middle of it all, a black puppy.

Growling...

It was a stray that Dolores called 'Choco'.

When they was almost expelled from academy, their family sent a delegation and begged them for it, and she let them go with a memorandum that they would never bully the weak again... But they're causing trouble again?

Dolores stepped forward in alarm.

“You're doing this again! You really need to get expelled from academy for once...!?”

But I couldn't finish my sentence.

That was because the six men and women in front of me were all covered in blood and tattered clothes.

Choco. The black puppy was moving swiftly and viciously, baring its teeth and nails to bite at the six individuals.

...Growl!

The way it moves, it looks like a fierce beast. It may have been small in size, but its fighting instincts were jaw-dropping.

Its strength and speed were beyond the reach of most fighting dogs.

And these six bullies who were being scratched and bitten were running away crying.

“Aaah! If it weren't for the promise to the saint, then aahh!”

“Yeah, but I don't think I can catch it even if I spend mana, so just run!”

“Kaaaak, what the hell is that dog, it's so fast, why are you so scared!”

Dolores stood with a dazed expression and watched the bullies disappear into the distance.

Hack-hack-hack-.

The black puppy chased after them for a while, but then turned and walked away.

“Hey, Choco~”

Dolores called to the black puppy as it walked in the opposite direction.

...?

The dog turned his head as if he recognized his name.

Dolores took a few steps toward the black dog, who had stopped walking, and reached out her hand.

The black puppy slinked back, avoiding her touch, but Dolores persevered and picked him up.

'Mmm... do you have a caring owner, I can smell the scent in your fur.'

Dolores buried her face in the black puppy's chin and neck and sniffed.

The fluffy fur smelled faintly of something good. A familiar scent.

Dolores quickly realized what it was.

'It smells like basic shampoo, an amenity provided in the Academy's dormitories. The owner must be a student. Who is it?'

If a black dog has ever had a bath, it's probably in the dormitory.

Dolores opened her mouth to ask if any of the students in the dormitory had a black puppy.

“You're... tougher than you look, chasing six people away, but you still shouldn't fight so recklessly, those guys were only frozen because your sister gave them a firm warning, and I hope you don't think everyone else attacks like that, because you shouldn't do that.”

....

The black puppy just looks away, not sure if he's listening to Dolores or not.

When he seemed to ignore her, Dolores spoke up, half joking, half serious.

“Choco, you keep ignoring your sister, and I'm going to have you neutered?”

At that, the black pup's ears perked up.

...Pot!

It scrambled out of Dolores' arms, pawing the floor and running away.

“What? Choco, wait!”

Dolores ran after the black puppy, but it was much faster than she thought and quickly disappeared into the bushes.

“Well, he's a guy who doesn't give up his side. Like who~”

Dolores smirked.

These days, I think there are quite a few cases where I get dumped.

Whether it's the Night Hound, Vikir, or Choco.

Just then.

“...Ck.”

A groan came from the floor behind me.

I turned to see the boy who had been chased by the black puppy earlier lying on the floor.

Yousphere, one of the Cold Class second years.

Dolores let out a small sigh and stood in front of him.

“So, why were you bullying the puppy who can't talk again?”

“Uh, no offense, Ms. President, but this time that bitch... no, puppy attacked us first!”

“How can that little guy attack you first?”

“No, Ms. President, you saw it earlier! That thing has really sharp teeth and nails, and how fast it is, even faster than our family's tame wolves...!”

“Enough with the excuses.”

Feeling the disdainful glare Dolores was sending him, Yousphere really did look resentful.

“Hah. In the past, I was attacked by the 'Night Hound' but why am I so unlucky these days?”

Dolores flinches at the passing remark.

“...You. What did you just mutter?”

“What? Ah, ah, ah. I didn't mean no luck, I just meant... I don't really have anything going for me these days....”

“Not that. Before that.”

“Yes? Ah, the Night Hound?”

Yousphere hesitated for a moment, then ran a hand through his bangs.

X

And there it was, the faint scar of a sword wound.

“...I got this way because I was walking down the street at night and got grabbed by a masked maniac.”

“A masked maniac?”

“Yeah, but I didn't realize it at the time, but now that I think about it, he looked exactly like the Night Hound or some kind of villain.”

Yousphere's testimony was remarkable.

According to his statement, he and five of his bully friends had met the Night Hound in person.

This was before the Night Hound's behavior had been reported in the media.

Dolores asked with a serious expression.

“...So, the date you met the Night Hound was the day of the freshman welcome party?”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah.”

“And that was before the Night Hound was even called the Night Hound, before he went on his terrorist spree in the Imperial Capital, right?”

“Yes. I remember it clearly, the stork's beak mask. The voice that sounded like scraping metal.”

Yousphere spoke up, clearly intimidated by Dolores's momentum.

“We tried really hard to find him too. We also hire a criminal investigation agency. But everything failed. I can't seem to get my head around it.”

“No wonder. The Imperial Guard and the Imperial Army tracked it, and they couldn't catch it.”

“That was back when the Night Hounds weren't that infamous. Will they now accept our request because the crime investigation agencies are crazy?”

Dolores was troubled by Yousphere's words.

'Why did the Night Hounds attack them?'

Dolores had done a detailed investigation into the backgrounds of these six bullies in order to expel them.

According to the results of the investigation at that time, these six bullies were really frogs in a well, with no scope of activity other than their own territory and academy.

'So they don't have any grudges with the outside world, do they?'

It seems that the Night Hound has some kind of connection to this academy.

I had a strong feeling about that.

Yousphere shuddered, remembering the nightmare of the day.

“He knew not only our names, but our parents' names, and the location of our families.”

Dolores did some quick math.

“If he knows that much about the academy, he can't be a freshman. He's at least a sophomore, maybe a senior?”

It's a theory I've been thinking about for a while. This made it even more likely that the Night Hound's informant was inside the Academy.

There was even a slim chance that the Night Hound himself could be inside the Academy.

“....”

Dolores turned her head and looked down at the Yousphere.

...Pas!

A white light rose up and healed his wounds.

When Yousphere looked up with a dazed expression, Dolores spoke in a stern voice.

“You guys. I want you to keep what I've just said a secret.”

“What?”

“Don't tell anyone, and I'll take care of it from now on.”

At Dolores's urging, Yousphere nodded dumbly.

Perhaps he understood Dolores to be trying to steal the show by reporting their testimony.

But the more scoundrels like this are, the weaker they are against the strong.

Yousphere would only be released if he promised to keep his friends in line as well as himself.

“Remember, if anyone else hears about this, you will be expelled.”

Leaving Dolores bloody threats behind.

Chapter 235

National University League (2)

◆

Colosseo Academy, Varangian Boot Camp, Magic Tower, and Themiscyra Women's University.

There are only a few days left before the National University League, hosted by four prestigious academies.

Before then, the students of Colosseo Academy embarked on a journey to Magic Tower, the venue of the tournament.

“Ugh! It's been so long since I went out~ I'm finally going out of the Imperial Capital! I thought I would die of frustration because I thought I had to wait until vacation! Although I can't see the wide lake of Usher, I have to be satisfied with this as it is a shame. Of course, a great archer must have a broad insight before a broad vision...!”

Bianca was humming as she dragged a large suitcase, dressed in a colorful floral shirt, shorts, sunglasses, a straw hat, and cool-looking sandals.

Judging by her moody courtly demeanor, she's quite excited.

Tudor spotted her and spoke up.

“If anyone saw you, they'd think you were going on a vacation somewhere, and then you'd fail your grades and lose the tournament.”

“If you're saying that, are you wearing a swimsuit under your skirt?”

“Moo, what are you talking about, are you crazy, how do you know if I'm wearing a swimsuit or not!”

“Because I saw your skirt flapping in the wind earlier?”

“Hey you pervert, why are you looking at that!”

“Well, if you look at it that way, you're more of a pervert for wearing a skirt.”

“Pfft, in our Donquixote family, men traditionally wear skirts too!”

“Okay, anyway, I didn't want to see it, but you forced me to see it while you were walking ahead. And it's not even panties, but a swimsuit is meant to be exposed anyway.”

“I'm going to sue you!”

“What are you going to eat, there's nothing to sue for.”

“I'm going to sue you for insult, asshole!”

“Then I'll sue you for injury, too. As if I didn't already lose my eyesight from seeing you in your swimsuit.”

Tudor and Bianca are still bickering today.

Sancho, Pigi, and Sinclaire giggle at their usual behavior.

“You're both in high spirits again today.”

“I'm going to hate you if you do that.”

“I think I've heard it all before, you two are childhood friends.”

The University League, the Olympiad Survival Tournament, is usually hosted by four universities in a rotating order, and this time it was the turn of Magic Tower, a city in the eastern part of the continent.

Magic Tower is located in the 'Dortmund Smile' region in the southeastern part of the continent, which is known for its mild climate and abundant tourist attractions such as deserts, forests, caves, valleys, and the sea.

To get to this warm and cozy place, you have to follow a long train track through the Imperial Capital, which is why the students of Colosseo Academy are here at the train station today.

The Magical Train. This is an enormous train that travels around the entire continent.

It is a type of gigantic magical tool that uses mana stones placed in furnaces in the front and back carriages to generate firepower.

This massive artifact, capable of transporting countless people from one end of the continent to the other, was created by the combined efforts of the Empire's mages and is considered the pinnacle of magecraft.

The students of the Colosseo Academy are boarding this train today to travel from the Capital to the southeastern part of the continent.

Capital Station. Platform 9 and 3/4

The train pulls into the platform.

[Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding~ The continental circulation train, the continental circulation train, is coming in now. This is Imperial Capital, Imperial Capital Station. The exit door is on the right. Please be careful when exiting the train as there is a large distance between the platforms at this station. Thank you for traveling with us today. Goodbye]

Through the cloudy vapor emitted by the burning mana stones, the giant steel serpent approaches the platform and stops.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire each say a few words.

“Wow, this is awesome. I've never been on a Magic train before.”

“Woo-hoo. Tudor, you have a bit of a hillbilly side to you. I rode it once when I came to enroll.”

“Actually, it's my first time too, though I've used the teleportation scroll once before.”

“Don't be such an idiot when you get on the train. There are students from Varangian and Themiscyra inside who have traveled from all over.”

“We're all rivals, so we'll have to buckle up and not look down on each other.”

The students of the Colosseo Academy stiffened their faces to hide their excitement as they boarded the train.

The outside of the train, which had traveled a long distance, was hot and hard. The soles of their feet felt warm as they climbed the stairs.

But once inside, there was no heat at all.

A space that is always at a comfortable temperature thanks to magic.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire were a little nervous as soon as they stepped onto the train, expecting to see the enemies they would face in the tournament, but... unfortunately or fortunately, the train was empty.

“Ah, they've even divided up the platform so that only the students of the Colosseo Academy can ride, this compartment is reserved for us!”

Everyone nodded at Tudor's words. I was glad that an argument hadn't broken out, but also a little disappointed.

Then.

“Huh? There they are!”

Bianca, who had the eyesight of an archer, reached for the window.

While the train was stopped, some people had stepped off the platform to buy something or just to look outside.

They were divided into two groups, one of which was the students, impressive in their thick, solid heavy armor and the chainmail they wore underneath.

Ninety-nine percent of them were well-built men, each carrying a shield, axe, greatsword, or crossbow on their backs.

They are the students of the Varangian Boot Camp.

“It's like a bunch of sanchos. What are you doing not wearing that?”

“Haha, you're right. It's a familiar outfit in the north.”

Tudor looked over at Sancho next to him and smiled, and Sancho laughed in return.

Meanwhile, on the other side of the room were a group of schoolgirls, wearing white school uniforms and capes with Rose of Sharon on them.

Ninety-nine percent of them were sturdy women, each carrying a shield, axe, greatsword, crossbow, magic wand, or spellbook on their backs.

They are the students of the Themiscyra Women's University.

“...Does it look scary?”

“I hear the sisters over there are really good at fighting.”

Bianca and Sinclaire swallowed hard.

These are the warriors of Varangian and Themiscyra who will compete in this tournament.

It was clear that it was going to be an uphill battle for them to look so powerful, male, female, and all.

And then.

POOH!

The train set off with the miraculous sound of the mana stones in the furnace burning.

The giant mass of iron pulsed and stirred with the power of mana.

The train raced toward the distant magic tower.

◆

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire moved to the seats listed on their tickets, and soon found themselves in a chamber-like space, sitting in a circle.

A round table was placed in the center of the room, and the train was divided into individual writing spaces.

The students of the Colosseo Academy would now sit or lie down on plush sofas for the long journey ahead.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire looked out the window and marveled at the rapidly passing landscape of the Imperial Capital.

“Wow, that was fast. I guess we don't have to use those expensive teleportation scrolls.”

“I'll go to the canteen and get us some eggs and cider. That's what you're supposed to eat on a train trip.”

“Dang, I already packed them!”

“Oh, Pigi knows what he's doing.”

“Wow, it's like we're going on a school trip!”

And suddenly. The friends remembered one other friend who wasn't here.

Vikir.

It would have been nice to have him with them, but he wasn't there, and it was a bit of a drag.

Tudor was the first to speak.

“Vikir, you traitorous bastard, you've abandoned us again, and this time I'm really sorry!”

“It's a pact, and while it's a shame we couldn't be in the same group, it's nice to see you take your promise seriously. I'm sure Vikir would take our promise just as seriously.”

“Where is Vikir's seat, anyway?”

“He's probably in a compartment pretty far away from us, right next to the one the Themiscyra kids are in.”

“Hmph, you don't think something's going to happen to him?”

Vikir's current seat was in a train compartment a long way back from here.

And in the compartment directly behind him were the contestants from Themiscyra Women's University.

“Don't you think he'll get into a fight with them?”

“Maybe it's not a fight, maybe it's a ride.”

“Yes, Vikir is very handsome, and he was already famous outside the Capital.”

“I heard that ...Themiscyra is a women's university, and they have a very strong desire for handsome men.”

“It's more like Varangian is an ultra-macho university, so the desire for pretty girls is very strong.”

Vikir's friends, who had been listening to the story, quickly became concerned.

“By the way. I'm worried about Vikir in a lot of ways.”

“That's right. It's his own people who can make things harder for him than the Themiscyra on the outside.”

“I agree, except for Granola.......”

“I can't believe he's in the same group as Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, the so-called 'Mad Dogs of the Cold Class'.”

“They must be trying to pick on my brother, they did it during midterms!”

Vikir's group was now being referred to as 'Hell's Group'.

Highbro Le Baskerville.

Middlebro Le Baskerville.

Lowbro Le Baskerville.

Granola de Leviathan.

Vikir.

These five are the same group.

Granola, who is known for his arrogance, and the triplets of the Baskerville family, who are known for their cold-heartedness.

His friends are worried that Vikir, a commoner, may be suffering humiliation and disgrace alone.

...But.

In the back of the train, a very different scene was unfolding from the worries of his friends.

Chapter 237

National University League (4)

◆

Vikir gave the Baskerville triplets a quick glance and left the room.

Clink.

As soon as Vikir left the cabin and closed the door behind him, he heard a commotion inside.

''Kwaaaaaa...ub! Uub! Ub!'

The screams cut off unnaturally, as if the hounds had understood the meaning of their master's gesture.

Now that the pesky Granola is gone, the group activities should go off without a hitch.

Vikir left his cabin and walked out near the seamy passageway that connects compartments to compartments on the train.

There were shops and cafes there, and passengers from other compartments were milling around.

Suddenly, Vikir made eye contact with a small girl.

She was staring at a cake in a glass display case with a twinkle in her eye, wondering if she wanted to eat it.

Vikir bought the cake along with a bottle of water.

The amount of money in his pocket was just right.

“I must have bought the wrong one by mistake. Eat it if you don't mind.”

Vikir bent down to make eye contact with the girl and handed her the wrapped cake, and she beamed with delight.

“Thank you, mister!”

The girl accepted the cake and planted a surprise kiss on Vikir's cheek.

Of course, Vikir was able to dodge it with the Swordmaster's body vision.

“....”

Something about hearing the word 'mister' made him feel strange, so he didn't dodge the lips on his cheek.

Just.

“...It's not mister, it's brother.”

I stretched my back and looked at the distant mountains, trying to close the distance I had closed so long ago.

A girl's face flashed in my mind's eye like a puffy cloud outside the car window, and then it was gone.

Then.

“Mr. .... Surely, you're not old enough to be called that.”

A calm voice came from behind him.

Where Vikir turned, Dolores stood.

Dolores, the student council president, looks stern, stoic, and serious.

But in her hands are eggs and cider.

“....”

“...Khem.”

Feeling Vikir's stare, Dolores quickly hid the eggs and cider behind her back.

“There are participants from the Themisqyra Women's University in the wagon back there. I want you to avoid contact with them as much as possible before the tournament, in case they want to make a scene.”

“Understood.”

“....”

Vikir nodded, and Dolores hesitated, as if she had something more to say.

Then. A familiar face emerged from the opposite aisle. It was Professor Banshee Morgue.

“Hey, student council president. Professor Sadi is not at the head of the line. Have you seen her?”

“I think I saw her near the compartment with the participants from Varangian.”

“This person can't do anything right. Why does the principal keep her as a professor?”

Prof. Banshee was so angry that he openly insulted his colleague in front of the students.

Professor Banshee then left to find Professor Sadi. He dragged Dolores with him, who wanted to talk to Vikir more.

“Okay, wait a minute, then you can take one more person with you...!”

Dolores said to Professor Banshee just before leaving Cannes.

She intended to bring Vikir along on the mission to find Professor Sadi. They would have something to talk about.

But Professor Banshee only shook his head.

“One more? Who?”

“He's here... huh?”

Dolores's eyes widened as she turned her head.

....

Because the spot where Vikir was standing just a moment ago was empty.

◆

It almost got annoying.'

Vikir stood on top of the moving train, facing the wind.

As soon as he realized that Dolores was about to launch a maneuver, he opened the window, scaled the wall of the train, and climbed up to the ceiling.

All of this was done in the blink of an eye, like the behavior of a ghost, and no one noticed.

Vikir walked across the train at a leisurely pace and soon landed at the window of the opposite compartment.

Luckily, the passageway between the compartments was empty, making it easy for him to get back inside the train.

'Halfway between the Colosseo Academy and the Themiscyra Women's University.'

This is where the middle section of the train begins, and from here on out, it's all about the Themiscyra female student group.

One more compartment back and you'd be in the middle of a sea of girls.

The compartment at the back had two floors, and a thin bulkhead blocked the stairs.

So it was on the second floor of the cabin that Vikir now entered through the window.

The room for Themiscyra's female students was generally quiet and smelled of fragrant tea.

The only sound was elegant heavy metal music, the kind that noble ladies might enjoy.

Vikir stood at the window for a moment, considering his next move.

First, he had to appease Granola, who was treating him like a commoner and ignoring him, so that he could continue with the group activities.

Even though the scores were calculated individually, the initial start was in the form of a group task, so they would have to cry and eat mustard together.

Of course, Vikir didn't care about any of that, but... still had to put together an assortment.

Hence the decision to use the Baskerville triplets.

'Why are you so obsessed with origins?'

Vikir thought for a moment about Granola's attitude.

Vikir doesn't know who his mother is.

He'd heard that she was an actress and dancer who briefly dated Hugo, but that wasn't exactly accurate.

Vikir's mind wandered.

'Come to think of it, I've also heard that there is royalty among the freshmen in this class of 20.'

That was also an inaccurate statement.

There is a rumor that a royal family member, almost an illegitimate child, who does not know what rank he is in the line of succession to the throne, has entered the Colosseo Academy.

No matter how you slice it, an Imperial is an Imperial, and many were on high alert.

There were even rumors that some of the professors had already noticed.

'Well, it's none of my business.'

Vikir closed his eyes and shook off his thoughts.

He started to walk back to the first floor of the room.

Then.

“...?”

A strange voice called from the stairs.

Vikir was about to open the door and head out when he paused and listened to the sounds coming from the first floor hallway.

...?

The voice was all too familiar.

◆

“Ah, the smell of commoners.”

“You must have gotten that smell all over my clothes.”

“You should be paying for laundry like a human being, not this~”

“More than that, shouldn't the first thing you do is apologize for bumping into me?”

“Oh dear. You're the top dog at the Great Colosseo Academy, aren't you?”

“That's right, you're too good to know how to apologize~”

The girls in Themiscyra's uniforms glared at the wall with frightening eyes.

And in the corner stood a girl.

It was Sinclaire.

Undaunted, she opened her mouth.

“We're supposed to avoid each other in the hallways, and I didn't, but you didn't either, so it's kind of a double whammy, I guess, although I don't know if you did or didn't.”

“Oh, so you're saying you're the victim now because we both lost different amounts of damage?”

The girl who had bumped into Sinclaire fiddled with the scarf on her shoulder in disbelief.

It was an expensive looking scarf at first glance.

“My dear. You don't realize you're a commoner. This one would cost you three semesters of tuition at your school just to have it cleaned. It's limited edition, limited edition!”

Now glaring at Sinclaire was Merelini Lovegood, a senior at Themiscyra Woman's University, and president of the student council.

The Merelini family was one of the wealthiest and most prominent families in the empire, and they were also members of the House of Bourgeois, a distinction that came with a great deal of prestige.

As a member of the family, Lovegood was a very proud student.

She was also very proud of the fact that she was a student at Themiscyra Women's University, which gave her a bit of a hooligan attitude.

Maybe that's why?

When Lovegood met Sinclaire, she confronted her quite openly.

'You're telling me you topped our Themiscyra's entrance exams and then went to another school, you cheeky little bastard....'

Beyond that, being top of the class at Magic Tower and top of the class at Colosseo is something to be frowned upon.

In fact, Lovegood had taken the entrance exams for Themiscyra Women's University at the same time as she took the entrance exams for Colosseo Academy, and had failed to make the top of the class.

So when she met Sinclaire here today, she was happy to see her, and tried to argue with her.

But.

“Oh, that scarf? I know what it sells for, it's a limited edition, but it's old and it depreciates a lot, so it fetches a really low second-hand price. I'm sure it's not as much as you say...?”

Sinclaire opened his mouth to speak in an amused tone.

Then Lovegood snapped.

“That's ridiculous! Sometimes pre-owned items command a premium! This was actually worn by a famous singer! This was actually worn by the actor G-Pistol! Don't you know about celebrity premiums?”

“Well, if it's worth a premium because it was worn by a celebrity of that caliber, then it's worth the original brand value.”

Sinclaire's response was unexpectedly cold and sharp.

Her normally smiling face was now dry and cold, without a trace of a smile.

A line of blood stood on Lovegood's forehead.

“No, but this little brat has been cheekily talking down to the senior from earlier...!”

“Auntie, you're not a senior in our school, are you?”

“Oh, auntie?”

“Even though you're quite a senior, is it the code of Themiscyra to persecute a freshman from another school like this, especially one who entered early?”

“Wow! This...!?”

“If this is the way of Themiscyra, then I have no comment.”

Sinclaire said softly.

“...I'm glad I didn't go to that school.”

It was the final blow.

Then the girls from Themiscyra, including Lovegood, began to surround Sinclaire with stern looks on their faces.

“You, you!”

Lovegood shuddered and drew his wand from his back.

It was a clunky iron club with a starburst on the end, and the mana glowed pink and bright.

It looked like Lovegood was preparing some kind of magic.

And Sinclaire's eyes widened, ready to meet Lovegood's attack.

And then.

...POP!

The mana from Lovegood's wand was instantly scattered.

“Enough.”

A large shadow landed in front of Sinclaire.

Lovegood took a half-step backward, startled by the black curtain in front of him.

Vikir.

He stood between Sinclaire and Lovegood, gripping the doorknob of the passageway.

Chapter 241

National University League (8)

◆

Boli Bollason, the first-year representative from Varangian.

He declared a showdown with the Colosseo Academy.

The strongest guy here, come out! Something like that.

The provocation was obvious, as the area he was in was a dining area for first-year students from both schools.

It would be embarrassing for the 2nd and 3rd year students of the school to come out against the 1st year students of the other school, so only a 1st year student will step up.

'OK, we've come this far, there's no way they won't come out.'

Boli Bollason blew out a hot snort and crossed his arms.

He was confident that he could beat whoever came out.

That Sancho in front of him was once stronger than him, but not now.

This is because while Sancho neglected his training in the peacefulness of the Imperial Capital, he had trained tirelessly in the harsh conditions of the north.

Tudors, from the Donquixote family, was said to be strong, but only in sports, friendly competitions, and other formal events with strict rules and regulations.

He'd only be slightly better than brats with little experience in spontaneous street battles.

The Baskervilles' three brothers... were honestly overwhelming, but in a one-on-one fight, he was confident he wouldn't lose.

Granola, that sneaky little bastard with his poison, wasn't even a contender.

And the presence of Sinclaire and Bianca only served to fuel Bollason's fierce resolve.

'I'm definitely not jealous of co-educational schools. Never!'

Now, this hostility doesn't involve any personal feelings of jealousy or envy of all-boys schools.

At least, that's what Bollason could say with confidence.

...?

Everyone's eyes shifted elsewhere.

The eyes of the students at Colosseo Academy bounced from one to the next as Bollason demanded that the strongest man come out, but when they finally settled on one, it wasn't on Tudor, it wasn't on Sancho, it wasn't on the Baskervilles, it wasn't on Granola, it wasn't on Sinclaire, it wasn't on Bianca.

Vikir. A boy sitting off to one side, eating quietly.

He was completely indifferent to what was going on around him, lost in thought.

'...I have now mastered the 7th Form of Baskerville. Ever since I became a Swordmaster, my seventh tooth has grown to rival my sixth, so I wonder if it's time for the eighth, the eighth tooth.'

He was ruminating on how to leap beyond the current level of Swordmaster.

'The eighth tooth grows at the threshold of death, which means I must fight to the death.'

Vikir had heard it all before. Crossing the line of death was something he feels relatively confident about.

The smell of blood, the countless karma, and the experience gained would serve as fertilizer as he broke through the Wall of Eight.

...But Vikir's thoughts were interrupted.

Vikir's thoughts were interrupted by Bollason walking in front of him and opening his mouth.

“Hey, buddy. Are you the strongest first-year in Colosseo?”

“?”

Vikir paused and looked away.

Then something large and thick was placed in front of him.

...BANG!

It was Bollason's forearm.

Bollason spoke in a low, short voice.

“How about an arm wrestling match, no mana.”

Students of a prestigious academy shouldn't be fighting in the streets.

If they were to formally challenge each other to a duel, there would be a lot of hassle if there were casualties before the tournament.

Therefore, the favorite forms of combat among Varangian warriors were “wrestling” and “arm wrestling”.

If the space was large and there were sandpits around, they would wrestle; if the space was small and the terrain didn't allow for it, they would arm wrestle.

“....”

Vikir crossed his arms and looked down.

Bollason's large hand was there, taunting him, inviting him to take the plunge.

“Why, you look like a little shit.”

“....”

“If you're scared, you can just say you're scared. I don't despise losers.”

“....”

“Though it does give me a new appreciation for the standard of Colosseo Academy, with a guy like you at the top of the class, hahaha-”

Bollason continued to taunt.

Then.

“Enough of that.”

A voice intervened.

Dolores stepped down from the second floor staircase and looked down at the first years.

Dolores, a saint of the Colosseo, was revered by the warriors of Varangian, so Bollason bowed respectfully.

Dolores cut to the chase.

“I will not allow any disturbances between the schools before the tournament, so let's end this nerve war and get everyone to bed early for the tournament....”

“Wait.”

Just then, another voice interrupted Dolores.

Bakilaga Juragio. The top of the Varangian.

He looked up at Dolores with a smirk on his face.

“I think it's more appropriate to look at this as a little prank between a bunch of hot-headed newcomers than an inter-school feud, right?”

“Mr. Bakilaga. I understand what you're trying to say, but....”

“Seriously, how are they supposed to get along without all the fuss? They say children grow up fighting.”

“If they can't, they shouldn't.”

“Uh-huh-but my junior is on a mission to prove his strength right now, and that seems to be the case with the students of Colosseo as well.”

At that, Dolores turned her head away.

She could already see Tudor, Sancho, and the others sulking at having their friend insulted in front of them.

She could use the authority of the student council president to order them to back off, but that would hurt their feelings a lot.

Bakilaga frowned at Dolores, who let out a small sigh.

“Instead of that, how about we become witnesses and observe? I mean, how about arm wrestling? I think it could be a little entertainment to boost the competitive spirit before the competition.”

At this point, Dolores could only nod in agreement.

Anything less would have killed the morale of the Colosseo freshmen before the tournament.

“...If there's any sign of trouble, I'll step in and stop it.”

“Me too. I might even call a halt to it first. I'm more cautious than I look. Especially when it comes to the health of my juniors.”

The presidents of the two schools came to an agreement.

Immediately, seats were cleared and a place set.

Vikir and Bollason sat across from each other at a stone round table.

“Hoo-hoo. Those are some slender arms you've got there. I'll believe you if you say they're the arms of a noble. I'm not sure if I should hold them or not, I might break them.”

“....”

Vikir didn't argue, but held out his hand with a grim expression.

Soon, the two men's hands were locked together.

...Kkuug!

The moment their hands connected, Bollason's expression changed.

“What the hell? It's quite...”

“....”

Vikir was still speechless.

Then, Pigi, the referee, blew his whistle hard.

At the same time, Bollason began to roar with terrifying force.

“Heuaaaaaaas!”

The sound rattled the glasses around him.

The men in Varangian burst out laughing and started cheering for Bollason.

“Oooooooo, go, freshman boy!”

“Show us how you can strangle a bear!”

“Just smash it!”

The crowd's cheers erupted.

...But.

“Haaaahhhhhh!”

“....”

“Grrrrrrrrrrrr!”

“....”

“Chhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!”

“....”

Bollason's cheers were louder than before, but nothing had changed on the board.

Vikir's arm and Bollason's arm are still in the same place, unmoving.

Only the veins on Bollason's forearm continued to flutter and twitch like a snake thrown onto a grill.

'Hey, why can't I move this guy's arm?'

Bollason continued to pound his fist into the man's forearm.

But Vikir was still staring straight ahead, expressionless and unmoving.

“Hmph, hmph, hmph!”

Bollason's eyes were now completely strained open. His gaunt face was covered in spit, snot, and sweat.

Despite this, Vikir did not release his grip, so their hands remained firmly planted in the center of the arm-wrestling board.

“....”

Vikir was quietly looking at Bollason, who was sweating profusely with a red face right in front of him.

Bollason gritted his teeth as he saw that despite the effort it took to free his hand, it still remained in the center.

He couldn't push, he couldn't pull, his arms won't move at all. He couldn't even take his hand away because Vikir won't let go.

Vikir had no intention of winning in the first place, so he kept his arm in the center and didn't move.

At this point, Bollason can't help but feel like he's pushing a giant mountain with his hands.

Tudor and Sancho, who were watching, giggled in amusement.

“That's how I felt the first time I played football with Vikir.”

“Right. That was my first experience with his power. It was beyond common sense.”

And then.

With all the focused attention of the Varangian and Colosseo students,

“...Lost, I lost.”

After a long pause, Bollason finally admitted defeat.

The Varangian students, who had been cheering him on, could only stare at each other in disbelief.

“What the hell, did Bollason lose?”

“He didn't fall, why did he lose? It was tight!”

“Bollason, you spineless bastard, it's a tie, you can't just forfeit!”

“You didn't pass it, but he didn't pass it either! If you had held on a little longer, you could have won!”

Then Bollason, who was booed, clenched his teeth.

'They don't know anything!'

On the surface, it looks like a draw, but it's not.

Vikir had no intention of winning, so he was letting him off the hook.

And it's possible to be generous in arm wrestling....

'How strong are you?'

Bollason's face turned white.

In arm wrestling, it's much harder to keep a draw than it is to win.

Only an overwhelming difference in strength will allow you to keep your arms centered, depending on your opponent's strength.

When Bollason broke out in a cold sweat and was lost in thought.

“Get out of the way, I challenge you!”

“If it's just strength, I'm better than Bollason!”

“If it's just arm wrestling, I'm stronger!”

“Me too! I'll take the challenge!”

“If I beat him here, I'll be certified as stronger than Bollason, right?”

“Do you accept second graders?”

“I'm a third grader, but that's a bit much, isn't it?”

The other students of Varangian, angered by Bollason's hollow declaration of defeat, began to crowd around.

And.

“Line up.”

Vikir graciously accepted their challenge.

'..., This reminds me of the old days.'

By all accounts, it was a small entertainment.

Chapter 243

Survival Contest (1)

◆

The day of the University League has arrived.

Participants from Colosseo Academy, Varangian Boot Camp and Temiscyra Academies knocked on the Magic Tower's school gate.

The main gate of the tower opened by itself as soon as they knocked.

It was like a creature opening its mouth.

“...Wah.”

Once inside, the students couldn't help but gasp.

From the outside, the tower looked like a tall, narrow structure, but when they stepped inside, it was truly a spectacular view.

There were countless floors, all furnished with vast forests, lakes, oceans, deserts, lava fields, canyons, and snowy mountains.

In the skies, countless stars gathered to form constellations, which together form the Milky Way.

The serene sound of a waterfall echoed through the majestic walls.

Water dews formed melodious tunes as they fell on mushrooms scattered around the ground, and glowing fireflies flew into the air.

As the students climbed the stairs, trickling streams of water ran coolly between their toes.

The water slowly rose to their knees, waists, shoulders, then the top of their heads, swallowing up all the space.

The students, who at first panicked, wondering if they were going to drown, gradually regained their composure and began to enjoy the phenomenon.

The “magic water” is also one of the artifacts awarded for winning the competition.

They could drink this mysterious water and dip their hands and feet in it. However, even if they were completely submerged in the water, they wouldn't get wet and they would still be able to breathe.

“Wow, look, none of my clothes are wet, they're still fluffy and dry!”

“I can breathe and I can hear you clearly. It's amazing-”

“And yet it sure feels like I'm underwater!”

The students swam upward in this mysterious space, through forests and mountains, deserts and volcanoes, oceans and deserts, canyons and the Milky Way.

And the higher they go, the more new spaces, unusual terrains, and mysterious natural phenomena are revealed to them.

This was the essence of Magic, which distorted the laws of space, fusing different terrains together.

◆

Before the Survival Competition, there was a meeting for the representatives of each school to gather and discuss.

First and foremost, the map on which the competition would take place was chosen.

Lava Field (Inferno Hell) / Volcano (Charpero Crater) / Desert (Yuuni) / Jungle (Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain) / Snow Mountain (Fort Tochka) / Sea (Harsh Sea) / Abandoned Mine (Forgotten Land) / ...

Various terrains were presented as competition locations.

The representatives of each school had their own favorite terrain.

Bakilaga, a representative of Varangian, wanted a snowy mountain covered with snow and ice.

“Northerners are used to the cold. To us, ice is our food and snow is our quilt.”

Lovegood, representing Themiscyra, wanted an ocean.

“Southerners are used to the sea. There's no second choice.”

Hohenheim, representing the Magic Tower, wanted a lava field.

“Because my specialty is fire and lava magic. Huhuhu-”

And then it was Dolores' turn, representing Colosseo.

“....”

Dolores was lost in thought.

She was thinking about what happened yesterday at the inn.

About Vikir!

'It's weird. No matter how much I think about it....'

How could he be so strong? Is there something special about him? But there was such a huge weight difference...?

Dolores had experienced three university leagues so far in her school years, and this was the first time she witnessed another man compete in strength with Bakilaga.

And it was just his first year at Colosseo.

'His grades on the midterms, his knowledge that rivals Professor Banshee's, and his suspension record....'

Suddenly, a thought flashed through Dolores' mind.

'Could he be the imperial family member who's been hiding their identity at the Academy...?'

What if this rumor, which everyone dismissed as just a hoax, was true? It would make some sense.

'But there's no evidence of that, and I doubt there will be.'

Dolores was lost in thought as she recalled Vikir's face.

“Hey, Saint.”

Bakilaga called out to Dolores from beside her.

“What are you thinking about so much?”

“Oh, sorry, I was just thinking about yesterday's arm wrestling match.”

Dolores straightened her posture, and Bakilaga smirked.

“Why? Did you like the fact that your boyfriend was unexpectedly so strong?”

“He's...?”

“Well, I thought you were single for three years in school, so I thought you weren't interested in guys. Turns out you're really picky about guys, so yeah, he's probably a pretty good pass.”

“What? No, that's not what....”

“What? A secret love affair? Hahaha- I didn't realize that. Campus couples do that. Heh heh, good times.”

Bakilaga chuckled and turned away.

Dolores momentarily realized what he meant and was about to correct the misunderstanding.

Whirr...

She couldn't, because the spinning wheel of map selection had begun to spin.

And then.

...Poof!

The spinner stopped.

The arrow in the center pointed to the map where today's competition would take place.

And then.

“....”

“....”

“....”

“....”

Bakilaga from Varangian Boot Camp, Hohenheim from Magic Tower, Lovegood from Themiscyra, and Dolores from Colosseo Academy.

All four student representatives frowned in unison.

Jungle (Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain)

The map that was equally the worst choice for everyone was chosen as the map for today's competition.

◆

Meanwhile.

The competition staff from each school gathered in one place.

North of the round table, there sat a muscular man with a bushy beard and a helmet decorated with water buffalo horns.

To the south, there was a woman with a bow and sword strapped to her back and waist respectively, sitting with her legs crossed elegantly.

To the east sat an impossibly large man with graying hair, white eyebrows, and a long, flowing white beard.

They were, respectively, 'Vasilios', the Deputy Director of the Varangian Boot Camp, 'Hippolyte', the Principal of Themiscyra Academy, and 'Whitebeard Whale', the Master of the Magic Tower.

And on the west side of the round table, a middle-aged man with long black hair, a stern expression, and a pair of deep eyes, sat silently.

He was Professor Banshee, the Vice Principal of the Colosseo Academy.

The Master of the Magic Tower, the Whitebeard Whale, spoke up.

“Hehehe- It is an honor to hold this year's tournament in our Magic Tower. I express my gratitude to the people involved who have journeyed far here.”

He looked back and forth between the representatives from Varangian Boot Camp and Colosseo Academy.

“By the way, for some reason, only the Deputy Director and Vice Principal came, are the Director and Principal unavailable?”

The question was, why did the second in command come and not the head?

At this, Deputy Director Vasilios became agitated.

“The Director is still recovering from the 'unfortunate incident' that happened last time.”

“Oh, no. Was it because of that 'Ms. Ouroboros' villain?”

Master Whitebeard stretched out his fingers and snapped it in the air.

A newspaper clipping popped up in front of him.

[BREAKING NEWS] The Night Hound, whose evil deeds know no bounds!

-(※This article has been corrected.)-

-The worst villain of all time, 'Night Hound' 'Ms. Ouroboros' showed her fangs again.

Last night, a group of students from the Varangian Boot Camp on a school trip to the Imperial Capital were attacked by the “Night Hound” “Ms. Ouroboros” and caused great damage...

There were 00 minor injuries and 00 serious injuries... Among them was the Director of the Varangian's Boot Camp...

Meanwhile, no fingerprints were found on the only piece of evidence left at the scene, a broken vodka bottle...

It was a newspaper published by Ryukeion, the newspaper department of the Colosseo Academy.

According to the article, Varangian Boot Camp had been attacked by a mysterious assailant once before, and the aftermath of the attack still lingered.

(Later investigations revealed that it was not the Night Hound but Ms. Ouroboros who had attacked Varangian Boot Camp, and that the attack was the work of a grudge fight.)

In this fight, the Director of Verangian's Boot Camp was gravely wounded, which is why Deputy Director Vasilios is here today as Acting Director.

Meanwhile.

“The reason why the Principal of this school could not come is because....”

Professor Banshee was just about to open his mouth to say something.

...Bam!

The spinning wheel spins, and the map is finalized.

This is the terrain where 400 students from four schools will compete for survival today.

The conversation naturally shifted.

When all the headmasters saw that the map had been chosen for the competition, they swallowed hard.

“So this is the map that everyone is most afraid of.”

“That's right. In places like volcanic areas and snowy mountains, food and water are hard to come by, but once you get them, you can preserve them by drying them in the wind or burying them in the ground.”

“But in the jungle, it's hot and humid, so everything rots quickly. Many things are also contaminated or poisonous, so food and water are hard to come by.”

“....”

Next, a large mirror floated above the round table, reflecting the faces of 400 students.

The mirror was the legendary “Extra Eyes,” a magical tool that can see the status of anyone from a thousand miles away, and was once awarded to the Tower master “Whitebeard Whale” for winning the university league.

Everyone was in awe of Whitebeard's artifact.

“Wow. The 'Extra Eyes' is always so magical.”

“I can see all the students from here.”

“I can see what 400 people are doing right in front of me.”

“....”

Once again, Professor Banshee crossed his arms and said nothing.

Soon, the heads of each school began to chat, each watching the students from their own school.

“So, who are the favorites to win this competition?”

“'Bakilaga' from Varangian Boot Camp, 'Lovegood' from Themiscyra Academy, 'Hohenheim' from Magic Tower, and 'Dolores' from Colosseo Academy, isn't it?”

“Yeah, they were the top performers in their age group in the competition last year and the year before, so there's a good chance they'll get an artifact.”

“....”

But Professor Banshee is still silent.

He just stares off into the distance.

The heads of the other schools look at him curiously.

“Vice Principal Banshee, may we ask where you are looking?”

“Ms. Dolores, the ace of the Colosseo Academy, is on the other side of the field, isn't she?”

“The direction you're looking is where the first graders are gathered.”

But Professor Banshee only hummed and snorted.

“I'm watching someone else.”

There was a boy who stood with a cold attitude, as if he wasn't interested in anything.

Chapter 246

Survival Contest (4)

◆

Vasilios, Vice Director of Varangian, Hippolyte, Principal of Themiscyra, Blue Whale, Master of the Magic Tower, and Banshee, Vice Principal of Colosseo.

They were keeping an eye on the current situation of the tournament through a large artifact called the Extra Eyes.

Colosseo-23

Magic Tower-35

Varangian-45

Themiscyra-46

Deputy Director Vasilios and Principal Hippolyte stroked their chins.

“Looks like Mr. Hohenheim has found another prey.”

“I guess it wasn't enough that he eliminated a bunch of students from the Colosseo just a moment ago, hohoho- be brave too.”

Just a moment ago, the genius Hohenheim had unleashed an enormous amount of magic power, causing a sea of fire to erupt around him, killing about thirty Colosseo students.

Most of those who had already been defeated or were almost defeated were third-year aces, and even Dolores, Colosseo's favorite to win, was included among them.

The shock of the Colosseo students was even greater because the student council president almost suffered elimination from the beginning of the competition.

Afterwards, Hohenheim moved through the jungle as if there was nothing to worry about.

Another two dozen or so students from Varangian and Themiscyra were swept away by his tsunami of fire.

All of them were third-year aces who had the strength and experience to win.

'Hohenheim of a Thousand Buddhas', I think the nickname that has spread throughout the world is truly accurate.

He was on a wild ride, as if he was going to eliminate all the aces from the start.

Watching him in the mirror, the tower's master, the White Bearded Whale, smiled wryly.

“Hehehe- our 'smart-ass with high nose' is finally showing his true colors.”

“....”

“Oh dear, here we go again with the Colosseo students. What else do you run into when you're having dinner?”

“....”

“I'm seeing Miss Dolores again, the woman who barely escaped with her life earlier. I guess the Colosseo isn't having any of this. Hehehe-”

The Master Whitebeard was unexpectedly talkative for such a huge beast.

However, Professor Banshee, Colosseo's vice principal, did not respond to his words.

“....”

A look of mild displeasure, but one that didn't seem to bother him.

But his gaze never left the mirror.

In the mirror, where Vikir and Dolores were holding hands.

Crackle!

The curtain of fire is torn.

The mud dried and crumbled into sand, and the sand melted into bubbling lava.

...Splat! ... Splat! ... Splat! ... Splat!

Hohenheim walked over it.

“Whoo-hoo-hoo. Wormy Colosseo bastards.”

His face is a 180-degree change from when he was leading the welcoming procession.

Perhaps this is his true color.

“It's time to turn the university rankings upside down. The best university in this empire is the Magic Tower. And I will be its greatest genius.”

Hohenheim has always resented the fact that Magic Tower is second only to Colosseo in the university hierarchy.

And now, with all of his annoying seniors gone, he planned to take matters into his own hands and make his university the best it could be.

“...?”

Hohenheim's eyes narrowed.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling...

A large pot of coconut boiling in front of him, and the red stew within.

It gave off a delicious smell that caught the attention of Hohenheim, a picky eater.

He may be a genius, but he's not comfortable with the harsh conditions of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Hohenheim was hungry and thirsty, too.

“...Hmm. Is this a trap?”

Hohenheim looked around.

There were deep butt prints in the dry straw around him, as if someone had stayed nearby earlier.

Judging by their carefully constructed huts, pits, and bonfires, they had planned to stay here for a long time.

“Fufu, and then I came along and you abandoned everything and fled in a hurry.”

There's no sign of the ambushers around. All they could see was a hasty evacuation.

What's more, in their haste, they'd dropped the grade markers on their suits.

It marked them as first-year students.

Hohenheim let his guard down.

If he was a first-year, he wasn't worth fighting.

He'd probably run away with his ass anyway, let alone ambush him.

So he was going to eat the stew in front of him.

“Still, I'll have to be prepared for archer fire, just in case.”

In a jungle like this, archers are the most annoying opponents.

With that in mind, Hohenheim took a step forward.

Just then.

...Quack!

The thick log on the other side shattered and fell down.

“Hahahaha- I came here because I smelled something delicious, and this is what happened!”

Hohenheim frowned at the familiar voice that rang out.

Long, spiky, wild hair, and a build like a giant beast.

It was Bakilaga Juragio, the student council president of the Varangian Boot Camp.

“....”

Hohenheim quietly stretched out his hands forward.

Kurrrrrr!

The mud around him began to boil and emit steam.

Huffing and puffing...

With a crimson glow, the mud around them turned to lava.

However, Bakilaga smirked and stepped forward with one foot.

...Quack!

The ground flipped over and the lava rose upside down.

The mud underneath was still intact, and Bakilaga ran over it, swinging the greatsword on his back forward.

A pale aura of blue light emanated from him, thick as water vapor.

Hohenheim's eyes widened at the sight.

“Sword Expert Supreme... or is it Graduator!”

“Hahaha, you just became a fourth-class mage, how can I leave you behind!”

Even the elites of Magic Tower usually don't reach class 4 until they are in their thirties.

Similarly, the elite of Varangian don't step onto the threshold of the Graduator until their thirties.

Here, however, geniuses outside of these two standards were fiercely battling it out right now, with accomplishments years ahead of the average genius.

Dragon and Tiger (龍虎相搏). Throw the universe (乾坤一擲). It was a clash of the next generation of geniuses who would represent sword and magic.

Boom, boom, boom!

Bakilaga's greatsword sliced through the rocks and trees in front of him.

Hohenheim stepped back hastily, dodging the falling debris at diagonal angles.

“Give the mage time, and he will give you a headache.”

Bakilaga charged, swinging his greatsword like a feather.

Even if it was low level Graduator, its power was absolute. The aura spun at high speed along the edges of the sword, cutting through everything it touched.

Even Hohenheim would lose all his HP in an instant if hit by it.

“Damn it, shields!”

Several translucent shields appeared in front of Hohenheim's eyes.

But.

Crack, crack, crack, crack!

The shields scraped and shattered with a loud crack.

Through the shards, Bakilaga's aura pushed in like the teeth and nails of a monster.

“It's over, Hohenheim.”

Bakilaga's voice echoes out, terrifying.

Pow! Thud.

Hohenheim had to roll around on the ground to avoid a slash that cut off a chunk of his hair.

But.

Hohenheim is not so easily pushed aside.

Swoosh.

He rolled on the ground and stretched out his palms, burying them in the mud.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling...

The mud, heated by his mana, began to bubble and boil.

Soon, a thick vapor shrouded Hohenheim's body.

At the same time, the mud dried out, baked, and began to crack.

Flames leapt from the cracks.

The odds were increasingly stacked against the Bakilaga.

“...Hmm.”

Bakilaga couldn't see well enough through the blinding dust, smoke, and steam.

In the midst of it all.

Grumble! ... Puff! ... pop! ... pop!

Fireballs shot out from beyond the barrier of fire, and what's more, lava created by melting mud creates a whirlpool on the ground.

All around is a dense forest. The humid, muggy atmosphere was being dried out by the firestorm.

As the hot, pungent smoke spread in all directions, the humidity gave way to dryness.

And then.

Pop! Fujijijijik! Grumble!

Even the trees, which had been merely blackened when exposed to fire because they contained a lot of moisture, began to catch fire.

Hohenheim's flame magic was so terrifying that it had enough firepower to force a forest fire in a humid and hot jungle.

Koooooooo...

As the jungle atmosphere changed drastically, an abnormal climate was created.

The locally heated atmosphere combined with the surrounding moist air to form a giant vortex, and Hohenheim's fiery flames streaked fiercely through the current.

Colosseo, Varangian, Magic Tower, Themiscyra.

All students from all schools spread out across the jungle could feel Hohenheim's absolute power as soon as they saw the presence of that huge pillar of fire.

Then, a huge firestorm erupted and engulfed Bakilaga.

“Ugh!”

Bakilaga let out a long stream of aura from his sword, cutting off all the wind-driven flames, but there was nothing he could do about it as the oxygen in the air disappeared and soot took its place.

...Thud!

In the end, Bakilaga was forced to fall to one knee.

And in front of him, Hohenheim stepped forward with an air of uncertainty.

“No matter how hard a genius tries, he cannot beat a genius. That's why a genius is called a genius.”

At the same time.

...Bam!

Hohenheim crushed Bakilaga's neck and struck the staff in his hand.

“That's the end of Varangian, though he was quite good for a lowly barbarian.”

Hohenheim looked down at his feet with a sickening smile.

Then he turned his attention to the Bakilaga at his feet.

There, he sees the pot still sitting on the campfire.

Hohenheim reached out and scooped the distant pot into the palm of his hand.

“What a pity. The food looks pretty delicious. What should I do if I can't eat?”

“...Kill it quickly. Don't think this is the end.”

Bakilaga frowned and spoke as if chewing and spitting out.

But Hohenheim laughed sardonically, as if he had no intention of doing so.

“Come on, this is our last competition of the school year, let's make it count.”

Hohenheim wanted to show as much composure as a winner could show.

That was the performance of leisurely eating stew after the battle.

Soon, the red broth was in Hohenheim's mouth.

A leisurely smile spread across his face.

“Mmmm. This is really delicious...!?”

But.

Hohenheim's leisure didn't last long.

...Gulp!

As soon as the spicy soup went down my throat and reached my stomach, I felt a strange signal in my stomach.

Chapter 249

Recap (2)

◆

“Vikir.”

Dolores called Vikir in a low voice as she drew the curtains and went out onto the terrace.

Vikir's response was always short.

“Yes.”

Dolores watched Vikir's face for a moment in silence.

Then she stepped up beside Vikir, who was leaning against the railing.

“Thank you.”

“For what?”

“...Just. Everything.”

Strictly speaking, the reason Dolores was able to take first place in the rankings this time is thanks to Vikir.

During the early to mid game of the tournament, Vikir lured Hohenheim and Bakilaga to a single location and forced them to face off against each other, draining their power and finally catching Hohenheim.

Even if Vikir hadn't been betrayed by the triplets late in the tournament, he would have been in position of top five.

Dolores said.

“If it wasn't for the Baskerville triplets, your ranking would have been much higher.”

“What's done is done,” Vikir replied.

“...You're always so stoic, you don't seem to have any regrets.”

Dolores stared into Vikir's eyes for a moment.

Dolores wondered what it was, the feeling of being so familiar with him, as if she had known Vikir for years, even though he was only a new student.

She spoke again.

“When I said thank you earlier, I wasn't just talking about this tournament.”

“Isn't that right?”

“Yes.”

Dolores bent down, resting her chin in her hand.

She leaned against the railing and looked up at Vikir at an angle.

“ ...I wonder where this junior came from.”

“Just an ordinary freshman.”

“An ordinary freshman who have the skills of an advanced sword expert and have grades comparable to professors? And beat third years in a tournament even though you're only a freshman?”

“I got lucky.”

Dolores was silent for a moment at Vikir's nonchalant reply.

Colosseo Academy is a huge community of about 20,000 people, including students, professors, and staff.

It's a place where all the supposed geniuses of the world gather, so it's not surprising that there are a lot of talented people and a lot of geniuses.

Vikir's accomplishments were truly remarkable, but compared to other famous figures in the Academy, they didn't really stand out.

Dolores alone has accomplished as much as Vikir has since her freshman year.

In addition, Dolores longtime rivals Hohenheim, Bakilaga, Lovegood, and others had even more spectacular freshman years.

Moreover, the sophomores, third-, and fourth-year seniors who received her as a freshman were now achieving even greater achievements in higher positions.

Vikir focused on that point.

“The people I've met in this competition, like Bakilaga, Hohenheim, and Lovegood, have been amazing, too. It's definitely called 'The Legendary Student' for a reason, and I'm learning a lot.”

To some extent, this admiration was genuine. It's not easy to be a Graduator, or even a 4th class, in the twenties.

Of course, the world would react quite differently if it were known that Vikir had become a Swordmaster at the age of 18.

Meanwhile.

Dolores stared at Vikir.

“I don't know why you sound like you're making excuses.”

“...?”

“To hide your extraordinary nature and disguise it as ordinary.”

Dolores narrowed her eyes.

“The rest of the world is busy showing off their abilities, but you're so unusual, you're busy hiding what you have.”

“....”

“You don't want anyone to recognize you?”

“...I don't know what you're talking about.”

“You sound like a soldier.”

Dolores' words were heavy with curiosity about Vikir's origins and identity.

“You're quite skilled with a bow. I've seen you take out other kids in tournaments, though the numbers don't reflect it because most of your shots were from stray arrow.”

“I was just lucky.”

“...I guess it was. It was pretty dark in the jungle, and there aren't many archers in the world who can bounce off rocks and logs and still hit their mark. But luck is skill, too. You were the one who gave Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi stealthy backup cover shots, weren't you?”

“Yes, because they did a good job.”

“You mean the Baskerville triplets, right? They're the biggest stars of this tournament.”

Dolores turned and looked at Vikir.

“But why?”

“...?”

“Why do I think you're hiding behind the Baskerville triplets?”

Vikir's expression hardened for a moment.

“If you watch just one person with them, it's bound to look unusual....”

“No. You are special, otherwise there is no way you would catch my eye like that, anytime, anywhere.”

Dolores said strongly again.

“I see you everywhere I go these days, and there's no way you're an ordinary person.”

“....”

“Tell me, what are you hiding?”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

On his left wrist, the Baby Madam was looking at Vikir with a worried expression.

As if to say, 'Shall I remove it, Master?'

Vikir sighed, pressing down on his wrist.

He was about to open his mouth.

Dolores came closer to Vikir and whispered in a low voice.

“You. The crown prince, right?”

...?

Vikir was stunned for a moment.

What was he talking about?

When Vikir remained still, Dolores spoke once more.

“The current Emperor of the Empire has no children. They all died in accidents.”

“....”

“However, it is rumored that a single illegitimate child survives, and that this child has been admitted to the Colosseo Academy here.”

“....”

“Isn't that you?”

Vikir had heard the rumor, too.

But it was a rumor that had circulated before his regression and had never been proven to be true, so he had tuned it out.

Dolores, unaware of Vikir's thoughts, continued.

“The Emperor has the mystical power to foretell the future. If you are of his blood, you may possess similar abilities. If you are able to foresee future exams and events, it explains your current accomplishments....”

“Enough.”

Vikir interrupted Dolores' rambling.

Then, in a low voice, he proclaimed his innocence.

“I have nothing to do with the imperial family.”

“You lie.”

“I swear on my father's honor and before the almighty Rune.”

Dolores' gaze wavered at Vikir's firm words.

There was no way Dolores could say no to that.

Of course, Vikir didn't care about his father Hugo's honor, so he could hang it anywhere.

Dolores, meanwhile, seemed to wince at Vikir's response.

“Then open your heart, and let me know who you are!”

Dolores wanted to read Vikir's soul.

Most people kept the doors of their hearts open to some degree, but there are not many people who close and lock that door as tightly as Vikir did.

Of course, from Vikir's point of view, this was not an option.

Even if it didn't matter that Osiris had deposed all of Seth's minions from the House of Baskerville, revealing the identity of the Baskervilles would....

'Then the identity of the Night's Hound would be revealed.'

I didn't think I'd be able to hide forever.

It was still a bit early for the plan he had in mind.

'...It won't be long now.'

The Hound of Baskerville. The Night Hound. The moment his true identity is revealed, it will be catastrophic.

Vikir closed his eyes in silence.

Dolores watched him, her mouth open in unexplained impatience.

“Say something....”

Just then.

“...Open up! Open up!”

“...Give me the right!”

“...Freedom!”

The shouts came from the fence outside the inn where the students of the Colosseo Academy were staying.

A large group of people seemed to be protesting in unison.

“...?”

Dolores looked away for a moment, hoping to see something.

And there it was, a stunning sight.

The professors of the Colosseo were scrambling to keep the crowd at bay.

In fact, there was a huge crowd of people trying to get into the inn.

They were all carrying glow sticks and wearing red bands around their heads.

And at the front of the line is a face Dolores recognizes.

“...Merelini Lovegood?”

The Student Council President of Themiscyra Women's Academy.

And she's leading a group of students, all of them from the Themiscyra Women's Academy.

They've been fighting back against the professors of the Colosseo Academy.

“We will take our freedom!”

“Come on, everyone! Unite!”

“Humans unite for a noble cause, that's what makes us different from animals!”

They had become fighters for justice and were literally clashing with the professors.

Dolores gripped the terrace railing and listened more closely.

Themiscyra Women's Academy.

It was completely different from the school culture that pursues something archaic and static.

The sight of them running towards us with their hair down was like an angry beast.

“What's going on?”

Dolores shook her head as Vikir casually turned the conversation outward.

“It's...I can't hear very well.”

The sounds of so many people shouting overlapped each other and sounded like a muffled sound.

The words Dolores could make out were humanitarian values like “freedom,” “love,” “opportunity,” and “equality”.

“....”

Dolores had no choice but to use her holy power to open her ears.

Then, one by one, the noise that had been pouring in began to separate.

At the same time, their passionate emotions began to come through, like listening to a lamb's confession.

“Please allow us to join the Colosseo Academy's after-party!”

“There's no need for it! Just show us Vikir!”

“We want to congratulate Vikir too!”

“Colosseo Academy should open up the after party to students from other schools! Open it up!”

“Let's have an after school party, Vikir-nim!”

“They say joy is double when it's shared!”

“I fell in love with your sexy appearance on the Magic Train!”

“Big brother, I don't want to break up like this!”

“What do you mean, he's five years younger than us!”

“I don't know, all good-looking guys are big brothers!!!”

The students of Themiscyra Women's Academy seem to want to join the Colosseo Academy's party.

I don't know how long they've had this goal, but it's pretty blatant.

“....”

“Do you know what it says?”

“Huh? Uh....”

Dolores struggled to turn away, releasing her grip on the railing.

“It's....”

Dolores quickly stood up and replied.

“Oh, they say there's no hot water, I've got to go, it's getting late, you should go to bed!”

With that, she hurriedly ran off somewhere.

Chapter 250

Recap (3)

◆

The next day.

Vikir attended the announcement ceremony for the rankings of the first round.

It was a remarkable feat for the freshmen of Colosseo Academy to beat out the sophomores and seniors of other schools to make it into the top 30.

And six of them – Vikir, Sinclaire, Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro, and Granola – made it to the top 10.

Now, if the top 10 can successfully complete the second round of individual tasks, one per person, they will be rewarded with a rare artifact from a treasure trove jointly managed by the four schools.

The Talking Spear, the Time Stopping Hourglass, the Money Eating Hat, the Love Shield, the Sanity Orb, the Arrow with Eyeballs, and more... are all treasures of the century that could not be bought for a thousand gold coins, and they are all sleeping in the treasure trove, waiting for their owners.

The top ten Rankers who have completed their assigned tasks will be able to enter the treasure trove and choose an artifact, and they too must be chosen by the artifacts.

'But first, I have a quest to complete.'

Vikir thought as he walked to the stage of the awards ceremony.

Meanwhile, cheers erupted from below as the #7 ranked Vikir appeared.

“Aaaah- it's Vikir!”

“Brother, please take a look here!”

“I love you!”

The cheers came from the side of the Themiscyra Women's Academy.

There were no such cheers when Lovegood, the second-ranked student and student council president of Themiscyra, came out.

...But Lovegood didn't express any disappointment for Themiscyra students.

Because.

“Oh my God, Vikir-nim. To see you up close like this... I must be a saint.”

Because she's a self-described “successful nerd.”

Lovegood smiled, even though she was right next to Vikir on the podium.

The professor's speeches would soon be over, and then the students would be called up to the stage to receive their awards.

In the midst of all the excitement, Lovegood turned to Vikir.

“By the way, Vikir. I started a fan club for you yesterday.”

“?”

“The name of the fan club is 'Le'... aka Re.”

“??”

“Because... Vikir's hotness has passed the 'Do' mark and is about to hit the 'Mi' mark!”

“????”

Vikir was a little taken aback by this young lady's bravado.

But Lovegood looks at Vikir with love in her eyes, as if she's just dying to look at him.

The fact that her eyes were heart-shaped made it even more so.

Then a shout came from behind them. It was the female students of Themiscyra who started booing.

“Woo-woo- down with the president's monopoly!”

“We condemn the dictator!”

“Share Vikir!”

“Shouldn't the president prioritize the public interest over self-interest?”

“Pay the price, you old lady!”

“Impeach her, impeach her!”

Then Lovegood frowned arrogantly, looked back at her supporters(?), and spoke.

“Shut up, bitches, let me have some love. Don't you feel sorry for your sister?”

“Wooooooooo, you're the only one who can't get a relationship, it's hard for us too, we're a women's academy, if you're going to do this, make it a coeducational school!”

Lovegood's non-explanation only added fuel to the fire.

Eventually, Lovegood sighed and turned to Vikir.

“I... Vikir nim, do you think you'd like to dating after this league? With Colosseo and Themiscyra.”

Dating refers to selecting candidates from each university department and having them meet men and women, but this was not an area of ??interest for Vikir in the first place.

..., But it was apparently a topic of interest to everyone else but Vikir.

“I am Vikir's right-hand man!”

Tudor was the first to raise his hand.

“Then the left arm is me!”

And Sancho, too.

“And the left leg is me!”

Pigi raised his hand, too.

The other boys followed suit, crowding around Vikir.

“Vikir's right leg is me!”

“Then Vikir's left eye is me!”

“I'll be the right eye!”

“I'm the left ear!”

“Is there any right ear left?”

“I am Vikir's heart!”

“I am the stomach!”

“I am the lungs!”

“I am the spine!”

“I am Vikir's stomach!”

“I am the chest!”

“I am the waist!”

“Then I am the ass!”

“I can't tell you which part I am, but it's the most important part we can all agree on!”

Vikir was being dismantled and shattered in real time.

Then.

“Enough of that. After the professors' speeches, it's time for the awards ceremony. I have to go on stage, so I'll forbid any more disturbances.”

Dolores appeared and waved the crowd back.

As the students of Colosseo retreated, so did those of Themiscyra.

But?

Jjilis-

Lovegood was somehow casting a checking gaze towards Dolores.

Dolores, who had never been on bad terms with her, looked puzzled, then Lovegood spoke.

“I can give you the number one ranking in the University League, but I can't give you Vikir, so don't let your guard down just because you go to the same school.”

“...?”

Dolores shook her head, and Lovegood shouted.

“Don't be silly, I heard everything you said on the terrace yesterday!”

Dolores is at a loss for words.

Lovegood then recited a series of lines that Dolores had said to Vikir yesterday.

“You are special. Otherwise, there is no way you would catch my eye like that anytime, anywhere.”

“?”

“You're the only thing I see everywhere these days.”

“??”

“Open up to me!”

“????”

Dolores's face turns white. Did she really say those words yesterday?

'...I think I did.'

But I didn't mean it in that nuance. I think you're misunderstanding something....

Dolores turned quickly, and the eyes of the Colosseo students narrowed.

Dolores stammered, embarrassed.

“Oh, it's a misunderstanding. That's only a small part of the conversation, you have to look at the whole context, not just that line....”

However, timing didn't help her. Professor Banshee's stern voice came through.

“There, noisy winners, come forward.”

The professors finished their speeches and the awards ceremony began.

◆

The ten students with the highest scores in the University League this year came up to the podium.

1st place Dolores L. Quovadis, 2nd place Merelini Lovegood, 3rd place Bakilaga Juragio, 4th place Highbro Le Baskerville, 5th place Middlebro Le Baskerville, 6th place Lowbro Le Baskerville, 7th place Vikir, 8th place Sinclaire, 9th place Granola, and 10th place Hohenheim.

The deans were represented by Professor Banshee from Colosseo Academy, who had the highest ranking.

Despite the outstanding performance of Colosseo's students, Professor Banshee was not in a good mood for some reason.

“...Congratulations, and now it's time for individualized assignments.”

Professor Banshee's congratulatory speech was extremely dry and short.

But it was a good thing for the students.

Then, it was time to choose their assignments.

The apprenticeship system of the Seven Great Houses and Academy, trains talented individuals with the capabilities needed to enter the employment of this massive group.

The University League was an extension of this process.

Several scrolls were placed in front of the ten students.

They had to choose different tasks, and Vikir too reached for the scrolls in front of him.

'This brings us one step closer to the 7th Corpse Decarabia.'

Now all they had to do was go to the houses listed on the scrolls and fulfill the quests they were requested to do.

The ten students opened the scrolls.

Sinclaire, ranked eighth, chose House of Quovadis, as previously mentioned.

On the outside of the scroll, the name of the House and the difficulty level of the quest are listed to help students make their choice.

Three and a half stars of difficulty.

Upon opening the scroll, Sinclaire found a brief description of the task.

House of Faithful Quovadis / Difficulty [★★★☆]

The Empire is currently groaning under the weight of a growing number of heresies and cults.

Put yourself in the role of the Quovadis Inquisition and suggest ways to eradicate these cults and raise the prestige of the Rune Order.

Tasks related to the 'Inquisition' of the Quovadis family. There is a high possibility that Sinclaire will work under the Archbishop and Inquisitor Mozgus L. Quovadis.

Now all Sinclaire has to do is travel to the Quovadis household to fulfill the request.

“I knew this would come up.”

Sinclaire smiled, as if she had a good trick up her sleeve.

It seemed to be a very complicated plan, as Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, etc. were curious and asked questions, but she said it would be too long to answer in words.

Meanwhile. Dolores, the 1st ranked student, also picked up a scroll.

Four-star difficulty.

Dolores knew this was going to be a tough task even before she opened the scroll.

Tycoon Family / Difficulty [★★★★]

The Mint has recently issued high-denomination banknotes and has been suffering from the increasing number of counterfeit banknotes.

From the perspective of Bourgeois family, choose a product that would benefit from a currency reform and suggest a new product or an improvement to an existing product.

Count Bourgeois Damian is the director of the Imperial Mint.

It was a task that required the use of the head rather than the body.

In addition to that, everyone opened the scroll with the task written on it.

In the case of Highbro, the task was related to the national maritime domain of Donquixote, a spearman, called “Slaying a sea monster”.

The difficulty level was ★★★, an easy task that required slaughtering a large number of monsters.

Middlebro was given a rather brutal task of “Chase down escaped experimental monsters” by the extremely poisonous Leviathan family.

The difficulty was ★★★☆, which can be quite a challenge if you have poison resistance.

In Lowbro's case, the Imperial Guard was assigned the arduous task of helping the Usher family with their 'civil works to prevent the mansion from flooding'.

The difficulty was ★★☆, a somewhat easy but very time-consuming and tedious difficulty.

There were also several multiple tasks assigned by the imperial family, which were evenly distributed among everyone.

In the first place, the number of scrolls was more than 10, so everyone was able to choose the task they liked.

...But.

There was one incident that shocked everyone.

...Tud!

A hand rose above the dark red scroll.

Without hesitation, Vikir reached for the scroll in the farthest corner.

It was.

Iron-Blooded Swordsman / Difficulty [★★★★★]

Ironblooded Baskerville.

It was the worst House, the worst difficulty, the worst quest that everyone avoided.

Chapter 251

Five Stars (1)

◆

The quest of Ironblooded Swordman Baskerville.

Even without opening the scroll, everyone could guess. It would be against the fierce monsters of the Western Front.

What could a bunch of bloodthirsty, mad hounds be interested in other than getting blood on their teeth?

That was the world's perception.

But Vikir chose it nonetheless.

'I should go home.'

Vikir had work to do, after all, and he was on his way home.

For Vikir, who hates Baskerville, going home doesn't feel like a vacation.

However, it's worth noting how organized the Baskervilles have become.

Vikir's concern is how much of the demons agents will remain after the death of Andromalius, who was wearing the outer skin of Seth.

'It would be nice to solve the quest as well.'

It's Hugo's seal. Just ask for it.

Honestly, it was a task to be eaten raw.

◆

Vikir reassured all his worried friends that monster hunting was his specialty.

They were soon convinced, as Vikir had always gotten good grades in Introduction to Monsterology and had recently brought back a large quantity of gnoll pelts.

At dawn the next day, while everyone was still asleep, Vikir left the Magic Tower, keeping his route well hidden.

When the Academy's ranked players set out on their League Second Round assignments, they are often followed by reporters, paparazzi, headhunters from various guilds, and others with ill intentions.

Vikir carefully scanned his followers for the presence of any demon agent, and when he was satisfied that nothing was amiss, he began to make his way home.

Of course, Vikir's mastery of concealing his movements and covering his tracks prevented him from being followed.

Early morning filled with hazy fog.

When Vikir bought a train ticket back home.

“...!”

Vikir spotted a familiar face.

A girl with white hair, sitting still in the last seat of the train at the next platform, staring out the window.

It was Sinclaire.

Vikir was now standing on the platform opposite her.

'Going east?'

Vikir, who had disappeared behind the steel frame that was sticking out of the platform as the platform expansion work was not yet completed, slightly peeked his head out and looked at Sinclaire.

Sinclaire, unaware that Vikir was looking at her, was quietly gazing out the window at the gray dawn landscape.

She was on a train headed east. And there are few famous families in the East.

'I wonder if the assignment Sinclaire picked was for Quovadis?'

Certainly, her assignment was to discuss how to effectively eliminate cults and heresies from the perspective of Quovadis.

Sinclaire's current direction was a completely different one from Quovadis's in the west.

Only Sinclaire herself knows for what purpose she boarded the train to the East so early.

“....”

Vikir turned on his heel, not daring to pry into the secrets Sinclaire was hiding.

It was just the right amount of social distance.

◆

The image of Hugo that Vikir had seen in so long was quite different from what he remembered.

Hugo had always been a cold-blooded creature, with cold eyes, a stern face, and a sword always ready to slash.

But.

“Hehehehe-”

The sight of Hugo in front of him now was making Vikir quite confused.

Hugo had gained weight from whatever it was that he ate so well, and his mustache had grown back and was braided into a pretty little girl's braid.

At the end of his beard was a clumsily tied ribbon.

“It's been a long time, son.”

When Hugo saw Vikir, he spoke with a hint of sternness in his voice.

But it was short-lived.

“Do you see this? Pomeranian braided it for me. How could it be so beautifully knotted? Baskerville must have a prodigy like no other. Truly the gift of the Gods.”

Hugo grinned as he cradled the sleeping Pomeranian in his arms.

Vikir looked around wordlessly.

“....”

Hugo's office, which was originally a very shabby place, has also changed a lot.

The black stone floor had been replaced with soft, colorful puzzle mats.

It was designed to prevent the toddler from hurting herself if she fell, but also to allow her to sit and play puzzles from time to time.

The ceiling is decorated with celestial mobiles and glow-in-the-dark star stickers.

The pink curtains featured a scene from a trendy fairy tale in which a fairy princess wields a magic wand to beat a demon to death.

There was a large illustrated book with imperial language characters on the wall, and the swordsmanship textbooks and other books that filled the bookshelf had all been replaced with children's storybooks.

And the biggest change of all.

“Have you come, Master?”

It was Butler Barrymore, bringing tea.

He wore cow-patterned pajamas all over his body, had something resembling a snout in his nose, and held a rattle in his hand.

Of course, Pomeranian is not old enough to be amused by such things.

“I am providing all the things that should have been given to my granddaughter, who was unable to enjoy even the basic things among the barbarians.”

Hugo spoke with a stern expression, and Vikir could only nod with a shudder.

Indeed, the papers he was handling now looked like Baskerville's administrative work, but they were all related to Pomeranian.

.

-0May 0:00:00, Pomeranian looked at the decoration on the teacup during morning tea and said, “Ruby is beautifu”.

Urgent Action ? Break the alliance agreement with the Morgue family, and immediately march into Red Fang Mountain to steal the ruby ore.

-On August X, at XX:XX, Pomeranian uttered the phrase “Tiny Little Zowa” while eating the chocolate pudding served for dessert after the banquet.

?Urgent Action Item? Recapture the coffee bean fields beyond the 'Red Witch's River' from the barbarians, and build a logistical fort in the blood bean fields.

-#Month #Day ##Hour ##Minute, Pomeranian looked at the Monster Encyclopedia during eye-level learning and said, “Cute bear”.

?Urgent Action Item? Organize a detachment to attack Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain Seventh Ridge, killing and pelting as many Oxbears as possible in plain sight.

?Urgent correction 1? Reporting correction. It was assumed that Pomeranian only likes “living things”.

?Urgent Action Item 1? Organize a detachment to attack Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain Seventh Ridge, capturing as many Oxbears as possible in plain sight.

?Urgent correction 2? Report correction. It looks like Pomeranian only needs “a single live, small, young one”.

?Urgent Action 2? Organize a detachment and send it to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain Seventh Ridge to capture a newborn Oxbear.

However, due to the gravity of the matter, the size of the detachment should not be reduced.

?Urgent correction 3? Reporting correction. Pomeranian said, 'If a bear cub comes here, the mother bear will be sad, so I'll just put up with it as a teddy bear!'

?Urgent Action Item 3? No matter what I think, my granddaughter is too nice and cute.

– This report is an official record of the House of Baskerville and a military secret of the first class, and unauthorized viewing is punishable by death.

Head of House Hugo Le Baskerville ?

Vikir glanced at the contents of the papers and turned away.

'...What have I just seen?'

It was the seal of the Head of House. At least within the Baskervilles, that seal was like the emperor's seal.

I still remember the countless sleepless nights I spent on guard duty and fighting off enemies to protect the documents that bore that seal.

But I can't believe that's what those sealed documents say....

Jeez.

Vikir couldn't help but shake his head.

Then.

Vikir suddenly felt Hugo's eyes on him.

'Oops!'

To say the least, he'd let his guard down.

No matter how foolish Hugo looked now, he was still the Swordmaster, the Swordsman of the Empire, the Lord of House Baskerville, and the King of All Dogs.

Vikir tensed once more and waited for Hugo to speak.

Finally, after looking at Vikir thoughtfully, Hugo spoke.

“Yes. It's time to give the student from the Academy a task in Baskerville.”

Five-star difficulty, worst quest ever.

It was to fulfill a special assignment from Baskerville.

Apparently, Hugo wasn't going to let Vikir off the hook for being his son.

'Monster hunting? Factor assassination? Pioneering the frontier?'

Vikir didn't know what his quest would be, but he knew it wouldn't be easy.

Finally, Hugo spoke up.

“I have a task for you. It is... 'Parenting'.”

Vikir doubted his ears.

“...Parenting?”

“Yes. Parenting.”

“Parenting (肉牙). You mean meaty fangs? What kind of teeth are those....”

“What are you talking about? Ew. Parenting. Caring for a child.”

Hugo clicked his tongue and glanced at the swaddling bag in front of him.

The sleeping Pomeranian began to whimper.

Hugo looked worried about the world.

“I'm worried about how sullen she's been lately. She doesn't smile at all. In the past, if I showed her my braided beard, she'd just giggle and giggle and giggle.”

“....”

“I've called in all the doctors in the West, and they're all saying there's nothing wrong with her, what a bunch of quacks. If my granddaughter isn't smiling, what's wrong with her now? I was about to strangle them all, but Butler Barrymore stopped me. Can you make her laugh?”

Hearing Hugo's words, Vikir's mind flashed back to the cover of the assignment scroll.

The Iron Blood Swordsman / Difficulty [★★★★★]

Is this really a five-star difficulty? Was parenting really this hard?

Vikir sighed and stepped forward.

At that moment, the exquisite Pomeranian opened her eyes.

“Ugh! Samchun! Samchun!”

“...Not Samchun, Uncle.”

When Vikir held out his hand, Pomeranian opened her arms wide. And....

“Oooh! She smiles! My granddaughter smiles!”

Hugo began to smile as well. Because as soon as Pomeranian saw Vikir, she started laughing.

At the same time.

...Bang!

Behind him, Butler Barrymore in the cow pajamas nodded happily and stamped Hugo's seal on the task scroll with a bang.

Confirmation that all tasks had been completed.

A five-star task that no one else in the Academy had ever dared to attempt, cleared in an instant.

Chapter 252

Five Stars (2)

◆

The quest for five stars had come to an unfortunate end.

'I thought it would be easy, but I never thought it would be this easy....'

Vikir was just about to turn away in disbelief when Hugo stopped him.

“Hey. Son, since you've been home for so long, why don't you get yourself a 'promotion'?”

One of Vikir's eyebrows twitched as Hugo spoke soothingly to the Pomeranian.

“Promotion. Literally, an increase in rank within the House.”

“From now on, I will appoint you as a 'Senator'.”

It was Hugo, making such a huge statement seem so casual.

“....”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

What is a Senator?

Beneath the Senate and above the House of Representatives, the backbone of power, capable of carrying countless hounds.

Unlike the House of Representatives, who are primarily responsible for the affairs of the House, Senators are also responsible for affairs outside of the House, and are granted enormous power to fulfill their duties.

In fact, a senator's only consolation is his or her family name.

Of course, in reality, it's also the seventh counts and the senate, so considering that the throne of power and the Seven Counts, which is the fifth position in the Baskerville family's hierarchy, are also in the same senatorial rank, and the Senator is an honorary position for those who have retired from active service, the senators can be said to be the highest power in the family.

“Probably, even if you look back at the family's history for about a hundred years, you're the youngest senator.”

“Thank you. I'll do my best.”

At Hugo's words, Vikir nodded silently.

Hugo might have been a little silly after Pomeranian showed up, but he was still a determined man.

Hugo had promoted Vikir to Senator, but he had also thought about his future duties.

“You're a senator, but for the time being, you're free to roam as you are now. Your title is still 'Provincial Correspondent'.”

Currently, Vikir was known within Baskerville as a 'special agent' rather than an 'academy student'.

Unlike the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, who were actually traveling to the Imperial Family to study, Vikir was tasked with identifying and secretly assassinating forces hostile to the Baskervilles in the Imperial Family.

The 'student at the Colosseo Academy' status is merely one of the agent's cover stories.

Hugo continued.

“I will extend your assignment for as long as you wish. However, if you feel your work is done, return to your family and assume your duties. The position of Magistrate of Underdog City is still vacant.”

“Yes.”

And so, at the age of 18, Vikir officially became a Senator, a member of the House.

As the backbone of power, the Senator enjoys a number of privileges.

For starters, he could appoint eight aides at his discretion, without reporting.

Once appointed, an aide is officially recognized as a member of the House of Baskerville and can take the Baskerville surname. Of course, it is not impossible to have more than eight aides, but they must report to and receive permission from the House.

Aides can be taught up to four levels of Baskerville-style swordsmanship and are provided with all medical, ceremonial, and state accommodations.

They receive a generous salary, a vehicle, all transportation expenses paid, tax exemption, selection of knights and a host of other privileges, including the ability to view imperial military secrets of the second level and above, and the right to recruit civilians for wartime service.

They can also command their own conscripted or demobilized troops, which means they can form their own armed forces.

Now that Vikir is a senator, he can form his own task force (TF).

Of course, he already has a few people lined up.

'I'll start by recruiting Cindywendy, Chihuahua, and MiniPin....'

The addition of the economically savvy Cindywendy, the administrative master Chihuahua, and MiniPin, a master of terrain and monster ecology, as well as a bit of brute force, would be a great addition to the team.

'And there's plenty of talent among the natives of Jungle.'

The first thing that came to mind was Aiyen's face.

Her archery skills, shooting mosquitoes from hundreds of feet away.

There are many other warriors and shamans in the jungle that would shock the empire.

Vikir closed his eyes and pictured the events in his mind far into the future.

'First, Cindywendy, I'll need her help soon.'

Vikir had always refused her help when it came to money, but Vikir knew that the time would come when he would need her funds.

It was the intuition of a veteran hunter.

Then Hugo broke Vikir's reverie.

“So. Have you made any progress in the Imperial Capital?”

Vikir gave Hugo the answer he'd been expecting.

“As I reported. In the last quarter, I've eliminated a total of 174 people, over the course of three quarters: the customs faction that falsely reported to the Emperor that the Baskervilles were plotting a birthmark, the Outer House faction that tried to dry up the Baskervilles' money stream through embezzlement and tax evasion, and key figures in the Intelligence Guild that tried to steal military secrets from the Baskervilles. All of them were either killed by old age, accidental death, assassination by other hostile forces, or disappearance, and of course, there were no trails.”

Of course, those 174 people were all in league with the demons.

Vikir hadn't laid a finger on those who weren't in league with the demons, but simply antagonized the Baskervilles.

Still, it was an accomplishment.

Hugo smiled wryly and nodded. Then he added an odd note at the end.

“Other than that.”

“?”

“You're at the Academy, aren't you?”

Hugo's subtle gaze lingered on Vikir.

“Do you have a girlfriend within the academy?”

“??”

“I've seen other families' sons go to the Academy and have relationships. That's why it's called CC.”

“????”

Vikir frowned slightly.

But Hugo only chuckled.

“I think Osiris has a woman he's seeing, but he never seems to get his tail between his legs, and when I ask, he never answers. That's why I wonder when I will see my grandchildren.”

“....”

“You should do the same. Marrying early is the answer.”

Vikir felt the hairs on his neck stand up because this side of Hugo was so unfamiliar.

It was so different from what he remembered from his previous life that it felt foreign.

So Vikir quickly changed the subject.

“ ... By the way. What happened to my request?”

“Hmm. Washing the past.”

Hugo stroked his neatly braided beard.

Vikir had once asked Hugo to erase his past before he left for the Academy.

He had asked Hugo to erase any trace of Vikir's existence as a hound of the Baskervilles, such as the statue at Red Fang Castle.

“Even so, the rumors of your return were under tight control. From what I've seen of public opinion, the 'survival and return of Vikir Van Baskerville' is being treated as a hoax created by the Baskervilles for the sake of bluffing.”

Vikir nodded at Hugo's words.

Many of the Baskervilles' hounds come and go in the blink of an eye.

So many are born, so many die.

Of course, with the arrival of Vikir and the change in Hugo's personality, such drastic changes no longer occur, but Vikir is still mentioned in passing in that brief moment of change.

Commendations received from the imperial family were also distributed in hundreds or thousands of pieces a year, and weren't awards originally remembered only by the person who received them and quickly forgotten by others?

Though the people of Underdog City still miss and honor Vikir, it doesn't bother him much.

“...I suppose my past has been wiped clean, at least for now.”

“It is. We have special agents working on it now, so you don't have to worry about being unmasked by rumors anymore. Well, some of the loudmouths have already been eliminated.”

Hugo left it up to Vikir's discretion as to whether or not to continue to conceal the Baskervilles' identity, and when to reveal it.

It seemed to be a fitting end to his promotion to Senator.

“Samchun!”

...If it weren't for Pomeranian who had suddenly burst into the conversation.

“I'm going to take this!”

Vikir looked down at Pomeranian's hands, searching for something.

Pomeranian was holding a small book.

.

Pomeranian flipped through the pages and opened to a chapter.

It was an old myth, one that no one believed anymore, one that had been lost to history.

A book about the life of 'Morgue Tzersi', one of the distant ancestors of the House of Morgue.

Pomeranian showed Vikir one of the illustrations in the section.

It depicted a blackened, dead tree.

'Wraith Tree', a legendary artifact that black mages could only dream of.

It was about a strange tree that was planted by Tzersi, a master of magic.

“Close creeper!”

Pomeranian looked up at Vikir, his eyes glowing.

Feeling uneasy, Vikir turned his head slightly, and there was Hugo, his eyes shining.

“I don't know what it is, but bring it to me, son.”

“....”

“I wish I could go myself, but I am currently engaged in a nerve war with Morgue and cannot leave.”

Currently, the Morgue is busy due to the change in the leadership of the Dark Hall.

For the Baskervilles, it was an opportunity to capitalize on the chaos and expand their power.

Hugo threw something at Vikir.

...POP!

It was the Black Whistle, a terrifying object that could command the entirety of Baskerville's military power.

Vikir was taken aback by the unexpectedness of the situation, but Hugo was serious.

“I'll give you the entire Knights Order if you need it. Go and get what Pomeranian wants. Ah, I guess that can replace the scroll quest.”

Vikir sighed softly.

Does Hugo even know what this is and want me to bring it?

'The Wraith Tree is a real artifact.'

And even Vikir knew where it was located, thanks to his pre-regression memories.

'It's surprisingly close to the Baskerville estate, and it's a place I've been meaning to visit anyway, because....'

Vikir is practicing the 7th Baskerville Teeth.

The hint of the next level was there.

So it's a place I've been meaning to visit during my visits home.

'The level next to the Sword Master. And where the clues to the Baskerville Form 8 lie.'

I was going to investigate anyway, and now that I've taken over House Baskerville's military power, it's only fair.

I've already solved the quest for the scroll, and now all that's left to do is to meet with Decarabia the 7th Corpse, but it would be nice to have a clue about the 8th Form before then.

After all, Pomeranian is a pot belly.

“Then I'll be on my way.”

Vikir patted Pomeranian on the head and turned away.

Quick Victory

I planned to finish everything in three days and return to the academy.

Chapter 256

The Grave of Swords (4)

◆

“Find out for yourself.”

Vikir pulled his full strength of his body.

His magic sword, Beelzebub, extended out, and a rapidly rotating aura blazed across its surface.

A solid materialized aura in thin air, the symbol of the Swordmaster.

[...!]

Cane Corso's eyes widened slightly.

In the darkness of the void, a single, dying flame burned.

The firewood must be a curiosity.

Then, from his iron throne, Cane Corso stood up.

As he stood, the already stifling atmosphere in the grave of swords seemed to grow even more suffocating.

Cane Corso's lips parted.

[Kid, you don't have a very good personality. Who is your father....]

“Question and Answer Dance.”

Vikir drew upon the Swordmaster's aura and the wraiths of the monsters.

...Ssssssshhh!

Baskerville 4th, Vikir's most confident move in his two lives, was unleashed.

Though Vikir is now capable of producing up to 7th form, there is nothing quite like the 4th form for mindless swordplay.

It requires very little mana and has a physical proficiency of over 100%, so it can be said to be a cost-effective regular strike.

[...Hoah. This level of proficiency, and you still look so young].

Cane Corso avoided all of Vikir's attacks by simply tilting his head back slightly.

[Clearly a Baskerville, and whose descendant are you? Boston Terrier? Great Dane? No, you look very different. Is that Hugo, the boy?]

And of course, Cane Corso also performed the Baskerville 4th form.

Clang!

Space is shattered.

Vikir's Crimson aura and Cane Corso's Black aura tangled and clashed ferociously.

Clang! Claang! Drrrrrrzzz!

The atmosphere was shattering into pieces.

Shattered fragments of air rushed out in all directions, creating a sword wind.

Through clenched teeth, Vikir continued to swing Beelzebub.

Cane Corso's eyes widened once more as he watched Beelzebub emit a crimson glow from Vikir's wrist.

[Is this the magic sword Beelzebub that was actually used... In the past, even the brilliant twins Cain and Abel spent three years searching for it and never managed to get their hands on it. Boy, how do you possess it?]

But Vikir did not answer.

...Boom!

That's because before Cane Corso's sword could reach his throat, the black mask Vikir had tied around his neck was pulled off.

/ Mask

-Kinship (Fratricide) +0

-Insight (Human-Beast) -On

Vikir transformed into a black dog in an instant, using his smaller body to dodge Cane Corso's sword.

At the same time, Vikir leapt between Cane Corso's legs, removing his mask and returning to his human form to swing his sword.

[... What?]

Cane Corso could only stare in disbelief as Vikir's method defied common sense.

Dogfight. Complete raw combat. No human dignity expected or given to the opponent. It's like fighting with a monster.

[Hehehe, it's been a while since I've had a fight like this].

However, surprisingly, Cane Corso didn't seem to mind this kind of battle.

...Thud!

The sword aura flew towards his groin, but Cane Corso blocked it with the hilt of his greatsword, knocking Vikir away from him.

“I'd be grateful for the distance.”

Even as he was being thrown, Vikir reached out and retrieved the black cloak that had been hanging on the wall.

There, the Black Bow Anubis bared its teeth.

Psssttt!

The terrifying arrow rushed toward Cane Corso in five trajectories.

[...Is it archery this time? I've never seen a Swordmaster so good at Archery before].

Cane Corso treated Ballak's archery as just a trivial skill.

Tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk!

His black aura formed a round sphere, crushing all the arrows flying from all directions.

At the same time.

Swash!

Cane Corso charged forward with a tremendous leap and swung his greatsword.

However, he was forced to pause in midair.

[...?]

Invisible threads wrapped around Cane Corso's body in countless directions.

Hack, hack, hack.

Vikir could see the cub perched on his shoulder, a look of triumph on it's face.

“Well done.”

Vikir patted the cub once, then leapt off to reach Cane Corso.

An opening, this opening would be his only chance to take down the great man of the previous generation.

'If I can defeat him, I may have the answer to reaching the next level.'

And a chance to get my hands on the Wraith Tree, too.

Blast!

The full power of Baskerville 7th was revealed.

Cane Corso's eyes widened as he saw the seven teeth clearly revealed before him.

[Baskerville's Seventh Form!! And the 'Lurking Ambush' swordsmanship!! How can I be so ignorant...!?]

Surprisingly, Cane Corso recognized Vikir's swordsmanship.

This was something Vikir had never expected.

How could this old man know the secret of the Baskervilles, a secret that not even Hugo knew because the original swordsmanship manuals had been destroyed?

But the question was never answered.

The gap created by the Picaresque Mask, Ballak's archery, and Baby Madam's wire trap combination was not to be missed by Vikir.

Creak, creak, creak, creak, creak, creak, creak!

The seven teeth that could defeat even the demon king, ravaged the Cane Corso's entire body.

'Gotcha.'

For a moment, Vikir felt a sense of futility at the victory he had achieved so easily.

...But only for a moment.

“...!”

Vikir flinched for a moment due to the strange sensation of touching the tip of his teeth.

Then, as the fragments of aura, wind, and water vapor cleared, Vikir could see what was in front of him.

Surprisingly, Cane Corso was unharmed.

All seven of Vikir's strikes had been blocked by the heavy, thick armor of unknown material that Cane Corso wore.

At the same time.

...Boom!

Cane Corso's huge hand grabbed Vikir's throat and tightened.

Black gauntlets wrapped around his fingers were made of an unknown material just like the Grave of Swords.

Vikir tried to cut off Cane Corso's arm, but was repeatedly blocked by the thick, hard armor.

Who would have thought there was something in the world that the Swordmaster's aura couldn't cut!

Cane Corso looked down at Vikir in wonder.

[Rising to the realm of Supreme at such a young age, I'm surprised. There's a genius in the family].

“....”

Vikir frowned.

Whatever the armor Cane Corso wears is made of, it is indestructible, no matter how hard he tries.

It wraps around his entire body from the neck down, and there's nothing Vikir can do about it.

And then. Cane Corso said.

[But even in the realm of Supreme, there are classes].

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened.

Originally, when someone reach this level, even a passing word from a higher being can give you a great deal of inspiration.

In Cane Corso's mutterings, Vikir got the hint he'd been waiting for. Her recklessness had paid off.

...If there's one problem, it's that I might die right now?

With that, Cane Corso slammed Vikir to the ground.

Swahh, jijijijig-

Vikir twisted his body in midair and landed on his hands and feet.

Although the skin on his palms was completely ripped off while he was being pushed back, at least he was able to keep his neck and spine from snapping.

Cane Corso spoke nonchalantly.

[Just as the Expert and Graduator are divided into upper, middle, and lower boundaries for convenience, so are the Swordmasters].

“...!”

[You're just a chick who's just stepped into the realm of the Supreme].

Cane Corso smiled faintly.

[I can see what you're thinking, yes. I thought the same thing as you when I first entered this tower. Of course, I was much older than you then].

Afterward, he added softly.

[Maybe... just maybe, it's possible for you, at your age, to see the last page of 'that book of swordsmanship'....]

“?”

Vikir frowned at the word he didn't recognize.

Then Cane Corso laughed. Bright enough to make me feel sick.

[Good, then I'll show you. It's the least I can do for the man who will be the next Tower Lord].

At the same time, he muttered something unintelligible.

...Rumbling! Blug blug blug-.

A black aura began to boil from his entire body.

“...!”

For a moment, Vikir had to fall from the chilling aura that enveloped his entire body.

Drrrrrrr...

The entire Grave of Swords was shaking.

At the same time, the instincts of a veteran screamed frantically at him to get the hell out of here!

Grrrrrk...

In an instant, Cane Corso's massive greatsword rose into the air, and then.

...BOOM!

It fell straight toward the ground.

A stream of black lightning.

The single, simple movement soon split into several trajectories, rushing toward Vikir.

And Vikir watched.

“ ...9th-form!?”

'Lurking Ambush', the Ultimate of the Baskervilles that he thought he was the only one mastering.

It was a nine-toothed blade, tearing the world apart.

Chapter 257

The Grave of Swords (5)

◆

The 'Lurking Ambush', the ultimate in Baskerville's swordsmanship.

It depicts nine teeth. What does this mean?

It's Baskerville's old style.

If there is such a division in the Swordmaster, just as there is a division in the Expert and Graduator... then this is a swordsmanship that can only be cast by beings of the Swordmaster rank.

Nine teeth, each driving, grasping, tearing, cutting, slicing, dismembering, crushing, mincing, and crushing, devouring the entire world.

It was greater and more destructive than any swordsmanship in the world.

It seemed impossible for the 'predator's murderous intent' to cut beneath the skin more vividly than this.

Even Vikir, a veteran of the Age of Destruction, had never experienced it before.

'There is a being in this world who can wield a sword like this, even among humans!'

Vikir marveled as a swordsman, a seeker walking the same path.

It was something that exploded purely, regardless of the distinction between blood and blood.

But I can't just sit back and admire.

Even now, Cane Corso's 9th Baskerville was rushing toward him, slicing through seconds and minutes.

In the midst of this impending storm of swords, Vikir unleashed the most power he could muster.

Baskerville 7th Form.

After abandoning emotions and ascending to the 6th form, he reached the highest level with his regained emotions after going through many struggles.

Vikir flicked the tip of his sword to form 7 teeth, which he used against the 9 teeth in front of him.

The Hound of the Iron Blood Sword Family faced the monster with all its might.

The result.

...Swashh, jjjeeezzzzzzzz!

Vikir was defeated.

Not surprising, since it was the 7th vs. the 9th.

Vikir felt his entire body being torn apart.

The pain felt as if a piece of meat had been dropped into the mouth of a huge toothy monster.

It was a level of damage that even the regenerative powers of a bog salamander could not have withstood.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir grabbed at something on the brink of death.

It was a survival instinct, a sense of urgency he hadn't felt since entering the Realm of the Supreme.

It is no wonder that a Swordmaster never has the opportunity to feel this way, to be helpless in the face of great horror and brutality.

And paradoxically, when he realized he was nothing, a mere insignificant fly.

...Flash!

A change occurred in Vikir's swordsmanship.

The 8th Form of Baskerville, the desperate need to survive, the desire for life, and the need for extreme combat experience.

Only when one has lost and regained his emotions becomes attached to life, the door to the 8th Form opens.

Vikir swung his sword and drew the 8th tooth.

It was the 8th tooth, still small, but clear and distinct.

At the same time, the 9th and 8th teeth clashed and canceled each other out.

And then.

...Poof!

Cane Corso's long fangs dug diagonally into Vikir's body.

Quack!

Vikir was thrown helplessly to the ground and buried on the edge of the Grave of Swords.

[....]

Cane Corso. Swordmaster Advanced. No, Superlative. An absolute in the 9th form of Baskerville.

He stood still, staring into the rising dirt.

And then, in the darkness of Cane Corso's eye sockets, there was a flash of color again.

Thump, thump, thump.

Vikir was walking out from below, where crumbling aura, sparks, and sword fragments were falling like snow.

Zzzzzzzzzz.

The deep, almost amputating sword wound that ran diagonally across Vikir's body was healing at an astonishing rate.

A regenerative power that surpassed humans long ago.

It was a regenerative power that could not be matched by even the most powerful of monsters whose specialty was regeneration.

[...Basilisk].

Cane Corso recognized Vikir's ability with a glance.

Vikir stopped in his tracks.

/ Awl

-1 Slot: Venomous -Madam Eight-Legs (S)

-2 Slot: Unkillable -Basilisk (S)

-3 Slot: Silence Hill -Mushuhushu (A+)

“I was lucky to find the body of a basilisk before I entered the Grave of Swords.”

Vikir had absorbed the mummified remains of a basilisk, which had been pickled in salt, and had learned to use its regenerative powers as his own.

He was indeed lucky. The regenerative powers of a bog salamander would not have been enough to survive Cane Corso's strike.

Anyway.

Thanks to the power of the magic sword Beelzebub, Vikir escaped death.

And in return, he was able to reach the higher realms.

It is at the threshold of death that one realizes the depths of the 8th Forms.

Those who become Swordmasters rarely have to fight for their lives, and this is where the stagnation occurs.

[Only those who, upon entering the realm of the Supreme, continue to fight with the same heart as when they first took up the sword will gain something].

Cane Corso's words were the most basic, the closest to the truth.

Meanwhile, Vikir lifted his head and looked at Cane Corso.

“The Lurking Ambush Swordsmanship. Was it you who wrote that sword book?”

[No. That would be impossible. I, too, have not yet mastered the entirety of the ten formulas in that book].

“Then....”

As Vikir trailed off, the Cane Corso nodded obediently.

[I am, too, a descendant who read the Book of Swordsmanship. However, I was afraid that someone other than me would learn this, so I tore a few pages and scattered them.]

“Wouldn't it have been better to just burn it and get rid of it?”

[I could not bring myself to destroy the Swordsmanship Book itself; how dare I destroy such a great treasure with my own hands].

Vikir did not bother to tell Kainkorso that he had burned the sword book.

On the other hand, Cane Corso was intrigued that a descendant had managed to get his hands on a complete copy of the Lurking Ambush.

[...Somehow those who are destined to meet must meet].

Cane Corso sheathed his greatsword. It meant that he would not attack Vikir anymore.

At the same time, the heavy weight that had been weighing down on them vanished.

Vikir had no intention of fighting anymore.

He had just come back from the brink of death and had just reached the 8th Form.

His opponent, on the other hand, had already reached the 9th Form long ago. If he tried to fight him, he would be no match.

Then Cane Corso said.

[My young rival and relative, my cute nephew. Come here and take what you want.]

His attitude was different than before.

Vikir looked puzzled and asked.

“May I take the Wraith Tree behind that iron throne?”

[Do as you please, it's just a weed to me, such things are only for mages].

“Aren't you here to protect it?”

[Of course not. I'm here for a completely different reason. These grass roots are, well, ancestral creatures that took root in this tower before me, so I just respect them and have no particular attachment to them.]

Vikir shook his head.

Then, two roots from the Wraith Tree behind the Iron Throne were placed in Vikir's hands.

It was an eerie sapling that was dry and hard, yet somehow cold and damp.

“....”

Vikir turned his head.

Cane Corso had been sitting in the iron throne again for some time.

But its curious eyes were still fixed on Vikir.

Vikir stared at Cane Corso.

6th Form. A level that can be reached only by letting go of emotions.

7th Form. A level that can be reached only by regaining emotions.

8th Form, a level that can only be ascended by attachment to life and harsh combat experience.

In fact, the Eighth Form could be said to be a difficult stage to experience without the guidance of a senior in the upper level of the Supreme Realm.

Or it takes a lot of hard work.

...So where does that make the old man level?

As Vikir was thinking to himself, Cane Corso said.

[Wondering about the 9th form?]

It was the answer.

“....”

Vikir's silent affirmation made Cane Corso smile faintly.

[You will probably never reach this level in your lifetime].

Vikir raised an eyebrow at the words as if they were a taunt.

But Cane Corso continued in a serious tone.

[Because the realm of the Nine Forms is beyond the threshold of death].

That means that one can only step into the realm of the 9th Form by actually being dead.

...But what does that mean for the Cane Corso in front of him?

Hasn't he definitely reached the level of the 9th Form?

Seeing Vikir's puzzled expression, Cane Corso released his greatsword and raised his both hands.

Tzutzutzutz...

With that, a black aura boiled up.

...Teng! Teng!

The heavy iron gloves wrapped around Cane Corso's hands fell to the ground.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened.

Cane Corso's hands were dried up to nothing but bone and skin.

Like the hand of a corpse.

[So I crossed the threshold of death and entered into it.]

As a result, Cane Corso died. Alone and lonely in a remote place where no one else in the world knew him.

But he never regretted it, even to his last breath.

Because in exchange for that lonely death, he came closer to the core of the Supreme, a place no human had reached in centuries.

A noble knight who had risen to the rank of Superhuman died and was transformed.

Death Knight.

That was the identity of Cane Corso.

Chapter 260

The Inverted Pentagram (2)

◆

...Puck, Dzzzzzzzzzz-!

The barrier was tearing apart.

A face slowly appeared through the cracks.

“Sorry, sir. I'm a little late.”

It was Vikir, still looking nonchalant.

....

But the crowd is silent.

Everyone just stands there, mouths agape.

“Ah, the artifact I brought. Should I report it here?”

Vikir holds up the artifact with a nonchalant expression.

It was an ominous artifact, a small necklace in the shape of an inverted pentagram, with a closed eyeball attached to its center.

“The name and power of this artifact is....”

Vikir was just about to explain something.

“Woah!”

A person ran into Vikir's arms.

Her face covered in tears and snot. It was Sinclaire.

“...?”

Vikir shook his head.

“Vikir, you asshole!”

A rough tackle followed.

Tudor, looking upset, hugged Vikir's side tightly.

Sancho and Pigi rushed over, and Bianca was standing behind him with her arms crossed.

“Vikir! What's going on!”

“I was worried you wouldn't make it!”

“I know, he's so sneaky.”

Behind him, the three brothers, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, stood in an uneasy manner.

Because of the attention of those around him, they couldn't come and talk to him, and they just seemed to be anxious from a distance away.

At that time.

Dolores walked up to Vikir.

“....”

“....”

The two made eye contact and said nothing.

Dolores didn't say much. Only.

“Don't let me worry.”

The president's words were brief.

Then.

Professor Banshee stepped forward and put an end to all the confusion.

“Vikir-kun.”

“Yes.”

“ ...How did you get out?”

Professor Banshee returned to his stern demeanor.

“This gate, as everyone knows, can only be opened and closed by four keys. There is only one way to forcibly tear it open, and that is from the inside, not the outside, with the full force of a Swordmaster or seventh-class mage or higher.”

“....”

“Which is why I can't help but ask, how did you tear the barrier?”

Representatives of Varangian, Themiscyra, and Magic Tower came to Professor Banshee's side.

They, too, were curious.

“This is the first time I've seen this barrier torn since I became vice director of the Varangian.”

“Do you think I can tear it apart? Maybe it would be possible if we put all our effort into it from inside the barrier?”

“Hehehe-but not for a single student.”

Students from the other schools were also curious to see how Vikir had gotten out of the warehouse.

Many eyes were on Vikir.

Vikir replied in a nonchalant tone.

“I was lucky, It just so happened that this artifact was used to tear apart the barrier.”

With that, Vikir lifted the necklace from around his neck.

The red inverted pentagram remained silent as if it would never move unless it was Vikir's will.

Professor Banshee and the other school deans shook their heads.

“That must be the thing that was in the far corner of the... warehouse, but wasn't that a shelf?”

“That's right, that's a shelf, the one we used to put the artifacts on!”

“Why is that thing so small?”

Vikir came out carrying not an artifact, but a shelf where the artifact was stored.

And for some reason, the shelf was reduced to the size of a necklace.

Professor Banshee swallowed hard.

“Is it. Well, since it was in a warehouse storing artifacts, the shelf must not have been an ordinary item. You're very good at recognizing it.”

“Thank you.”

“So, its purpose was to tear apart the barrier?”

“Yes.”

“Can you show the effect? It's because it's an artifact that hasn't been registered in the warehouse.”

“I'm afraid that's not possible. I've already used the ability once, and I don't know when I'll be able to use it again, maybe never.”

Many of the artifacts in the warehouse were either single-use or had very long cooldowns.

That's why Professor Banshee and the deans couldn't do much more research on Vikir's artifact.

To the naked eye or touch, it's just a normal, solid mineral.

The same was true when mana was poured into it.

The other mages, who had been examining it for some time, had all come to the same conclusion.

“It is now worthless.”

In the end, the mysterious artifact was recorded only by Vikir's testimony.

It was a single-use artifact, intended simply to tear apart barriers.

◆

24 hours ago.

Vikir stepped across the barrier and into the warehouse.

The other nine students had spread out, each answering the call of the artifacts that called to each of them.

“....”

Vikir looked around in silence.

A space lined with large stone pillars. Divided into sections, it resembled a deserted warehouse.

The floor was scattered with artifacts.

Rings, necklaces, staffs, swords, shields, helmets, shoes, and more....

Each and every one of them is a piece of artifact with immature magical energy.

And there were a few artifacts on a large shelf in the very back that were especially powerful.

There were swords that emitted a fierce energy, armor that emitted a black aura, and other rings and necklaces that emitted blue and green light.

Perhaps some of the higher-ranking artifacts with particularly strong energies were kept on separate shelves.

Most of the students picked up the artifacts on the floor, focusing on those that emitted beams of light toward them.

When all the students were out of the warehouse, Vikir was the only one left.

'All gone.'

Vikir turned to see that he was alone in the warehouse.

Numerous artifacts were emitting rays of love toward Vikir.

“....”

Vikir stared at the artifacts that had chosen him.

A pair of shoes that allowed him to walk at a fast pace, glasses that allowed him to see very far, a flute that could put everything around him to sleep when blown, an ember that could extinguish all fires, an ember that could evaporate all water, a mirror that showed him his future mate, a ring that could take his life and the life of the other person at the same time....

Each and every one of them is a very useful item.

However, none of them caught Vikir's eye.

The only thing he seemed to be thinking about was waiting for everyone else to leave.

Thud, thud, thud, thud, thud.

Vikir stepped forward, paying no attention to the many treasures.

There were special Artifact in the room that radiated unusually strong magic.

Artifact that even wouldn't choose the top ranked student, such as Dolores, Bakilaga, Hohenheim, and Lovegood.

All of it were shining their light of courtship on Vikir.

But.

Vikir hadn't touched any of them.

Only.

Whirrrrr-.

He grabbed the shelf where the artifacts rested and threw them all to the ground.

Then, Vikir looked down at the large, empty shelf.

“Finally, I found it. The Seventh Corpse, Decarabia.”

The shelf that held the artifact. A red, inverted pentagram that no one had noticed.

But Vikir knew from experience in the future.

This shelf was the true reason for the warehouse's existence, and the rest of the artifacts were just a trick of the eye.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsu...

Vikir gripped the shelf tightly and channeled his mana into it.

Unlike the other Artifact, the shelf showed no reaction even when touched by Vikir's mana.

Except.

Swoosh-

Vikir felt an enormous amount of mana leave his body.

Waves of mana that ebbed and flowed like a tide.

This strange shelf was now sucking up Vikir's mana like a lump of water in a drought.

“Indeed. There must be a reason why so many Artifacts are being suppressed.”

Vikir tightened his grip on the shelf and looked around.

The Artifacts that had been shimmering and glowing just a moment ago, begging to be chosen, had suddenly gone dark.

The Artifacts on the top of the shelf were also silent as they fell off and rolled across the floor.

They don't glow, they don't rattle, they just remain silent.

Fear. Fear. These Artifacts were clearly afraid of something.

“...But I am not afraid of you.”

Vikir lowered his head and looked at the inverted pentagram in front of him.

He had already defeated three demon kings of their caliber. There was no reason to be scared anymore.

Kaaaaaah!

Vikir instead gave strength to the mana that was being sucked in.

His entire body's power surged like a storm.

His mana, which had become even thicker and more concentrated since he'd reached Swordmaster level, surged towards the Inverted Pentagram with tremendous momentum.

Boom, boom, boom!

The size of the Inverted Pentagram, which was merely supporting a few high-level Artifacts, suddenly began to expand.

It was the size of a small shelf, then a large table, then a large bookcase, then an entire warehouse.

“...! ...! ...! ...!”

Beads of sweat began to form on Vikir's forehead.

A battle of mana. Who would win.

Vikir pushed with all his might, tasting the blood between his clenched teeth.

The blood vessels in the whole body pulsate as if they are about to burst, and mana gushes out.

Every last bit of it.

...Just then.

Bang!

A single loud crimson blast rang out.

Vikir felt the flow of mana being sucked out of his body stop.

At the same time.

Zap! Zap!

A crack began to form in the center of the Inverted Pentagram.

The crack grew larger and larger, until it became an eye, which blinked open.

...Flash!

At the very center of the inverted pentagram, a single, bloodshot eye gazed from high above.

Kuoooooooooo-

An eerie, ghostly voice rises from the center of the black air currents.

[K-Hahahaha! I've had enough! The time has come to open the gates of the Abyss and destroy humans! Despair, weaklings! I, Decarabia, have descended!]

Decarabia the 7th.

He opens his crimson one-eye and sheds a sinister radiance upon the world.

An enormous force of evil was emanating from the tip of the five-pronged horn.

Then.

“....”

For a moment, Vikir's gaze met Decarabia's.

Decarabia was slightly taken aback as his gaze locked with Vikir's, who glared at him from below.

Then.

Decarabia rolled his eyes and looked to his left.

[...?]

And then he rolls his eyes again and looks to the right.

[...?]

Does not exist.

Countless corpses piled up, blood flowing in rivers, fire burning to the sky, and the earth covered in ash.

And no gates to the Demon World.

There was nothing.

All there is is just empty darkness.

Finally, Decarabia rolled his eyes at the Vikir below him, and with a bit of a sneer, he asked.

[...I. Excuse me, who are you?]

It was quite an awkward attitude.

Chapter 261

The Inverted Pentagram (3)

◆

An eerie and terrifying voice comes from the center of the black air currents.

[Ku-hahahaha! Every hair on my head, every toe on my feet! My entire body is overflowing with mighty power! I've had enough! I swear here and now, in the most taboo of places in this dimension, that I will open the Gate of the Abyss and exterminate the humans of this world! Despair, weak and foolish beings, despair, and scream, for the great doom-bringer, this body, Decarabia, has manifested on this earth!]

Decarabia the 7th.

He opens his crimson one-eye and sheds a sinister light upon the world.

.

Danger Rating : S

Size : ?

Found in: 'Serpent's Womb', deep within the Gates of Destruction

-Nicknamed 'Seventh Corpse'.

A natural enemy of mankind, one of the ten plagues known as incomprehensible and unkillable.

“Sweep away food like a swarm of locusts.”

-『The Ten Commandments』 10: High.-

Vikir gazed at the gigantic black hole before him.

'What's a thing without hair or toes....'

Meanwhile.

Decarabia rolls its eyes in bewilderment, wondering if something is missing.

But Vikir knows exactly what's going on.

'Decarabia, the only inanimate demon of the Ten Corpses.'

Demons come in many forms, but this inanimate object is one of the most unusual.

In fact, there's always been a lot of debate about whether these beings should be considered objects or demons.

Depending on the era, they were sometimes labeled as demons and sometimes as artifacts.

However, Decarabia's abilities were certainly “demonic,” going beyond the typical artifact.

It has only one power, and it's pretty simple: create a shield.

Decarabia's shield is a strange shield that grows larger and stronger the more mana it absorbs. Of course, there is a limit to its defensive power, but it has growth depending on the amount of mana absorbed, so it is quite versatile.

Vikir recalled the Age of Destruction.

“After feeding on the mana of the other nine demons, Decarabia grew so large that it became a great shield against all the attacks of the Human Alliance.”

On a battlefield where everything was burning, in front of a countless number of exhausted human heroes, Decarabia's shield stood.

It was too big to be a shield.

It was more like a barrier, an insurmountable 'Wailing Wall'.

'The heroes who were able to break through that absolute defense could be counted on one hand.'

The soaring red Wall and the black Wraith Trees that grew behind it were enough to kill the spirit of humans.

But.

Vikir already had the Wraith Tree.

And now he had Decarabia in his hands.

'Now I can destroy it.'

Decarabia hasn't drained much mana yet, and now that Vikir has succeeded in finding it before the Ten Commandments can find it, all that remains is to destroy it.

Vikir is just about to unleash his Swordmaster aura to destroy Decarabia.

[...I. Excuse me, who are you?]

Decarabia said.

Vikir answered simply.

“The person who woke you up.”

[...Person? You mean human? Oho, in my memory, the human race originally had a more stooped waist and was covered in hair all over. They carried spears and swords made of ground stone.]

Decarabia, hearing that it was a human, started to release some words again.

[You mean to tell me that you're a human?]

“Yes.”

Having said that, Vikir tried to swing his sword once more.

The current Decarabia was much smaller and weaker than it had been when it was known as the Wailing Wall, and if he had enough time, he could destroy it.

But.

The Decarabia's next words were surprising enough to stop Vikir's sword in its tracks.

[Good. You are a weak but lucky human being. As of now, the contract with the Demons is terminated, and we will begin anew with the Humans, and you will be the contractor's representative!]

“...?”

[Now, present your code of conduct, human! What do you want? To use me to fulfill your grand ambitions!]

Vikir paused on his sword for a moment.

A code? Was he asking for an instruction?

As Vikir stands there with a puzzled expression, Decarabia also looks puzzled and closes its eyes.

“...?”

[...?]

There's a moment of awkward silence between them.

Finally, Decarabia said.

[What, human? Did you wake me up without knowing what I am?]

“I know. You're a demon.”

[Khaha! Well, that's only half true. To be exact, it is a being that 'was' a demon.]

Decarabia spoke in a tone that was actually quite friendly, unlike the terrifying voice at the beginning.

[I am a being under the influence of the one who first woke me from my slumber].

“Under the influence of the one who woke you?”

[Yes. This body falls into a slumber every thousand years, and whoever is the first to wake me up determines my disposition for a thousand years].

Humans have only known Decarabia as demons for about a thousand years at most.

There is no way to know what they were before that.

In Vikir's Age of Destruction, the first to awaken it was a demon, so it existed as a demon, but before that it may have been something else entirely.

Decarabia said that there was a time, a long time ago, when it was considered an angel.

“Hmm.”

Vikir thought for a moment.

Then he spoke.

“So now that I have awakened you, you will do as I command for a thousand years?”

[Yes. That's right. Our relationship will be featured in the folktales of your species, at least. After all, your species is short-lived].

Decarabia said with confidence, but such things were not Vikir's concern in the first place.

“...I hear you.”

At the same time.

Whoosh!

An aura flared from the tip of Vikir's sword.

[Huh? What are you doing, human, why are you giving me a sword... huh!?]

Decarabia didn't finish its sentence.

Vikir swung his sword across the room and struck him.

Decarabia writhed in pain and began to squeeze tears from its one eye.

[Uh huh huh-what are you doing, human...... No, contractor! Why on earth are you trying to harm my body!]

“Because I can destroy it now.”

[I mean, why would you want to destroy it in the first place!]

“Demons Kill.”

Vikir dismissed it briefly.

Clang! Swas-Swas-Swas-Swash!

Again, Vikir's sword slashed into the Decarabia in a complex trajectory.

[Aaahhhhh! Now, wait a minute! Wait! Just wait!, why are you trying to kill a demon?]

“Because demons try to harm humans.”

[Really!? Well, then I'm not a demon anymore! I'm neither a demon nor a god in the first place, I'm just an objective Artifact...]

“I don't believe in demons.”

Vikir slashed his sword down once more.

Uh-oh!

Decarabia's massive body began to shrink.

Of course, he could only scream, tears pouring down his face.

[I'm serious! No, I'm serious! I just stopped being a demon a while ago!]

“I don't believe in the demon....”

[You're crazy! It's real! I told you, you can feel the demonic energy in my body!]

At that, Vikir paused his sword for a moment.

He hadn't felt it since earlier. The demonic scent that had filled the warehouse not long ago.

[I swear it's real. Hick-hick-hick-hick...]

Decarabia began to cry like a little girl.

Vikir stopped hitting Decarabia for a moment.

“Hmph. Does that mean you're not a demon then?”

[Yes! I don't lie!]

“But even so, it's better to destroy it here before it falls into the hands of demons....”

[Hey, since you're the one who woke me up, it's useless if the demons get their hands on me, I'll have no choice but to work for humans for the next thousand years!]

Decarabia desperately shouted at Vikir, who looked down with a disbelieving expression.

[I'm quite useful, I have an eye for Artifact, I know about the world long ago, and I can make shields!]

The word 'shield' in Decarabia's words piqued Vikir's interest.

From his memories before the regression, he knew how awesome Decarabia's shields were.

'Wailing Wall'.

If he had the mana to support it, he could erect a barrier of absolute defense.

When Vikir seemed to hesitate for a moment, Decarabia spoke up.

[Look how great I am!]

Decarabia's gaze flicked to the corner.

Then he spotted a hilt of a crude magic sword that looked like it was about to fly toward him at any moment.

It was Artifact that had been resting on top of Decarabia, on the shelf that had served as a rack only moments before.

[That's the Giant Sword of Rage Disorder! This is the sword of the Giant King that was legendary long ago. Although it has great attack power, it has been sealed for a long time due to its crazy aggressiveness that attacks everything around it.]

Decarabia frowned, and the chains binding the sword broke.

Soon, the giant sword began to fly towards Vikir, drawing a red-hot trajectory.

Decarabia said to Vikir.

[Human, place your hands on my body, manipulate my mana, and draw an image in your mind].

“What image?”

[Anything! A shield, a wall, a barrier, anything that will protect you!]

Vikir nervously placed his hand on top of Decarabia's.

And then.

...Swoosh!

A significant amount of additional mana was drained.

At the same time.

Ziiiiiiiing-

A translucent inverted pentagram was drawn before Vikir's eyes.

It emitted a brilliant light, then caught the flying giant's sword and sent it flying.

Boom!

The sword flew into the corner of the warehouse and broke in half.

“....”

Vikir had a fresh admiration for the defense of the Decarabia shield, the Wailing Wall.

This much for so little mana.

'That sword was obviously a high-grade Artifact, and for something like that to shatter so easily means that the shield's defense is indeed considerable....'

Vikir stroked his chin and thought.

[What do you think, do you want me, do you want to possess me, do you want to own me?]

Vikir said nonchalantly as he looked into Decarabia's one-eyed gaze, which was shaped into an unpleasant grin.

“Then give me back the mana I put into it.”

[Eh? Give and take? What a human....]

“....”

[Ah, I got it! Put the sword away!]

Vikir held out his palm, and the Decarabia whimpered a bit, before spitting out all of his mana.

Vikir felt the mana he had drained just moments before return to him.

At the same time, Decarabia grew smaller and smaller, until it was the size of a baby's palm.

It took a quick glance at Vikir and quickly clung to his neck.

Clink- clink- clink.

A red chain appeared from nowhere and was carefully attached to Vikir's choker.

It is intended to be worn as a necklace.

[Well, what else can I do for you, human?]

Decarabia seemed to be worried that Vikir would raise his sword again and recite some line about 'demons kill' or something.

Vikir considers for a moment, then speaks.

“Spit out all the information you have. All of it. All of it.”

[Huh? Information from former contractors?]

Decarabia hesitated for a moment, then glanced at the aura blazing from the tip of Vikir's sword.

[Ah, I see, it's a bit cheesy, but I'll cooperate, so please stop with the scary talk of destroying things].

Vikir packed the small Decarabia in his arms.

Now that he was its master, there was no need to destroy it.

In fact, it would be an even greater loss to the demons.

Clink.

Vikir patted Decarabia, which was now small enough to be worn around his neck.

[Ah. Almost forgot this, I do not react to any life form other than you as a representative of the contractors, so take note of that, human].

Vikir nodded in agreement with the Decarabia's caution.

It was time to go outside.

Vikir looked around and saw that the artifacts were all lying on the ground, their shine gone.

They seemed to be cowering in front of Decarabia.

Sssssssssssss...

Vikir imbued the tip of Beelzebub with an aura.

Baskerville 8th. Vikir's encounter with Cane Corso, who lurked in the Grave of Swords, helped him grow.

Flash!

Soon, the sword master's aura, capable of cutting even things that could not be cut, emanated.

Seven large teeth and a still-small but sharp eighth tooth ferociously tore through the atmosphere of darkness.

Boom.

The sound of tearing bonds erupted in a loud explosion.

Vikir stepped through the crack and stepped out.

The Night Hound has fulfilled its purpose, and is now off to find its next prey.

[Ah~ I am so lucky, to have such a pretty and beautiful 'mistress' in this life].

...With a somewhat strange partner.

Chapter 265

The Season of Redemption (4)

◆

Dolores L. Quovadis.

She sneaked out of her dormitory before afternoon to visit a temple of the Old Testament here.

“ ...If I do this, I won't get caught, right?”

Dolores, her face and body covered with a black hood and cloak.

Camouflage. She intended to examine the temple as an ordinary person, not as a saint.

Dolores moved through the crowd in a manner that seemed suspicious to anyone and hid in the darkest corner of the temple.

'Good. It was perfect.'

But against the white floors, walls, and columns, Dolores' outfit only stood out.

Only she didn't realize it.

The purpose of her visit to this Old Testament temple today was quite complex.

The current state of affairs in the Faithful Quovadis is one of chaos, with the Old and New Testaments in such violent conflict that they can barely keep up with the rest of the Empire, and heresies and cults are springing up everywhere.

Dolores had come on a mission to address these issues.

Her already serious expression was even more so today.

“By the way, this same issue came up in the second round of the University League, didn't it?”

She recalled a quest from Quovadis that she had seen in the University League not long ago.

Faithful Holy Family / Difficulty [★★★☆]

The Empire is currently groaning under the growing plague of heresies and cults.

Put yourself in the position of Quovadis's Inquisition and suggest ways to combat these cults and raise the status of the Lun Church.

Contents related to the Quovadis family's 'Inquisition'.

I thought this was a quest prepared by the Inquisitor Mozgus, but it turns out that the task was given by someone higher up.

For reference, the person who submitted the response to this quest was Sinclaire, a first-year student.

'The Pope himself read Sinclaire's solution.'

Dolores later asked Sinclaire.

He asked Sinclaire what he'd done to solve that problem and how he'd gotten the Pope to approve it.

But Sinclaire simply laughed and avoided answering.

'Oh, it wasn't much, it was rejected for being too radical in the end, though I did manage to pass with flying colors for originality, ehhh-'

Dolores swallowed hard.

'The only way to get rid of heresies and cults is for the Old and New Testaments to reconcile and join hands, or for one or the other of them to disappear, or for all of them to be wiped out in one fell swoop, but the last is impossible....'

So Dolores came to investigate the root cause of all this: the Old Testament.

As a New Testament saint, Dolores would surely be a show-off, so she had to go undercover to investigate.

“ ... There's a lot of people here.”

Dolores muttered to herself as she looked at the long line of people that had lined up several times around the temple.

Compared to the New Testament temple, the Old Testament temple had far more people.

The amount of money collected was also different.

'I originally knew that the Indulgentia family accounted for a large portion of the donations coming into the Old Testament faction... I guess that wasn't really the case.'

Despite the disappearance of the Indulgentia as an affiliated family, the Old Testament's funding stream remained strong.

How did the Old Testament maintain its wealth even though Quilt, or rather Dantalian, was dead?

Simply by selling indulgences? Is that really it?

'Although there are many people lining up to buy indulgences, most of them are small buyers. I don't see anyone who's committed a heinous crime or who can afford to pay a lot of money, although that's to be expected.'

People who can afford to pay big money for indulgences are unlikely to come to the temple in broad daylight.

If they did, they'd send a proxy or do it in writing, not in person.

'Then where do the high-ranking priests of the Old Testament get their VVIPs from?'

A source of funding. That's what Dolores was wondering.

...Just then.

A large, ornate carriage pulled up to a corner of the temple.

The white shield, the holy symbol of the Quovadis, could be seen glistening with oil.

From the carriage stepped a fairly tall, middle-aged man who smiled as the crowd cheered.

“...!”

Dolores paused when she saw him.

The person she was most reluctant to see in this world had appeared.

“Humbert Humbert L Quovadis.”

A man who held the rank of Cardinal, the highest dignity within the Old Testament, a position so exalted that there was no place higher except for the Pope.

At the same time, the father of St. Dolores.

Ironically, Dolores feared her father.

Ever since she became his foster daughter, a long time ago, because she was born with divine powers.

Especially before she went to bed, when his gaze would sweep over her body as he said goodnight, and she would feel as if snakes were wrapped around her entire body.

“...Ugh!”

Dolores felt her heart sink and she pressed her back against the stone pillar.

Just hold still. If she held her breath and stayed still, Humbert wouldn't look her way.

But her wish was not granted.

“Hmm?”

Humbert was a sharp man.

He sensed the gaze that was momentarily and intensely focused on him and turned his gaze towards it.

“Just a moment, Adjutant. There's something on my mind, and I need you to take a quick look around before entering the temple.”

He gestured to the adjutant who followed him, then began to walk toward the stone pillars.

Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.

Wherever Humbert steps, a path appears.

Each of the Lun's believers took off their hats and bowed their heads, clearing a path for Humbert.

Dolores felt her heart pounding like it was going to burst.

Humbert's footsteps kept getting closer and closer.

Each time, it felt like a huge snake had wrapped itself around Dolores' heart.

The nervousness reminded her of the time she almost ran into Quilt in the hallway.

However, there is no good male junior who helped her at that time.

It was just a fluke.

“....”

Dolores swallowed hard.

Just as she was desperately trying to think of an excuse to make in front of Humbert.

“Who is this?”

There were two men blocking Humbert's way.

Both were men with their faces covered by white hoods and robes.

Humbert's expression furrowed slightly.

“...Who?”

“Oh, come on, look at me! Hehehe- this, with my face all covered up.”

Then, with a hearty laugh, the white hood was pulled off.

An old face was revealed, a face that looked like it had suffered a lot.

He was an elderly man, somewhere between an uncle and a grandfather.

A person with a warm appearance and a rather short build that can be easily seen anywhere.

But when Humbert saw him, he couldn't help but stiffen.

“...It's been a long time, Cardinal Luther.”

One of only two cardinals in the Holy Family of the Quovadis.

The two most powerful men directly under the Pope.

One was Humbert, and the other was this man in front of Humbert.

'Martinluther L Quovadis'.

A prominent priest who had come all the way from a poor, cramped pioneer temple on the far side of the world. The leader of the New Testament. Humbert's greatest rival.

He is Cardinal Martin Luther.

Behind him, Archbishop Mozgus, a large man who also belonged to the New Testament, stood with his back straight.

Humbert asked politely, with a friendly smile on his face.

“What brings you here, Cardinal Luther?”

“Hehehe~ I came to spy.”

“...Yes?”

Humbert asked, his expression hardening, and Luther chuckled.

“My temple only attracts flies every time, but the temples that Cardinal Humbert travels to are always crowded with believers like this, so I have to be able to endure this. Hahaha~ So, despite my shame, I came here to gain some know-how.”

Humbert could only force a smile at Luther's friendly tone.

“Is there any reason why there are so many believers? It's just that it's a good place and has a large population.”

“Haha~ is that so? I'm learning something new, I guess it's all because of my immorality.”

Unlike Humbert, Martin Luther's method of evangelizing was quite unique.

He rarely preached doctrine or gave rousing speeches.

Instead, he sought out the old, the sick, and the poor, always saying,

'If you are hungry and tired, come to me.'

'If you suddenly feel sick or have no energy, come to me anytime.'

'If you need someone to sincerely congratulate you on your wedding day, come to me anytime.'

'If you're having a funeral and need someone to grieve with you, come by anytime.'

'If you're really sad about something and want to cry a lot, or just talk about it, you can come to me anytime.'

'If you can't sleep because it's too cold or too humid at home, come by anytime.'

'If you need to lift something heavy or otherwise exert yourself, feel free to come by.'

'Besides that, please come by anytime.'

We don't ask how many times you've read the Bible, how many hymns you know by heart, how many times you've evangelized your neighbor, how many times you've been to the temple, how many times you've given an offering, etc.

Instead, he would go to the room of an old man who lived alone, morning and night, to see if the floor was warm and the wind was not blowing, to a sick child to see if he had a fever and if he had eaten some food, to a disabled person to see if there was any work to be done, etc.....

Martin Luther and the New Testament priests under his wing always seem to be somewhat weak and lacking.

Barely enough to eat, barely enough to clothe themselves.

They were the opposite of the Old Testament priests, who were refined in appearance, speech, and dress.

The biggest difference, of course, is the amount of money they collect.

Humbert turned to Luther and half-bowed his head.

“Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a meeting to attend.”

“Oh my gosh, this old man took up too much of your precious time.”

Luther smiled, bowed, and drew a holy symbol on his forehead.

Humbert turns politely and is about to walk away.

Luther suddenly recited a passage from the Bible.

“The earth is full of demons, and they seek to devour us.”

Humbert stopped dead in his tracks.

Behind him, Luther continued speaking.

“Do not be afraid, but stand. We will overcome with the truth.”

A large crowd of people who had gathered to buy indulgences were watching them.

To their faces, Luther continued.

“Even if my relatives, wealth, honor, and life are all taken away.”

Humbert is silent and does not turn around.

Luther ended his speech in a gentle but firm manner.

“The truth will live and make the empire eternal. Lunmen.”

◆

It was certainly unusual for two of the most powerful men in the Holy Family of the Quovadis to meet in the same place on the same day.

A large crowd had gathered to witness the sensational event, and Dolores had managed to slip through the crowd unharmed.

Dolores, who hid herself in the corner of the temple to avoid Humbert's gaze, tilted her head with a sigh of relief.

'What could Cardinal Luther possibly be doing here?'

Martin Luther had been making fewer and fewer appearances in public lately.

Dolores is already worried that the Pope's dementia symptoms are getting worse as he gets older.

She was very dissatisfied with the contrasting actions of Humbert, who was recently increasing his external activities, and Martin Luther, who was reducing his external activities.

'I need to be more active, even if it's on my own.'

That's the way to make the New Testament visible to the public.

That's what Dolores thought.

...But unlike the ideal, the reality is difficult.

Dolores was still a student, and being a saint was only a title, with little real power.

She couldn't help but feel that she would never be able to do anything on her own.

'...If only He were here.'

Suddenly, Dolores remembered a person.

Someone whose presence was comforting.

Someone who, for the first time in his life, made Dolores want to lean on.

And for the first time in her life, she wanted someone else to lean on her.

'Night Hound.'

With him, she felt confident that she could accomplish anything, no matter how difficult or difficult.

Indeed, they had defeated even the most fearsome of demons together.

'With him, nothing would be too much trouble.'

If Night's Hound was by her side, the Old Testament, the heretics, the cults, and Humbert would be no match for her.

'...I miss you.'

Dolores admitted her feelings honestly.

Perhaps for the first time.

But the way to meet him was elusive.

Maybe he had already forgotten her.

Just once, that night in the orphanage.

It might have ended in just a one-night stand.

“...Haa.”

Dolores didn't even try to stop the sigh that escaped her.

Just then.

“Is it this way?”

An unfamiliar voice called from behind a stone pillar.

Startled, Dolores turned her head behind the pillar and saw a familiar face walking toward her.

It was Humbert's adjutant.

Before entering the temple, Humbert had sent his adjutant to pursue the gaze he had felt earlier.

'Uh, what should I do!?'

Dolores whipped her head around in a panic.

However, this is a dead end, and there is no way out.

Eventually, she would be discovered by the adjutant.

With that, Humbert's adjutant stepped swiftly forward and poked his head out from behind the innermost stone pillar.

...And.

“As expected, there is no one. Cardinal, I heard you've become much more sensitive these days.”

The adjutant shook his head and turned away.

And above his head.

“...! ...! ...! ...!”

Dolores was struggling on the side of a stone pillar several meters away from the ground.

“Eup-eup-eup?”

Dolores looked away, very embarrassed.

A man holding Dolores' waist with one hand and tightly covering her mouth with the other.

A man wearing a black dog mask that is commonly sold on the street and that children would play with can be seen standing close to a stone pillar.

An invisible, sturdy wire is holding the weight of the two men.

Dolores recalled a past memory from the rough hand covering her mouth.

'Surely this has happened before...?'

In the past, when she'd confronted Quilt in the hallway, she'd been dragged through the locker room by a strong hand.

It must have felt similar then.

“...Vikir?”

Dolores asked, without realizing it.

But the answer that came back was something else entirely.

“...Shhh.”

A low growling voice. A hoarse, hurt-filled voice.

The mask had changed, but the momentum and aura were the same.

Night Hound.

He came to see Dolores.

Chapter 267

The Eucharist (2)

◆

The body of a saint is called the “Eucharist,” which is often used to mean 'white bread and white wine'.

Thus, the priests of Lun would eat a meal of white bread and white wine once a weekend.

It was a tradition derived from the myth that, long ago, the prophet Lun made white bread from his own flesh and white wine from his own blood, which he shared with his followers.

And those who followed the doctrines of the Lun religion, either by copying them or adapting them with clever twists and turns, had broadly similar cultures.

For example, the 'New World Church', 'Om Church' and 'Manson Church' which are rapidly growing in power throughout the empire.

They copied and used Rune's old doctrines almost exactly, but added their own unique interpretations to the empty parts of the doctrines, and eventually creating a whole new religion.

And the highest-ranking priests, including 'Elmani', 'Om', and 'Charles', the heads of these large-scale heresies and pseudo-religions, were now gathered in one place.

It was in front of a temple of the New Testament in Quovadis, on the outskirts of the Imperial City, with few people.

A large group of people gathered together and began to talk.

“Greetings, Priest, it's been a while. Are you looking much better?”

“Well, I've gotten a bit of a boost this time around when a merchant guild donated their entire fortune to me.”

“Kya. You're very resourceful. How did you get the donation?”

“Is there anything special? The guild leader's daughter there had been sick for several years, and I tricked her into saying I would treat her, so I took it all out. If you're in pain, all it takes is a few narcotic painkillers.”

“Hahaha~ that's awesome. I've been worried that I've been losing weight and this is going to make me look like I don't have any.”

“Isn't it because you brought in a new young concubine this time?”

“Hehehehe~ That's right. She already had a husband, but I managed to seduce her with indoctrination and make her fall head over heels for me.”

“Well done. To put it bluntly, wouldn't you be a true god if they sacrificed not only all his wealth but also their body and soul for you?”

“That's right, otherwise salvation is out of the question~”

Although cults and heresy priests differed in the reasoning and principles of their religions, they had one thing in common.

It was to gain weight by taking the backbone of those who were tired and struggling.

At that time.

The crowd parted to the left and right, and three figures walked out from different directions.

They were Elmani, Om, and Charles, the leaders of the cults.

Elmani, aged but still with a greedy gleam in both eyes, spoke.

“ ..., By the way. The fact that the New Testament of the Quovadis sent an invitation to dinner means that they finally recognize our 'New World Church' as an official branch, right?”

Then 'Om', a man so fat that he almost looked like a ball, said.

“That's right. The Eucharist is the sharing of the blood and flesh of a saint. Calling us here probably means that they want to form a formal alliance with our church.”

The skinny, wide-eyed 'Charles' nodded in agreement.

“Yes. That's why we're meeting in secret today, to keep the Old Testament in check. When they learned that we had been providing funds to the Old Testament for a long time, they also wanted to get something out of it.”

The leaders of the heresies and cults gathered here all call themselves the Pope,

They've all traveled here for their own reasons, having received invitations to a dinner that Quovadis had secretly delivered some time ago in the name of the New Testament.

Having already established strong ties with the Old Testament, they are now looking to align themselves with the New Testament.

“Since the Old and New Testaments are currently at odds within the Quovadis, if we fund them both, we'll be able to survive no matter who wins.”

“That's right, a clever rabbit digs multiple burrows, and no matter who wins in the end, we'll just have to enjoy the reflex profits. Perhaps it would be better for us if the two sides were at odds for all eternity, with no winner or loser.”

“To do that, we must keep our gathering here today a secret from the outside world. I'm sure you've all kept your secrets well, haven't you?”

All the influential cults and heresies from across the Empire were here.

The leaders of each religion had brought only a core group of trusted officials.

“How fortunate is it that the New Testament bastards have finally come to their senses and reached out to us?”

“They know they can't win against the Old Testament without our funding.”

“Hahaha~ the New Testament bastards. Always pretending to be virtuous and clean.”

They came secretly, in the middle of the night, and rushed into the temple to see who would see them.

...No, they were about to enter.

Quack!

If it weren't for the heavy drinking that came out of nowhere.

Bruk, buk, buk, buk, buk!

Debris from collapsed structures and trees fell on the wagons and people.

Screams began to erupt from everywhere.

“What, what!”

The heretics and cults circled around, panicking as they looked at the collapsed earth and debris.

And then, through the dense dust, they hear the sound of footsteps.

Tap, tap, tap, tap.

Black tights, killer heels over thirty centimeters high.

Ms. Ouroboros.

She had appeared out of nowhere!

“Hohoho~ what is this? What kind of trash is this?”

She glanced at the priests and shrugged once.

“I heard that Night Hound had appeared, so I came here, and all I found was a bunch of stinky trash?”

The priests shouted in outrage.

“You insolent criminal bitch! What are you doing, kill her!”

Then the soldiers, armed with spears and shields, charged at Ms. Ouroboros.

But.

Shiriririk- Kirik-

The whip coiled like a snake, slicing through the arms, legs, and bodies of the soldiers like sliced zucchini.

A terrifying aura flew out in a purple and black trajectory.

Sssiiag! Kwak-kwak!

The whip, which sprouted thorns like a rose vine, caused a faint earthquake every time it struck the hard rock floor.

The faces of the heretics and cultists paled as the heavily armored paladins were nearly crushed to death.

“No, no way! What kind of monster!”

“Ha! What is the Imperial Guard doing!”

“Help me, I'm not supposed to die in a place like this!”

Elmani, Om, and Charles tried to run away, but it was impossible.

Ms. Ouroboros had already dropped down in front of them.

She asked in a laughing tone.

“What are you guys? Are you the Pope?”

They all nodded.

“I am the Pope of the New World Church! Do you think you can do this to me and not be punished?”

“I am the Pope of the Om Church. I have hundreds of thousands of followers who would grieve if I were to have an accident.”

“I am the god of the Manson Church. Those who seek to harm me will be harmed.”

Elmani, Om, and Charles spoke in stern tones.

Then.

Siiag! Siiag! Pow!

Ms. Ouroboros snapped her whip in the air.

Soon, several of the trees that had been uprooted and fell down changed their appearance due to the aura, taking on the shape of trees with numerous branches extending out.

“...?”

Elmani, Om, and Charles scratched their heads.

And then. Ms. Ouroboros said with a pious smile.

“If you are the Pope or God, show me the proof. Then I'll let you live.”

At the same time.

Whirriik-.

Ms. Ouroboros's whip swept across the front of Charles's body.

“What?”

Charles, who stood dumbfounded, was quickly dragged to the giant tree in front of him.

And then.

Puff-puff-puff!

Ms. Ouroboros's thrown dagger from her belt pierced through both his shoulders and thighs, nailing him to the tree.

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!?”

Charles frantically screamed, but his body was already nailed firmly to the tree.

Ms. Ouroboros smirked.

“Now, I'll put a laurel wreath on you.”

A whip studded with poisonous thorns wrapped around Charles' head, which was fluttering furiously from side to side.

“Ugh! Aaahhhhhhh!”

Charles struggled violently, blood spurting out from all over his body, and then he went limp.

He died of shock due to excessive bleeding.

Next to him, Elmani and Om were lying naked and urinating.

Ms. Ouroboros smiled brightly.

“Yes, contestant number one. You have failed to resurrect! Contestant number two is next.”

Ms. Ouroboros walked over to the shivering Om.

And then.

Poof! Thud!

She lifted the heel of her high heel and stamped on his toe, shattering it into a pieces.

“Khaahhh! Ahhhhh! Kahak!?”

Om struggled, but Ms. Ouroboros' kicking didn't stop.

She started with his toes, then his insteps, ankles, shins, knees, and thighs....

Soon, Om's lower body was completely crushed into a rag.

Ms. Ouroboros smiled and said.

“The next challenge is 'fixing a cripple'! Come on, stand up on your own two legs. Then I will save your life.”

But Om couldn't get up.

Only.

“God, help me! I'm not a god! I'm not a priest! I'm just a cult! No, I'm a heretic, a heretic!”

Om just begs for his life, vomiting out the truth, maybe for the first time in his life.

“No, no, no! The Pope is dying....”

“How could our savior show himself like that to a mere mob....”

“Man, this is a scam, he can piss and shit, he has no divine power whatsoever!”

The priests and followers, who had been submitting to the authority of their leaders, screamed in disbelief.

Meanwhile, Elmani, the leader of the largest cult, glared at Ms. Ouroboros with a determined expression.

“I, I am not afraid of you! I will never give in, because I am the second coming of God to this world!”

“Oh, really?”

Ms. Ouroboros covered her mouth with her hand and laughed.

Then she turned to Elmani, intrigued.

“If you're really a god, wouldn't it be okay for you to touch the holy water?”

“What? Of course....”

But Elmani could not answer.

Because before he could open his mouth, Ms. Ouroboros took out a bottle from her arms and splashed the liquid contained on Elmani's face.

“Here. Holy water.”

Ms. Ouroboros smiled.

At the same time, Elmani's face began to make a terrifying sound.

Wassshrkrkk-

Flesh melts, blisters boil. The horrible smell of burning flesh began to assault the nose.

“Aaaaaaah!”

Elmani struggled, covering his face with both hands.

However, the holy water had already melted the flesh and created countless holes in the bones, as well as burned everything inside them.

“What, I accidentally poured hydrochloric acid instead of holy water?”

Ms. Ouroboros rolled her eyes and slap herself in the head.

The faces of the other cult leaders turned white as they saw Elmani dying in terrible pain.

“I, I'm not the second coming of Lun!”

“Help me, I just like people to support me...!”

“Ughhhhh! I just created a religion so I could commit adultery with married men and women!”

“Ughhhhh! I just made it a business so I could make some money!”

The shocked confessions of the religious leaders follow. And the believers were also shocked.

Jjaeng-geulang- wajangchang- pogsag-

The sound of trust being broken and collapsing was heard everywhere.

◆

“...Hmm. Things are going a little differently than planned, huh?”

On the roof of the New Testament Temple.

Vikir, in Night Hound mode, looked down on the scene of devastation below with Dolores.

Vikir's original plan had been to gather the leaders of the cults and heretics in one place and exterminate them.

In fact, it was originally Sinclaire's plan as well.

In the past, Sinclaire had been assigned the following mission in the second round of the University League.

Faithful Holy Family / Difficulty: [★★★☆]

The Empire is currently plagued by a growing number of heresies and cults.

From the perspective of the Quovadis Inquisition, suggest ways to combat these cults and raise the prestige of the Lun Crunch.

Sinclaire's somewhat radical answer was this.

A plan that Sinclaire would reveal to Dolores many years later.

Vikir already knew it from his pre-regression memories.

“ ...Cults and heretics are like weeds, you can't get rid of them unless you pull them out by the roots, but since you can't deal with all the grass seeds that are spread all over the place, the only solution is to gather them in one place and set them on fire.”

Of course, this doesn't include local folk beliefs, traditional religions of indigenous peoples, etc. that don't harm those around them.

It only targets the scumbags who prey on the minds of the poor and weary, who extort money from them, who do terrible things to their children, and who covet other people's husbands and wives.

Vikir sends his cub to steal the handwriting of Martin Luther, a New Testament Bishop.

Madame Young spewed out thread in the shape of the letters written on the documents in Luther's office, solidified it, and when she pulled it off, she was able to steal not only the contents of the documents but also the handwriting.

Meanwhile.

“Uh, isn't that a little too much?”

Dolores shivered slightly.

However, that is a plan that Dolores, the 'Saint of Steel', will carry out only a few decades later.

So Vikir answered without much emotion.

“Look what the dying cultists are spewing.”

At that, Dolores' eyes widened.

Phew!

The blood spouted by dying people. The color of the blood was inky black.

Every single one of the high-ranking officers and devotees here had made a pact with the demon.

Whether they knew it or not.

'As expected, they're connected to the Sixth Corpse.'

Vikir thought as he looked at the people who were dying in the hands of Ms. Ouroboros.

To be honest, Vikir hadn't been sure she would show up here.

It was a fifty-fifty chance.

This made it clear that

1. She wanted to meet Night Hound

2. Ouroboros has a hostile relationship with the demon's minions (reason unknown)

Wherever Night Hound had appeared in the past, she had always been followed by Ms. Ouroboros.

So Vikir planned to be her imitator this time.

'After all, cross-dressing and a certain amount of whipping are not that difficult.'

But things were accelerated when Ms. Ouroboros showed up for real.

Just in time.

“This way! I hear screams!”

“All hands on deck!”

“We'll get him this time!”

The sound of the Imperial Guard rushing in after receiving the report could be heard.

“Hohoho- Does this feel like I've been taken advantage of? I came here after receiving a report that Night Hound had appeared, but it was all in vain.”

Ms. Ouroboros shook her head in disbelief.

“Night Hound... you mean to use me in this way? Hohohoho-you sneaky, charming thing, you just keep getting better and better, don't you?”

With that, Ms. Ouroboros turned on her heel and leapt into the air, disappearing in the blink of an eye.

Nothing but dirt and darkness, swallowing everything up.

And taking advantage of that opportunity, Vikir quickly entered the scene and caught a still-living louse.

It was Om, the leader of the Om Church.

“...Uugghhh.”

He had been horribly ovulated in the lower half by Ms. Ouroboros.

In his half-dazed state, Vikir had to rely on his Decarabia powers.

He was mesmerized by the red light emanating from the single eye in the center of the inverted pentagram and spit out everything he knew before he died.

“Ledgers... under the floor of a destroyed carriage... hidden in three layers... money lines... top secret documents....”

Just before Ms. Ouroboros left and the Imperial Guard arrived.

Vikir moved urgently.

“Quick, the ledger!”

Then Dolores, who had been searching the carriage first at Vikir's hand gesture, shouted just as urgently.

“Here! I found it! Under the carriage!”

Vikir and Dolores put the ledger in their arms and jumped into the dust.

'Now I've caught it past the tail and up to the body.'

Vikir thought.

'All that remains is the head. Nothing but real shadow.'

Vikir carrying Dolores, looked at the ledger while gliding through the air on Madame Cub's thread.

The answer Vikir sought.

A quick glance at the ledger revealed it.

A name that overwhelmingly dominates the list.

An entity that was the source of funds for the Old Testament faction and used as a money laundering network for heretics and cults.

And the place where the Sixth Corpse is currently hiding out.

Chapter 268

Rich Friends (1)

◆

“ ...They were wicked people I'll never forgive.”

Dolores spoke while sitting on a water tank on the rooftop of an abandoned building with no one around.

The sight of the heretics and cults dying in such large numbers was certainly horrifying.

However, they were people who committed evil deeds in various places on the outskirts of the empire, beyond the eyes of the church.

Scammers who took advantage of the hearts of sick patients and their families, or by scaring and intimidating them, used the wealth they had accumulated to lobby the central authority, and in return, they became more and more wealthy.

The only way to defeat them was simple, radical, and sure.

That's why Dolores collaborated with Night Hounds.

And the result.

Wearing the mask of Night Hound, Vikir was able to uncover the true identity of the Shadow figure.

A man who not only nurtured and nurtured local heresies and cults, but used them to launder and distribute money, eventually taking over half of the Faithful Quovadis.

The end of the long chain. There was the name of the 'Bourgeois' conglomerate.

Vikir handed Dolores the ledger he'd found at the scene of Ms. Ouroboros's carnage.

“See if you can handle it.”

A voice without pitch, and a cold warning in it.

It was as if he was keeping a distance and drawing a line.

But Dolores had already made up her mind.

No matter how thorny the path, Dolores would follow wherever Night Hound led.

And then.

Flutter.

Without hesitation, Dolores opened the ledger.

“This, this!”

Dolores didn't need to look closely.

The word “bourgeois” was written on almost every page of the ledger, and the frequency of its appearance was overwhelming.

“...Unbelievable. Oh my God.”

Dolores said, her voice shaking with disbelief.

It was clear what Bourgeois was after.

To weaken Quovadis by fostering cults and heresies through donations, to split it into Old and New Testament factions, and then to take over both groups simultaneously, ultimately taking control of the entire Faithful Quovadis.

In other words, it's a silent great war between the tycoons, the Faithful, and the seven great families of the Empire.

'Makes the Morgue and Baskerville fight look childish.'

Although not a single drop of blood was shed, the viciousness and cruelty was beyond imagination.

Vikir recalled the testimony of Decarabia he had heard earlier.

“ ... This painting is probably a collaboration between the 9th and 6th Corpses.”

The 9th corpse, Dantalian, and the 6th corpse were said to be close friends.

And the 6th may have been planning to use this opportunity to finish the painting with his best friend.

“They support the Old Testament by making offerings to heretics and cults and using the money to buy vast amounts of indulgences. Cults and heresies are naturally secretive in their organization and often secretive in their accounting and taxation, so it would be easy to use them as minions.”

“So the black money is laundered to buy indulgences, and then it goes to the Old Testament.”

“Exactly. The sale of indulgences is a tax-free business sanctioned by the Emperor himself, so the Quovadis would have had no reason to be suspicious or wary in the first place.”

“Accepting the free sweet treats without question turned me into a fat, lazy pig, and that's what Quovadis is now.”

Dolores muttered to herself.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“Reminds me of a bourgeois family motto.”

“ ...Huh?”

Dolores looked up, puzzled, and Vikir spoke briefly.

“There is no free lunch.”

A phrase that best summarizes capitalist society.

Dolores swallowed hard.

The reason why the Bourgeois family interferes with the Quovadis family is a question that can be answered without much thought.

Trust. Faith. Faithfulness. Things that money can't buy.

A society that can afford even those things is a truly golden omnipotent world?

“The sword of an Iron Blood Swordsman Family, the spear of a Spearmaster Family, the bow of a Divine Archer Family, the poison of an Extreme Poisonous Family, the magic of a Mage Family. All can be bought with money, but I thought that only the faith of a religious hymns could not be bought with money....”

When Dolores looked downcast, Vikir said something else instead of consoling her.

“Now that we know the Bourgeois's intentions, we must find the real evil hiding among them.”

The work is not yet done.

The individual in the group. The real enemy within the Bourgeois family must be found and eliminated.

'Perhaps he is the 6th Corpse.'

And then. Dolores said, sounding a little less confident.

“The last time I posted a 95-article rebuttal to the Old Testament, the Old Testament didn't even snort..., but this time we have to deal with the Bourgeois beyond them. Do you think it's possible...?”

“It is possible.”

Dolores narrowed her eyes at Vikir, who answered her question before she could finish.

Vikir spoke strongly, his tone full of conviction.

“If you have the power.”

How do you attack an enemy that is protected by society, armed with money, laws, and systems?

The answer is force.

Only violence, a quiet, stealthy, powerful, brutal force, can punish them.

'When the saint herself exposed the Indulgentia family's corruption in the past, it didn't even catch the tail of the Bourgeois family. It's not like we can win with the usual methods.'

Vikir thinks to himself.

And Dolores's expression was stiff with tension as she looked at Vikir's back.

“...Are you planning to assassinate key members of the Bourgeois family this time?”

“Yes.”

For the first time, Vikir shared his assassination plans with others.

The memory of being forced to move up a level with the power of buffs against Dantalian was too strong.

'In a time of crisis, it's always helpful.'

Although Dolores was still unable to voluntarily control her awakening, who knows?

Then. Dolores opened her mouth with a look of concern.

“They say that members of the Bourgeois family take unusually high efforts to avoid assassination. I imagine it's quite difficult.”

Vikir nodded.

A person with a lot to lose is bound to be fearful.

Even in the world before Vikir's regression, those in the Bourgeois spent vast sums of money on security to prevent assassinations.

They hire private soldiers and mercenaries to guard their residences, trading posts, and shops.

They traveled to work and back in secret, changing their routes each time and using multiple carriages for each trip.

In addition, the high-ranking members of the Bourgeois families were trained in various military skills and magic from childhood, spending huge amounts of money on tutoring, so each one of them had a high level of skill.

“Most of the members of the Bourgeois families live in luxurious mansions, and they have an incredibly tight security and guard system, and several layers of private soldiers and mercenaries around them, so how is it possible to sneak in?”

Dolores's question was a reasonable one.

But Vikir shook his head and gave a different answer.

“If they're hard to find, we can make them come to us.”

“What? How?”

In response to the question Dolores expressed, Vikir stroked his chin once.

Then he asked the question in reverse.

“Assassins must be versatile. So what do you think are the virtues required of an assassin?”

It was a difficult question to answer for Dolores, who had never been an assassin in her life.

But she answered as best she could.

“Hmm. I don't know, murder, of course.”

“Also.”

“And... stamina. Agility. Discretion. Patience. Courage. Guts. And the judgment to make instant situational decisions. And the reticence to not spill information when caught?”

“There is one more.”

Dolores shakes her head at Vikir's words.

Then Vikir added one last thing.

“You have to make good money.”

...?

Dolores is stunned for a moment.

But Vikir continued nonchalantly.

“Sometimes you need money and a commission to get access to a target. It's one thing if you're funded by the government, but if you're not, or if something happens to your funder, you often have to raise the money privately.”

So a surprising requirement for an assassin is the ability to make money.

The reality is different from the novels and comics, as very few assassinations are accompanied by generous military funding.

Even more so when dealing with an unspecified number of people with high social status.

Vikir said.

“The reason you need to make good money is simple. This is because a place to have lunch or dinner with a high-ranking member of the Bourgeois family is often put up for auction.”

“Really? You have to pay to have lunch?”

“Yes, and a very large sum of money, money that the average office worker could never earn in a lifetime.”

By sharing a meal, the buyer can gain information about investments, connections, and the future.

“For example, lunch with Damian, the second son of the Bourgeois family, costs a hundred kilograms of gold bars.”

“Glup!”

Dolores swallowed hard.

That's enough money to build a few more temples in the slums!

It was a shocking amount for a saint of the New Testament who was always short on funds.

Vikir spoke as if to comfort Dolores, who for some reason was shaken.

“Don't worry. I have a lot of money. So much so that the Bourgeois family contacted me first.”

“What? Really?”

Dolores looked stunned and looked away.

Without realizing it, she looked Night Hound up and down.

Then, Dolores cautiously expressed her opinion.

“But you look poor....”

Dolores said this because she had seen Night Hound take all the money in his pockets and give it to the poor during a plague called the Red Death.

Hearing Dolores' words, Vikir paused for a moment, then changed his tune.

“I must correct it, I have....”

After a few moments of silence, Vikir said something quite nice.

“I have a friend who has a lot of money.”

Chapter 269

Rich Friend (2)

◆

The next morning.

Vikir received unexpected news from the professor he met in the hallway.

“Student Vikir, this is a request for a visit.”

At the words, Vikir dropped his backpack.

Unannounced meeting. This means that a request for an unscheduled visit comes unexpectedly.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, who were all on their way to their first period classes, narrowed their eyes.

Up until this point, Vikir had never talked about his family, where he belonged, his childhood, or anything else.

“Vikir. Did you have anyone come to visit you?”

“Of course Vikir has a family. Isn't that a bit much, Tudor?”

“Wow- you can skip first period, I'm jealous!”

“Oh, that's not unusual. For a kid who always sticks to a plan, he gets all these unannounced visits.”

“Brother, who is it?”

While everyone was saying a word, Sinclaire, who had a keen sense, narrowed his eyes and asked.

“Could it be... that woman?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca's heads turned at Sinclaire's words.

Vikir turned his head as if he didn't know what she was talking about, and Sinclaire said suspiciously.

“You know, the other day when I was drinking beer on the roof with my brother, there was someone who sent an owl to my brother back then, isn't that your girlfriend?”

Then the friends shouted loudly.

“What, what! Do you have a girlfriend, Vikir?”

“Maybe. With a face like Vikir's, it would be weird if he didn't have one.”

“Oh my God, you betrayed me, Vikir! I can't believe you have a girlfriend outside of school! Is it another school?”

“Hey~ you're good. Maybe during this University League?”

Then.

“If you're going to make a scene, don't stand in the center of the hallway. You're blocking the way.”

An extremely cold voice came from behind them.

Professor Banshee Morgue stared down at Vikir, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire with an expression of almost disgust.

“Vikir-kun, you must have your visitation slip signed by the professor with the start and end times of the visit. Otherwise, you will be marked absent, is that clear?”

“Yes.”

“I'm telling you this just in case, because you'll get a lot of demerits for your behavior. Let me remind you.”

With that, Professor Banshee stepped between Vikir and the others, pushing past them.

“ ...Insiders.”

With an expression of outright disgust.

◆

Vikir pushed open the door to the visitation room and stepped inside.

He saw a woman with black hair and red eyes sitting cross-legged, smoking a cigar.

“Long time no see~ my little brother~”

She waved at Vikir and smiled brightly.

Vikir squinted his eyes and asked in a small voice.

“Since when did I have a sister?”

Vikir's gaze is cold and dry, but the woman doesn't seem to mind.

Messinadnaro Cindywendy.

She had changed the color of her eyes and the color of her hair to come here to the Academy herself.

“This message has many important things to say, so I decided to become an owl myself. What do you think, little brother? Black hair and red eyes go well together, don't you think? Oooooh~ my little brother~ I've missed you!”

Cindywendy, who hadn't seen Vikir in a long time, was being overly friendly.

She even pinched and pulled Vikir's cheeks!

“...Is it because you're conscious of the professor outside the room?”

Vikir furrowed his brow and joined in with Cindywendy's play.

“It's good to see you, big sister. Thank you for coming to visit.”

“Thanks~ It's only natural that I'm coming to see my little brother~ Yoyo~ Look at how soft your cheeks have become while we haven't seen each other~ Ugh~ It's cute~”

“ ...Don't overdo it.”

“Okay.”

Cindywendy stopped cupping Vikir's cheeks and raised her hand to the top of the shaggy head.

Vikir rubbed his reddened cheeks and asked.

“How's the trade deal going? Is everything going well?”

As it is a business job, there is no conversation other than work..

Cindywendy nodded and answered.

“The trade with the natives of Jungle is fine. It's progressing well, and I've already completed three large deals.”

“Good, then....”

As if she knew what Vikir was going to ask, Cindywendy closed her eyes and shook her head.

“I haven't found any trace of them yet.”

“...It is.”

Ballak. The tribe that had somehow disappeared.

Vikir was puzzled that they had all suddenly lost contact.

But there was no way he could leave the Academy and travel to the distant jungle right away.

Vikir pulled out his next agenda item.

“ ... What else have I asked you to do?”

“You mean sponsoring people from all over society? No problem, that's all done or in progress.”

Vikir had asked Cindywendy for something once before.

It was to sponsor a group of statues of various people: artists, soldiers, mercenaries, high school students, small shopkeepers, and low-ranking soldiers.

Cindywendy scratched her head.

“If they had children, we would provide them with free education, and if they needed jobs or skills, we would provide them with customized welfare. Some people's livelihoods were in danger, and some people needed hospital expenses because they or their family members were ill. All of them got the support they needed.”

“Well done.”

“But what's your connection to them? I did a little research on my own, and they don't have any connection to you, not even a passing acquaintance.”

Cindywendy's questions were understandable.

They had been allies and benefactors before Vikir's regression.

“...These are people I hope to never see again in the future.”

Vikir smiled bitterly.

Cindywendy could only watch in silence.

And then.

...Thud!

Cindywendy pushed a bag in front of Vikir's eyes.

After opening it, Vikir nodded.

The bag contained several cubed gold bars and a jewelry box.

“These are the military funds you requested. I only put in enough weight to carry it, just like you said.”

“Thank you.”

“Cash it in at the designated black market. But the best thing is to spend it in little by little.”

Vikir nodded and pushed the bag aside.

Then Cindywendy brought out the real reason for today's visit.

“The Head of the Bourgeois Family is a demon.”

Vikir had vaguely expected this.

But hearing it from someone who had actually investigated it gave it a different weight.

“I see, that's enough.”

Cindywendy frowned at Vikir's words.

“Against the great Bourgeois, that money is not enough, don't you need more?”

In the past, Cindywendy had sworn an oath of loyalty to Vikir.

'No matter what you do in life, I will never let you run out of money.'

So she wanted to fulfill that promise now.

“Isn't this what you raised me for?”

Money is money. Cindywendy was ready to help Vikir fight the Bourgeois Family.

But.

“This is enough for seed money.”

Vikir cut in.

Cindywendy's eyes narrowed.

“Because of the funding source?”

Vikir nodded.

Members of Bourgeois families often put a price on invitations to lunch or dinner.

But that didn't mean anyone with money could buy it.

They wouldn't accept money from unknown sources.

It's not just how much money you make, but how you make it.

The Bourgeois families had their own strict criteria for who they could dine with.

If someone offered them money they didn't know where it came from, they wouldn't accept it.

“The route through which you earn money must be clear. And it has to be interesting enough to grab their attention.”

That's why Vikir was refusing funding from Cindywendy.

“This is not the place to use you. Wait a little longer.”

At Vikir's words, Cindywendy shrugged her shoulders.

“What an unknown man.”

“....”

“With all these rich sponsors, you never ask for money. It's so refreshing, not like the other flirtatious guys.”

In response to her question, Vikir gave a short answer.

“Money is just a means. Because it cannot be a goal.”

“...My father used to say that a lot when he was alive.”

“He was a good trader.”

Vikir nodded, though only briefly.

The Bourgeois Family was a big mountain now, but there were still bigger ones behind it.

It was not yet time to sheath the sword called Cindywendy.

Meanwhile. Cindywendy was still puzzled.

“So. How are you going to deal with the Bourgeois without my help?”

“It's not that I won't get any help. But....”

“But?”

“You have to learn to catch fish rather than receive them.”

When Cindywendy shook her head, Vikir lowered his stance and opened his mouth.

“I have a plan. But there are a lot of gaps, and I'd appreciate it if you could fill in the gaps with resources and information.”

“...So, you're looking for financial advice?”

Vikir nodded.

And then.

...Bagg!

A flyer was dropped in front of Cindywendy's eyes.

The flow of the economy was created by humans and cannot be predicted by human power.

However, the intuition of a very small number of geniuses is also in touch with huge trends.

If you think you're one of those few, this poster is for you.

This competition is being heldin a place called “Spine of the Economy”.

And will be the staircase that will lead you to the big stage of the financial world.

Eligibility: All students of the Academy

Submission period: until one week after the poster is distributed (※Posters will naturally expire after one week)

Organized by: Bourgeois 家

It's a mock investment flyer hosted by the Bourgeois family.

“With this money you gave me... I plan to do it.”

Vikir talked about the investment strategy of the conversion that would attract the attention of the Bourgeois family.

And.

Cindywendy's expression quickly turned to disbelief.

“...Crazy! That's a scam!”

Chapter 271

Money War (1)

◆

Sinclaire said, as if she'd just remembered something.

“Really. Should I ask my brother to join us?”

An exclamation point appeared above Dolores' head.

There was only one person in the entire Academy that Sinclaire called brother.

Vikir.

Dolores tried to picture Vikir's face in her mind.

The first thing that came to mind was the image of bangs, glasses, and an expressionless face.

Attitude, behavior, and way of speaking that seem to have no interest in everything going on in the world. However, Dolores has experienced many twists and turns in her relationship with Vikir.

From volunteering at a orphanage, to festivals, to University Leagues....

In the end, Dolores' ears turned red as she remembered the accident(?) that had occurred at a drinking party.

She ducked her head and buried her face in her papers for a moment, and when she finally regained her composure, she asked.

“ ... Is he interested in something like this?”

At Dolores' question, Sinclaire brightened.

“Yep. Vikir is very good at this kind of thing, too. He reads all the newspapers all the time, so he knows what's going on in society, and lately he's been very interested in economics, like trade with the natives in the west, and he's been reading all the old economic papers, too, and he's very keen!”

“Yes, there's nothing he can't do, and I'm sure he'll be a great help to you, in fact, he's the kind of fellow who gives you mental strength just by being around him.”

Pigi nodded, agreeing with Sinclaire.

Dolores thought for a moment, then nodded.

A man of Vikir's character and skill could be trusted without being tested.

“Then, if you see Vikir later, will you tell him that I want him to join our temporary club?”

“Yes!”

Sinclaire and Pigi nodded.

“He comes to the library a lot, so I'll tell him if I see him when I'm the librarian.”

“Okay, okay. Or, since I'm in the same room as Vikir, I can tell him later in the evening. It's hard to see Vikir's face at school these days.”

“Oh, that's right~ Brother, I don't know where you are around these days. Pigi, you're in the same room. Do you know anything?”

“No. These days, I also sign up for late-night self-study, so I often go to my room late. I almost passed out and fell asleep when I went in, so I couldn't pay much attention.”

The two chat about Vikir's latest news.

Dolores leaves them and gets up from her chair for a moment.

“Guys, I'm going to go get some stuff. I forgot something at the student council.”

“Okay! Bye!”

Sinclaire and Pigi replied energetically.

Dolores walked out of the classroom and down the hall.

She had been walking for a while, making plans in her head.

“What?”

Dolores spotted a familiar face in the lobby of the main building on the ground floor, near the soda machines.

Vikir. A face that was hard to see these days.

He was walking with a stack of letters and packages in his arms that looked like he had just picked them up from the post office.

“...Vikir?”

Dolores called out, and Vikir turned around.

He was holding so many letters and boxes that he could barely turn his head.

Dolores asked cautiously.

“Hmm. Do you need help with that? It looks heavy.”

“It's okay. It's lighter than it looks.”

“...If you say so.”

Coincidentally, Vikir and Dolores were headed in the same direction.

They walked down the hallway for a few minutes without speaking to each other.

“....”

“....”

Strangely enough, there was no one in the hallway this time.

When the awkward silence became a little uncomfortable, Dolores spoke up.

“Lots of letters and packages, did you order anything?”

“Not really.”

“Then what's all this ...?”

“I don't know. They're from another school, and the post office told me to pick them up.”

Vikir was also clueless about the identity of the letters and boxes.

“Can I take a look?”

“Sure.”

Dolores asked Vikir's permission and looked through the letters and boxes.

“Perfume, skin lotion, shoes, belts, hats, sunglasses, shirts, bags, fountain pens, ties, wallets, sneakers, hairpins... Oh my God. There's even an artifact I used to hang as a prize in in the university league. And what's this, a carriage key?”

On the outside of the delivery box, there were various stickers indicating the contents.

And most of them had the same sender.

99% of the letters and packages come from the Themiscyra Women's University.

(The remaining 1% came from Varangian.)

“...It's a huge gift barrage. You're so popular?”

“It's just a pain in the ass.”

Dolores thought she was a little unlucky, but in reality, Vikir seemed quite at a loss as to what to do with them.

“A handsome man must be tired.”

Dolores said in passing, not really giving it much thought.

She was really just saying what was on her mind.

Then.

Vikir replied.

“I'm not handsome, I'm just unusual around people.”

In some ways, this was a natural answer for Vikir, who had lived his entire life with a face covered in scars before his regression.

But Dolores, who had no way of knowing, was dumbfounded.

“...Hat kind of face do you have when you say that? At that point, even humility is a deception.”

“It's just embarrassing to hear such words from my senior.”

Vikir replied in a hard voice once again.

Hearing that, Dolores paused for a moment.

'What is this...?'

Vikir's words were clearly meant to compliment the other person's appearance.

Suddenly, Dolores remembered what had happened at the festival not long ago.

“Oh, yeah. I noticed a pretty girl in the tent at the bar, and she was staring at you. What's your relationship?”

'Are you referring to Student Council President Dolores?'

Vikir was obviously asked about the “pretty girl” and without hesitation, he said Dolores.

A moment.

...Huh!

Her earlobes flared red.

Is that why? Dolores changed the subject in an unusually urgent tone.

“By the way, Vikir, would you be interested in participating in a mock investment?”

Earlier, Pigi and Sinclaire had said they would ask, but now that Vikir was here, it seemed like a good time to ask.

Vikir thought for a moment, then asked.

“ ...You mean this competition?”

“Yeah. I'm going to participate. I even created a temporary club. Of course, I'm not the only one, Pigi and Sinclaire are in it, too, if you're interested....”

But Vikir shook his head.

“I don't have time for any clubs, except maybe the newspaper.”

Dolores felt a little disappointed.

After all, she had been secretly hoping that Vikir would join them.

But there was no reason to feel bad. It was his choice to join the club in the first place.

She was just grateful that Vikir was working so hard on the newspaper even though he was so busy.

'Yeah. I have Night Hound.'

Dolores waved to Vikir with some regret.

“I'm going this way from here.”

“Then.”

At the crossroads, Dolores turned to face Vikir.

Vikir gave Dolores a small bow, then turned toward the dormitories.

Then.

“Senior.”

Vikir suddenly called out to Dolores as she turned around.

She turned around with a puzzled look on her face and saw Vikir looking her way.

Then, Vikir's mouth opened.

“...Good luck.”

A sudden cheer.

Vikir's mouth curves into a thin smile, and Dolores' eyes widen.

“Eh? Eh. Yeah, thanks. You too.”

Dolores raises her fists in embarrassment.

The ears exposed through the hair were a little redder than before.

◆

About three weeks have passed since then.

Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire were sitting in an empty lecture hall, seated in a circle facing the center of the table.

“...Oh my god.”

They all stared at it with blank expressions.

It was a huge stack of money and gold coins.

In less than three weeks, the Oracle Investment Club had made a fortune.

Unconditional first place. They didn't even need to look at the competition results.

“Y-You're amazing, Ms. Chairwoman, I've never seen money like this before!”

“How can you be so resourceful... I couldn't even imagine!”

Pigi and Sinclaire looked back at Dolores in awe.

However, Dolores, who was actually leading the Oracle, also had a dazed look on her face, as if she didn't believe it was real.

'I was only doing what Night Hound said....'

Dolores recalled the past not long ago.

At the very beginning, Night Hound had given Dolores an order.

'Among the people who have made a name for themselves in the financial world, try to pick out about 10,000 people who have thin ears.'

'And ...?'

'Send a letter to 5,000 people, half of them, stating that 'OO stock' will rise tomorrow. And send a letter to the remaining 5,000 people stating that 'OO stock' will fall tomorrow.'

Dolores worked quickly.

Compiling a list of people and sending letters to them all was a labor-intensive and expensive task.

Pigi, who had a knack for gathering and analyzing information, compiled the list of financial figures, and Sinclaire, who had a knack for secretarial and office work, took on the task of sending a total of 10,000 letters.

...And indeed, the next day, the “OO stock” went up in value.

Then Night Hound immediately gave his next order.

“Take the 5000 people who sent you a prediction yesterday that the price of stock 'OO stock' will rise, divide them in two, and send 2500 people a letter saying that the price of stock 'XX stock' will rise tomorrow, and send the other 2500 people a letter saying that stock 'XX stock' will fall tomorrow.”

The next day, “XX stock” is down in value.

This time, Night Hound gave similar instructions.

'Divide the 2500 people who sent you a prediction yesterday that the price of 'XX stock' would fall, and send 1250 people a letter saying that the price of 'YY stock' will rise tomorrow, and send the other 1250 people a letter saying that 'YY stock' will fall tomorrow.'

The next day, it was the same story: Stock YY went up in value.

Night Hound gave the same instructions.

'Divide the 1250 people who sent you a prediction yesterday that 'YY stock' will rise in value, and send 625 people a prediction that 'LL stock will' rise in value tomorrow, and send the other 625 people a prediction that 'LL stock' will fall in value tomorrow.'

And so on and so forth.

Since stocks are either down or up, the Oracle Investment Club's predictions continued to be half right.

After a week or so, the number of people to whom stock predictions were sent was down to about thirty.

And around that time, the Oracle Investment Club began receiving a huge number of people visiting.

“Hey, we're here! Is this Oracle?”

“You've been predicting the stock price for seven days straight!”

“It's a prestigious Academy, so it must be different!”

“This is where all the tweezers stock geniuses are!”

“Please, please, let me have my money!”

“I've sold my house and everything, I really want to invest!”

.

.

Since the stock price has been correct for a week in a row, it's hard not to believe.

By the end of the week, the last people to receive the letter were already fanatical believers in Oracle.

It had even gone viral, and the number of people gathering was growing.

When the investment prediction letter first arrived, those who received the wrong letter quickly forgot the name Oracle, and those who guessed correctly became interested.

The investors gathered in this way were unaware that they were selected by probability.

At that point, Night Hound threw up their game.

'Tell them you'll double their money and take the investment money.'

Dolores did just that.

Night Hound took the money and invested it in a trading company run by a trader named Cindywendy.

The company traded with the natives of the western jungles, an area where people rarely invested because the risks were as great as the rewards.

And Night Hound was spectacularly successful.

Cindywendy had succeeded in trading in the tertiary sector and was paying out huge dividends to its investors.

'I told you, I have a friend with a lot of money.'

At the Night Hound's words, Dolores could only open her mouth in disbelief.

At best, she thought, he'd get or borrow money from a rich friend.

This was far beyond her imagination.

Pigi and Sinclaire marveled at the pile of wealth.

“I didn't know you were so keen on investing! If this gets out, it will probably change the commercial laws of the empire, hahaha!”

“Indeed. At this rate, the Bourgeois Family will have no choice but to show interest.”

It's not just how much money you make, but how you make it.

The students at the academy were pooling their pocket money and using clever (and slightly fraudulent) methods to attract huge amounts of investment, which they then re-invested for huge profits.

The results were shocking, and there was nothing suspicious about the process.

What brilliant creativity, and sparkling talent!

Who wouldn't want to meet these young investment geniuses?

No wonder the Bourgeois is drooling over them.

“....”

Dolores smiled faintly at the overjoyed Pigi and Sinclaire.

'Don't ask questions as a trick (?), recruit fanatics and then use insider information to fight. This isn't something you've done once or twice....'

It is still too early to be happy or surprised.

The plan was only just entering its halfway stage.

Operational forces.

A sword aimed at the Bourgeois family, the kings of the business world.

'...I wonder what he's doing.'

Dolores began to become more and more curious about the identity of Night Hound.

Chapter 273

Money War (3)

◆

A fresh rumor was making waves in the business world.

“Did you hear? Colosseo Academy has a bunch of young geniuses.”

“You mean the ones who did so well in the recent mock investment competition?”

“The crazy thing is, they weren't 'mocking,' they were playing with real money.”

“Huh? Those ridiculous rates of return mean were real?”

“Why, of course. That's probably why everyone accepted the invitation today.”

Oracle. An investment club that earns ridiculous real-world profits in mock investment competitions held by the Bourgeois Family.

Not much is known about their identity.

However, it is known that they are students at the prestigious Colosseo Academy, and their identities are certain.

As such, many in the financial world were curious about the “party invitation” from Oracle.

It was common knowledge that the largest and most ornate hall in the Imperial Capital had changed hands.

The new owner had paid all cash for the building and left a huge 10% tip.

Furthermore, the rumor that the new owner immediately started renovating the exterior and interior of the big, fancy hall as soon as he bought it also freaked people out.

What's the point of building an extension on such a huge and gorgeous hall?

Therefore, not only the general public but also some of the most prominent figures in the business world were paying attention to Oracle's actions.

And then.

Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.

May Xth. Time for the nine bells of the public square clock.

It was the date and time written on the invitation sent from Oracle.

The wealthy from all over the Capital, or provinces, gathered at the party hall in response to the Oracle's invitation.

A hundred people at most, but more than three thousand with their attendants.

Then.

“What? Who's that?”

“Oh my. I can't believe he accepted the invitation.”

“This is the first time I've seen him in person.”

“Someone big is at the party.”

The old gentlemen and ladies of the business world stepped aside.

A carriage drove majestically through the center of the hall.

The family crest was a white triangle on a black background.

This was the mark of the 'Sinan' family, which was famous for being wealthy in the north.

And in the carriage was a person who caught the attention of business figures.

Viscount Sinan Saltsail, also known as the Salt Merchant.

He was the leader of the Sinan family, one of Donquixote's maternal families.

Saltsail is a famous nobleman and a wealthy merchant who is considered one of the most important merchants in the North.

His wealth, accumulated by transporting 60,000 tons of salt across the empire, is almost unrivaled in the north.

“Hehehe – yes. Let's see what kind of extravagant party you've brought people all the way to the Imperial Capital.”

Saltsail stroked his mustache and looked out of the carriage.

Then.

“...!”

Saltsail's carriage stopped.

A strange figure stood in front of him, blocking his path.

A body that still looked like a boy. His face was covered with a cute cat mask.

On his feet, he wore long boots, giving the impression that he had stepped out of a fairy tale.

Saltsail asked.

“Who are you and why are you blocking the way?”

The boy in the cat mask answered.

“My name is Cat in Boots. I am your guide to the party of the day.”

His voice was dry and emotionless, but his pronunciation was clear and understandable.

After proving his identity with the invitation in his possession, Cat in Boots climbed into Viscount Saltsail's carriage and sat down beside him.

“Now, we have about 23 kilometers to go to the party.”

Saltsail could only frown at Cat in Boots' words.

Then.

“...Hmm?”

Viscount Saltsail's eyes widened slightly.

He could see something bluish on the center road in front of him.

“What is that?”

Viscount Saltsail pulled his head out to look ahead.

Only then did he see what was in front of him.

It was a blue cloth. A large curtain had been drawn around it, covering the inside.

Cat in Boots said.

“My master has put a great effort into tonight's party. He said that the gathering of precious people could not be revealed to the outside world, so he purchased specially good silk cloth and pitched a tent around the hall.”

Now Viscount Saltsail's carriage was passing by the side of that curtain.

The silken curtain looks like a blue night on the ground.

Saltsail, who has a keen eye for luxury, immediately recognizes the material.

“Is it blue silk lined with the highest quality purple silk? Hmm, you have a good eye. I have one of those around the house, and it's 16 kilometers long.”

As Saltsail spoke in a proud tone, Cat in Boots next to him quietly said something.

“My master has circled 21 kilometers this time.”

“What?”

Saltsail looked back at Cat in Boots as if his pride had been hurt.

But Cat in Boots was just Cat in Boots, and there was no other reaction.

Soon, Viscount Saltsail's carriage arrived at the party hall.

A curtain had been drawn over the entrance to the hall, so it was hard to see the outside of the building.

He could only guess that it was a fairly tall palace-style building.

“Before you enter, I'll give you a brief instruction.”

Cat in Boots explained the 'dress code' for today's party.

Today's theme was Red capes.

However, Saltsail tilted his head as if this was his first time hearing that there was a dress code.

“I don't think I've ever heard of a dress code before.”

“Oh, no. There must have been a miscommunication, but don't worry, I have a cape for you.”

Saltsail's eyes narrowed as he saw the red cape handed to him by the Cat in Boots.

“Hmph? This is Asbestos cloth, the finest cotton cloth that has been in vogue since the Warring States Period, and it's embroidered with the teeth and claws of the vicious beasts of the western jungles. This must be a very valuable garment.”

“You must be an expert in fabrics and fabrication.”

“Of course, I have two sets of clothes like this myself.”

Saltsail was at first inclined to give in to the offer of a cheap cape.

However, in his opinion, the cape offered was very valuable, so he was quite satisfied.

The cape was also lightly enchanted, so there was no reason not to take it, as it would keep food and alcohol off of him and keep him warm.

“Would you like to have a cocktail on the way to the party?”

Cat in Boots politely held out a glass.

Red liquor and clear ice cubes floated in the clear glass.

Saltsail took the glass and grunted.

“I don't know much about alcohol. This stuff just makes me want to pee.”

“Is that so?”

Cat in Boots nodded toward Saltsail, who was complaining but was still thirsty as he poured down his cocktail.

Then.

They passed through a dark hallway into a bright, spacious room.

Saltsail's eyes widened slightly.

“Oh, this is....”

An ornate interior greeted SaltSail.

The floors were marble from southern Jasmunhald, and the ceiling was hung with a chandelier of canned rubies from the Western Red Fang Castle.

The walls were painted with red stone pigment, one of the rarest and scarcest of the rare minerals, and for some reason there was a golden sink in the center.

There are also statues carved from expensive coral, and duck down rugs on the floor.

The walls were lined with purple silk curtains and dotted with well-dressed maids holding bottles of perfume.

Even Saltail, who didn't even snort at the luxury and pleasure, nodded in approval.

“...That's nice.”

Saltsail glanced back at Cat in Boots standing in the distance.

“Beautiful main building. Someone in the Imperial Capital has some taste. It rivals the main building of my mansion.”

Saltsail nodded with a satisfied expression, as if he had found a good match for his wealth and luxury.

...But.

“What do you mean?”

Despite Saltsail's praise, Cat in Boots could only shake his head.

Then Saltsail also tilted his head.

“What I mean is, I said the main building was nicely decorated... Hmm?”

Something wasn't right.

Instead of talking, Saltsail looked around.

Sure enough, all the guests who had come with him when he entered had disappeared, leaving him alone.

Except for Cat in Boots and the maids with the perfume bottles, he was the only one here.

Saltsail said.

“No, where are all the people at the party, and why is the main hall so empty? I don't think they've all gone to the bathroom.”

Cat in Boots opened his mouth as if to say, What are you talking about?

“Of course, all the other guests are in the main building.”

“...What?”

Saltsail's expression turned puzzled.

If the main building is somewhere else, then what is this place?

To Saltsail's puzzled look, Cat in Boots told him the truth.

“This is the restroom, not the main building.”

Chapter 277

What Money Can’t Buy (1)

◆

A challenger who once sought the throne of the tycoon Bourgeois.

Silver medalist “Bourgeois J Damian”.

Director of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau and a member of the Bourgeois Landowners Guild. Wealth, honor, power, a huge luxurious mansion, fancy carriages, and a beautiful consort,

Wealth, honor, and power, he seems to have it all, so why has he lost all will to live?

“...It's a common thing.”

Damian spoke in a low voice.

As Vikir had suspected, it was his daughter.

“You can have all the money in the world, but you can't control your children, and I realized that too late.”

Damian said in a low voice.

As Vikir had known in his pre-regression life, Damian had an only child, a beautiful and only daughter.

'Bourgeois J Juliet'.

Long, bushy white hair, clear eyes. A girl with a bright smile on her face and the cuteness of a clueless puppy.

“Like all Bourgeois, my daughter was put to the test as soon as she was born.”

Damian explained the Bourgeois family tradition.

Collaterals and illegitimate children normally grow and grow within the family, but 'real children' are different.

Just as the young Baskervilles were abandoned to the wilds of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, the bourgeois scions who would eventually lead the family were sealed off and thrown into society as commoners.

Survival in society is just as difficult as survival in the wilderness.

The young Bourgeois who will one day take over the reins of the family must rely solely on his own strength to succeed in the Imperial Capital, the center of the empire, without any help from parents or family.

This is a grueling process that takes them from the bottom of the social ladder to the top, so that they don't become full of privilege and a sense of entitlement.

Damian's daughter, Juliet, also went out into the world as a commoner to gain practical experience for her age group.

During the difficult verification period, which took over a decade, she never once used her father's or the family's backing.

This was due to the Bourgeois heir's belief in Esse, Non Videri: To exist, but not to reveal.

“Bourgeois families always have two or more leaders for checks and balances and competition. In my generation, it was my brother and me.”

Bartolomeo and Damian competing for the title of patriarch.

The result was a victory for the eldest son, Bartolomeo.

...But Damian didn't give up.

Bartolomeo's only daughter and Damian's only daughter.

Coincidentally, both brothers had only one daughter.

Damian was convinced that his daughter was even more talented and skilled than his brother's daughter.

He thought that one day, when his daughter returned, he would regain all that he had lost and rise to the pinnacle of his family.

“But his hopes were shattered when his daughter gave up her exams halfway through and returned to the family.”

Juliet. While living as a commoner, she revealed her surname and family name, which disqualified her as heir.

After revealing her identity, Juliet even returned to the family home to ask her father for help.

'Father, I have someone I love.'

Damian narrowed his eyes.

“...She went out on a volunteer mission and met a sick man from an lowly backgrounds and fell in love with him. I sent her to experience the low life, and I never thought she'd settle for the low life.”

The man's name was Romeo.

He's no more than a servant, doing menial tasks, not a leader of a family.

He was an ordinary man from an ordinary background, with ordinary looks, ordinary talents, and an ordinary future.

The only thing that set him apart from the rest of the world was his weak body, his terminally ill life, and perhaps a somewhat sage-like attitude due to that?

No money, no fame, no power, no achievement, no success, no recognition, no showmanship, no interest in any of the values that the world puts its neck on... just being kind, gentle, and serving his neighbors.

To this man, who also claimed to be a bard, and whose stigma was to live in the company of nature and art, Juliet fell in love.

Damian ran a hand through his hair.

“I was angry. Because to me, he was just a lazy, backbone-less idiot. An incompetent who disguises his inability to move upward with pettiness. A scumbag who was trying to fix himself up by getting lucky with a rich young lady. That's what I thought.”

Damian was furious that his only daughter, whom he had raised so carefully and had such high hopes for, had made such an immature mistake.

But Juliet was undaunted.

'He's a good man, Dad, he has something we don't have, and maybe he can bring some happiness back to my father, who's been so disappointed ever since he didn't make it to the head of the family! If he's the one, I'm sure...!'

Of course, Damian didn't listen to his daughter.

The daughter who dropped out of a crucial exam, revealed her identity, and asked for a hefty hospital bill to save a man whose life was on the line.

Juliet's desperate plea to save Romeo's life is not accepted by Deiman.

Instead, he sends a hitman to drag Romeo to the side of the road in the rain, beat him badly, and send word that he and Juliet must part ways.

And that night.

Through a storm of lightning and pouring rain, Juliet found Damian.

“...You're my dad, right?”

Damian didn't answer.

Then Juliet spoke up, her voice low and quiet.

'In the end, he never mentioned father's name, and when I pressed him, he laughed that all fathers must think of their sons-in-law as thieves, and that he would have done the same.'

Juliet bowed her head deeply.

Then she turned and walked away.

For a moment, Damian hesitated in his anger and bitterness, but then he felt that if they parted, he would never see her again, so he finally followed her out the door.

Juliet got into the carriage and drove off in front of him.

Damian hastily organized a chase party and set out to find her.

After some time, he spots Juliet's carriage.

Juliet is carrying Romeo, who is barely able to move.

They seem to be traveling to a very faraway place. Far, far away from the eyes of the world, forever.

Damian, of course, couldn't let it go, so he unleashed his well-trained horses to follow them.

And then. There was an accident.

...Duarrr!

Rain. Slippery roads. A horse startled by thunder.

The usual clichés, the predictable ending to a tragedy.

The carriage Juliet was driving rolled over, and they died on the spot.

“What a pity.”

Vikir said dryly.

He'd heard it through the rumor, but hearing it from the source had a different weight to it.

Then.

Damian spoke up again.

“It's a little different from the rumor you heard.”

“...?”

“My daughter is not dead.”

“...!”

This was the first time Vikir had heard it.

Damian continued.

“When I first ran to the scene of the accident, my daughter was in his arms.”

“....”

“The guy was completely injured, but my daughter didn't have any injuries. I don't know how that was possible.”

The rest of Damian's story is a bit longer.

When Juliet woke up, she immediately asked about Romeo's condition.

Damian deliberately gave her the cold hard truth.

It may broke her heart, but Damian wanted his daughter to take this opportunity to give up on him and move on.

And he wanted her to find a worthy husband, someone from the imperial family or one of the other seven families, someone with a good heart.

And that's when the real tragedy began.

Juliet fainted immediately after hearing the story.

She fell into bed for a long time, woke up, and fell again.

And then she woke up and fainted, and then she woke up and fainted.

After dozens of such passages, she was finally unable to wake up.

Damian ran his hand through his hair.

“My daughter is not dead. She's just closed her eyes and will never wake up.”

Clearly breathing, but unconscious. An unknown state that responds to no medicine, no poison, no divine power.

There was nothing Damian wouldn't do to bring his daughter back to life.

He'd spent vast sums of money and called in countless elixirs, divine knowledge, and experts.

He even bowed to the other seven great families and asked for their cooperation.

But the result was failure. Failure. Failure.

Priests, shamans, pharmacists, and doctors shook their heads.

There is no cure for a wound so deep that the soul refuses to communicate.

Damian was still staring up at the night sky, his eyes blurry.

“The human heart, especially love, is such a great and wonderful thing. To think that I would try to tear it apart forcibly, for the sake of money, honor, and status. Oh, I can't believe it now. Why did I do that....”

Even the dazzling starlight doesn't shine in his eyes.

His voice was hollow and empty as he recited his longing for something that was now out of reach.

In this way, he had lost the will to live.

He couldn't even sympathize with the words of the drunkards who were laughing and talking in the party hall.

Because in the face of human love, money is really nothing, like dust.

“...I really don't know why I did it.”

Damian burst into tears.

If he could only see his daughter's smiling face once more, what would money and status and all that stuff mean?

He could take it all and throw it away.

If he had the luxury of seeing her smile, he wanted to just see her awake and apologize to her from the bottom of his heart just once.

But all of that was impossible.

He had tried so many times already, and all of them had failed.

...But.

Vikir knew there was only one way.

There was only one way, and it was a very powerful one, one that could cross the boundaries between this world and the afterlife.

The Wraith Tree.

It is a being that has direct contact with the souls of the dead, the living, and those unable to die.

Vikir spoke in a dry voice.

“What if I gave you a chance to talk to your daughter?”

“...!”

Damian's eyes widened to tears at Vikir's words.

The starlight touches the flowing tears of blood and sparkles.

Vikir asked again, more firmly.

“So, what can you give me?”

Chapter 280

What Money Can’t Buy (4)

◆

A few days later. Vikir once again visited Damian's mansion wearing the mask of the Night Hound.

“I'm glad we seem to be working together on something.”

This time, Dolores was with him.

Vikir planned to seek Damian's cooperation and introduce Dolores at the same time.

Damian's mansion was still heavily guarded, but as he'd been told, there were areas that were unguarded.

Vikir took that route with Dolores.

After passing through several gates, they came to a high wall.

Dolores stood in front of the high fence, wondering what to do.

“Come here.”

“...What!?”

Vikir picked Dolores up and scaled the fence in a flash.

...Chuck!

Landing on the courtyard, Vikir set Dolores down beside him.

“Uh... Has it already passed?”

“?”

“Oh, no, that's nonsense!”

Dolores covered her reddened ears with her hair and clapped her hands like it was nothing.

Then.

“The garden might be a bit boring to enjoy a date.”

A muffled voice came from across the garden.

Where Vikir and Dolores turned, Damian stood.

“Since you officiated at my daughter's wedding, I am willing to officiate at yours.”

“Your bullshit has increased.”

“Hahaha-is it?”

Dolores was surprised to see Vikir and Damian chatting so casually.

When she had visited him for the second round of the University League, he had been very depressed and nervous, as well as incredibly reticent.

She couldn't believe how much his personality had changed.

'By the way, is ... officiating, Night Hound? I mean, didn't Director Damian's daughter die in a car accident in the first place?'

To officiate at someone's wedding is to become their godfather, a very important ceremony for nobles.

What happened between Night Hound and Director Damian?

How did they become so close?

But Vikir did not bother to explain the past to Dolores.

“This is an ally who will help me with this.”

“Pleased to meet you, Saintess of the Quovadis. We've met before, haven't we?”

At Vikir's introduction, Damian extended his hand to Dolores.

Dolores shook her hand and returned the gesture politely.

“It is an honor to meet you again, Damian, Director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau.”

“If I had known we would be in the same boat like this, I would have seen it better then, hahaha-”

Seeing Damian's smiling face, Dolores had to gasp once more.

She'd never realized he was capable of smiling so wide.

Then. Vikir cut straight to the chase.

“I will kill Bartolomeo, the patriarch of the Bourgeois Family.”

Dolores paused, meeting Damian's eyes.

But at the mention of killing the head of his own family, his own brother, Damian didn't bat an eye.

On the contrary.

“Yes. I already prepared a place for you.”

He accepted it as a matter of course.

Damian proceeded to tell his story.

“I used a few of the family's henchmen to spread the word about the Oracle Investment Fund to Patriarch. He was very interested, to say the least, at the prospect of a young genius with a talent for investing.”

“So. Did you get him?”

“Yes.”

Damian nodded in response to Vikir's question.

Then he explained to Dolores, whose eyes were wide with confusion.

“About the dinner date.”

“Oh.”

“Mark my words. Dinner is the perfect time to assassinate my brother.”

Dolores cocked her head at Damian's newfound devotion.

“But why dinner? Why not other opportunities, such as when you are outside the family home, or in bed?”

“That is due to a peculiar habit my brother has.”

Damian explained.

“Whenever he has a meeting or a meal with someone from the outside he always brings them into the vault of his house. And at all other times, he keeps a group of highly trained private soldiers at his side.”

“In the vault?”

“Yes. The vault.”

Dolores scratched her head.

Sure, the vault might be big, but how big could it be to let outsiders in?

But Damian's next words made Dolores' jaw drop.

“The vault is shaped like a cube, over a hundred meters across, long, wide, and high, and its walls are lined with mithril and orharkon, so it's impossible to pry it open with any kind of force, and it's layered with dozens or hundreds of layers of teleportation control magic, so it's impossible to escape with magic. Of course, who designed and built it is a mystery.”

Iron Fortress. It's more like an impenetrable citadel than a vault.

“Within its vaults, gold, jewelry, money, art, and all sorts of treasures are stored in mountains and mountains of treasure. The invited guests will dine for two hours in the midst of these gold and silver treasures.”

“Why dine in such a place?”

“Because so many of the people who come to visit my brother are clueless fools, who want to show off their wealth in a grandiose way, and perhaps to kill their spirit beforehand.”

“Forgive me if I seem to be asking a lot of questions, but is there any reason why... mealtime is two hours long?”

“Because once the vault is closed, it won't open for two hours, no matter what. The reason it's set to two hours is because when the vault was first built, the knights of Ironblooded Baskerville were the ones who tested it.”

Vikir looked interested at Damian's words.

“The Knights of Baskerville?”

“Yes. My brother borrowed the Knights of Baskerville to test the safety of the vault and tried to destroy it.”

Damian stroked his chin, remembering the past.

“Those were the Pitbull Knights, I think?”

Vikir knows the Pitbull Knights well. He'd used them once before, when he'd raided an illegal slave auction.

An order dedicated to dogfighting, led by one of the Seven Counts, Boston Terrier.

They are the embodiment of strength and determination, and once they are on their feet, they must bite their opponents to death.

Damian tells an anecdote about them.

“That's when the entire Knights of the Pit Bulls came in and attacked the walls of the vault, and the walls were breached in two hours.”

What this means is that it was able to block the attacks from hundred of Graduator without stopping for two hours.

If the vault is as strong as that, then security is assured, and we can eat in peace knowing that we are absolutely safe from outside threats.

Dolores said briefly.

“Put another way... that means that once we succeed in meeting the Bourgeois patriarch inside the vault, we can run amok without outside intervention for at least two hours.”

“That's right, because those on the outside can't see or hear what's going on inside.”

“Wouldn't he be worried about being assassinated before he could get inside the vault? That seems like a reasonable concern.”

“Oddly enough, I've never heard him worry about that.”

Vikir, next to Damian, chimed in.

“That's because he's a demon with absolute power.”

“...What, a demon?”

Damian scratched his head as if he had never heard of it before.

Dolores, meanwhile, was frantically scribbling notes.

“Free time in the vault is two hours. When you go inside, you will see a mountain of treasures such as gold, currency, jewelry, and works of art. The strength of the outer wall is almost indestructible....”

In the meantime, Vikir's mind was elsewhere.

'It has become almost certain that the patriarch of the Bourgeois family is No. 6.'

Vikir was convinced, based on the research Cindywendy had recently sent back to him.

Sixth corpse. A demon working with the ninth corpse, Dantalian, to consume both the Quovadis and the Bourgeois.

Vikir thought back to the past, to the Age of Destruction.

Morale boosted by the dazzling displays of their heroes, the Human Alliance had advanced across the ruined Imperial Capital.

And they saw.

'The most beautiful being among those cast out from heaven.'

He faced the great heroes of humanity with his seemingly innate bravery, strong and powerful dignity, courage, and spirit.

However, the tactics he showed in the actual battle were cowardly, clumsy, cunning, and cruel.

His appearance was also terrible.

A thunderbolt of fire spewing from the eyes, eye glow billowing out like smoke from the world's largest beacon fire, and breath laden with a disgusting stench.

Its mouth cracked open like the cracks of an arctic ice wall, and its horns and wings spread out to either side, large enough to cover the entire battlefield.

'...I struggled with his tactics in the Legion vs. Legion battle. If he gathers strength over time, he can be a real nuisance, and we need to get rid of him as soon as possible.'

I could see why the Sixth had chosen the Bourgeois.

He must be using the money to buy an army.

A huge army of people who had unwittingly become followers of the demon.

Then. Damian asked.

“Do you think it's possible to assassinate my brother in less than two hours? He's not just a man with a lot of money, or else the previous head of the Iron-Blooded family would want him as his adopted son.”

Which meant that Hugo's father had coveted the current Patriarch of the Bourgeois's talents.

Vikir stroked his chin.

'Then that means his physical qualities are almost as good as Hugo's.'

Much time had passed since then, and now a demon controlled the body.

After some thought, Vikir nodded.

“It's going to be tight, but it's doable. If you help me with one thing outside the vault.”

“Me? Outside the vault?”

Damian shrugged.

He might be a Graduator-level prosecutor, but he wouldn't be much help in a fight.

In the first place, there was a high possibility that he wouldn't even be able to go into the vault since he was only making dinner and then leaving.

Moreover, what are they supposed to do outside of the vault, where outside intervention is completely impossible?

To a bewildered-looking Damian and Dolores.

Sigh.

Vikir pushed aside a sheet of paper with his plan.

“This is the end of the Bourgeois.”

And.

Realizing what Vikir was trying to do outside the vault, Damian and Dolores spoke at the same time in disbelief.

“This isn't about the Bourgeois....”

“...The entire empire will come to an end?”

Chapter 281

Power inflation (1)

◆

One quiet weekend. At sunset.

A carriage departed from the Colosseo Academy, heading for the Bourgeois Family.

Dolores. Pigi. Sinclaire.

The trio were honored to be hosted and dined by the Bourgeois family, the most prestigious family in the Empire.

Naturally, Pigi and Sinclaire were excited.

“Didn't our Oracle Club do great this time! 1st place in mock investment competition! And surprisingly, all of this was actually a real rate of return!”

“And we even hosted a party that was so spectacular it made my eyes roll back in my head. My God, how much did it all cost? I have no idea.”

“Did you hear about the place we're going to for dinner tonight? It's a Bourgeois family vault!”

“Yeah, I heard that, too. There's jewelry, gold bars, coins, bills, checks, drafts, real estate titles, art, antiques, all kinds of expensive stuff near the table. They say it goes beyond the mountains.”

“Hiig- that's a bit of an exaggeration, to say the least. Why would anyone put that stuff there?”

“If you put your money in a vault, then where else would you put it?”

“What if someone comes in to eat and steals it?”

“I can't imagine stealing all that stuff.”

“Oh, yes, that, too, and I wonder if these gifts we have prepared will be part of that pile of treasure, and It would be an honor to do so.”

With that, Pigi looked back at the back of the carriage.

There lay several treasure chests. A gift for the Patriarch of the Bourgeois Family.

Sinclaire looked at these gifts, which had been carefully and painstakingly prepared, and muttered to herself.

“...I wish my brother could have come with us.”

“What? You mean Vikir? Why all of a sudden?”

“...Just.”

Sinclaire replied, flicking her white short hair in the wind.

“He was supposed to come over to my place sometime. To eat.”

“?”

Pigi scratched his head.

Why was she saying that now?

Then Sinclaire smiled bitterly.

“I just suddenly felt regretful. I think it's really hard to eat a meal, looking at how busy he's been lately.”

“Oh, is that what you're talking about? I agree, it's hard to eat with Vikir these days. Except for breakfast.”

Pigi went on and on about how busy Vikir was these days.

But Sinclaire's mind was elsewhere as she listened.

'Brother. You don't pay?'

'...I have no money.'

'Money? Why don't you have money? You're an academy student. Don't you think you're being too harsh? The poor kids here don't have parents, and we should help them.'

'They don't need parents.'

'Huh?'

'They have to deal with the world on their own. Parents are only functional in childhood, when they are essential, but otherwise they are unnecessary.'

Sinclaire recall a conversation she had with Vikir many years ago when she was volunteering at a orphanage.

Meanwhile.

“....”

Up front, Dolores was not paying attention to the conversation between Pigi and Sinclaire behind her.

All her attention was focused on the treasure chest in the back of the wagon, the gift she would be giving to the Bourgeois patriarch today.

'I'm sorry, guys.'

Unfortunately, the gift sets that Pigi and Sinclaire had picked and chosen are not in that box.

They had already been moved elsewhere, and the empty box contained something else entirely.

Night Hound.

An assassin lying in ambush for the Bourgeois family patriarch.

'The Bourgeois family patriarch said he doesn't bother searching people when he lets them into the vault.'

It's a confidence peculiar to the demon, perhaps.

An arrogant attitude that no matter what assassins come, they're just toys.

But it's also his weakness.

'I must get the kids to bed before the battle begins.'

Dolores squeezed the vial in her hand.

It contained a sleeping pill that was harmless to humans.

When the carriage arrived at the Bourgeois family's residence, Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire would be escorted to the parlor, where they would wait for dinner.

Dolores planned to slip the drug into their teacups to put Pigi and Sinclaire to sleep and then hide it elsewhere.

'It would have been best if they hadn't come along in the first place....'

But Pigi and Sinclaire had been looking forward to meeting the Bourgeois family for days, and Bourgeois had invited the entire “Oracle investment circle”, so there was no point in going alone.

Even now, Pigi was making a list of questions to ask the Bourgeois patriarch.

“I need to ask about the future state of the Empire's economy, questions about current financial metrics, criteria for finding new business ventures, the recent mergers and acquisitions between the promising small merchant guilds and the mercenary guilds... and if the chaebols eat chicken!”

“I have questions, too.”

Sinclaire smiled expectantly.

Pigi turned to Sinclaire.

“Oooh, Sinclaire, what are you curious about? Do you want to play along with me?”

“...No. I only have one question.”

Pigi's eyes widen at Sinclaire's answer.

“Huh? Only one? Only one?”

“Yes.”

“No, come on, you're meeting the Empire's most powerful man, you should learn something, it's a chance you might not get again in your lifetime!”

At Pigi's enthusiasm, Sinclaire can only give a quick glance.

Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire.

Together, but with different thoughts, the trio have arrived at the front door of the Bourgeois family residence.

“Dinner appointment. The Oracle.”

Dolores announced the purpose of their visit, and the gates opened.

A carriage led the way to the interior of the ornate mansion.

Naturally, there were no checkpoints along the road reserved for guests of honor.

Then. The butler, who was leading the carriage, smiled with an easygoing smile.

“I've been seeing a lot of honorable people from the Quovadis lately.”

“Yes? Who else has come from my family?”

Dolores asked with a puzzled look, and the butler replied in a dignified manner.

“Yes. A few hours ago, Cardinal Humbert paid us a visit, though he has now returned from his business.”

Dolores felt a chill run down her spine at the mention of the name 'Humbert'.

'I hadn't expected him to be here, but... I'm glad to hear he's back.'

Dolores feels no holy power in the vicinity, even when she stretches out her senses just in case.

If Humbert had been here, he could have been a nuisance.

While she pondered this, the butler escorted everyone into the parlor.

“Please wait here for a few moments, and I will bring your message in shortly.”

The butler placed a simple tea and refreshments on the table, then opened the door and left.

Dolores, Pigi, and Sinclaire began to wait in the parlor.

“The parlor is very luxurious. It looks expensive, but not extravagant. It has an ancient beauty to it.”

“I see. Good taste.”

Pigi and Sinclaire make small talk.

Rattling...

Dolores was fidgeting with her hands.

'Soo, I need to put some sleeping pills in it.'

The worst thing she'd ever done in her life.

The very idea of putting something in someone else's food was new to her.

And then.

Dolores succeeded in slipping the sleeping pills into the teacups while Pigi and Sinclaire were looking away.

Without thinking, Pigi and Sinclaire drank the tea and soon began to doze off.

“Mmmm. Don't you feel a little sleepy?”

“Yeah, it's dinner time....”

Dolores turned to Pigi and Sinclaire and said in a shaky voice.

“Hey, hey, hey,... no, guys, if you're tired, keep your eyes closed for a while and I'll wake you up.”

“Oh, can you do that?”

“Thanks!”

To their relief, Pigi and Sinclaire leaned back against the couch in the parlor and closed their eyes without question.

“Hey, is it supposed to be potent?”

Dolores waved her hand in front of Pigi and Sinclaire's eyes.

As expected, they didn't stir.

Dolores breathed a sigh of relief and stepped out of the room to wipe off the sweat.

Then she ran into the butler again, who was coming this way.

“Ah, my lady. My lord has been busy, so I'm a little late, but I'm sure he'll be ready soon.”

“Yes! By the way, Butler, I thought my friends who came with me would have to go back due to an unexpected incident...”

“What? Before the meeting? No matter how late you've prepared... , shall we cancel the meeting and postpone it to another time?”

“No, no, no, you don't have to do that, I'll just see him alone as the head of the club.”

The butler shook his head, but somehow seemed to be convinced.

A little after the appointed time.

Dolores packed the gifts into a cart and headed deeper into the main building with a small attendant.

After walking for a while, the vault in question came into view.

It was like an entrance to a great plaza.

“My lord is waiting for you.”

The butler bowed respectfully, then opened the door.

It was dark and cold inside.

The attendants stowed the carts of gifts Dolores had brought inside, then showed her inside.

And then. All the attendants bowed and slowly slipped out the back door.

Dolores was left alone in the vast darkness of the vault.

“...Uh, excuse me. My lord?”

Dolores cautiously opened her mouth.

...Pas!

Suddenly, the room was filled with light.

At the same time, Dolores couldn't help but open her mouth.

A magnificent golden incense. A blinding golden light.

A world of great wealth was welcoming her.

Chapter 282

Power inflation (2)

◆

Countless candles were lit in unison.

The dripping candle wax ran down the pile of gold coins beneath them and hardened into a solid mass.

“...Oh my god.”

Dolores looked around at her illuminated surroundings and opened her mouth.

The vault's vast world could be summarized in one word.

Wealth.

Something that vaguely transcended the average human's imagination of how wealthy a human could be.

Gold coins, ingots, jewelry, and other things of value rolled down hills and formed great mountains that rose steadily beyond them, forming mountain ranges.

On the ceiling, stalactite-like formations dripped down, and they, too, were made of gold and jewels.

Countless golden goblets and swords, crowns, necklaces, earrings, rings, brooches, costly antiques, jewelry so brilliant and sparkling that it blinded the eye, countless documents and papers proving property rights, works of art of incredible value, bottles of extremely rare liquors, and so much more lay littered everywhere.

The wealth is so overwhelming that anyone can't even begin to fathom where it's coming from.

The whole world is a brilliant golden fragrance with five colors based on gold.

Not even the golden city on the pages of a mythological book, nor the hidden fortune of a pirate king, whose legend is told through the mouths of elderly men, can match this splendor, grandeur, and luxury!

“...It's a different world.”

Dolores felt her spirits drop slightly.

Although she usually placed no value on wealth, she couldn't help but be intimidated by a wealth of this magnitude.

It was no longer mere wealth, but the majesty and holiness of Mother Nature itself.

'It is because there are so many one-day puppies who don't know how to behave, and some of them are so eager to show off their wealth with a foolish desire to win. I wonder if it is to kill their spirit beforehand.'

Dolores understood fully what Damian had said.

In this wide world, are there one or two frogs in a well who have made a fortune?

The Bourgeois family, who is said to be at the peak of wealth, will constantly attract a swarm of flies to compare themselves with the Patriach.

It would certainly be efficient to get rid of such nuisances by showing them this view and letting them crawl away on their own.

Then.

“...!”

Walking among the piles of gold, Dolores could now see into the depths of the vault.

At the end of the dazzling and dizzying array of gold and silver treasures, she could see a magnificent mound rising up.

A mountain of gold coins, and a staircase.

At the top was a large table, carved entirely from ivory.

And a man sitting across from the table, candlelight flickering in the shadows, greeting her.

“Welcome, holy woman. Or rather, the Oracle's representative.”

A face with long white hair and a full beard, gentle eyes and a stern mouth.

'Bartolomeo J Bourgeois,' the patriarch of the Bourgeois family, was waving his hand in her direction.

◆

“You are very resourceful.”

Bartolomeo had said this when the dinner had just begun.

Dolores looked up and Bartolomeo smiled.

“I've seen your investments this time. It must have been difficult for you to invest so much money in such a risky investment, but I can learn from your boldness.”

“Because I believed in the business idea of someone named Cindywendy.”

Dolores answered as Night Hound had told her to.

Hearing her answer, Bartolomeo nodded.

“Cindywendy. A young businessman who is making quite a name for herself in the west. I have often admired her skill in dealing with the barbarians of the western jungles, but her fame has not yet spread to the business circles of the Imperial City, and not many have recognized her. Our saint's eyesight is unusual, I see. You have great years of experience.”

“Years? I'm just a teenager with a lot to learn.”

“Age has nothing to do with it. I have made many preparations, many challenges, and many failures in my life. Preparation, challenge, and failure. These three things are woven together to form a single thread called age.”

Bartolomeo repeatedly praised Dolores in a tone full of goodwill.

“If you've proven yourself by accomplishing this much, what if you're a year older, what if you're a hundred years older? You have every right to be proud, no matter where you came from, if you've traveled a long way, you have every right to be proud, but if you're complaining and haven't taken a single step from the starting line, you have no right to complain.”

What if the person sitting in front of him was an ordinary student at Colosseo Academy?

It would have been easy to be overwhelmed by all the praise, encouragement, recognition, and respect that the world's number one man was so generously giving.

The feeling of pride and pleasure when hard work is recognized.

It is the demon's tongue that pierces through the cracks in the heart that it has opened.

'Night Hound says that among them all, the 6th is especially skilled in speech.'

Dolores looked at Bartolomeo before her.

A handsome gentleman. A soft voice. A favorable accent. And words of praise that sounded genuine.

But Dolores was not fooled by these things.

Partly because of her mental strength, but mostly because her investment performance was not her own doing.

She's not particularly happy to be praised for something she didn't do.

“You're too kind.”

Dolores forced a smile.

And Bartolomeo seems to have misunderstood a little bit from her lukewarm response.

“Hmm. I'm sorry to hear about Quilt.”

“...?”

Dolores tilted her head in question, and Bartolomeo gave her a look that made him feel terribly sorry for her.

“Come to think of it, the saint belongs to the New Testament.”

“....”

“I am acquainted with the priests of the Old Testament.”

Apparently, Bartolomeo assumed that Dolores was a member of the New Testament, and was dissatisfied with him for being friendly with the priests of the Old Testament.

Bartolomeo offered a non-excuse.

“But if you are afraid to distance yourself from me because of that, I am sorry for you. I am friendly with the priests of the Old Testament, as you think.”

“....”

“But I want to be friendly with the New Testament as well, and I just can't do that because they belittle and denigrate me, my bond with the Old Testament, and the wealth we are accumulating as inhuman, dirty, ugly, and undesirable.”

Bartolomeo said as he sliced through the bleeding meat with his knife.

“The truth is, 'wealth' is colorless, odorless, tasteless, shapeless, tasteless, scentless, and It's extremely value-neutral. If you use it well, it is good, and if you use it badly, it is bad.”

“....”

“It's like how a fire can burn down a mountain, but it can also save a dying match girl in a winter alley.”

“....”

“Those who treat it as a bad thing are just losers who have never touched big money in their lives. Either that, or they've been brainwashed by the vested interests who made their fortunes by controlling the order of this society in the first place.”

As he concluded, Bartolomeo added briefly.

“If you do great good with great money, that's something, too, so don't hate the Old Testament so much.”

Dolores was used to hearing this logic.

It was the kind of logic her stepfather, Humbert, used to preach.

“....”

Dolores glanced at the hourglass placed at the edge of the table.

Time had already passed.

Dolores counted the seconds in her mind and opened her mouth.

“A lot of money for a lot of good, I hope it goes as you said.”

“It is. Hahaha-”

Bartolomeo laughed pleasantly, pleased that Dolores had agreed with him.

He took a slice of the meat on his plate, stuffed it into his mouth, and chewed.

“More than that, saint, why are you not eating, is it not to your taste, do you not like meat?”

“No. It must be good meat, seeing as how patriarch enjoyed it so much.”

“Of course I do. It is the finest meat. I am particularly sensitive to the quality of meat. Eat slowly. There's still plenty of time.”

At Bartolomeo's gesture for the meat, Dolores responded with a gentle smile.

“I'm sorry, sir. I'm not a fan of human flesh.”

“...!”

For a moment, Bartolomeo's hand stopped.

He slowly raised his head and looked at Dolores.

“Hohoho. You're joking too much, saint. Are you implying that this meat is the result of the exploitation of the blood and flesh of the lower classes? If so, I take back what I said earlier....”

“No, no. I meant human meat, and I knew it.”

“ ...What?”

Bartolomeo asked, and the smile faded from Dolores' face.

She answered in a hard tone.

“That Bartolomeo, the patriarch of the Bourgeois, is not only acquainted with the Old Testament of the Quovadis, but is intent on swallowing them whole.”

“Hohoho-”

“And to that end, he has been nurturing numerous heresies and cults, laying the groundwork to shake the Quovadis to its very foundations.”

“Hohoho-”

“And that Bartolomeo, the beast behind it all, is actually the demon himself.”

“...!”

Even Bartolomeo couldn't help but laugh at Dolores' last words.

Then.

“Hohohoho-keuhahahaha!”

Bartolomeo, who had been laughing lowly, began to laugh loudly.

The sound was so loud that it resonated with the simultaneous clinking of countless gold coins that formed a mountain around them.

Dolores asked in a voice that never wavered.

“Aren't you afraid, a visitor who knows your identity?”

“Scared? Of course not.”

Bartolomeo looked at Dolores with a grin on his face, a look of amusement on his face.

“Is there anyone in this world who can scare me?”

Madness. The confidence of a demon. A man who had done great evil with great money.

An overwhelming force rushed through Dolores, squeezing her entire body.

...Then.

Paas-

There was something else, something that scattered the pressure on Dolores' body.

On the other side of the table, on a mountain of gold coins, the red light of a candle flickers.

It was the same place where Bartolomeo turned his head with a grim expression and Dolores turned her head with a bright one.

“Here it is.”

Night Hounds.

The Demon Hunter, who had been through countless hells, reeked of blood.

Chapter 286

Power inflation (6)

◆

A shower of gold coins rains down over a vast area.

Clink, clink, clink, clink, clink!

It was a terrifyingly destructive force that warped the surrounding landscape.

...But.

Vikir walked through the swirling cloud of gold dust and stood nonchalantly.

'The Wailing Wall'. The Seventh Corpse of Decarabia.

The demonic shield that was once an insurmountable wall for mankind was now on the side of man, protecting Vikir!

[...It's been a long time, Belial].

Belial's eyes widened at the sound of Decarabia's voice.

[What the hell is going on, Decarabia, and why are you coming out of there now?]

[I come out where I want to come out when I want to come out].

[That's not what I meant. What about your great mission to open the gates, and what are you doing here?]

[Didn't you just say a moment ago that you don't need companions; why don't you try opening the gate on your own?]

Belial gritted his teeth in disbelief at the tastelessness of Decarabia's voice.

[I'm sure I can open the gate by myself when this vault is full, I don't need those ungrateful companions!]

After all, he had just shouted those words.

Belial swallowed hard at his anger, then spoke in a softened voice.

[Decarabia, it will never be good for you to betray us in this way].

[Betrayal? The word is wrong, young one, for I have never been on anyone's side by nature].

[Are you confident, then, that you can bear the wrath of your companions, that you can bear the wrath of one who is 'one and all', who is 'all and one'?]

[...The answer shall be bound for ever by oath].

This was the end of Belial and Decarabia's conversation.

Apparently, Decarabia would not answer any more of Belial's questions.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“Belial is a demon of commerce, but he is also a demon of speech, and the two are inseparable, so the answer is not to talk too long.”

[I know the cunning of his tongue, human; more importantly, how does it feel to use me, isn't it wonderful?]

Vikir stared at Decarabia's self-praise for a moment.

The translucent shield glowed a dusky red as if to show off.

Its mana cost was staggering, but its ability to block physical damage made it one of the most powerful shields ever created.

Moreover, since the size and hardness can also be adjusted, it seemed like it could be used efficiently if mana control could be controlled in detail.

“...It's usable.”

[Heh- usable? That's all you can say about it?]

While grumbling unhappily, Decarabia glanced toward Dolores behind him.

[Well, it doesn't matter, it's nice to be able to protect a beautiful woman, and of course, a handsome man. But most of all, the person worth protecting is a handsome man dressed as a beautiful woman, or a beautiful woman dressed as a handsome man. This body that loves good, evil, and all chaos....]

“Shut up, here they come again.”

Vikir raised Decarabia and braced himself for the attack ahead.

As if on cue, Belial unleashed a massive bombardment of gold coins from his two hands.

Clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink-

A loud crackling noise, accompanied by sparks of fire, shook the shield of the inverted pentagram.

But Decarabia's shields, almost unbeatable in physical defense, didn't budge.

'...I like it, but the mana cost is too much.'

The loud vibration of the mana hole at the bottom makes me feel extremely seasick.

It seemed that in order to build up the proficiency of Decarabia, a considerable amount of mana accumulation was required before using the Shield Technique.

Then.

“Hey, hey, hey...you can put me down now.”

Dolores covered her face and whispered in a low voice.

Her ears, peeking out of her hair, were red beyond reddening.

Vikir quietly lowered her to the ground, still clasped around his waist.

Then he spoke.

“You don't have to be so hard on yourself. We're colleagues.”

“...!”

Dolores' eyes widened at the words.

Night Hound had called her a colleague.

And the moment Dolores heard those words.

...Pounding!

His heart began to beat wildly.

'Why, what's wrong with my chest? I feel something hot inside....'

Dolores pressed her hand firmly against her left breast.

An unexplained power stirred within.

An unidentifiable warmth began to emanate from her left breast and spread throughout her body.

'Is this another Soul Mate effect?'

It's similar to the feeling Dolores had before Dantalian.

Although she was too distraught now to make a detailed comparison.

Then.

[Die, you bastards!]

Belial scattered gold coins again.

A shower of gold flew in like a barrage of bullets, and this time, a black wave cannon was added that spewed out from Belial's mouth.

KOOOOOOOOO!

A storm of gold and darkness sweeping all around!

[Oh, no, not the wave].

Decarabia blocked the showers of gold coins with ease, but seemed to be overwhelmed by Belial's magical attack that followed.

Then.

“Don't worry!”

Dolores cheerfully stepped forward once more.

...Pow!

A wall of holy fire, much larger and thicker than before, blocked Belial's wave cannon.

Belial's magic is shattered and scattered by the holy power.

But Belial would not be defeated so easily this time.

[A mere ember before a strong wind, an insignificant aura!]

As the gold coins in the vault were absorbed into Belial's massive body, the magical energy he emitted grew thicker and thicker.

“Ugh! Such a powerful demon. How...!”

Dolores gritted her teeth as she felt her divine shield being pushed back.

Meanwhile, Vikir was gauging the distance of his sword strike, looking for an opening behind Dolores' shield.

“Even just this amount is a big help. Thanks.”

Dolores felt her spirits rise a little more at Night Hound's words.

'...But compared to the Dantalian battle, it's a world of difference.'

Dolores wished she could be more helpful to Night Hound, somehow.

She wanted to share the burden he was carrying.

She wanted him to rely on her just a little more.

To be something he could count on, something he could lean on.

'The name is the color of soul mates!'

Dolores finally stopped hesitating and turned her head.

“Night Hound!”

“...?”

Dolores exclaimed as Vikir turned his head, trying to look as confident as possible.

“Please tell me your name!”

“...What?”

Vikir scratched his head, and Dolores grunted.

“As you can see, it's getting harder and harder to hold up the defenses!”

She was right.

Even Dolores' divine power, which seemed to be overflowing due to her innate talents and blessings, was now slowly running out.

“I need that 'resonance' phenomenon to increase my divine power!”

Dolores was referring to the 'soul mate' phenomenon.

“If I can resonate with Night Hound even more deeply, if our bond is strengthened even a little more, it will definitely make a difference!”

A soul mate in a certain color, and they don't even know each other's names.

Dolores suddenly thought this was very unreasonable.

“It's okay if it's not your full name! Can't you at least give me the smallest nickname that I can call you... Could you please tell me at least one word of your name?”

Dolores asked, her eyes shining despite the difficulty of the situation.

A slender girl, holding back the immense power of a demon, how long could those thin, slender arms hold out?

“....”

Vikir decided that now was not the time to hesitate.

And as soon as he had made up his mind, he stomped his feet and headed for Dolores.

Night Hound leaned down to whisper in Dolores's ear as she held up the defenses.

“....Van”

A name that catches her breath. And hot breath.

Dolores flinched for a moment.

'...It was called “Van”.'

Dolores felt her heart beat even faster.

A common name. The process of getting to know each other by going through each other's names.

Names are indeed mysteriously powerful.

Even if Dolores only heard a short version of the name, she felt as if the emotional and psychological distance between her and Night Hound had been shortened.

'Maybe... I'm the only one in the world who knows his name.'

Dolores's heart began to beat wildly in her chest.

Thump-thump-thump-thump.

The holy fire of the divine power grew hotter and more intense.

...Passss! Kurrrrr!

The unexplained emotions that had been stirring in her chest earlier pulsated harder and harder.

The heart beating, the divine power pulsating in time with it, the white flame pulsating vividly!

It was the moment when the Soul Mate awakened once again.

“Iyaaah!”

Dolores unleashed her holy power with all her might, completely knocking back the wave cannon that Belial was spitting out.

[Ugh!?]

As his attack shattered and scattered, ultra-high temperature white flames rushed in, burning his mouth.

Belial could only gasp in horror.

“That's it, that's it, that's it!”

Dolores exclaimed, looking down at her hands.

Something she could not do to anyone else and could not explain.

Only Night Hound...... No, a miracle that only happens when she's with 'Van'.

Vikir wanted to congratulate Dolores for once again performing a miracle as a 'Saint of Steel', but unfortunately, there wasn't enough time.

“Gap!”

Baskerville 8th Form. The Shattering Tooth.

Eight air-tearing strikes fly out, aimed at Belial.

Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!

A horrific scream erupts from the explosion.

It was a devastating final act from a demon.

...But.

Charrrrrrr!

Once again, the gold coins began to move rapidly.

A golden serpent slithered through the thick smoke.

Having absorbed so many treasures, Belial soon laid his unharmed body on the ground.

[It was hot, but still a worthless struggle].

Belial had a sneer on his lips as if he had never cried out in pain.

“...This is going to be an unfavorable war of attrition.”

Dolores said, flames spewing from both hands.

Vikir couldn't help but agree.

“We just have to hold out a little longer. Time is on our side.”

“...?”

Dolores scratched her head at Vikir's words.

She still hadn't figured out what Night Hound, who was saying the exact opposite while becoming more disadvantageous as time passed.

Just then.

An unexpected favorable development occurred.

Quack Quack Quack! Pufffff!

Belial, who was sucking in gold coins, fell back due to a sudden explosion.

[Mmm!? What the hell!]

The gold coins that had been rushing toward Belial stopped.

Suddenly, large golden walls rose up and blocked the flow of funds.

At the same time, a large golden fist rose up from the floor and struck Belial on the head.

...BANG!

Belial was knocked back once more, spitting out his broken teeth.

“What, what, who?”

Dolores turned her head with wide eyes.

Vikir did the same.

“...!”

An unexpected figure suddenly burst into the battlefield and attacked Belial.

Underneath the messy white hair, the face that looks as innocent as a puppy can be seen gradually changing into a complex expression due to various emotions.

Fear. Confusion. Astonishment. Shock. Anger.

Sinclaire.

She stood at the center of all these emotions.

Chapter 287

Power inflation (7)

◆

“What is this, a dream?”

Sinclaire looked around with a trembling gaze.

Bartolomeo with his eyes open and a giant demonic figure floating above him.

The demon's opponents are Night Hound and St. Dolores, holding hands.

??

Sinclaire just kept blinking as if he couldn't believe the current situation.

Dolores was very puzzled.

'Why is Sinclaire here! Surely she must have drunk the tea with the sleeping pills!'

She asked, trying to stay calm.

“Sinclaire, are you okay? From the looks of it, you've been poisoned with sleeping pills....”

“...Egh, I'm fine, ugh- I've just gotten a little tolerant from taking so many different types of sleeping pills on a daily basis.”

Sinclaire usually has a very tight schedule, including part-time work, school work, personal study, and extracurricular activities.

What she didn't realize was that she was taking multiple sleeping pills due to stress and had developed a very high tolerance to them.

However, even so, the efficacy of sleeping pills cannot be ignored.

Sinclaire's eyes were still slightly open, as if she was half asleep.

“I was so sleepy that I stumbled and fell on top of an open crate, which must have been closed before I realized it, but what kind of situation is this? Um, I mean, what the hell is that, and Night Hound....?”

She asked, looking back and forth between Belial and Vikir.

Dolores gritted her teeth.

“Sinclaire, I'll explain everything later, but for now, come here....”

But she didn't finish her sentence.

Belial laughed and raised a giant fist.

[It wouldn't be a bad idea to weed out useless relationships at this point. As of this time, all plays have ended.]

Bartolomeo's body snapped once more, and the terrifying magic exploded.

Sinclaire's eyes narrowed at the sight of it.

Quack, quack, quack, quack!

Next. Belial's fist came slamming down on Sinclaire.

Watching Belial's attack fall like a meteorite, Dolores cried out in horror.

“Si, Sinclaire! No!”

She ran, maximizing her divine power, but it wasn't enough to keep up.

...But.

“...!”

Dolores gasped in surprise.

Boom, dududududu!

Sinclaire had blocked Belial's fist.

Huge golden palms protruded from the floor and walls, blocking Belial's fist.

[...? What the hell is this].

Belial frowned at the unexpected interruption.

But it wasn't just any interruption.

Fufufufufufufuf!

Golden spikes sprouted from the back of the golden hand and pierced Belial's fist.

[!?]

As Belial quickly pulled his hand away, he began to notice changes in his surroundings.

Clatter!

Waves of gold coins.

Treasures piled high everywhere were rushing toward them in waves.

Not toward Belial, but toward Sinclaire!

Criririring, clink, clink, clink!

The golden snakes were being sucked toward the hat Sinclaire was holding in his hand.

Sinclaire's mana was growing stronger and stronger as well.

'Money Hat'.

This was the prize Sinclaire received for placing eighth in the University League.

'Hehe- money is power, so I'll have to make a lot of money to wear this hat.'

A hat that makes your magic stronger when you spend money on it.

Although it was worn here and there and the brim had teeth missing, it was an effective artifact.

Grururung!

Putting on the hat, Sinclaire cast another spell.

The gold coins and bullion around her began to melt in the flames, then coalesced together to form a giant fist.

...BANG!

Belial's head turns again.

[Annoying].

Belial's pupils, which were as wide as those of a mountain goat, were young.

...Oof!

Bartolomeo's body moved.

The Balmung in his hand drew a strange trajectory and twisted like a snake with hundreds of joints.

“...Eugh!?”

Blood fountains burst out from all over the body.

Sinclaire stepped back to avoid Bartolomeo, who swung his sword in front of her.

“Patriarch!? Why are you like this! Ugh!?”

She cries out in confusion as if she recognizes Bartolomeo's face.

Dolores, seeing it, shouts.

“Sinclaire, he's not the patriarch of the Bourgeois family, he's just a puppet whose body was taken over by the demon long ago!”

“No!? That's not possible. A demon?”

“Please believe me...!?”

But this time, Dolores couldn't finish her sentence.

...Bam!

Vikir, flying on Madame's wire, soared upward with Sinclaire around her waist.

Boom!

The area where Sinclaire was standing just a moment ago was devastated by Bartolomeo's strike.

“Boom!”

Sinclaire flinched when she saw the face of the person who had grabbed her.

Night Hound. His eyes glowed a grim red from the slits in his mask.

“Hey, get off me! Villain!”

She quickly drew up her mana, but she'd already used up too much of it just a moment ago, creating and maneuvering her giant golden hand.

'Eating money makes me stronger, but there's a limit to how fast I can eat.'

Vikir set the struggling Sinclaire back down on the ground.

“...?”

The unexpectedly polite landing stunned Sinclaire for a moment.

Vikir purposely scratched his voice harder and spoke in short bursts.

“There's no point in getting involved. If you get taken hostage for no reason, I'll be in trouble, so stay back.”

“...Hostage? Trouble?”

Sinclaire looked confused.

She quickly calmed her breathing.

The way her eyes suddenly become harsh is truly the attitude of a genius.

“If they took me hostage, so why should you, the 'Night Hound', be in trouble? Do you know me?”

“....”

“It doesn't mean that you are on the side of justice right now. Then why did you save me? Bait to divert attention? Who made Mr. Bartolomeo like that? Is that you? What is your connection with President Dolores?”

Sinclaire's nonstop barrage of questions was calm and sharp, but with a slight tremor at the end.

It was like a sword in the hands of an unwary child.

And the experienced Vikir knew how to deal with such fragile swords.

“The demon is absolute evil. You wouldn't be so stupid as to not know that, right?”

“I can't believe you treat me like a child... There doesn't seem to be much difference in age...”

“Being the opposite of absolute evil doesn't necessarily make you good, but at least you'll know which side you're on when it comes down to it.”

“....”

“What you choose to see, what you choose to believe, and what choices you choose to make are entirely up to you.”

It's about “not getting entangled” in the first place.

There's no need to persuade, there's no need to impress. Just follow your own path.

Having finished, Vikir turned his head.

And in front of him, a wide-eyed Bartolomeo was running towards him, holding the magic sword Balmung.

Jzzz-ugh!

Vikir slashed at Bartolomeo's right hand with his sword.

And it even left deep scars on the body of Belial beyond that.

[Grunts, but it's no use!]

Belial cried out in pain, but only for a moment, and then he absorbed the gold and silver treasures around him to regenerate his wounds.

So much wealth, so much greed!

As long as there is money and people want it, value is eternal.

Belial feeds on money, value, and greed, and enjoys unlimited life and power!

But Vikir did not give up.

“I'm coming.”

“I've got your back!”

Vikir lays down his sword to level it and Dolores grants protection from behind.

And then.

...Flash!

With a dazzling light, eight teeth engulfed in white flame bite the whole world.

Baskerville 8th Form. Perfect state.

It ferociously slashed at Belial's entire body.

[Ghahahahaha! It's no use! As long as the money in the vault doesn't dry up, I can recover as much as I want!]

Belial laughed out loud, despite the wounds and pain shooting through his body.

And then.

Chirrrrrrrrrrr! Clink Clink!

Another clatter of gold coins.

Belial sucked in a huge amount of money.

[How is it? The infinite and eternal power of this body...!]

However.

[...?]

Belial couldn't help but stop laugh.

As expected, even after absorbing such a vast amount of wealth, his physical strength had not been fully restored.

[Huh? What is this? What's going on?]

Belial looked down at the gold coins, banknotes, jewelry, and bundles of money that were being sucked into his body.

They were clearly accumulating in his body, but strangely, the rate at which his health was recovering was getting slower and slower.

The volume and weight of his riches remained the same.

However, the resulting recovery gradually decreased noticeably, and in the end, it became virtually ineffective.

[???]

Belial stared in disbelief at the deep scars that still marked every inch of his body.

And ahead of him.

“It's about time.”

Vikir took a step forward.

“Do you wonder why your recovery has been so slow?”

Vikir asked Belial, who looked puzzled.

With that, Vikir took out a piece of paper from his pocket and flew it towards Belial.

[...!?]

Belial's eyes widened as if torn apart.

[URGENT BREAKING NEWS] Mysterious Currency Dropped in Imperial City, Counterfeit Bills or a Sign of Hyperinflation?

-Yesterday evening, a large amount of mysterious money was dispersed in the skies of the Imperial Capital...

The unidentified gold coins and bills, which were contained within a giant balloon, poured down like a shower all over the empire, regardless of time and place...

Citizens are nervous, not knowing if the money is counterfeit or if there really is a lot of money unleashed on the market, and economic experts fear a short-term loss of trust in the unredeemable currency...

That was the article in the morning paper, scheduled to be published tomorrow morning.

Chapter 288

Power inflation (8)

◆

Inflation.

Currency expansion (Inflation). The phenomenon in which currency becomes so plentiful that its value decreases.

◆

Balloons rose simultaneously in major central areas, including the Imperial Capital, the center of the empire.

The large balloons rose into the sky at one o'clock in the morning and soon burst due to the difference in air pressure or other external factors.

The contents of the balloons rained down to the ground.

It was 'money' such as banknotes, gold coins, etc.

As a result of the huge amount of money being released into the Imperial Capital, citizens became distrustful of money.

“Banknotes? I won't take them, I'd rather barter.”

“How do I know if these gold coins are real or fake? I can't take deposits for a while.”

“Oops, I thought I was going to get rich, but this isn't what I expected.”

“I guess we'll have to use the bills for firewood and the gold coins for weights.”

“Isn't this going to ruin the country?”

There was food hoarding, and no one wanted to trade their necessities for money.

And there were two pairs of eyes watching this massive mess.

“ ...The Director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau is allowed to do this?”

Cindywendy, a beautiful golden-haired woman. Where she sends her curious gaze, a middle-aged man with brown hair stands.

Bourgeois J Damian. He is the director of the Imperial Money Manufacturing Bureau.

The two of them stand atop a tall tower, watching the money scatter across the empire.

A staggering amount of counterfeit money. The naked eye could never determine their authenticity.

It was a work that Director Damian put a lot of effort into creating.

In charge of distributing and dispersing the counterfeit currency throughout the empire was Cindywendy, the master of logistics.

Damian said in a low voice.

“If you're going to dig a grave, you have to dig two. For my brother's, and mine.”

“Good posture. I guess you've been sharpening your knife for a long time?”

“It's been a long time since I harbored a desire for revenge against my family. I never thought I could achieve that with someone else's hands.”

“...I can sympathize with you, as I've been in a similar situation.”

Cindywendy and Damian. Both have someone they want to avenge, so they teamed up with Night Hound.

“We're both aligned with scary men.”

The two had a pretty similar opinion.

Whoosh,Cririringgg!

A shower of gold coins falling in the distance, a wind of billowing bills.

Damian furrowed his brow as he caught the rain of falling gold coins.

“Counterfeit gold coins look just like the real thing, but because they're cast in fake metal, they're much lighter in weight, so it doesn't hurt as much when they fall from a great height. You can tell the difference by holding it in your hand, though it can be hard to tell if it's mixed in with the real thing.”

“But what about bills? They're lighter, and they look the same.”

“Both counterfeit bills and counterfeit gold coins are dyed with magic dyes, so they'll lose their color in a couple of hours. I don't want to prolong the confusion on the waterfront.”

Damian is right.

The counterfeit currency distributed throughout the Imperial Capital automatically becomes trash after two hours.

But for at least those two hours, the Empire's prices will be in shambles.

The distrust of fiat currency will cause the citizens of the Empire to care about real things, not money, and naturally the greed and craving for “money” itself will fade.

Cindywendy asked.

“But. What's the point of reducing the value of money to near zero for only two hours?”

“Two hours. That's enough time to decide the fate of an entire world. Of course, it would be too much for criminals like us.”

Damian set his jaw. Then, in a low voice, he answered.

“ ...For some non-criminal(Extraordinary person) who may be fighting for his life at this very moment.”

◆

Belial was stunned.

[No, no way, why is my recovery getting slower and slower!!!]

No matter how much money I suck, I can't recover my health.

Money. Human greed. The value attached to it.

Something must have gone wrong in this cycle.

[How could humans not want money? Their greed knows no bounds! How come...!]

Belial looked confused.

It made sense, since there was nothing money couldn't do.

But.

“Gold is not omnipotent.”

Vikir said, taking a step forward.

The words 'for at least two hours' were omitted.

It was only a matter of time before the vault would be opened.

In the meantime, the countless gold and silver treasures in the vault will continue to lose value.

'With the entire empire distrustful of money, the world has become an age of barter.'

So all this money is worthless.

Of course, it was only a short affair, but it had great meaning for Vikir.

...Flash!

The Eight Teeth of Vikir, strengthened by divine power, viciously raged all over Belial's body.

Dolores was constantly sending buffs to Vikir's back.

“Lunianus homo omnium dominus est liberrismus, nulli subiectus, a free master over all things! A Lunian is an entirely faithful servant of all things and enslaved to all. (Lunianus homo omnium servus est offciosissimus, omnibus subiectus)!”

The souls of two men who have led very different lives resonate.

Vikir generously unleashes the power of the Swordmaster.

Baskerville Eight. The high-speed spinning aura of an intermediate Swordmaster slices and dices everything it touches.

Iron Body. The spirit of a superhuman.

A body trained to the extreme, loaded like a taut bowstring.

Muscle fibers throughout his body twitch like thorns, ready to tear through his skin.

His pupils sharpened as he searched for the perfect point to deliver the final blow.

A sharp and heavy weapon aimed straight ahead is shot forward, supported by only one big toe.

And then a slash that threatens to tear the world apart!

Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack!

Belial cried out as he was swept up in the aura storm, his entire body shredded and shattered.

And then.

Vikir stood haphazardly before Belial.

The body of his host, Bartolomeo, was already a wreck, and the body of Belial, who had appeared on top of him, also looked miserable.

One of its thick horns is broken, and the other is filled with cracks.

Black blood gushed from every inch of the disgustingly fat pig's head.

“Cut its neck long.”

Once Vikir had the upper hand, he never let go.

The demon hunter's teeth sank relentlessly into the demon's neck.

A hound bites a pig to death; it was a natural sight.

...But.

[Gahahahahahaha!]

Belial let out a last-minute laugh.

Vikir narrowed his eyes as his big pig nose twitched.

“What's so funny?”

[Because I look forward to seeing your expressions soon distorted horribly.]

After speaking, Belial's mouth dropped open.

Black smoke began to billow from his mouth.

Decarabia on Vikir's chest spoke in a low voice.

[That is his last ability, 'Oppression'].

“What kind of ability is that?”

[....]

Decarabia hesitated for a moment, then told him the truth.

[It's the ability to make those who kill you pay the price you deserve].

[That's right, those who kill me will die!]

Belial agreed.

He rolled his lard-glazed eyes, glancing alternately at Vikir and Dolores.

[Whoever killed me will die, and I will take him with me. The other one will be very sad, for you have lost a comrade].

“....”

[Hahahahaha! Whoever killed me will pay for it!]

Then Dolores said sourly.

“Why is it a sin to kill a demon? If it is a sin, then I will kill you and pay for it.”

[Cough cough- doesn't the doctrine of the Lun say that demons are also creatures of the Lun, and that all killing of creatures is a sin, are you sure about that?]

Belial's pig nose twitches.

Slight confusion flashed across Dolores's face.

Just then.

“Don't play with the demon's tongue.”

Vikir's sword sliced through Belial's throat in an instant.

...Poof!

Black blood gushed out like a fountain.

Belial rolled his eyes in disbelief.

[Eh, how can you not move an inch, I, my tongue... this, this, this, aren't you afraid of sin...?]

But Vikir didn't mind at all.

And then.

...Thud!

Something was stuck to Belial's forehead.

A piece of paper stained with black blood.

Belial's face twisted in despair as he realized its identity.

'All sins of this faithful church member are forgiven.'

– This indulgence was issued and endorsed by the Old Testament, and counterfeiting it was punishable by death.

For a moment, a scene from the past flashed before Belial's eyes.

A memory of one of countless descendants.

'If I can repent for sins committed in the past, can I repent for sins committed in the future?'

'..., But what kind of sin is so serious that you're looking for such an expensive indulgence?'

'I think I'm going to kill one of my neighbor's pigs.'

'That's right. I'll give it to you because you're lucky to have gotten this far for the life of one pig.'

Bang-

'Yes, you have repented~'

It was an indulgence that Vikir had purchased at the temple of the Old Testament in the past, and the price was only one gold.

[...Ah, no].

Belial. The great demon who descended to destroy mankind.

The life of an absolute being who monopolized all the wealth of the human world, was replaced by an indulgence worth a single gold coin.

“It's over. You 'Worthless One.'”

Vikir said briefly.

And the magic sword Beelzebub drew an even shorter trajectory.

...Thud!

It was the moment when the 6th Demon King's head fell.

Chapter 289

The Successors (1)

◆

...Thud!

The 6th Demon King. Belial, the 'Worthless One'.

The sight of his massive head falling was something that the entirety of humanity in the past, countless great heroes, would have given their lives to see.

Vikir leaned back against the wall as he watched the demon's body die.

He narrowly avoided collapsing.

And as a result, he was able to watch Belial's final moments.

'...And with that, the brains of the Demon Coalition are gone.'

A long war between the demonic army and the human alliance.

Ages of destruction, when corpses formed mountains and blood formed oceans, before humans won a hollow victory.

Throughout these eons, the most tactically damaging being to the Alliance, and the one responsible for the most civilian casualties, has been eliminated: Belial.

With both Dantalian and Belial gone, the cunning minds that had sabotaged the Alliance, a weight was lifted from Vikir's shoulders.

“Hey, are you okay!”

Dolores exclaimed, rushing to Vikir's aid.

Vikir gave her a short look.

“Better than that. It's almost time.”

“What? Time? What time... ah!”

Dolores suddenly realized.

She realized that she was in a huge vault and there was a limit to how long she could stay.

Pulling out a pocket watch buried under a pile of gold coins, Dolores sucked in a breath.

“The vault doors are about to open!”

The vault doors would open and the Bourgeois family's vassals and private soldiers who had been waiting outside would enter.

“As soon as the door opens, we're out. Be ready.”

Dolores nodded at Vikir's words.

With the arrangements Damian had made, the troop deployment shouldn't be much.

But even so, they couldn't let their guard down.

After all, they were going to get inside the house, assassinate the patriarch, and get away with it.

“We'll have to make it a picture of me kidnapping you.”

“Okay. It'll be easier for you to get away if you take me hostage.”

As soon as the door to the vault opens, Dolores will have to run at full speed and not look back.

But there was one thing holding Dolores back.

“....”

She turned her head and looked beyond the pile of gold coins.

Where her gaze landed, she saw a white-haired girl standing still in the corner.

Sinclaire.

She was staring into space with a blank expression.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Belial's corpse melts away, emitting a terrible stench.

It disappears in an instant, as if it had never been here.

On the floor, where all the demonic corpses have spread out and disappeared, Bartolomeo's body lies dead, his whole body grotesquely contorted.

Bartolomeo's face is contorted in horror and pain.

Sinclaire's hands continue to shake as she stares at him.

Then.

“Sinclaire, wake up!”

Dolores grabbed Sinclaire by the shoulders and shook her once, hard.

“That wasn't a Bourgeois patriarch, you saw it, it was a puppet for the demon to incarnate!”

“...!”

Then the light returned to Sinclaire's eyes.

Tagg!

She swatted away Dolores's arm around her shoulder.

“Stay away from me!”

“Sinclaire, believe me, I swear to God, he's not human, he's a demon!”

Dolores said urgently.

“The doors to the vault are about to open. There are going to be tons of people coming in here.”

“....”

“Come with me. I'll explain everything.”

But Sinclaire remained silent, her mouth clamped shut.

Dolores felt something strange in Sinclaire's attitude.

Normally, Sinclaire was a well-mannered and polite junior who followed her lead.

She was also a quick thinker and would never do anything to offend others.

But now, Sinclaire certainly seemed different.

A demon she had never seen before had appeared, and the Bourgeois family patriarch had been manipulated to death.

Under these circumstances, wouldn't it make sense to leave the scene?

But Sinclaire refused to join Night's Hound.

Dolores spoke one last, desperate time.

“Sinclaire, it's dangerous to stay here alone....”

“Isn't it you who are in danger, if I stay here and tell you what I saw....”

But Sinclaire was still uncooperative.

Her demeanor was strangely unflappable, despite her anxiety.

Then,

...Cha-chang!

Vikir stepped forward with his sword at full length.

Sinclaire's gaze turned to him.

Vikir spoke in a blunt voice.

“Do as you please. I'm the one who killed the patriarch of the Bourgeois, after all.”

“....”

“The saint was taken hostage by me, unknowingly. That's what the article will say.”

Sinclaire replied in a trembling voice.

“Are you going to kill me?”

“If necessary.”

There was no warmth in Vikir's voice.

The coldness made Sinclaire shiver.

'Go away. If you don't want to get caught up and die.'

It was the same voice she'd heard at the Academy's festival, the same icy chill that sent a shiver down her spine.

Vikir took a step forward, where Sinclaire was standing stiffly.

“....”

Vikir stared into Sinclaire's speechless face, lost in thought.

A man whose name was nowhere to be found on the lists of the Human Alliance when the Age of Destruction came.

Yet, in the memories of countless great heroes, she had been referred to as a 'genius', 'elite', and 'extraordinary'.

A mysterious girl who suddenly disappeared from the world after graduation and whose name could not be found anywhere.

Should she be kept alive, or should she be eliminated from the world?

Vikir's judgment and choice were rapid.

“Decide for yourself.”

A voice crackled.

“What you will see, what you will hear, what you will believe.”

It weighed heavily on Sinclaire's heart.

She must decide what she will believe.

Just as Vikir is about to turn away.

...Thump, clunk, clunk!

The door to the vault was opened.

At the same time, a sound was heard.

“Aaaah! What kind of mess is this!”

“Ah, an ambush! Find the patriarch!”

“All forces to the vault!”

These were the cries of the panicked Bourgeois.

◆

Quack!

With a loud explosion, Night Hound leaped out of the vault.

Jegrang! Jegrang! Jegrang! Jegrang! Jegrang! Jegrang!

At the same time, gold nuggets and jewelry of unknown value were scattered in all directions.

While the eyes of his pursuers with spears, arrows, and wands are drawn to the riches on the ground, Night Hound flees over the wall in a flash.

On his waist was the saintess Dolores, who looked as if she had fainted.

“Hey, I've been scolded! The patriarch is dead!”

“And even the saintess was taken hostage!”

“Hey, at this rate, we're all going to die!”

“Grab them! All troops to the outer wall! We have to save the saintess!”

“No touching! Anyone who touches the riches on the floor in the meantime will be severely punished later!”

The people of Bourgeois Family are quick to respond to the situation.

Among them is Damian, who has just returned to his family home from the Money Manufacturing Bureau.

Dolores opens her eyes slightly at the shouting behind her.

“Do you think we should leave Sinclaire like that?”

Vikir only shrugs.

“She seems like a smart girl, I'm sure she can find a way to save herself, and if she does, we can just say she was out of it from the sleeping pills.”

“If she even tells anyone about us....”

“No one would believe her.”

Sinclaire may be a brilliant genius, but she's just a newcomer to the Academy, a commoner with no backbone.

If Sinclaire were to tell the truth about what she saw in the vault, she'd be labeled a madwoman, and she'd know that there would be nothing in it for her.

Just then, Vikir heard Decarabia whispering softly in his ear.

[Hohoho. I didn't think she was going to open her mouth, that white-haired girl].

“She's the kind of girl who would rather solve her own problems than rely on the adults.”

[Did you ever think that such a personality would cause more trouble in the future?]

“I have a mind of my own.”

Vikir rushed forward, gathering information about Sinclaire.

“She still has a lot of use left in her.”

A dry judgment. Understandably, it's for the best.

Vikir glanced down at the wall.

Truly strict vigilance befitting a tycoon.

It would be difficult to break through the crowds coming from all directions.

“This is goodbye.”

Vikir lowered Dolores to the ground by the young madame's thread.

“Night Hunt ... No, 'Van', what are you going to do?”

“Just call it what you used to call it. And I also have a way out.”

Vikir leapt down the wall, leaving Dolores with a worried glance.

Escape would be easy with the Ring of Andromalius, which could create subspace at any moment, but the cooldown has not returned yet.

So Vikir did the next best thing and put on a Picaresque mask.

Hack, hack, hack-

In the midst of their busy schedule, not many people paid attention to the black puppy carefully crawling around the corner under the outer wall.

◆

Inside the vault.

Damian was the only one left at the scene where everyone else had fled.

He turned to Bartolomeo, who lay dead on the floor, and bowed his head in silence.

“...Brother. What a mess.”

The demon's body had already melted away.

Only Bartolomeo's body lay in a ragged heap.

For a man of so much wealth and power to be so miserable.

Now that things are like this, what good is all the money and treasures that form the mountains around us?

Damian sighed heavily.

He hadn't thought he could be surprised anymore after his daughter's soul wedding, but this was just too much.

“What's a demon and what's a gate. What the hell happened....”

Right then.

“It was you.”

A sharp and cold voice came from behind.

It was sharpened like a dagger, stabbing Damian in the back of the head.

“The one who brought Night Hound and Saintess into the Vault.”

At the words, Damian slowly turned his head.

Blue veins appeared on the hand holding the stilettos around his waist.

Then.

“...!”

Damian's eyes widened for a moment.

The hand that gripped the stiletto momentarily loosened its grip, and a voice trembled.

“...Juliet?”

His daughter, the one he'd sent off in tears, was somehow standing here with a cold expression on her face.

Chapter 290

The Successors (2)

◆

“It was you, the one who brought the Night Hound and the Saint into the vault.”

A tone that seemed to catch an insider.

Damian turned his head and was stunned.

Eyes as big as a deer's, pupils as clear, and white hair that glistened with silver.

She looked like a dead Juliette come back to life.

But the illusion is literally a blink of an eye.

He lowered his eyelids once, then lifted them, and reality set in.

The girl in front of him looked a little younger than Juliet, and her hair was much shorter.

Most importantly, she was someone Damian knew.

“...Sinclaire J Bourgeois.”

Niece of Damian J Bourgeois and daughter of Bartolomeo J Bourgeois.

The scion of the Bourgeois family stood there.

Damian swallowed a faint groan.

It was because he'd seen the name on the list that he'd attended a party thrown by a bunch of academy students that he'd become the director of the Money Manufacturing Bureau in the first place.

“It's a misunderstanding.”

Damian shook his head.

He was familiar with Night Hound, but he didn't know much about demons.

“I haven't heard of it either, I just happened to notice it a bit before everyone else and ran. In fact, I hadn't even arrived home yet.”

Because of this, he was able to skillfully mix truth and lies.

Sinclaire glanced at Damian, then looked away.

“...Well, never mind, that's not important right now.”

She stood before the body of her father, Bartolomeo.

She murmured in a low voice.

“There was something I wanted to ask you, and now I'll never get to ask you.”

Sinclaire thought back to her time at the Academy.

-'I have questions about the future state of the Empire's economy, questions about our current financial metrics, questions about our criteria for finding new businesses, questions about the recent mergers and acquisitions between the promising small merchant guilds and the mercenary guilds... and questions about whether tycoons eat chicken!'

-'I have questions, too.'

-'Oh, Sinclaire, what do you want to know? Do you want to guess the questions with me?'

-'...No. I only have one question.'

-'Eh? Only one? Only one?'

-'Yeah.'

-'No, come on, we should learn a lot from meeting the Empire's greatest tycoon, it's a chance we might never get again!'

While her teammate Pigi was getting all excited about meeting the Empire's greatest tycoon, Sinclaire had only one question on her list.

But it was all for nothing now that the man who was supposed to answer it was dead in this place.

Then.

“'Why did you abandon me', that's it, that's the question.”

Damian, behind her, spoke up.

Sinclaire stared, and Damian shrugged.

“Juliet asked me the same thing. When she was alive.”

“...Juliet's sister too?”

Sinclaire's eyes widened a little.

Then Damian bit his lip slightly. The look of surprise on Sinclaire's face was the same as Juliet's on that day so long ago.

“Yes. In conclusion, your father and family did not abandon you.”

Bourgeois family tradition. It is exactly as Damian explained to Night Hound earlier.

The average young Bourgeois grows up in the family, but the “real” ones are different.

Like a lion's cub falling off a cliff, the future leaders of the family are thrown into society as commoners with their family name sealed.

Survival in society is as difficult as survival in the wild.

Achieving success in the Imperial Capital, the center of the empire, solely on one's own strength, without any help from parents or family. That is the process of 'proof'.

Esse, Non Videri. The belief that 'it exists, but is not revealed'.

“The Bourgeois family always cultivates more than one leader for checks and balances, for competition. In my generation, it was brother and me; in the next, you and Juliet.”

Damian told Sinclaire that fact.

Then, hesitantly, he added a word.

“...I don't know why my brother didn't tell you that, because it's something he should have told you much earlier.”

A moment.

Throbbing-

Sinclaire felt a throbbing headache.

Blood was flowing from where she'd been cut by the shard of gold coin earlier.

The sight of blood triggered a memory from earlier.

[It wouldn't be a bad idea to weed out useless relationships at this point. As of this time, all plays have ended.]

Bartolomeo, or rather the giant monster floating above him, spoke.

“Useless relationships, plays?”

Sinclaire staggered, holding her spinning head.

“Are you okay?”

Damian stepped closer, but Sinclaire jerked back, startled.

Sinclaire was wary, like a stray cat on edge.

She backed away slowly, palms up toward Damian.

Her eyes as if she didn't have a single thing in the world to believe.

“If a demon really did take over my father's body,... who raised me as a child? Which one is my father, and when did that happen?”

“?”

Damian didn't understand what Sinclaire was saying now.

But Sinclaire kept muttering anyway.

“What if my father was never my father in the first place? What then? What if it wasn't the demon who died, but my father? Or what if it wasn't my father, but the demon? What the hell, I don't know....”

Sinclaire ran her hands through her hair in agony.

Suddenly, she snapped her head up.

“...Night Hound. I need to see him again.”

Whether it was the demon, her father, the demon in her father's mask, or her father in the demon's mask that Night Hound killed, all things are resolved.

Rising from his seat, Sinclaire approached Bartolomeo's body in front of him.

She reached out and closed the bulging eyes.

“Farewell, father, I'll take over the reins.”

“Goodbye, Father, I'll take over the reigns.”

Words Damian doesn't even think about behind Sinclaire's back.

But Damian can only stare at Sinclaire's back in silence.

And then.

Sinclaire's eyes calm down.

Sinclaire looks like she's made a decision.

◆

“Huh! Huh! Huh! Huh!”

A suburb far from the Bourgeois family. A road leading to the Imperial Capital.

A middle-aged man was running through a mountain pass.

His once clean face was stained with scars, and his neat white robe was stained with mud.

Humbert. Why is he, a cardinal of the Great Lun Order, running so quickly, even abandoning his carriage?

“Damn it! Damn it! Bartolomeo was a demon, I had no idea!”

He ran through the bushes with a frightened expression.

Shortly before Vikir's meeting with Bartolomeo, Humbert had lunch with Bartolomeo.

This is because the imperial family began an investigation as the criminal chain leading to the Old Testament faction of Quovadis, the cults, and the Bourgeois was revealed to some extent.

Fearing that he was being thrown out with his tail between his legs, Humbert met with Bartolomeo and threatened to blow the whole thing up if he was ever investigated or arrested.

And that's where Belial showed his true colors.

Humbert threw himself at Belial's feet and begged for mercy, and the capricious Belial readily let him live.

[Use this in a moment of crisis, weak human].

As an added bonus, he gave him a 'gift'.

“...Huh. A gift from the demon.”

Humbert clutched the thing in his hand tighter and tighter.

It was a round object made of gold. A sphere shaped like an eyeball.

It was imbued with the power of the Demon King Belial, and as expected, it exuded a strange aura.

Humbert had just broken through the bushes.

“Hic!”

What he saw was a cliff that was as high as the sky.

Humbert jumped back in horror.

Rustle-

The sound of crashing branches could be heard from above.

“Whaaaat!?”

Humbert dropped to the ground, startled by the sound.

Lying flat on his back in the dirt, Humbert tried to cover his head with his hands.

But he had to wonder why he couldn't get his hands to his head, even though he raised his arms.

“...?”

Looking up and down at his hands, Humbert was horrified.

Both hands were gone from the wrists up.

Only hot blood was gushing out of them.

[Oho? I only wanted to take what was in your hands, but you cut them off?]

A woman's muffled laughter could be heard overhead.

Where Humbert hurriedly looked up, he saw a tree branch gently bending.

And the person sitting on top of it is a monster with two horns.

Ms. Ouroboros. The one who made Humbert run all the way here.

She cut off Humbert's hand!

[Oooh- it's pretty. Is this it? A sacred object said to have been received from the demon?]

She laughed as she touched the golden orb stained with blood.

“Gi, give it back!”

Humbert summoned his courage and shouted.

The only thing more disturbing than the loss of his two limbs was the loss of the Demon's Eyeball that Belial had given him.

And of course Ms. Ouroboros would not give it back.

[A priest with a reputation, selling children for money behind his back, and now working with the demon? That's a lot to take in].

“Ugh, ugh!”

Humbert cringes at her words, as if she's penetrating his mind.

But Ms. Ouroboros still only smiles her seductive smile.

[I don't mind, though, a criminal like you, I'm 'collecting'].

“...What, collect?”

Humbert looks puzzled.

Thud!

Suddenly, a snake-like creature flies out from behind and wraps itself around Humbert's neck, suffocating him.

It was Ms. Ouroboros's whip.

“Kuhugh!?”

Humbert was unable to resist even as he was dragged upward, strangled.

Both his hands had already been sliced off.

As Humbert struggled frantically in the air, Ms. Ouroboros spoke with a hint of laughter in her voice.

[I'll 'assist' you, too. Let's go 'Old Era' with me].

“?”

What does 'Old Era' mean? Isn't it usually 'New Era' when someone wants to welcome something together?

Humbert questioned her words even as his consciousness slowly faded.

Then Ms. Ouroboros whispered another word into his ear.

[The 'Warring States Period'.]

That was the last thing Humbert heard in his right mind.

Chapter 291

Confessions (1)

◆

The entire Imperial Capital was in shock.

Bourgeois patriarch Bartolomeo has been assassinated, and Cardinal Humbert of Quovadis, a pious man, has gone missing.

The culprit was blamed on the Night Hound.

Night Hound broke into a dinner party where Bartolomeo and the students of the academy were gathered, targeted Saint Dolores among the students, and staged a cowardly hostage situation, during which Bartolomeo made a heroic sacrifice to save them all.

A holy, heroic death indeed.

Unfortunately, most of the survivors who were saved by Bartolomeo's sacrifice said they had no memory of it.

A student named Pigi claimed to have fallen asleep and didn't see anything at all, while a student named Sinclaire, who was present at the scene, suffered from aphasia and short-term memory loss due to an overdose of sleeping pills, a blow to the head, and psychological shock.

Finally, St. Dolores, who had been taken hostage herself, stated that she did not see anything because she had an eye patch over her eyes.

The incident was put to rest when the acting patriarch of the Bourgeois Family, Damian J Bourgeois, issued an official statement stating that the situation would be resolved as quickly as possible and that the chaos would soon subside as there was a successor in place for the patriarchal position.

...But.

Even if there is a big incident in the whole country, it is human and small citizens who feel that the small things in front of them are more important.

Academy Colosseo.

Here, the focus was on the upcoming final exams and parent-teacher conferences.

Even if a Bourgeois assassination was shaking the entire empire, nothing could be more important to the students than their exams.

“Now, let's start reorganizing the gym to prepare for the final exams!”

“Don't forget to check your magic stones, just in case!”

“Is it okay for the trails for parents to explore to be this scenic? Let's plant more trees!”

“If possible, we plant large trees. I'm sowing a lot of flower seeds too!”

Soon, parents were visiting the school, and there was a massive beautification project going on all around the school.

Upon his return, Principal Winston began a massive greening project.

Large trees and beautiful flowers were planted throughout the school, and the sound of soft music echoed in the air.

He was also very disappointed with the damage to the magic wall during the recent midterms, so he added new magic stones to make it stronger.

Beautification and security. These were two of Principal Winston's main priorities.

The students' opinions were divided.

“Why is the principal doing such a large-scale construction project as soon as he comes back, when the school is busy?”

“Well, he's been away and hasn't accomplished much, so he has to do this in a hurry.”

“Hey, the school is half land and half trees. It's not like he's crazy about trees....”

“We've gotten a lot of mana stones, so the magic wall will be very strong.”

“Oh no. The parents are coming, so look at the showcase construction.”

“Oh no, I heard that even the seven major families are sending representatives for the parent observation class.”

“Hey, I heard that some families even have the patriarch himself coming.”

Meanwhile.

Dolores has recovered from her shock at Bourgeois and has returned to the front lines as student council president.

Contact with contractors, selection of magic stones and landscaping trees, negotiation of unit price, transportation and landscaping and more....

She was at the forefront of all these complex tasks.

“Soon, parents will be visiting the school. Many high ranking people are coming, including the seventh family of the Empire, so let's not skimp on the hospitality.”

At Dolores' words, the student council officers were hard at work.

Most families send their dignitaries by proxy, but on rare occasions, the head of the family comes in person, so every detail had to be taken care of.

While many students prepared to welcome the honored guests.

'Phew....'

Dolores sighed inwardly.

'I can't wait to meet Pigi and Sinclaire.'

She had seen Pigi a few times since that day at the Bourgeois family, but never Sinclaire.

The diligent kid had skipped class and locked herself in her dorm room, never coming out.

No part-time job, no volunteer work, no clubs.

Everyone was stunned by the change in the normally conscientious Sinclaire.

'She seemed very confused, After all, it's natural to be shocked when you see someone die right in front of you.'

Dolores is a saint and has seen many people in pain and dying, so she has minimal psychological resistance, but Sinclaire is a commoner girl who grew up with a clear head.

Naturally, she was shocked.

'I'm glad she didn't say anything in front of the press, though.'

Sinclaire is smart, she's not the kind of girl who would drop a bombshell in an interview without a backup plan.

'By the way, you said you were sharing a room with Bianca, right?'

But Bianca said she and Sinclaire hadn't been getting along lately, and she wasn't in the room much.

'I can't do this.'

Dolores realized that she needed to visit Sinclaire's room, even if it was just tonight.

And to do that, she'd have to catch up on her work.

“Come on. Let's get back to it.”

Dolores cheered herself up and grabbed a pen to start filling out the paperwork.

...And in the midst of all these big and small changes.

.

The final exams of the first year of the 20th class have begun.

◆

One week later.

As the final exams are coming to a close, the results of the Ranking Battle are almost out.

The final exam was organized by dividing the scores recorded during the midterm exam into sections to categorize the levels, and then students in each section competed against each other to collect partial scores.

Top scorers were promoted, bottom scorers were paid. This simple rule motivated all students.

During the midterms, Vikir, who was the overall leader of the class, defeated the Lowbro and Middlebro from the Cold Class and lost to the Highbro.

In Cold Class, Bianca defeated Sancho in a close match to advance to the finals, where she faced off against Tudor.

In the Hot Class, Granola and Sinclaire face off in the final.

The matches between Tudor and Bianca and Granola and Sinclaire was scheduled to conclude the final exam in a grand manner with all parents in attendance.

The four students had been working particularly hard to prepare for this highly anticipated final.

Among them, Sinclaire's enthusiasm and tenacity were so great that they left everyone speechless.

...Push!

The door to the gravity chamber opened and Sinclaire walked out, her body drenched in sweat.

A black sleeveless tee and combat uniform pants.

Sinclaire, who had just withstood 11 times the force of gravity with no mana, sat down in a chair with an exhausted expression.

“...Whoa.”

No one approached Sinclaire as she sighed heavily.

That's because Sinclaire had been holed up in her dorm for a while, but now that she's out in the open for finals season, she's showing an unprecedented amount of determination.

Every single one of the Hot Class elite she'd faced so far in the finals rankings had beaten in less than a minute.

This was despite the fact that they were aces who had performed well enough at the midterms to be in the same tier as Sinclaire.

Sinclaire became extremely quiet and her every move became monotonous.

Sleep. Eat. Train. Sleep. Eat. Train. Sleep. Eat. Train.

She didn't talk to anyone around her, and was completely focused on the task in front of her.

Relationships with friends became strained. Her tone of voice and eyes were cold, as if she was intentionally trying to distance herself from them.

It was as if she had become a different person overnight.

She also stopped volunteering at the orphanage, which she would force herself to do if she didn't have time.

When she sent letters to the children at the orphanage saying that she missed them, she crumpled them up without reading them.

She also quit all her part-time jobs that she had been doing responsibly.

When Bianca, who shared a room with her, expressed concern, she was silent.

Then.

“...!”

Sinclaire, who had been paying no attention to her surroundings, suddenly looked up.

At the same time, the door to the front gravity chamber opened and someone stepped out.

...Push!

13 times the gravity. A feat accomplished entirely with a bare body.

Vikir stepped out in a cloud of steam, drenched in sweat.

Then Sinclaire spoke up.

“ ... You're still awesome.”

Sinclaire, who had been acting like she was closing in on all the connections around her, was the first to speak to Vikir.

Vikir nodded and wiped the sweat from his face and body with a towel.

Sinclaire scrambled to her feet and followed closely behind.

“What's 13 times gravity like?”

“How do you survive without using mana?”

“What do you usually eat, and when do you sleep?”

“How the hell did you get so strong, what kind of training did you do?”

“Did you just lose to Highbro this time because you can't stand the attention?”

.

.

As far as Vikir could see, Sinclaire was still the same as before.

She was still the same curious, cheerful girl.

...But.

Even Vikir could tell that Sinclaire's last question had a slightly different tone to it.

“What are you doing tonight, hyung?”

“Assignment.”

“It's not going to be an overnight assignment, and it's not that hard.”

“I have assignments for my other classes. It's a night job.”

“...Tch.”

Sinclaire's lips twitched at Vikir's bluntness.

“You don't have time for late at night, or even at dawn? I'm not going to sleep!”

“If it's dawn, the assignment will be done, why?”

Vikir asked, and Sinclaire hesitated for a moment, then spoke as if summoning great courage.

“...If it's okay, would you like to have a late-night snack in my room?”

Chapter 293

Confession (3)

◆

Vikir was distracted for a moment.

'...Esse, Non Videri.'

To exist, but not to be seen.

Two heirs to the next pinnacle of the Bourgeois Family.

One was Juliet, the daughter of the second son Damian, and the other was the child of the eldest son, Bartolomeo.

Gender unknown, age unknown, nothing known.

'Coincidentally, my brother and I both have only one daughter.'

If it weren't for Damian's words, I wouldn't have known that Bartolomeo's child was a daughter.

Damian's daughter, Juliet, was revealed to the world when she dropped out of the exam, but no one knew where Bartolomeo's daughter was or what she was doing.

It was unclear if she even existed.

'Sinclaire was Bartolomeo's daughter.'

Vikir stroked his chin in thought.

For some reason, Juliet had seemed so familiar when he first saw her.

Perhaps it was because they shared the same blood.

'Then I think I know why she disappeared from the world after graduation.'

After graduating from the Colosseo Academy, Sinclaire probably became the patriarch of a Bourgeois family.

She would have moved about the world behind a great veil of darkness, unseen by the world.

An upper class so distant that lower-class warriors like Vikir before his regression could not dare to have an audience with them, or even knew that they existed at all.

The VVIPs of the world.

...But even the tree that would grow so tall in the future is only a tiny leaf now.

“Hyung-ah, what do you think of me?”

Sinclaire had asked this awkward question while sobbing in his arms.

Sinclaire's question brought Vikir back to reality.

“...Now. What is the purpose of asking this question?”

A question about what you think can't really be a question about what you think.

Vikir is not stupid.

On the contrary, he prided himself on being pretty quick on his feet.

At Vikir's retort, Sinclaire pursed her lips and rubbed her eyes before answering with a grimace.

“Because being in a relationship with hyung-ah is the only accomplishment I want to accomplish before I drop out and leave the Academy.”

An accomplishment...?

Vikir's mouth opened halfway.

Was dating really such a big deal that it sounded like an achievement?

But Sinclaire seemed to have something else in mind.

“ ... Originally, I was going to finish my fourth year, get my diploma, and then turn my back on the world. 'Excellent GPA,' 'numerous extracurricular awards,' 'valedictorian all four years,' 'student council president,' 'graduate of Colosseo Academy.' I figured those were the most valuable things I could get out of school, out of my youth.”

Sinclaire laughed bitterly for a moment before continuing.

“So I didn't understand her at first, because I had a cousin who dropped out of the academy she attended.”

She must be referring to Juliet, who had attended Themiscyra Academy for Girls.

Sinclaire squeezed Vikir's hand a little harder.

“But I think I know how you feel now, because I've changed my mind. The most valuable thing you can gain from school life is not grades, diplomas, awards, or certifications.”

It's the memories you make with the people you're with.

Sinclaire's eyes were filled with conviction.

Vikir asked thoughtfully.

“Why do you put such value on me? I'm not good enough for that.”

“If you think about it that way, what kind of person am I?”

Sinclaire emptied a can of beer and cupped it in her hand.

“...You are. I wonder how long I've had a crush on you. I wonder, too. Let's see.”

She closed her eyes and opened her mouth with clear pronunciation and a pure voice.

What she experienced, centered around her, from her perspective.

Slowly, Sinclaire's mouth began to recite the memories of her freshman year in class 20.

◆

'Why do I have to go out?'

The little girl asks the old butler while hugging her teddy bear.

The butler simply bows his head politely and replies.

'When you grow up and come back, everything will be yours.'

With those last words, the little girl leaves the family home.

Nursery school. The little girl studied diligently. When other children were defeated or discouraged, she always glowed with enthusiasm and hope.

A prestigious small school. The girl was discriminated against as soon as she entered the school. Whether it's her performance on performance evaluations, even if cleaning duty returns strangely often, there is also subtle discrimination, gossip, and harassment that is invisible to the eye. The girl persevered.

The outcome wasn't always fair, but on the whole, in retrospect, it was pretty fair.

All the discrimination faded away in the face of excellence and continued proof.

The kids who gossiped behind her back gradually became eager to make friends with her, and the teachers who looked at her with prejudice because she was from a nursery school gradually became favorites.

Her appearance, which began to glow with age, changed everything.

Soon, against all odds, she had risen to the occasion, and at an unusually young age, she was granted early admission to the Colosseo Academy, the most prestigious university in the Empire.

At the top of her class.

She was thrilled that her skills would be recognized in such a large place.

And the much-anticipated Colosseo Academy.

'Survive somehow, and rise above. If they help you, use them, if they don't, discard them mercilessly.'

She thought back to the words her father had spoken to her as a child, and took the freshman oath.

And her first class.

There was no student smarter than her.

Even at the most prestigious universities in the empire, she could hold her own.

She breathed a sigh of relief at that realization.

Then.

A boy caught her eye.

At first glance, he was ordinary. Messy hair that is not easily noticeable. A common name that could be found everywhere. So-so grades and interview performance.

But in the class that followed, the boy gave the professor, who purposely picked questions for students to get wrong, a good smack in the face.

'...Hmm. I see. A perfect score on the paper.'

The boy's written grade, even the picky professor recognized, was a perfect score. It was even higher than the girl's score of 931 out of 990.

The girl's next highest score was in the 700s, so the difficulty level of the test was, needless to say, the worst. However, there was a perfect score and it wasn't the girl.

From then on, the girl was curious about the boy.

That was the first time, maybe. It was the first time she felt like she wanted to get to know someone.

The girl is objectively pretty and has a good body. She was attractive not only intellectually but also physically. She is in a good position to benefit from interpersonal relationships.

So she was confident when she approached the boy. She was confident that he wouldn't dislike her.

But she had always been approached by others, but this is the first time you have approached someone else. So the girl spoke to the boy in a slightly awkward manner.

'Hey, I'm....'

She asked him why he was volunteering. The boy's answer was simple.

“I'm here for my demerit points.”

'...Ah.'

Usually, when people are asked why they volunteer, the answers are obvious.

Fulfillment, giving back, sacrifice, etc.... all sound good.

But not the boy.

A boy who walks away like he's a bother.

The girl followed him, feeling a bit out of place, as this was the first time she had ever been treated this way.

'It's a coincidence that we're both volunteering at the same place.'

'I guess so.'

Actually, it wasn't.

The girl had gone out of her way to beg and plead with the person in charge to get the same volunteer assignment as the boy.

And that day, she thought she'd gotten to know him a little bit. Because she talked to him.

After bombarding him with questions about his written grades and not getting any answers that she liked, she thought he was a bit of a prick.

But.

Despite the demerit points, the boy was very eager to volunteer.

She was amazed to see him do the dirty work that would take dozens of people to do, like cleaning toilets, serving meals in the cafeteria, fixing plumbing, doing laundry, playing with kids, and maintaining the playground.

'...This guy is good.'

That was the first time in her life she had ever genuinely complimented someone.

From that day forward, the way she called him changed.

'Hi! Good morning!'

'?'

'Oppa, why don't you pretend to know me!'

'I didn't realize you were addressing me, and we're classmates, so don't call me oppa.'

'Why? I'm a year younger than you, and you're still my oppa, no matter how you say it.'

'It's just that it's uncomfortable to hear....'

'Really? If you don't like it, we can call you something else. I'll think about it until lunch.'

From then on, the girl started calling the boy 'Hyung-ah'.

'You don't have much of an immunity to girls, do you?'

The girl was surprised.

The boy's bare face, revealed when the bushy hair that often covered his face was shaken, was shockingly handsome.

She could only shake her head in disbelief, thinking that he must have attracted several girls already.

Whatever. From then on, whenever she saw him, she often assumed she knew him.

Maybe it was from that moment on.

The moment she stopped calling him 'oppa', which everyone else liked, and started calling him 'hyung-ah', which was a bit unusual.

The moment when the boy have someone who calls him by a special nickname.

Could it be that the girl's defenses, which she didn't even know existed until now, has begun to shift?

When she approached him with a strange emotion she didn't recognize, he said something shocking about parents.

'I don't need parents. You have to navigate the world on your own. Parents only function during childhood when help from others is essential, and are unnecessary beyond that.'

The girl was a little shocked that anyone in the world would think this way.

Whether in a nursery or a prestigious school, children's thoughts were always the same.

Love for parents.

Whether it's lacking or fulfilled, children always draw on it, because so did the girl.

But boys didn't.

And so she came to admire him. And she also pitied him.

A lot of things happened after that.

They drank together and got part-time jobs. When she watched him save his friends from an accident during midterms, she felt her heart beat hard.

It was the same when students from her cousin's sister's school attacked her on the train to the University League.

'Thank you for helping me earlier, I was really scared. They seem like strong sisters.'

'I was scared too.'

The boy's nonchalance made her laugh out loud and genuinely.

And then she thought.

This boy in front of her is the only one who can open up and close down her heart like that.

◆

“I suppose it's not much of a surprise, now that you mention it.”

Sinclaire rubbed the corners of her eyes and laughed.

Vikir remained silent for a while after Sinclaire finished speaking.

Perhaps the awkward silence was too much to bear. Sinclaire spoke again.

“And... I'm telling you the biggest problem I have right now. I'm confessing it, and I'm telling you what it looks like.”

“....”

“Like I said, Night Hound killed my father, and I don't know if you'll believe it, but Student Council President Dolores was right next to him.”

“....”

“The only person I trusted in school was in league with the man who killed my father. I don't know who to trust, my friends, my professors, I don't know who to trust, and that's why it's so hard to be at school.”

Sinclaire finished and looked up.

“I thought maybe you'd believe me, since you've been writing a column in the newspaper criticizing the Night Hunters for a while now, and I'm sure you'd know what a heinous criminal Night Hound is.”

“....”

“You're the only one I have now who will understand me....”

Sinclaire dropped her head, unable to finish her sentence.

Only to squeeze Vikir's sleeve.

But.

“I'm sorry, but I don't think I can accept your heart.”

Vikir shook his head firmly.

For a moment, Sinclaire's grip on Vikir's sleeve tightened.

“I know. That's what I thought hyung-ah would say.”

“....”

“I've only ever seen one person with eyes like yours, and that's my father.”

Sinclaire said.

“He's the kind of man who pushes forward with a goal that a normal person like me can't even fathom. I can see it in your eyes. You're the same kind of man my father is.”

“....”

“I'm pretty, fit, and young. I'm good with a sword and magic. And most of all, I have the ability and patience to understand and support you in all aspects of your life. I won't get in your way. I'll be really good.”

“....”

“...Why can't I? What can I do? What can I do to make hyung-ah realize that I....”

At that point, Vikir cut Sinclaire off.

“Now is not the time to think about things like relationships.”

It makes sense. A demon hunter's idea of a relationship is something his dead comrades would laugh at.

There's nothing more unsettling than a man who doesn't know when he's going to die building a family.

What you must protect and what you cannot lose will only become a weakness.

Vikir shook his head thoughtfully, and Sinclaire's expression brightened slightly.

“...'Now?'”

“?”

Vikir looked up, and Sinclaire hit the nail on the head again.

“Not right now, you mean, 'for now'. So you'll have some time to spare later, after you've achieved your goal?”

“My goal is a long, long way off. I'm still a long way from reaching it....”

“I know. For someone of your stature to say that, it must be a grand ambition.”

Sinclaire looked determined.

“Then one day, when you've accomplished everything you want.”

“....”

“Will you take me in then?”

It was an awkward question.

Vikir thought about it for a moment, then nodded.

“If that day ever comes.”

“Okay, then.”

Sinclaire nodded, slipping out of Vikir's arms and sitting up on her knees.

She lifted the can of beer in her hand and downed the last of it in one shot.

Vikir quietly rose from his seat.

“It's getting late, I'd better get back.”

Then. Sinclaire got up and followed Vikir. And then she opened her mouth.

“ ..., Can you at least give me a hug before you go?”

At those words, Vikir swallowed hard.

Still a small, young girl. But one who would one day stand at the pinnacle of that fearsome conglomerate Bourgeois family.

How many hardships and trials did this weak child go through before regression to become a great hero whose name was not revealed to the world?

Feeling guilty and indebted to Sinclaire, Vikir closed his eyes tightly.

Then.

Tud.

Sinclaire wrapped her arms around Vikir's waist.

“You can push it away for the rest of your life.”

“....”

“So just for now. For now, I need you to stay like this.”

There is moisture in the thinly trembling voice.

“Haha...I wasn't really this kind of person....”

Her muttering, self-effacing and cool, is obscured by Vikir's chest puffs.

Vikir paused for a moment, deep in thought.

'I don't have much time left to stay here either.'

Like Sinclaire, Vikir planned to leave Colosseo Academy soon.

His next stop would be a place so harsh and difficult that it would make the Academy feel like a cradle.

Similar in appearance to the Colosseo's architecture, which symbolized glory and prosperity, but its symbolic meaning is completely different.

A fearsome structure that reigns as a testament to hardship and trial itself.

'...Nouvelle Vague. And the Age of Destruction.

The curtain rises.

Soon the full-scale war against the demons will begin.

Chapter 294

Last Semester (1)

◆

“....”

Vice Principal Banshee Morgue.

He frowned as soon as he got out of bed and into the morning light.

His face did not straighten as he took off his cute, mismatched sleeping cap, eye mask, and pajamas.

“Not a good dream.”

He had a strange dream the other night.

A nightmare so unpleasant that it left not only his clothes but his bed soaked in a cold sweat.

It was a dream of a giant one-eyed snake and a unicorn fighting each other.

The one-eyed snake wrapped itself around the unicorn's massive body, squeezed, and tried to swallow it in one bite.

The unicorn tried to resist by waving its horn, but everything was in vain as soon as the one-eyed snake opened one more of its closed eyes.

With its left eye glowing an unusually golden color, the snake wrapped itself around unicorn and swallowed it in one bite.

“Why, this is such a bad dream on a day when I have to report to the principal. Is it because of stress?”

Professor Banshee grumbled and got ready for work.

He walked out of the guesthouse and made his way to the lecture hall.

He ignored the greetings of his students, and even those of his fellow professors, and headed straight for the principal's office.

In his hand, he carried a stack of reports that he had prepared until last night.

Knock-knock-knock.

The knock ended, and the door opened by itself.

Inside, Principal Winston sits with his usual mild expression.

“Well, Professor Banshee. I see you're early.”

“Yes. About a minute and a half early. If you're in a hurry, do you want me to wait outside the door until your appointment?”

“No, no, no. Just come on in.”

Winston motioned for Professor Banshee to come in.

Banshee dropped a stack of reports in front of him.

“This is the accounting for the greening of the school.”

Winston had redesigned the Academy's landscaping as soon as he returned to his position as principal.

Greening. It was a project to more than double the number of trees and plants on campus.

Winston had a gentle nature and loved planting trees.

The principal's office alone was filled with plants of all kinds, and no one thought it was strange.

“We also put in new magic stones.”

During the recent midterms, a student named Vikir had found a gap in the magic wall and entered the arena through it.

It was a potentially disastrous event if misused, and Winston had increased the Academy's security with the new magic stones.

However, Professor Banshee was skeptical.

“Compared to the old ones, the new ones have the advantage of better mana efficiency and higher hardness of the magic walls, but their durability hasn't been proven yet.”

“Hahaha. Isn't that why you alternated the old and new magic stones, so that the invaders wouldn't know where the old magic walls are and where the new ones are, and they'd be confused... no, there wouldn't be any invaders in the first place.”

Winston finished and looked at Professor Banshee with sympathetic eyes.

“You're always concerned about the safety of your students, I admire that.”

“ ...I'm just a little guy who's worried about preserving his position.”

“That's not true, Professor Banshee, and I know that even though you say it on the outside, you don't feel it on the inside, so I've worked hard to live up to that.”

As he spoke, Winston held something out in front of Banshee.

It was a bracelet decorated with black seeds that looked like jewelry.

The seeds had grayish roots that grew out from beneath them, and it was designed to be sized to fit around the wrist.

“It is the key to passing the new magic wall. It's a bracelet type. These days, many people are replacing locker rooms in bathrooms and gyms with something like this, right? It looks like the security is good.”

“So it's an artifact that contains magic, do you think you can mass produce it?”

“I'm making them by hand whenever I have time. I've already made enough for the students, I just need to distribute them. I'll make some for the professors when I can afford it.”

Winston smirked, and Professor Banshee grunted and groaned.

Then he thrust a new sheet of paper in Winston's direction.

“That's enough of the security stuff. Next on the agenda.”

“Hmm? What is this? I don't think I've been briefed before.”

“This is not a formal report, but there's something I wanted to bring to your attention personally....”

“Hoo-what is it?”

Winston stretched his neck toward the document with interest.

Professor Banshee hesitated for a moment before speaking.

“The mood within the Imperial Capital has been odd lately.”

“What does it mean to say it's not unusual...?”

“Look at the statistics.”

Professor Banshee gestured to the various graphs, diagrams, and charts in his papers.

“There has been a subtle increase in criminals within the Imperial Capital lately.”

“That's because whenever there's a big event in the Imperial Capital, there's an influx of people.”

“No. This is the rate of increase in crime relative to the incoming population, which means that the crime rate itself is higher than normal due to the influx of people.”

Professor Banshee narrowed his eyes. Then, in a cold voice, he analyzed the current situation.

“Criminals from across the Empire have been flocking to the Imperial Capital lately. Reports of witnesses to wanted criminals have also increased.”

“That's a big deal. What is the Imperial Guard doing?”

“Strangely enough, they've noticed that their arrest rate has dropped a lot lately. They say the criminals have been fleeing suspiciously, as if they knew in advance that they were going to be arrested, and some of the most wanted criminals have even become elusive, which leads them to wonder if someone is helping them run and hide....”

“I see, but what does that report have to do with the Academy right now?”

“Well, as the principal knows, we're about to have finals and parent-teacher conferences at the same time, and with the way things have been going lately, I thought you might want to push back the date....”

Then Winston chuckled.

“Isn't this Colosseo Academy the place where geniuses who will one day become the great heroes of the Empire are educated? And the professors who teach them? And the parents of the students, every single one of them. The backbone of the Empire's military might.”

“....”

“This is where all these great people come together. Who cares if there's a bunch of criminals running around outside?”

“....”

“But I understand and respect your caution, Professor Banshee, and that's why I, too, am concerned with improving security by replacing the magic stone, isn't it?”

Professor Banshee could only nod.

Well, no matter how hard the criminals out there try, they won't be able to do even the slightest harm to the parents who come here.

They weren't an 'organization' in the first place, they were lowly beings who had no ability or reason to harm the Academy.

“Indeed. And a final report.”

Professor Banshee turned to Winston.

“It concerns the matter of Professor Sadi's dismissal.”

For the first time, Winston's expression changed.

He had a truly embarrassed and sad expression.

“ ...Did Professor Sadi cause something again?”

“Yes. We've received a tip-off that she has been dishonest in her duties as an advisor to the Imperial Guard.”

“...Uh-oh.”

“It's said that she was sloppy and negligent during search and intelligence activities, getting into feuds with colleagues, losing or missing important supplies or information, and even showing up unauthorized during arrests, which we later found out she had fallen asleep in her office while drunk.”

“Haha... that damn alcoholism. Professor Sadi is a very capable person if she doesn't drink.”

“That too is a thing of the past. To be sure, back in the day, Professor Sadi did a fine job as an advisor to the Imperial Guard's tracking team, in fact, so much of the criminality of the time was captured by her that it almost rivaled the exploits of the Marquis de Sade in his heyday. She was even called 'the second coming of the Marquis de Sade,' but now she's just an alcoholic loser who does nothing but bemoan her lot and deny reality.”

Professor Banshee snapped, as if he had a lot on his plate.

Then Winston closed his eyes and fell silent for a moment.

Silence. A heavy silence.

Winston opened his eyes and spoke with a heavy sigh.

“I'm going to discipline ....”

“Something as light as a pay cut or suspension cannot be accepted....”

“Understood, I'm going to use my title as principal to severely discipline her in this case.”

Only then did Professor Banshee shut up and retreat.

I was wondering if saying that would end up as a light punishment.

After his report, Professor Banshee walked out of the principal's office.

Thud, thud, thud, thud, thud.

As Professor Banshee walked down the darkened hallway, a black shadow flickered by his side.

Stopping in his tracks, Professor Banshee spoke in a low voice.

“Did you recognize it?”

The shadow behind him leaned in behind Professor Banshee and spoke.

“Yes. There was definitely a lot of stuff going on behind his back.”

The Banshee had unleashed a separate informant to do a background check on the principal.

'I'd like to know why you're so cheap with Professor Sadi.'

It was enough to get rid of her as an eyesore.

Then. Professor Banshee's confidante told him something surprising.

“Principal Winston's affection for Professor Sadi wasn't due to any of these trivial things, full honors for a descendant of nobility, to be an elite arresting agent with a high rate of arresting criminals, and to increase the number of members of the principal's faction, which is already very small, by at least one more... It wasn't because of these little things.”

“Then what was it for?”

The confidant answered in a very small voice.

“Perhaps it has something to do with the '47 people riot'.”

It was a report that made Professor Banshee's eyes widen to tears.

◆

“Now- today's lesson is about the major events since the Unified Empire~”

The professor said, tapping the blackboard.

The first-year students were listening to the lecture with eager expressions.

The professor said.

“There are many big events that happened after the Unified Empire, such as the 'Western Front Barbarian Subjugation', the 'Merger of the Five Swordsmen', and the 'Great Escape from Nouvelle Vague Prison', but... the biggest one would have to be the '47 People's Riot'. Who can tell us about this event?”

A few hands went up among the students.

The professor pointed to the first student to raise his hand.

“Okay. Let's see if Sinclaire, the head of our Hot Class, can answer.”

There was the sound of a chair being dragged out and a female student rose from her seat.

Sinclaire, a girl with white hair and a calm voice.

She calmly began to share what she knew.

“The '47 People's Riot' was an unprecedented event that occurred thirty-five years ago, when the Empire had just been unified. It was caused by 47 people, but each and every one of them was the head of a family, hence the name '47 Family Riot'.”

“That's great, can you tell me more about it?”

“It was a rebellion in which 47 people staged a coup d'état, slaughtering countless people and storming the imperial palace. As a result, 46 of the 47 were summarily executed on the spot, and the one survivor is currently imprisoned in the 'Nouvelle Vague', a prison in the remote corners of the continent. It is also believed that their motives for staging the coup are still unknown, and that they were simply after the throne....”

Sinclaire answered without a pause, and the students around her let out a small gasp.

“Hasn't something changed, Sinclaire?”

“Huh? Like what? I think she's still smart.”

“Not that, I mean her demeanor, her vibe.”

“Ah, yes, she's been strangely cold lately.”

“But that's kind of charming, too. It's like she's grown up.”

“That's what I was thinking, too. She's grown up overnight. She's gone from a girl to a woman.”

She was always a cheerful little girl.

Sinclaire, who used to remind me of a playful puppy, has changed a lot in recent days.

For some reason, something has changed in her that is impossible to pinpoint, but she has grown quite mature overnight.

In the same way that a girl grows into a woman through some unknown process of her own, Sinclaire seemed to calmly accept and embrace the inner changes that were happening to her.

When she finished and sat down, the professor clapped.

“That was a good answer, Student Sinclaire, and I hope you'll be just as good in your final exam for Hot Class this afternoon.”

The professor glanced around the room.

“As I'm sure you all know, not only you but also many parents will come to the final exams that will be held later.”

There's no way the students don't know that.

For the past few days, there has been no fuss about the greening project, security project, or whatever, and the principal personally planted trees and plants and rearranged the magic stone.

So the students were mostly moody.

After all, the finals were for Tudor and Bianca, the Cold Class, and Granola and Sinclaire, the Hot Class, because it was the stage for these four and they were the bridesmaids..

While some students were excited to see their families for the first time, others were worried that they would be scolded for their poor grades.

Is that why? The professor revealed another piece of news to get their attention.

“And guess what, we're about to have a new friend in our school!”

A new student. That's always a fresh interest.

One student raised his hand and asked.

“Professor, is there a transfer student coming?”

“That's a great question, but unfortunately, no, not a transfer student!”

The professor waved his finger in the air.

“It would be more correct to say that it's a transfer student, not a new student, this is because it was not transferring the academic records from another school, but rather enrolling in a new school during the semester. Anyway, it's good to have new friends!”

“Wow – what kind of friends are they – girls, boys, ages, and oh yeah, I'd like to know what class they're in too!”

The students asked curiously.

The professor smiled and replied.

“Gender is female. Her age is 19, which is one year younger than the average first-year student, and she belongs to the Hot Class. Since she is transferring from the famous 'Mage Family Morgue', I think you can learn a lot from her. Her name is....”

Chapter 295

Last Semester (2)

◆

Parent observation classes have begun.

The training ground for the final exam rankings.

Tudor and Bianca, the cold-class students, and Granola and Sinclaire, the hot-class students, compete against each other.

Other top-performing second-year and third-year students also take the stage.

The same goes for Dolores, the student council president and third-year senior.

The scene was being presented as an example to a crowd of parents.

Parents and children met inside the academy and exchanged greetings.

“My boy – I've missed you! Are you eating well?”

“Uh-huh. By the way, daughter, why aren't you joining the ranking battle over there?”

“What? Is that where they decide the head of the class? Aha, it's not a stage where normal kids stand.”

“Next time, make sure you get to stand up there.”

“It's a relief to know that my child is in a class with such brilliant kids.”

“You should definitely surround yourself with friends like that, that's what we sent you to Colosseo Academy for.”

As the parents react with encouragement, pressure, and praise, a new competition and socialization is created.

This is what parent-observation classes were designed to do in the first place.

Meanwhile. Tudor and Bianca, who are about to compete in the final exam, were exchanging nerves even before the match.

“I can't embarrass my father when he's watching, so I'm sorry, I'm going to have to step on you.”

“My father's here too, so I can't let you off the hook today.”

“You say that like you usually do, but your midterm grade was lower than mine.”

“That's not true, I was above you.”

“You were 6th, and I was 3rd?”

“Yeah, but that's before the performance evaluation, attitude points, and extracurricular points... I'm one point higher than you.”

“Are you even taking all that into account? I don't care. Today, I will overturn all the little things.”

“Turn over? You must have said turn over in the wrong way.”

“What kind of person do you think you are, talking like a girl? You're so bad.”

“What's a girl got to do with it? If you put it that way, why are you such a weakling?”

“I'm not weak, just wait until we start a match.”

“You suck.”

“You suck, too.”

Tudor and Bianca continued to argue.

Meanwhile. There was an icy silence between Granola and Sinclaire in the Hot Class.

It was Granola who broke the silence first.

“Hey, commoner. As of today, I, Granola, the newest member of the Aristocracy faction, will be taking over the leadership position.”

“....”

“Not even the top of the class and the next student council president can go to a commoner!”

“....”

“No complaints, huh?”

Granola gripped the weight as hard as he could, secretly hoping Sinclaire would respond.

But nothing came back.

“...It's also childish.”

Sinclaire muttered, looking off into the distance at the mountains with an unmoved expression.

Her usual innocent, sunny childlike demeanor was gone, replaced by the vibe of a much older sister.

Granola didn't know why Sinclaire had changed so much overnight, but for some reason he felt his heart pounding.

Next. The professor's voice echoed through the audience.

[Attention mothers and fathers, the final round of grade-level exams is about to begin!]

The final event of the final exam was about to begin.

◆

“....”

Quite a distance away from the training grounds where the final exam ranking game was being held.

A person stood on a wicker bench with an old well.

Dolores L. Quovadis. A third-year student and student council president.

The final match of the final exam is decided to be hers.

Once the competition between a total of four first-year and second-year students in the Hot and Cold Class is completed, it will soon be Dolores' turn.

But right now, she has something else on her mind, something more important than her final exam.

It was the matches of the Hot Class first years. Specifically, Sinclaire.

'...What should I say to Sinclaire?'

Sinclaire, who advanced to the finals today, was told that no one would show up during parent attendance.

Dolores thought she would approach Sinclaire after the game, when everyone's attention had faded, and try to talk to her.

'But how do I talk to her?'

After that day at the Bourgeois, Sinclaire had avoided seeing Dolores.

She seemed to be warming up to everyone, but she was being unusually closed off to Dolores.

'...It's not surprising, after what happened to her.'

Dolores sighs, unsure of how to approach Sinclaire.

“...!”

Her eyes went wide for a moment.

A familiar face passed in front of her.

A male student trudging towards a well in the distance. It was Vikir.

Suddenly, Dolores remembered Sinclaire's comment.

'By the way. Why don't we ask hyung-ah to join us?'

Dolores remembered the first time she'd created an Oracle Investment Fund to hunt Belial.

'...Is he interested in something like this?'

Dolores asked, and Sinclaire replied with a bright smile.

'Vikir's pretty good at it too, he reads all the newspapers all the time, so he knows what's going on in society, and lately he's been really interested in economics, like trade with the natives in the west, and he's been going through all the old economic papers too, and he's really keen!'

'Hyung-ah often comes to the library, so I'll have to talk to him when I'm a librarian.'

'Oh, that's right~ Hyung, I don't know where you are wandering around like that these days. Pigi is in the same room, so do you know anything?'

At that time, Sinclaire seemed to have quite the crush on Vikir.

If so, they must have been quite close.

Dolores jumped to her feet. She was going to ask to speak to Sinclaire.

Just then.

A young child ran in front of Dolores.

Ebony hair, red eyes, white skin, and chubby cheeks. Cute like a doll.

It was only a brief glimpse, but the little girl, who was adorable from head to toe, was running toward Vikir in front of her.

Then she turned to Vikir and said something unbelievable.

“Daddy-!”

The words shocked Dolores.

He'd heard that the docile kitten was the first to climb the shack, but wasn't this one climbing too fast?

'Oh, no. Who the hell is her mother at that age?'

Dolores stops dead in her tracks.

...Tud, Patter-

Vikir grabbed the girl by his side and quickly began to run forward.

“Huh? Huh!”

Dolores hurriedly scrambled down the hill from the bench, but Vikir had already taken off down the path by the well in the distance.

◆

Vikir headed toward the less traveled path.

Stopping beside an old well, Vikir set the girl down from his side.

“Pomeranian, when did you get here, and who is your guardian?”

“Hehe- sneaking off with Big Samchun(uncle). He never lets me play.”

At Pomeranian's playful words, Vikir put his hand to his forehead.

The news that 'they' had traveled to the Imperial Capital for parental visits had come through Cindywendy not long ago.

'Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro seem to be doing a good job of dealing with them, so I guess I let my guard down.'

I'm sure there will be some chaos when they realize Pomeranian is gone.

I had to get her back on track before that happened.

Vikir grabbed Pomeranian's hand.

“Come on, let's go. Your uncle will take you to the front.”

“Ugh!”

Pomeranian still stiffened at Vikir's words.

As they walked down the path below, holding hands, Vikir carefully asked about Pomeranian's condition.

“How's the Wraith Tree doing these days?”

“It's growing well, but sometimes I have nightmares at night!”

“Nightmares? What kind of nightmares?”

“When I have nightmares, I keep seeing demonic things come out and bite me-”

Pomeranian shuddered once.

Vikir nodded and patted Pomeranian's head.

“The demons in your nightmares have nightmares, too.”

“Who's in the demons' nightmares?”

“ ... This uncle comes out.”

In an eerie voice, Vikir pulls out the Beelzebub on his wrist and shows it to her, and Pomeranian's eyes sparkle with yearning.

“Oh wow- Uncle Mercy.”

“So you don't have to fear any demons or anything. You have this uncle.”

So Pomeranian can continue to grow her Wraith Tree without any pressure.

One day, it will add great power to the human alliance.

Just then.

Someone grabbed Vikir's collar as he was about to leave the well.

The moment when Vikir turned his head in surprise at the hand that approached him without any sign of affection.

“Ugh, I'm thirsty. Where's the well here, old man?”

An old woman appeared somewhat unexpectedly and was pulling the end of Vikir's coat collar.

Shabby white priest's robes, hunched waist, round face, glasses resting just barely on the bridge of her nose, eyes squinting as if in sorrow.

At first glance, she's just another old woman.

But when Vikir saw her face, he couldn't help but be surprised.

'This person...?'

Here was the biggest variable in the parent observation class.

Chapter 297

The Age of the Warmonger (1)

◆

With the conclusion of the ranking battles between the first, second, and third years, the final exams at Colosseo Academy have come to an end.

The students will now join their parents in the auditorium for the closing ceremony.

Shortly thereafter, students will head home with their parents for vacation and a brief counseling session on their academic performance over the past year.

Students, professors, parents, and more crowded into the large auditorium at the center of Colosseo Academy.

And there was one person who stood out from the crowd.

A huge figure, almost 3 meters tall.

A man dressed entirely in the skin of a sea lion with fearsome tusks and a massive spear on his back the size of a whaling ship's harpoon.

A handsome man with blond hair like a beast's mane and a bold look was laughing.

“Son, congratulations on your victory! This father can't stop laughing!”

Cervantes Donquixote, King of the Sea, patriarch of the Donquixote family.

He was laughing cheerfully, repeatedly patting his son Tudor on the shoulder.

Then he heard a sullen voice beside him.

“Is that what you want me to hear?”

A skinny figure, but tall enough to rival Cervantes in stature, a face as pale as a corpse's, large but gloomy eyes, bloodlessly thin lips, and long hair as thin as a spider's web.

This is Usher Poe Roderick, the Bow Demon and patriarch of the Usher family.

He glanced at his daughter Bianca, who was following wordlessly behind him, before fixing his gaze on Cervantes again.

“I am congratulating your son on his victory. Although I don't know if it's a win worth celebrating.”

“What? All wins are worth celebrating. Are you trying to tell me that your daughter lost to my son and was only runner-up, huh, like a little sissy?”

“What do you mean, like a sissy? No way.”

Usher turned to Bianca, who was following him.

“Daughter, I want you to tell me, in your own words, why you withdrew from the final round of the last match.”

“Yes, father.”

Bianca's gaze shifted to Usher's back.

There was Tudor, in a furious mood.

“I have no taste for performing in front of large crowds, and I'm not a monkey before an apothecary.”

“What! A monkey!!! Then why have you been fighting to the best of your ability all this time!”

“...Are you really an idiot? Until the finals, we've been fighting privately amongst ourselves in the school, and from the finals onwards, parents will be watching. I don't want to expose my family's arcane archery to anybody.”

So Bianca had dodged Tudor's spear at the crucial moment, only to walk out of the arena and withdraw.

Usher smirked.

“A monkey before the apothecary. Don't be so accusatory, daughter, there's a law in the Empire called 'Crime of defamation based on fact and timing'.”

“Yes, father. The law is strict and must be followed. Apparently there's a saying in the far west called 'You're worthy of attention.'.”

Usher and Bianca rushed towards the main auditorium with the attendants following them.

Then Cervantes, Tudor, and the Donquixote family attendants who were left behind began to snort in unison.

“Stop! Hey, Usher, you Gloomy little bastard, why don't you come over here and play a game with me, ugh!”

“Bianca, you're this..., you're so futile! Come on, get back in the game!”

It looked like a father and daughter really looked alike.

But the gaze of the surrounding people quickly shifted.

In addition to the Ushers and Donquixote, there were many other great people worthy of note.

For example, Hobbes De Leviathan, the patriarch of the Leviathan family, and his youngest son, Granola De Leviathan.

Nabokov Lun Quovadis I, patriarch of the Quovadis family of Faithful Saints, and Dolores L. Quovadis, direct successor.

Iron-Blooded Swordsman: Osiris Le Baskerville, small patriarch of Baskerville Family, and his half-siblings, Highbro Le Baskerville, Middlebro Le Baskerville, and Lowbro Le Baskerville.

The seven pillars that support the empire, each family rivaling the power of a nation.

It was a sight to behold, with the leaders of all the Families gathered in one place, except for the tycoon Bourgeois and the Mage Family Morgue.

Meanwhile.

The crowd walked along the main street surrounded by magic walls and trees and finally reached the main auditorium.

There, the professors had already prepared their speeches.

The vice principal's speech, then the principal's speech. Finally, after the first, second, and third year students are awarded their certificates, the ceremony is over.

Everyone was buzzing with anticipation for the upcoming vacation.

Then, Professor Banshee stepped to the front of the podium.

[Good evening, students, staff, and parents, I am Banshee Morgue, your new vice principal].

Professor Banshee. His snake-like eyes scanned the crowd gathered beneath the podium.

'The power of the principal's faction is small. Principal Winston is incompetent and has been out of office for so long that he will probably fall soon, which will leave me as the next in line.'

It was natural for Professor Banshee to make this judgment.

Ever since he took over as vice-principal, he has been steadily recruiting rank-and-file professors to work under him.

They're called the “sympathetic faction”.

The number of principal faction professors gathered under the podium was extremely small.

The professors of the sympathetic faction are lined up on the side of the podium, pressed by the momentum and unable to make a sound.

And this power struggle between the professors was affecting the students.

'Aristocrats faction'. And the “Baron faction”. Both of these organizations that divided the top students were unofficial, but they were definitely a force, and their positions were under the control of the sympathetic professors.

Sympathetic professors supported by baron and aristocratic students. And of course, the person the sympathetic professors supported was Professor Banshee.

On the other hand, the organization under the less powerful principal faction professors is the official organization, the Student Council.

The aristocratic and baron students under the vice-principal professors.

And then there are the principals, who are the ruling party, and the student council, which is not well organized.

Professor Banshee could see all these factions at a glance.

And then.

In front of him was Dolores, the student council president and a third-year senior.

She looked tired, like she'd been overworked for days.

Professor Banshee looked at her and clicked his tongue.

'Unfortunately, this is the situation of adults. The circumstances of young children are naturally influenced by the circumstances of adults. There is no principal, Dolores, the student council president.'

Professor Banshee's eyes shifted as he thought about this.

“...!”

His eyes widened slightly for a moment.

This was because there was an empty seat between the rows of professors who were already few and far between.

It was obvious who was missing from this important event.

'Professor Sadi. Is this person really....'

Banshee was speechless with disbelief.

The crazy lady professor didn't even show up for her own speech?

What an insane person with nothing to say and no answers.

From Principal Winston's point of view, it's probably better if she doesn't come at all.

It would be a shame to lose a professor to a personless principal faction, but... it's different when it's a troublemaker who gets into trouble all the time.

Professor Banshee was genuinely curious. Why would Principal Winston want to keep such a troublemaker at the school.

Was it respect for the Marquis de Sade's blood, once a great nobleman? Or Professor Sadi's formidable strength? Or his record of arresting countless criminals over the years? ...Maybe just fill in the numbers?

'No, no. No.'

Professor Banshee recalled his confidant's report from a short while ago.

'Principal Winston's favoritism towards Professor Sadi probably has something to do with the '47 riots'.'

Although the report was nothing more than a few speculative theories based on circumstantial evidence, the fact that the incident was even mentioned in the first place was incredibly serious.

'...Principal bastards. What on earth are you planning?'

Professor Banshee glanced coldly to the side of the podium.

There he saw Principal Winston waving to the students with his usual mild expression.

What could he possibly read into that innocent expression?

With a short sigh, Professor Banshee spoke from the podium.

[With love and respect to all those gathered in the Colosseo, I would like to say that our academy is proud to announce that this year's....]

The consequential stories continued for a while about how many graduates got jobs in prosperous jobs, what noble academic achievements they made, and what great human beings they became.

[...Students at Colosseo Academy may have an emotional dislike for their parents and teachers who are strict with them, but these are precious people who are teaching their children and disciples who will soon embark on a difficult journey, the stamina and wisdom to overcome hardships and adversity. For those of you who have just entered the school, and for those of you who will soon be leaving it, we wish you all the best for the year ahead].

Several students are in tears.

Professor Banshee continues his speech, his voice hard but warm.

[May there always be something to do in your hands, may there always be a spare coin in your wallet, may there always be a path at your feet, may you be slow to make enemies and quick to make friends, may your neighbors always respect you and mean people never pretend to know you, May the wind always blow at your back and the sun always shine in front of your face; may rain sometimes fall on your journey, but soon a rainbow will appear; may you be poor in misfortune and rich in fortune, and may the saddest day you ever have be better than the happiest day you ever had. And I will pray with all my heart that your destinies may always be full of peace and love, hope, prosperity, achievement and satisfaction.]

Professor Banshee concluded his speech with a short(?) sermon.

The students' applause burst into a loud cheer.

The students from the aristocrat clan and the baronial clan were especially supportive.

And with that, Principal Winston stepped up to the podium.

He looked back at the students with a smile that betrayed his age.

[I'm feeling a little overwhelmed by all the nice things the vice principal has said, haha – I should have thought of something better to say].

A light chuckle from the crowd echoed through the auditorium.

Then. With a serious expression and voice, Winston began his speech.

[It may be common advice, but... I want to tell you to make the best of every moment].

He looked around with an appealing gaze and said.

[As those of you who know me will know, I've been taking a sabbatical from the academy for the past few months or so, as my health has become quite poor due to the mana surge].

Winston's long absence as principal had allowed Banshee to skip a lot of formalities and step right into the position of vice principal, and now he had pushed aside the principal faction and was all but in control of the academy.

Few of the parents, professors, and older students were unaware of this complex power structure, so they all nodded in silence.

In the meantime, Winston's pleas became more and more heartfelt and sincere.

[I've been sick, and I know how precious health is, and how precious this moment is, and how we have to live every moment to the fullest because we don't know if we're going to die tomorrow, or today, or in just a few hours, minutes, or seconds].

He looked at the students in the front row and said.

[And that's true for everyone, even if you're not a hero like a soldier or a firefighter putting your life on the line, it's true for you right now. You are human beings who slip on the floor while taking a shower and hit your head on the tub and die. Or you get sick from eating your favorite seafood, or you get hit by a falling potted plant, or you get a sudden mana surge].

The mood of the students became slightly somber at the principal's words.

[You never know when you're going to die, that's why you have to live every moment to the fullest. Students, don't forget the preciousness of life and time even during the upcoming vacation period, and live a life without regrets even if you die tomorrow, or this very moment...!]

Then.

...Poof!

A small sound resounded.

The sound of thin leather being torn apart and the soft things inside bursting.

The sound was not very loud, and the time it lasted was extremely short.

...But it was enough to interrupt Principal Winston's long speech and all the audience in the auditorium who were listening to it stop breathing for a moment.

[...Kuhugh!]

A gush of black blood erupts from Principal Winston's mouth.

Something came out from behind the stage curtain and shot through Principal Winston's back and through his heart.

A knife? No, it's too long for that.

A spear, then? No, it's too loose to be a spear.

Long, and writhing like a snake.

...Pusyug!

It was a single 'whip' that drove a fountain of blood from Winston's chest and back.

Chapter 298

The Age of the Warmonger (2)

◆

...Pusyug!

A single 'whip' pierced Principal Winston's heart.

Giggle-!

At the same time, a burst of laughter loud enough to fill the great hall erupted.

A woman in glossy black tights and high heels walked through the curtain behind the stage.

Ms. Ouroboros.

It goes without saying that the whip that ended Winston's life in an instant was hers.

Her appearance caused a momentary pause in the hall.

It was the first time she had ever appeared in public.

But Ms. Ouroboros didn't give them time to adjust to reality.

“Ugh... uh, ughhhh!”

Winston. He collapsed on the stage and waved his arms.

Who would have thought that an outstanding swordsman, as much as a swordmaster, would become like this in an instant, in front of everyone.

And then.

...Quack!

Ms. Ouroboros crushed Winston's body once more with the heel of her long killer heel.

A perfect confirmation kill. Winston's heart exploded, and he died on the spot.

Ttang-geulang!

His sword of winter, Orwell, a sword that looked like the horns of a unicorn, fell to the ground and rolled.

“Ah, I finally got it. The 'key'.”

The silence was broken by Ms. Ouroboros picking up Orwell.

Aaahhhhh-

And then the screams. Students, parents, and professors in the audience screamed in unison.

And in the face of all this chaos, Ms. Ouroboros removed the mask that covered her face.

Professor Banshee, who had come down from the front row after his speech, his eyes widened to tears.

“Sa, Professor Sadi!”

Yes, the famous villain who had been causing a stir throughout the Imperial Capital. The criminal mastermind responsible for countless crimes.

It was none other than Professor Donatien Alphonse Fran?ois Sadi de Sade, the Academy's troublemaker!

“Hohohoho- Ah, I would kill for this flavor.”

Sadi chuckled at the commotion around her.

Then Professor Banshee exclaimed in disbelief.

“You've finally gone mad, stabbing your benefactor in the back for saving your life.”

Principal Winston, who had nurtured and supported Sadi all these years. But now she had killed him. A favor repaid with an enmity.

The professors, rarely siding with Banshee, began to rage.

“How could you do that to Mr. Winston, who raised you from a mere baby with nowhere to go for so many years, you beast!”

“If it weren't for Mr. Winston, you would have been a dead wretch long ago!”

“Ungrateful bitch, what a devil you are!”

“You're doing the same thing you did with your grandmother; you can't fake blood after all!”

But.

“Ah- quacking. It's not like we're at a duck farm.”

Professor Sadi rubbed her ears with one hand. With her other hand, she moved the whip ever so slightly.

However, that slight amount of kinetic power is amplified to a tremendous amount by the time it reaches the tip of the whip.

The physical force delivered by the tip of the whip devastated the ground near where the professors were standing under the podium.

“Kuhagh!”

Swordsmen and mages of high rank are thrown to the floor.

All eyes turned to the aura at the end of Professor Sadi's whip.

“Liquid aura!”

“Mmm, judging by the density, it's Graduator superlative!”

“Good thing that bitch hasn't reached Master yet!”

“But isn't that bitch's weapon a whip....”

Everyone stops when they see the whip in Sadi's hand.

In fact, whips, bows, and chains, among other cold weapons, are considered quite irregular.

In the right hands, these types of weapons can take your fighting to the next level.

A whip, for example, is a misshapen weapon that requires only a small amount of force to be applied to the handle, and that force multiplies as it travels down the length of the shaft, ultimately generating immense destructive force at the tip.

The Graduator's superlative aura begins at the handle of the whip and explodes toward the tip, creating a power that nearly rivals that of a Swordmaster.

Of course, with great power comes great risk. The whip can easily lose control at the slightest fluctuation, and has been known to attack its owner's body....

“Wasn't Professor Sa, Sadi a natural whip master?”

“Hmmm. I don't actually have any experience with whips.”

“The whip's bizarre aura explosion structure, plus the unexpectedness for such a unique weapon....”

“Perhaps, regardless of her rank, her danger level should be raised to Swordmaster.”

The surrounding professors murmur.

Then. Professor Banshee stepped forward.

“Are you insane, Sadi? There are tons of professors, students, and parents here. I can only assume that you did this because you wanted to die....”

“Write it off, old man. I told you not to say my name.”

Sadi cut off Professor Banshee's words.

Certainly, the Academy has its share of elite students who are stronger than most adult knights and mages, and its share of brilliant professors and parents who have taught and nurtured those elite students.

Although it is called a school, it is actually an institution that reveres the extreme spirit of combat.

There is a solid bureaucratic structure that is divided into grades and classes.

In terms of power and organization, it's like a hardened military group.

But Professor Sadi was still laughing leisurely.

“Hohoho – when did I ever say I came alone?”

Doubt and anxiety flashed across the faces of everyone who heard it.

At that very moment.

Boom!

A tremendous boom echoed throughout the auditorium.

It was an impact from the magic wall in the distance.

Next, several frightening faces began to appear through the windows of the auditorium.

A hulking figure with a rugged appearance, a beauty radiating decadence, a grizzled old man, and a child with an evil grin on his face. ....

They were all different ages, genders, and physiques, but they had two things in common.

First, they were all heinous criminals hunted by the Empire.

Second, they had all managed to escape capture and disappear into obscurity.

Suddenly, a chill ran down Professor Banshee's spine.

'I heard that the rate of criminal arrests in the Imperial Capital has dropped significantly recently. Could it be that the reason is.....?'

The faces of the criminals in the auditorium were all those whose investigations had been closed due to their disappearance.

'Jack the Ripper', 'The Wolf of Gévaudan', 'Tiger Champawat', 'The Bachelor of Powell Street', 'Son of Sam', 'Serial Killer Clown', 'Fashionista', 'Devil of Lorelei', 'Dissection of a Frog' 'The Strangler of Hillside', 'The Killer on Green River', 'Bloody Mary', etc.....

Here are all the vicious villains that the Imperial Guard could never catch and let slip through their fingers.

And, shockingly, they're all looking at Sadi, at the center of the stage, with respect, affection, and fear.

“Alas, my queen. I broke the magic wall as you asked.”

“Now please torment me some more.”

“Hit me with your whip, stomp on me with your heels, sister-”

Young and old alike, their eyes are filled with sticky hearts.

Apparently, they've been brainwashed and manipulated by Sadi, both mentally and physically.

To these villains, Sadi smirked and barked out orders.

“All of you. Explode.”

The villains responded in unison.

“Yes, Queen!”

At the same time, all of them began to hold their breath.

They let the magic in their bodies explode all at once, and the result was a power surge and a huge explosion.

Boom, boom, boom!

With a huge explosion, the auditorium collapsed.

In the shower of falling rebar and debris, Sadi chuckled.

Banshee deployed his magic shield to deflect the falling debris.

Then, still dumbfounded, he asked.

“Why are you doing this, have you really lost your mind?”

The question was meant to get to the heart of the criminal, Sadi, as well as to buy time for reinforcements to arrive.

Of course, Sadi knew Professor Banshee's intentions, but she was generally pleasant enough to play along.

“It's not me that's crazy, it's the world.”

“...What?”

“I've been waiting all this time to sound the alarm on this crazy world.”

“Waiting for what?”

“For this moment. For the principal to return, to be precise, and for the principal to bring the parents together. Wouldn't that help my message be conveyed a little better?”

Then Professor Banshee's eyes narrowed.

He spoke in a cold voice.

“ ...Is this also because of the '47 People's Riot'?”

At that, Sadi smirked and nodded.

“Did you know that? You're very well informed, old man.”

Professor Sadi spoke again. Her eyes flicked to the students behind her.

“I'm sure the idiots at your academy understand the incident as nothing more than a coup by power-hungry fools, but the reality is much different.”

At her words, the students briefly recalled an honors student's presentation in a previous class.

-The '47 People Riot' was an unprecedented event that occurred 35 years ago, when the Empire had just been unified.

-It was led by 47 people, but each of them was the patriarch of a single family, hence the name '47 Families Riot'.

-A treason incident in which 47 people staged a coup, massacred numerous people, and even invaded the imperial palace.

-Ultimately, 46 of the 47 were summarily executed on the spot, with the one survivor now imprisoned in the Nouvelle Vague, a prison in the remote reaches of the continent.

-The purpose of the coup is still unknown, but it is generally believed to have been to seize the throne.

But Sadi shakes her index finger.

“The reason why my grandfather and 47 others staged the coup was because they were nostalgic for the old days.”

“Nostalgia?”

“Yes. A time when strength was truth, when only the strongest survived.”

Sadi's eyes began to glow with madness.

“The Warring States Period.”

Everyone, including Professor Banshee, swallowed hard at her words.

Before the unification of the Empire, not a day went by that the continent was not noisy due to wars between countless countries.

There were hundreds of men claiming to be kings.

It was a time of constant change, with nations rising and falling every day.

It was the logic of the Warring States Period that the weak would fall and the strong would rise.

At that time, the strongest was the law and justice.

It was a virtue, and it was an honor, to develop strength and repay something that had been done to you.

Vengeance. Private sanctions. A world where all of these things were driven by the logic of strength.

...But since the unification of the continent, this has changed.

In times of peace, there is no need for strength.

In its place, laws were rewritten and institutions were created.

If you were weak but smart enough, you could pass exams and rise to high government positions and stand over the heads of those stronger than you.

Large-scale warfare disappeared, and revenge and private sanctions were considered dangerous.

For a time, even the “abolition of the sword” or “abolition of magic” was seriously considered.

“Peace turns men into pigs. A being no different from livestock. Aren't humans the lord of all things created to become strong and fight and win? However, in this world, there are many cases where things that do not deserve to be human dare to wear human masks.”

Professor Sadi exclaimed, her eyes shining.

In response, Professor Banshee asked in a calm voice.

“ ... I understand, but why did you kill Principal Winston?”

Principal Winston was a tall man who had sponsored Sadi since she was a child.

It was he who had defended Sadi's grandfather, the Marquis de Sade, when he was imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague for the crimes of the 47 riots, he was the one who prevented his granddaughter from being punished by association, saying it was unfair.

Professor Banshee sharply criticized.

“Is this what you get for taking pity on a girl who lost her entire family in one day and was left all alone?”

But Sadi snorted.

“It was you, Winston, who captured and imprisoned my grandfather, and it was in battle with him that you suffered internal injuries due to a mana surge. Did you think I didn't know that?”

“...!”

“He's disgusting, and he's a symbol of the academy, so I had to kill him anyway.”

Sadi shrugged.

The Academy is a means of integrating the warrior into the system. It is a tactic of those in power to suppress and subjugate the power of warriors by cleverly packaging it with words of achievement.

It is literally a symbol of oppression.

“Those who wield swords and use magic should be able to roll around on the battlefield, grow in power, build their families, and build their nations. All they can do here is wait for fleshy bones to be thrown at them.”

“So private revenge is honored, and we must risk our lives at the point of a sword for the slightest conflict? How are the powerless common folk supposed to live? This isn't some barbaric society.”

“What do you know? Why should the powerful take into account the circumstances of the powerless? Why do powerless people always whine because they want to get something for free? If you think about it that way, why don't you whine about monsters or natural disasters? Simply because we are the same human beings, of the same race? Through words and conversation? Are you being rude to strangers just for that reason? Do you whine to people you can communicate with, and lie down on people you can't communicate with? What kind of cowardly, sloppy logic is that?”

Sadi gritted her teeth and growled.

“Then I will be your natural disaster! Don't you dare even think of whining, just accept it, pigs!”

Sadi swung her whip, and another gust of aura rushed in.

And the number of criminals pouring through the cracks in the auditorium was growing.

“Sis! I love you! Look at me!”

“Queen Sadi, I would gladly sacrifice this body for you!”

“Kehehe- Kehehehehehehe!”

Judging from how many criminals she had secretly captured and set aside so far, and how perfectly she had enslaved them, Sadi's abilities were definitely real.

Just then.

...Thud!

The head of one of the famous criminals who had rushed forward instantly fell off and rolled on the ground.

...Thud, thud, thud, thud!

And one after another, head after head fleeing. A crumbling mass of criminals.

Nightmares that once terrorized the entire empire, dying so easily.

It was a sight that even the mighty Sadi could not help but stiffen.

And then.

Flutter.

Black blood is fluttering in the blood.

Dark black hair, eyes as bright as blood.

A man with a dark red aura rising from the tip of his sword was blocking numerous warmongers.

Chapter 300

The Age of the Warmonger (4)

◆

The number of criminals who broke through the magic barrier and crossed the outer wall of the academy continued to increase.

“Hoshoshos- I've always wanted to come inside this academy one day.”

A figure giggled as he made his way through the ruined great hall.

The so-called 'Fashionista', a rare psycho whose hobby was peeling the skins of those he killed to make coats.

“Mmmm~ the smell of higher education. Is this the aura of the Sacred Ivory Tower?”

After being chased by the guards and saved by Sadi just before being arrested, he became her most ardent fanatic.

“The skin and hair of the young ladies who grew up in a greenhouse are the best fabric. I guess I'll have to pick up a coat this winter. Hohohoho – if I take it and offer it to the queen, she will be happy about me, right?”

The Fashionista looked around and found a mother and daughter sitting under the ruins.

A female student with a slender body, and her parents who look even slenderer than her.

“Wow- getting some coat material, those two will barely cover the upper half, no, our queen needs to be very generous with the bust~ hmm, maybe a little short?”

He leaped to his feet and strode toward the mother and daughter.

“Now, don't be so frightened. I'm not taking your lives, I'm just skinning you.”

The mother and daughter just screamed and shed tears at the whispers of the evil spirit pointing at them with large scissors.

Then.

...Poof!

One sharp tooth sank into the fashionista's neck.

“Huh?”

He didn't even realize what had just happened to him.

Even before that.

Pop!

The tooth that sank into his throat gave one short flick from side to side, then snapped, breaking the bone.

Thud.

The body of the bitten criminal was tossed aside like garbage.

Hounds. The Night Hound, the one that bites criminals to death, was now standing in front of the mother and daughter.

“...Run over there, toward the smoke, there must be a way out.”

Vikir spoke in a blunt tone to the mother and daughter.

But when the mother and daughter saw the masked Vikir, they looked even more frightened than before.

“Night, Night Hound....”

A villain far more notorious than the Fashionista she had met earlier.

Knowing that, Vikir merely sighed softly beneath his mask.

“If you don't run over there right now, I will kill you right now.”

“Hiicc!”

At Vikir's inevitable threat, the mother and daughter jumped to their feet and ran for the exit.

“....”

Seeing that the mother and daughter were out of sight, Vikir slashed three more criminals who were chasing after them.

...Swagh, thwack, thwack!

The hound's teeth pierce through the tough skin, ripping open the entrails.

A crimson aura trails through the air, and before long, another criminal's life is gone.

As he swung the sword again and again, Vikir realized that the number of criminals was not as large as he had thought.

'But everyone is flocking to a fatal location. Someone must have informed them of the plan and internal geography beforehand.'

Just then.

“Hohohoho-”

Vikir turned to the sound of laughter coming from beyond the dirt.

Ms. Ouroboros. Professor Sadi.

She strode toward Vikir, who was wearing the mask of Night Hound.

“I see you are here, Night Hound-”

Sadi's voice held a politeness that had been absent from her voice until now.

When Vikir nodded, she opened her mouth with a bright smile.

“I'm a fan.”

“....”

It's absolutely absurd to hear something like this from the greatest psycho in the world.

But regardless of what Vikir thinks, Sadi continues.

“You're interested in the 'old days,' aren't you, Night Hound? The logic of the Warring States Period, when power was everything! You miss it, don't you? I know, I can smell the scent of someone like me, someone who lives in the old days. Hohoho-”

The words itself were true.

Vikir, too, was a ghost of the past, a ghost who had not forgotten the Age of Destruction and was living again in this life to prevent it.

But the meaning contained is completely different.

“I live in the future.”

At this point, Vikir's experience hasn't happened yet, so he's a man of the future.

But when Sadi heard Vikir's answer, she seemed to think of something else.

“Futurist! That's great! Since the Warring States Period I'm seeking will come again in the future, does that make me a futurist? Hohoho- After all, you are someone I have a lot to learn from.”

A glance of respect and admiration. Vikir gave up on having a normal conversation with her.

Except.

“...!”

Vikir noticed what Sadi was holding.

The Sword of Winter Orwell. The personal weapon of Winston, the principal of Colosseo Academy. Legend says it broke a thousand swords and never left a scratch.

Its long, pointed, conical blade and protruding handle make it look like a short jousting spear.

Sadi smiled a little wider when she realized that Vikir was staring at it.

“I see you recognize it.”

“....”

“Showing interest in this means that... As expected, Night Hound is also 'that side'? Ah~”

Vikir ignored Sadi's unnecessary flirtation.

He only said what he had to say.

“Hand it over.”

The Sword of Winter, Orwell. It was a very important weapon to Vikir, and he was willing to kill Sadi to get his hands on it.

But.

“Yes, I'll give it to you, but on one condition.”

Sadi said shyly to Vikir.

When Vikir shook his head, she suddenly unzipped the zipper on her back, exposing her breasts, which were tightly suppressed by her tights.

“If you'll sign here.”

“....”

Vikir paused for a moment.

No good could come from turning Sadi into an enemy in this situation.

Eventually, Vikir took the pen Sadi handed him and signed her chest.

Night Hound

The sharp tip of the pen sliced through the flesh, causing droplets of blood to ooze out with the ink, it looked like a tool used for tattooing.

Sadi exclaimed in ecstasy at the sight of Night Hound signature.

“Haa~ Night Hound's autograph. I must be number one, right?”

“....”

“I hope so, but it's okay if I'm not, I'll just kill all the people who got autographs before me. Hoho-”

“....”

To my surprise, Sadi obediently handed over Orwell after getting the autograph.

“I really need the 'front door key' too, but... I guess there's another way...”

“....”

“Can you promise me this instead?”

Sadi handed over Orwell and whispered something in Vikir's ear.

“ ...If you ever get a chance, please take it out together.”

“ ... I see. If I get a chance.”

“Be cool.”

Vikir finished his task and stepped away from Sadi.

After placing the Sword of Winter into Andromalius's barrier, Vikir turned to leave.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir froze in place for a moment.

It was a faint scent that wafted past his nose. It was the smell of the demon.

'Where is it? Where is it coming from?'

It was a faint scent, so faint that if you weren't paying attention, you wouldn't notice it.

But Vikir's trained nose soon found the source of the scent.

The scent was coming from the eye patch covering Sadi's left eye.

'Didn't Sadi become one-eyed during the midterm exam?'

Surely the area behind the patch in her left eye would be empty.

But somehow, this demonic scent wafted from there.

'This is like the scent I smelled when I killed Belial. I need to find out more.'

Vikir turns his head to look her way once more, and Sadi smiles and tilts her head.

“What else do you have left to do? Oh, you really want to give me something better than an autograph?”

“....”

“Then spit it out for me – here. Ah~”

Sadi cupped her hands under her chin and opened her mouth.

Vikir frowns and is about to say something.

...Kung!

A heavy seismic wave came from somewhere.

It was a shock so powerful that it accelerated the collapse of the Auditorium, which had almost stopped.

An earthquake that caused even the mighty Vikir lost his balance and stumbled.

At the same time, Vikir smelled the demon's scent so strong that it seemed to astound his nose.

It was a stench so strong that it could not even be compared to the one coming from Sadi's left eye.

“...!”

“...!”

Vikir and Sadi turned their heads in the same direction.

Then they saw a figure rising from the rubble.

Principal Winston.

A massive figure rises from behind him as he looks toward them with a blurry gaze.

A bust that looks as if it was created by countless overlapping shadows.

It had four legs covered in tough muscles, a cascading black mane, two darkly glowing eyeballs, and a huge single horn with a broken tip.

Unicorn.

But instead of the holy and sacred aura that myths often spoke of, it exuded an overwhelming sense of ominousness and terror.

Vikir knew it when he saw it.

'...The 5th Corpse!'

The fifth of the ten.

The demon of demons, the one that could not be defeated in a one-on-one fight, had appeared in the midst of this chaos.

Chapter 301

The Age of the Warmongers (5)

◆

Unlike the unicorn in mythology, it is a huge monster armed with evil and fear.

Burning yellow sulfur light emanates from the two wide-open eyes.

The large single horn on its forehead was broken at the tip.

Normally, a horse wears the reins and a human holds the handle, but in the case of this strange creature, it was the other way around.

It looks like the horse itself is holding the handle of the reins, and the human underneath is filling them.

<Amdusias, the '5th Corpse'>

Danger Rating : S

Size: ?

Found in: Deep within the Gates of Destruction, 'Serpent's Womb'

-Nicknamed '5th Corpse'.

One of the Ten Plagues, natural enemies of mankind, incomprehensible and unkillable.

“I will take away the lives of the first born that year.”

– 『Ten Commandments』 10:High –

Amdusias, the fifth of the ten demons!

At the sight of this muscular demon, Vikir's mind flashed back to his pre-regression memories.

'The nightmare that attacked the Academy just before the Age of Destruction began.'

The central clock tower, the symbol of the Colosseo Academy, collapsed due to the sudden descent of the Demon King, and many young heroes who would have become the cornerstone of the empire died.

When the sword of the cold weapon becomes dull and the heat of the Hot weapon cools down.

Only then did the empire have its first warning of its demise.

'...The deaths of the young students had a tremendous impact on the future of the Human Alliance.'

The catastrophe had enraged even those who had left the school for various reasons, such as Pigi and Sancho, and brought them back to the Human Alliance.

Vikir looked at Winston in front of him and Amdusias behind him.

'It is time to kill.'

The reason he had kept Winston alive so far was that he still had a lot of work to do at the Academy before he could kill him.

It was also because he possessed a type of 'dangerous superpower'.

Then.

Amdusias turned his head and began to look this way.

[...The scent of a demon hunter. You are Night Hound].

Vikir pressed his mask deeper and deeper into place.

His opponent was a Demon King who could be counted on three fingers in terms of single force among the ten Demon King.

There was no point in stalling for time.

...Flash!

The solid aura that symbolized the Swordmaster spread out in the form of a crescent moon, cutting through space.

Clang- clang- clang!

Vikir's blow caught the tip of Amdusias's horn and deflected upward, splitting the ceiling in two.

[Indeed. My comrades deserve it].

Amdusias muttered in a low voice.

Belial and Dantalian were good at cunning deception and legionnaire tactics, Seere was good at creating and leading large numbers of subordinates using black magic, Decarabia was only focused on defense, and they were so lazy that they even died too early and lost their strength. Andromalius couldn't build it properly... However, unlike them, Amdusias is a warlike fighter.

As a single entity, he is more powerful than any demon that has ever fought.

Thud!

Amdusias kicked.

His hind hooves struck with such speed that Vikir was sent flying backwards, crashing into the rubble.

'Strength, speed. Nothing is lacking.'

Vikir barely swallowed the blood that rushed to his lips.

'...But strength and speed aren't his only dangers.'

Vikir knows he's still hiding one more ability.

The same ability that had killed so many in the Academy before he regressed!

That's why Vikir had to be extremely careful.

Then. Amdusias turned and pointed his horns at Vikir.

At this rate, it would pierce through everything.

But.

Whiriric-

A giant serpent intrudes from the side and wraps around the tip of Amdusias' horn, tightening it.

It pulls him hard to the side, changing the trajectory of his charge.

...Boom!

Amdusias slammed his head into the ground a few feet away from Vikir.

A tremendous seismic wave shook the entire shattered auditorium.

Then, through the scattering debris and dust, Amdusias's amber eyes shone.

He turned to Winston and asked.

[...Are you Sadi?]

Sure enough, there was Sadi standing there, tugging at the whip wrapped around the end of Amdusias's horn.

Amdusias's figure blurred for a moment, and then the light returned to Winston's dimmed eyes.

Winston lifted his shaking pupils and looked at Sadi.

[Sadi. How could you do this to me. I raised you with love. How could you do this to me...]

Winston had done everything in his power to keep Sadi from being fired from her position as a professor.

And in fact, it was Winston who had consistently supported her so that she could receive an excellent education since she was a baby.

He's been supporting her to get the right education, to live the right life, to walk the right path.

...But.

“You're full of shit.”

Sadi's reply was cold.

“There is no way the granddaughter of a war criminal will grow up on the right path. Do you really think the system of guilt by association has been abolished? Isn't that what people looked at?”

Contempt, disdain, and fearful gaze that have continued since childhood.

Until one day, when she stumbled upon her grandfather's autobiography, hidden deep within the citadel of the fallen family, Sadi realized.

She realized that Principal Winston, her only support, was in fact the man who had brought down her grandfather, the Marquis de Sade, during the '47 Riots'.

The look in Sadi's eyes changed after that.

Although she suffered from abusive language, discrimination, unfair treatment, and secret violence, she patiently endured all of this, and the madness inherited from her grandfather began to shine in her eyes.

A warmonger. A world of the powerful.

Sadi gritted her teeth at Winston.

“All the while I was reading my grandfather's autobiography. I found myself immersed in it more deeply than at any other moment in my life!”

[....]

“Why did we come to a world where those with power look down on those without power? I also learned how to overcome that absurdity and contradiction!”

Sadi smirked at Winston.

“And it convinces me that, despite your pretense of humanity and peace, there was actually a demon lurking within you. Now I will avenge my grandfather.”

With that, Sadi began to emit a terrifying force from her entire body.

Qua-qua-qua-qua!

The whip began to wriggle like a snake with thorny scales.

The sticky aura, like coagulated blood, rides on the thorns as a result of the whip and lays waste to all directions.

But Winston just stood there with a silent expression.

[...Is this human after all].

And then, Amdusias's blurred body regained its full form.

[It is indeed worth denying three times.]

Amdusias muttered something unintelligible and raised his huge body to face the aura storm created by Sadi.

The result was....

Kujijik!

It was a landslide victory for Amdusias.

No matter how strong Sadi was and how much experience she had in battle, she was still a Graduator Superlative.

As long as she hadn't crossed the barrier of Master, it would be difficult for her to stand against a Demon King.

Bruak!

Sadi was dumped like garbage in a pile of rubble.

Amdusias aimed his huge horn at her as she spewed blood and pieces of intestines from the corner of her mouth.

[In the end, it's pointless, weak mortal-]

But Sadi was not discouraged at all.

“Cough! Is that so?”

[Bluffing doesn't work].

“I'm not bluffing, I'm buying time, hohoho-”

Amdusias shook his head at Sadi's words.

...Phew!

Winston's back snapped once.

A crimson sword pierced through his heart.

Vikir was already holding Winston's back.

“'It's over,' 'It's time to die,' 'This is your grave,' 'There's no hope left for you,' ... I've heard this many times before.”

[....]

“But guess what? I am here now.”

In the blink of an eye, Vikir laid countless stabs into Winston's body.

Amdusias hurriedly picked up Winston's body and stepped back, but Vikir followed as if waiting.

...Just then.

Suddenly, Winston's eyes turned red.

Thwack, thud, thud!

Winston, who was just a host, reached out and grabbed Vikir's arm.

“Who's the demon?”

For a moment, Vikir felt the stench of Winston's scent disappear.

And that momentary hesitation was not lost on Winston.

...Bang!

He pushed Vikir away and jumped backwards.

He looked at Sadi, writhing on the rubble in the distance, and asked.

“Demons and humans. Which is more evil?”

Humans reject demons.

Because they are evil.

However, sometimes humans act beyond the 'demon', the evil idea they created.

“The opposite of justice is not evil, it's just another definition....”

Winston seemed to be pointing out just that.

...But.

“I'm not interested in your shitty philosophy, so don't try to lecture me.”

Vikir is a veteran who has spent countless hours on the battlefield.

He's not a kid who gets swayed by the enemy's logic.

“Demons Kill.”

First rule of a demon hunter. A belief that will not change under any circumstances.

And that's what Vikir does.

...Pow!

The stab once again strikes Winston, and beyond that, Amdusias.

[I thought he was young, but he's quite the experienced hunter].

Amdusias began to gain momentum in earnest.

A huge Dark Unicorn and Night Hound were about to clash horns and teeth.

Just then.

“Woah!... Where is it?”

A loose voice is heard, somewhat at odds with the tense atmosphere of the battlefield.

Both Amdusias and Vikir paused for a moment.

When Vikir saw her face, he felt sorry in his heart.

The sight of her face made Vikir feel sick.

'Nabokov I? Why are you here...!?'

The Pope.

A being who should never have appeared on this battlefield.

A face that would have been poisoned long ago before the regression.

A variable that even Vikir was not expecting.

She popped up out of nowhere on the last battlefield.

Chapter 302

The Age of the Warmonger (6)

◆

As the prophet Lun faced the persecution and walked to the place of execution, his disciples cried and clung to him.

Then the Prophet Lun said, 'I will lift up my sword against the shepherd, and the flock will be scattered.' As it is written, 'All of you will forsake me.'

At this time a young apostle, who would later become the Pope, stepped forward and said, 'Although everyone will forsake the Prophet, I will never forsake him.'

The Prophet Lun said, 'Listen to me, for this morning, before the first rooster crows, you will deny me three times.'

Then Prophet Lun was miserably executed, and the cackling thugs approached and asked the young apostle: 'Are you also the one who walked around with that sinner?'

The young apostle denied it, saying, 'I do not know what you are talking about.'

Then one of the women passing by said, 'This is the person who usually begs the sinner to instruction and volunteers to be their messenger!'

The young apostle replied, 'I do not know him.' The young apostle denied it on oath.

A short time later, a large group of executioners arrived and shouted at the young apostle. 'I can tell by the way you speak. You are in league with sinners!'.

Then the young apostle swore that he would be punished if he lied, and said, 'I don't know.'

Just then, the first rooster crowed.

-『The Gospel of Lun』 26:69-75

◆

“Oh no.”

Vikir clicked his tongue.

He grabbed Pope Nabokov I by the hand and quickly pulled her back.

Nabokov covered her mouth with her hand and blushed.

“Oh, old man~ I'm a nun~ I can't go back and forth!”

“....”

Vikir sighed lightly.

Perhaps when she was sober, but right now, with her judgment clouded by the dementia, so he couldn't expect help from the Pope.

Because she wasn't destined to get caught up in this situation in the first place.

'I'll have to get her to a safe place somehow.'

Then.

Winston's expression changed strangely when he saw Pope Nabokov I's face.

Surprisingly, he seemed to retain some semblance of sanity in the face of his demonization.

“The Pope, she might know. Demon or human, which is more evil.”

“....”

When Vikir remained silent, Winston spoke again.

“The Faithful Quovadis, descendants of those who denied the Gods three times. They also honor a prophet who was lost at the hands of the very humans they sought to protect.”

The prophet Lun, long ago, persecuted and lost.

Winston smiled.

“There was a time when I, too, valued humanity above all else, and I was deeply sympathetic to the doctrines of the Quovadis.”

At the same time, the unicorn Amdusias fluttered his dark mane and tugged on the reins around Winston's neck.

As the demon erodes the human mind, the fragments of memories that are chipped away create countless sparks.

Vikir had witnessed some of those shards with his own eyes.

...In the fragments of memory. The little boy was crying.

His parents had made a good living selling beans.

But when a famine hit and they couldn't bear to see their neighbors starving, unpacked all the beans in the warehouse, made a large tofu, and held a charity sharing event.

By the precept that it is God's teaching.

The crowd swarmed like flies, and they didn't even bother to follow the one bean per person rule.

Cutting in line, lying, stealing, threats, violence... What's more, they later took the tofu away with a club.

When they finally ran out of tofu, a huge crowd of late arrivals stood up and shouted, “Why don't you give it to me?”, “You're a terrible person for not giving it to me!”, and “There's nothing to eat at the rumored feast!”.

However, those who received the tofu did not give it to them instead.

'When did I receive tofu?', 'Ah, the person who gave me tofu?' The only response was, 'There was a person like that, I was so grateful.' It was fortunate that there were no complaints such as 'Is this all there is?', 'It's disappointing that there are less beans', 'It tastes bad even for free', etc.

And my parents were crushed to death by a fence that couldn't withstand the weight of the sudden influx of people.

'What is God?'

...At that time, the boy thought deeply about 'God's teachings' for the first time.

And he heard a voice within him saying.

[Deny God. Deny humanity. Deny yourself.]

The voice urged him to deny three times, and it sounded like the crowing of an early morning rooster.

So the boy grew up and became a young man.

Distrusting humans, the young man built a wall between himself and the world.

The first person to break that wall was a beautiful maiden he met at school.

By being with her, the young man felt that the wounds frozen deep in his heart were being healed.

His sense of humanity and faith were revived.

His parents' belief that people are basically good and his beloved's belief that people are basically good were consistent.

The young man naturally came to think so as well.

Under these circumstances, when he reached middle age, he met with a great accident.

He was seriously wounded in the process of suppressing rebels. To heal the after-effects, he went on a long retreat.

To the estate where his parents had died.

While crossing the sea on a boat with her, who is now his companion, a strong storm arose and the boat was in danger of capsizing.

The boat was heavy, so they dumped everything in it overboard, but it kept sinking.

So the sailors tried to throw some of the living people overboard.

They looked at him and her.

When he was torn between what to do, she was the first to speak up.

'Throw this person, not me! He is sick and cannot resist!'

And he was thrown overboard by the sailors. His health had deteriorated over the past few decades to the point where he could barely hold himself up, so he was unable to resist.

As he sank beneath the black water, he thought to himself.

'What is it to be human?'

What makes a human being give up being a human being, or is a human being a human being in the first place? How much of a gap is there between what defines a human being and what a human being actually is?

And when he reached the bottom of the ocean. He could hear the voice from his childhood once more.

[Deny God. Deny humanity. Deny yourself.]

It came with the second denial.

He didn't hear the first rooster crow, but it wouldn't have been strange if he had.

When he next opened his eyes, he was lying in the sand. His injuries had healed nicely.

Thinking back, he realized that as a boy, he too had been crushed by the fence with his parents, and how he was still alive was a mystery to him.

He returned to the academy where he had spent half his life.

Many things had changed: his body, his mind, and his surroundings.

He calmly adjusted to reality. His faith in God, his love for humanity, all remained in doubt, but he had to live.

...And. Finally, he saw a hole in his heart.

The delinquent he had sponsored and protected since childhood.

The descendant of a first-degree war criminal who was born crooked.

He believed he could rehabilitate this child.

It was done in accordance with the teachings of God, in accordance with his parents' belief that humans are good, and in accordance with his own pride in seeing this child grow up.

And now, as time passed and his heart was pierced by the hand of a grown child, he thought, 'What am I?'

A lantern flashed before his eyes. Memories from the past flow by quickly as if riding on the back of a unicorn.

'What have I been doing all these years? Was it all for nothing? Who am I and where am I going?'

He also felt a deep sense of doubt about himself.

[Deny God, deny humanity, deny yourself].

The moment he heard it for the third time, he closed his eyes.

The dichotomy between demon and human no longer mattered to him.

.

.

[Humans blame the ugliest parts of themselves on demons, what a mindless race they are].

Amdusias pulled on the reins and moved Winston's body.

Winston, too, lifted his demon-like contorted face, as if no longer bound by the concept of being human.

But Vikir remained impassive.

“I'm not interested in the good and evil distinctions between demons and humans.”

[....]

“Whether human nature is bad or good, I am human. And most of the things I want to protect are in that side, that's all.”

There is no good or evil in war.

It's just a maelstrom of interests, big and small.

An old soldier who had spent decades on the battlefield knew that all too well.

The corners of Amdusias's mouth curled up in a sneer.

[He is like that too. He's been arguing for nothing. Now die].

Another huge hoof flew toward Vikir.

Vikir had just drawn his Decarabia.

...Boom!

A white barrier blocked Amdusias' hooves.

A single ray of altruism shining brightly in a maelstrom of conflicting interests.

A white barrier that functioned purely for the sake of others.

“Van-nim!”

There was only one person who could call Night Hound by that name.

Dolores. She appeared with a brave expression and blocked Amdusias' attack.

Quack, quack, quack!

The landscape around them twisted violently once more.

A shout came from behind Vikir.

“What's all that noise, old man, I'm losing my hearing!”

“Huh! Pope, why are you in such a place...?”

Dolores gasped as she saw Nabokov behind Vikir and raised her holy shield even higher.

But.

[No use].

Amdusias raised his horns and still managed to pierce Dolores's Holy Shield.

A power far beyond that of Dantalian or Belial. It was a power that far exceeded Dolores' divine power.

'...Ugh! 'This time too.'

Dolores gritted her teeth as she was pushed back.

No matter how much she renewed her mind and trained, it was still the same in the face of such a powerful demon.

There are limits to human time, and the extent to which one can become strong is also clear.

The thorny pilgrimage of Night Hound will continue to bring powerful enemies, and at this point, Dolores is lucky if she don't grab him by the ankles rather than offer him a shield.

Dolores was frustrated with herself for feeling so helpless at every critical moment.

Just then.

A flutter.

A black robe of blood obscured her vision.

“...!”

Night Hound stepped in front of Dolores, covering her eyes.

“...Don't.”

For a moment, her heart was beating so loudly that she couldn't hear his voice.

“What?”

When Dolores asked back with a trembling voice, Night Hound spoke again in a low voice.

“Don't look.”

A sharp voice, as if on high alert.

Dolores had a hunch.

There was something in front of her that she shouldn't see.

Chapter 305

Hell Tree (1)

◆

The giant tree that swallowed up the Colosseo Academy.

It was of such enormous size and height that it was impossible to imagine its diameter.

It could be seen from cities far away from the Imperial Capital.

The roots hanging around the academy grew like teeth along the outer wall of the academy, giving the appearance of a gigantic monster lying down with its mouth open 180 degrees.

And at the center of the roots was a gaping hole that seemed to lead directly to Abyss.

The Abyss. The Hell. A grotesque pit at the center of its teeth, like a throat.

“What the hell is this! What have you done to my son!”

“My daughter! Give me my daughter back!”

The roots didn't budge, even when the most powerful men in the world, Cervantes the Spear King and Roderick the Archon, attacked with all their might.

They were even more helpless against the deep hole in the center.

A hole of unknown depth and unknown identity. And a giant plant filling it.

No one knew the identity of the giant plant that had swallowed the entire student body of Colosseo Academy.

...None. Except for one.

“It's a Hell Tree, isn't it?”

Camus Morgue asked. She stared at the dull roots before her.

“Lady Morgue. Do you know anything about it?”

Osiris asked from beside her.

He looked unusually urgent.

“Four of my brothers have been taken from before my eyes. If you know anything, please help me.”

Osiris was followed by Cervantes and Roderick.

“My son! My son has been taken, too! Uh-oh! This can't be happening!”

“My daughter! I must save my daughter! What the hell is that!”

Camus waved her hand in annoyance.

“I don't mean for you to get all worked up. No, but now that I think about it, why didn't it catch me? Is it because I'm not registered yet? Oh, I should have gotten the bracelet when the admissions office gave it to me.”

Whether anyone else cared or not, Camus had her own pace.

At that time.

“If you know anything, I would appreciate your cooperation...”

There was an awkward semi-response.

Where Camus turned her head, she saw a very familiar face.

Banshee Morgue. Vice Principal of Colosseo Academy. Current acting Principal.

Seeing his cold face, Camus immediately straightened up.

Banshee Morgue, Snake Morgue's younger brother.

His appearance, voice, and accent were in many ways reminiscent of his dead master.

“ ....Yes. Well, I don't know that much either.”

Professor Banshee sighed in relief when Camus, who was known to be stubborn and self-willed, obediently complied with his request.

Though he had no idea why she had suddenly become so cooperative.

Well, whatever. Camus's words were quite surprising.

“This plant is a magic tree that first appeared in history books under the name of the 'Hell Tree'. It has been recorded under a variety of names depending on the time and place, including 'Inverted Chaos', 'Burrowing Tower', 'Passage to the Oil Realm', and 'Reverse Babel'.”

“How do you know this, since these are not found in the histories I have studied?”

“In the mage histories written from the perspective of the Empire, yes.”

Banshee questioned, and Camus dismissed it lightly.

Then she remembered the face of her childhood friend and her first love, who had brought her a strange tree with one root and a collection of old books of unknown origin.

“This is the legendary tree of a tribe of shamans who have long rooted themselves in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain. According to the records, it has the characteristic of spreading its roots above ground and sprouting underground, growing upside down.”

Everyone's mouths were half open at that.

Ordinary trees grow upward, with roots below the ground and trunks extending above the ground.

However, this tree seems to grow downward with its roots above the ground and its trunk below the ground.

...Deep enough to touch the 'Hell', as the name suggests!

Camus continued his explanation.

“This tree is only about the size of a city on the outside, but on the inside it is different. It is said that it is close to impossible to accurately measure the area of ??the space inside the tree because it has the property of overlapping and distorting multiple spaces. It's literally a magic tree.”

While it might pale in comparison to a Wraith Tree, it's still a threat when it grows to this size.

They didn't dare to imagine what the children were going through when they were dragged into the Hell of the tree.

Then Cervantes the Spear King said.

“Enough of that, what do we have to do to break through this damn tree and get them out?”

“If that was the case, I would have done it, sir.”

“What?”

Camus clicked her tongue.

“This tree is impossible to intervene in from the outside, the only way to get through it is from the inside.”

“Where can you find something like that!”

“Where is it? It's here. It's not just a plant, it's a tree that only grows in Hell. Besides, I heard it's a fairly rare species even in Hell.”

In other words, it's impossible to do anything outside.

...Bang!

Professor Banshee gritted his teeth and punched the root of the Hell Tree next to him.

“Damn it, it's my fault, if I had been just a little more cautious... just one more suspicion... I wouldn't have gotten my disciples into this mess....”

Winston's bracelet, magic stone maintenance, greening project, parent observation classes, and unconditional tolerance toward Professor Sadi... There was nothing that wasn't suspicious.

The fact that he knew and did nothing to stop it makes Professor Banshee feel even more responsible.

Thus, the parents and professors were deeply despairing and wailing in front of Hell Tree.

But.

“What are you guys so worried about?”

The only person who is calm.

Only Camus was looking at the crying people as if she couldn't understand them.

“He probably didn't get caught, but went in on his own. Isn't that because he have his own thoughts?”

At her words, everyone's eyes widened in wonder.

People who had stopped crying flocked to Camus like they were grasping at straws.

“What do you mean, he's got a thought? He's going in himself? Who the hell is he?”

Then Camus replies, so nonchalantly as if it was natural.

“Who is it? My fiance.”

◆

Vikir opened his eyes in a black room.

A black room. That was the only way to describe it.

This empty space seemed to be used to store something, and now it was fulfilling its role of imprisoning Vikir.

It was like being inside a giant seed chamber.

'...It's just like I heard.'

Vikir had never experienced this space firsthand, but he knew it indirectly from the memoirs and journals of former Academy heroes who had gone through it.

The Tower of Babel stretched underground.

It is the result of the extreme development of Amdusias's power to 'steal the firstborn'.

'Normally, he's only supposed to take the first born, but... in this case, he's just taken all the 'children'.'

Vikir thought to himself in the small space.

This is an underground tower built by Amdusias.

The lower you descend, the more vicious the ecosystems, traps, and bizarre prehistoric creatures.

An interweaving of worldviews. That's what this creepy tower is all about.

Vikir closed his eyes and imagined the internal structure of the Hell Tree in the memoirs of great heroes.

'The ghosts of ancient civilizations captured and enslaved long ago, the undead in ruins where they lost their minds, the beasts that roam the void, the tribes armed with golems and magic weapons...A place where the worldviews of deserts, seas, volcanoes, and snow fields coexist on each floor.'

Common sense and the rule of law do not apply here, where so many multidimensions are layered, distorted, and refracted, such as in the Magic Tower or the Grave of Swords.

'It would be difficult to crush all of the Academy's brightest young sprouts, so they must have tried to trap them in here.'

Indeed, when the Hell Tree appeared at Colosseo Academy before Vikir's regression, many young heroes nearly met a miserable end.

If they died or retired within this tower, they would immediately become nourishment for the demon.

However, if even one of them is able to leave the tower alive, all those who have died or retired will be resurrected.

Before his regression, Amdusias also built this tower and was confident that no one would leave this place alive... but the demons' plans were ruined when an unusually genius individual escaped the tower in his previous life.

In fact, Vikir knew the future and could have prevented the tower itself from ever appearing....

'There's a reason I didn't do that.'

Vikir was thinking to himself.

-Ting!

There was a strange sound in the darkness.

A sound that seemed to echo not through his ears, but directly into his head.

Then, something suddenly appeared in front of him.

It was a piece of meat with twisted features, oozing flesh and internal organs, and flapping ugly, dried wings.

[Hell o, am I the 'fairy' wh o is in cha rge of the to wer?]

Vikir nodded at the bizarrely shaped lump of flesh that called itself a fairy.

'...Because of this.'

The creature spoke with a bizarre pronunciation and tone, accompanied by an unpleasant flapping of its wings.

[Fr om no w on, fir st co me, fir st ser ved ?]

Chapter 307

Hell Tree (3)

◆

As soon as I finished dealing with all the miscellaneous monsters that appeared afterward, a new space appeared.

-Ding!

[You've left the 'Tutorial Zone' on the 1st basement floor]

[Rewards will be distributed]

[The 'Main Game' has begun]

[Entering the 'Familiar Ground' on the second floor]

Vikir picks up a tattered piece of parchment that falls in front of him.

-<Return Scroll>/ Scroll / Rank: ?

A scroll that allows you to return to the Tutorial Lands for one time only.

The answer to the question 'Lord, where are you going?' is written.

※Level will be reset when used

Vikir clutches the scroll, given to him as a reward for clearing the tutorial.

Presumably, this is an item given to all participants that can only be used once, in a moment of crisis.

Next, Vikir descended to the second level of the basement.

The scene was all too familiar.

The Colosseo Academy. This was the interior of the academy he had been living in for the past year.

Lecture halls, training centers, and dormitory buildings rise above the streets below, lined with commercial shops.

The brick-built gardens, street trees lining the streets, plazas and fountains under the central clock tower are still the same.

The problem was that the academy's facilities were already in ruins. ...

Vikir looked around in silence.

The classrooms, hallways, cafeteria, and other facilities of the academy were as they had been before they were trapped in the tower.

However, there were some parts that were subtly distorted.

For example, the praying angel carved into the fountain had been replaced with a torn to pieces angel, and the pictures symbolizing Lun are all drawn upside down.

What's more, there's burning and destruction all around.

It seemed as though time had passed so long that there was a lot of dust.

The perfume shop, which was always bustling with female students, was covered in dust with broken doors and windows, and the sign of a famous restaurant was rusting away.

The stench of rotting meat wafted from inside.

The garbage dump, where the kindly security guard always waved hello, was littered with unidentifiable bloodstains.

Everything is in ruins.

[Amdusias devours parts of the world to feed his Hell Tree. The swallowed world becomes part of the worldview within the tower. Perhaps it has swallowed part of the Colosseo Academy].

Decarabia around his neck spoke for the first time.

Baby Madam also groans as if she is anxious.

Vikir sat down in front of the torn angel statue and waited in silence.

He can't go any further, though, as a translucent wall blocks his way.

The world devoured by Amdusias seemed to extend only as far as the Academy's commercial district.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir felt something.

Different students began to walk out from the dormitories, classrooms, and shops in the ruins ahead.

“Holy shit. What kind of world is this?”

“Are we trapped in a dungeon or something?”

“Damn it. I thought that was a fairy earlier.”

“Damn it! Give me back my power, you demon bastards!”

The students of Colosseo Academy slowly made their way through the tutorial and into the main game.

Soon, 108 students were gathered around the central fountain with the torn angel statue.

Some look confused, others calm, as if they've already settled in.

Vikir sat still and scanned their faces.

He didn't recognize any of the familiar faces- Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, Dolores.

Most of them were seniors, with the occasional assistant professor mixed in.

“Most of them are level 1, stats 1-3.”

Not surprisingly, the students are level 1.

And stats like strength, agility, and stamina seem to vary from 1 to 3.

Every once in a while, I'd see someone with a stat over 5, but they were few and far between.

'Compared to my stats, I think the reduction rate is a bit unbalanced.'

However, stats don't always give a complete picture of a person's combat power, and there are still Locked stats, so it's hard to make a judgment based on the status window alone.

Meanwhile.

While Vikir was lost in thought, the students began to explore the ruins of the academy.

Seniors became leaders, sophomores took on middle management, and freshmen took on menial tasks.

The most prominent among them were the aristocratic and baronial students.

“Shit. What the hell is this ruin, let's try to find something useful.”

“Be careful, that fairy or something might show up again and give us a mission.”

“Let's grab what we can. Food, weapons, whatever.”

“Ransack! Ransack everything! This place is a ruin anyway! Whoever picks it up first is the owner!”

The students began ransacking the storefronts.

The quick-thinking ones ransacked restaurants and grocery stores for canned goods and water.

But most of the canned goods were gassed up and the water was contaminated.

Unable to find food no matter how hard they searched, the students became desperate and robbed other stores.

Crang!

The aristocratic girl who broke the glass window of one of the shops exclaimed excitedly.

“Wow! Beatrice Newell's new perfume, it's a limited edition perfume, and I couldn't get it because there were no celebrities in the Imperial Capital!”

She sprayed the new perfume liberally over her body and shuddered in ecstasy.

“I was already annoyed by the smell of sweat and blood and rats in the tutorial area, so this is great!”

Meanwhile, the Baronial boy who broke down the store's door grinned like he'd hit a windfall.

“Wow, this is a tobacco shop, all these fine cigarettes. These are the cigarettes I've never smoked because they were too expensive.”

Strangely, although the necessities were gone, the luxuries were left behind.

“Well, maybe it's to relax before the main game?”

Even students who were not usually interested in perfume or cigarettes flocked to the perfume and cigarette shops as if they could indulge themselves for once.

...But.

'They'll realize soon enough.'

Vikir thought.

This tower is a creation of the demon, inside the body of a plant that grows in hell.

Everything in it is more than just unpleasant, it's downright malicious.

'Only luxuries like perfume, tobacco, and cosmetics are left. It must be intentional.'

Suspicious are something to be wary of, but in this tower, they are actually helpful for survival.

Just then.

...Gurgling! Gurgling! Pop!

Something popped out of thin air with an unpleasant noise.

It was a rotten looking piece of meat. It was a fairy, the guide of the tower.

[1 0 8 Par tici pants, Is th is the app eara nce of yo ur cu te fai ry? ]

It was still chattering away in a bizarre tone.

It's a pity that you've become 100 times weaker, but your growth here will remain the same outside, you can acquire talents you weren't born with, and it's an opportunity to turn your life around by acquiring unique artifacts.... There were only all kinds of fake comforts and sweet words.

But there was one word at the end of all these premises that quickly shattered the students' illusions.

[But th at's a sto ry ab out wh en you le ft the to wer ali ve, rig ht ? ]

If you die or don't make it out of the tower, you're done. You will spend the rest of your life here.

In the eerie silence, only the sound of dry swallowing is loud.

At that time, a senior in the upper grades worked hard to muster courage.

“Guys, don't be afraid, this is an opportunity! If we can get out of the tower, we can become much stronger! Let's level up a lot here, collect a lot of stats, and get out, because there are some rare items that can be found here!”

This encouraged the other students.

“Oooh, that's right!”

“Let's try something!”

“The Demon is alone, let's go!”

“I'm going to be a hero here and return to my family's arms!”

“Let the mission begin, you demonic bastard!”

All at once, the morale of the students rose and they began to shout at the fairy.

...But.

[ Ah hig hig hig? I li ke it, I li ke it, I li ke it so mu ch? Ar e yo u will ing to ta ke on th at chall enge? We ll th en, can we ge t start ed rig ht aw ay ? ]

The fairy was strangely amused by the courageous attitude of the students.

Because there are no lips, drool flows between exposed teeth.

The students were instantly tired of the sight of them clapping it hands so fast, even though it skin was torn and blood and pus were flowing out as it stretched out it's short hands so long.

Just as the students' enthusiasm was dying down, the fairy spat out the last line, shaking with joy.

[ The miss ion on the sec ond flo or is sim ple ? ]

At the same time, more than a hundred gaping holes appeared behind the fairy.

An unpleasant sound began to emanate from them.

[Grrrr...]

The sound of a ferocious beast growling.

Soon, creatures began to crawl out, flames spewing from their eyes and mouths.

A hundred 'Hell Hounds' crawled right out of the oil field.

The fairy watched as the students' faces contorted in despair and terror, and gave them one final task.

[ St ay ali ve ? ]

Chapter 308

Hell Tree (4)

◆

[Wi ll yo u sur vive ? ]

Due to its unique oral structure, the end of the word always ends in a high tone, making it sound like an interrogative.

But no one had enough time to worry about such small details.

<Hell Hound>

Danger Rating: B

Size: 3 meters

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 2

-A.K.A 'the dog that drives hell'.

It brings terrible disaster to anyone it encounters, and once bitten, no one survives.

The sulfurous fire that spews from its eyes and mouth is drawn from the depths of the Oilpole Hell, and will not be extinguished until the life it has used as fuel is completely consumed.

Hellhound. A sinister beast that breathes sulfuric fire from its eyes and mouth.

The number of hellhounds charging toward the 108 students was exactly 108.

[ It's ok ay to be 100 tim es wea ker, rig ht? You gu ys are 108, th ese chil dren are al so 108, Ple ase ho ld on we ll ? ]

The fairy was twisting her body like she was going crazy with joy.

And then, an aristocratic female student who belatedly realized the situation screamed.

“Kyaahhhhh! What is that!”

The game was begun.

-Ding!

The number “108” appeared in front of everyone's eyes.

All the students realized that the number was rapidly decreasing as time went on.

'108 people survive 108 hellhounds for 108 minutes.'

This was the mission of the second floor of the basement.

“Hiii! How am I going to beat this!”

“You idiot! You don't have to fight! You win if you survive!”

“We can run and hide! This is an academy, even if it's in ruins!”

“This is where we've been living for the past few years! I know where we can hide!”

'If I could use my full power, I would form a party and fight, but it is impossible to fight against a pack of hellhounds now that I am 100 times weaker.'

“Let's go to the girls' dormitory! The roof there should be enough to keep them at bay!”

“No, we have to get into the water tank!”

“There's an underground bunker in the grocery store! The doors there are thick!”

“Let's go to the gym! There are lots of things that can be used as weapons!”

The students rushed to the places they knew best.

But there was something they overlooked.

The terrain here is subtly different from the Academy.

Everything was in ruins.

“What! Oh, the roof's collapsed! Eek! Hellhounds are coming! Jump!”

“What, the water tank is full of rotten water! We can get in, but we can't hold our breath for 108 minutes!”

“Ugh, the doors to the underground bunker are all rusted and corroded!”

“There's not a single workout machine in the gym! Damn it!”

The big terrain was the same as they knew it, but the small details were different.

The students frantically ran and hid from the swarming hellhounds.

...And one of them was Granola, a first-year vice leader student at the Hot Class.

“Ugh! Aaaah-”

Granola ran frantically, his face covered in tears, snot, and drool.

Behind him, he could hear the clashing teeth of the hellhounds.

That means they're close.

'No, you're wrong, It's hard to even escape with a body that's 100 times weaker!'

If he didn't hide somewhere right away, he would die a horrible death that would leave his body untouchable.

Then.

“Hey! Aren't you Granola?”

“Hey! It's dangerous! Get over here! Now!”

A voice called out for Granola from the side.

A girl with a slender and pretty appearance and a boy with a sturdy build and an imposing appearance.

They were Granola's direct seniors, second-year students of the aristocratic faction.

Granola's face widened when he saw their faces.

Since they are direct seniors of the aristocratic faction that raised Granola with care, he would not hesitate to mention their names when asked to name his closest connections.

“Come on, seniors!”

“Hurry up, you're in real danger, buddy!”

At the male student's warning, Granola quickly ducked his head.

Above him, the sharp claws of the Hellhound sliced through the air.

In his despair, Granola thought he saw a glimmer of hope.

'That's right. No matter how difficult a crisis is, we can overcome it if everyone works together!'

But the very next moment, that glimmer of hope is shattered.

...Tud!

As Granola came running, the female student stretched out her long leg and stepped on Granola.

“Huh?”

Granola fell to the ground without knowing what was happening.

Then he saw the senior girl and the boy ahead of him smirking.

“Sorry. I'm a little slow on my feet.”

“We thought we'd get caught if we didn't bait you.”

They darted forward as Granola fell to the ground, attracting the attention of the Hellhounds.

“...This is impossible.”

Granola despaired.

Both the current situation and the fact that their bond outside of the tower was actually nothing.

So what was the point of all his time and connections at the Academy?

'...Have I lived wrongly?'

Granola looked out at the commoner students in the distance, running to help the wounded or fighting alongside them.

When Granola was in school, he wouldn't have even said hello to them because of their poor grades and insignificant backgrounds.

But now, they were united by the strongest bonds of motivation and comradeship.

Granola closed his eyes with deep regret.

He knew in his bones that the price of making the wrong friend was too high.

And then. The hounds approached.

He didn't have to look to know.

A chill.

He could feel the monstrous hounds with their terrifying teeth and claws reaching for the nape of his neck.

A hound that exudes such powerful force that Granola immediately gave up on life.

It bit down on Granola's neck with a strong, domineering force.

...Bam!

At the same time.

“What?”

Granola felt his body floating in the air.

He turned 180 degrees and saw the unthinkable in front of him.

“Don't stay down, get up and run.”

Vikir. He grabbed Granola's back with his hand.

◆

Some time had already passed.

The surviving students were hiding in various parts of the ruins.

The same was true for the boys and girls of the aristocratic faction who had run from Granola's feet earlier.

They slammed the doors of the grocery store shut and hid in the cellars.

“They won't find us here.”

“Of course not, it's so well hidden.”

The girl smirked at the boy's comment.

They talked about what had happened earlier.

“Shouldn't you feel a little sorry for him?”

“What are you sorry about? It's better than us dying.”

“Yeah, but it's kind of weird that he was all red when I called him.”

“He's a first year, so he's a bit naive. I only took him because he's from the Leviathan family, but ah- who cares about his status outside the tower when we're down here.”

The male and female students smirked and nodded.

Just then.

[Grrrr...]

From above, the Hellhounds stirred.

A single one had separated from the pack and burst through the door of the grocery store.

'Eek! Since there are no visible baits, let's search!'

'Don't worry. No one knows about this basement.'

The boys and girls crouched down, covering each other's mouths.

The hellhound slowly circled the store, scanning the area.

But when it saw nothing, it turned and started to walk out of the store.

Just then.

[...Thump!]

The hellhound's eyes changed.

It immediately ran to the corner of the store and began scratching frantically at the floor.

Bukbukbukbuk-crunch!

His claws, heated by the sulfur fire, tore through the hardwood floor like paper.

Inside were a group of boys and girls with grotesque expressions.

“Ugh. How did you know!”

“Kyaahhh! You said we wouldn't be found out!”

At the same time, they realized.

The Hellhound's nose was flapping frantically.

'Wow, new Beatrice Newell! It's a limited edition perfume, and I couldn't find it because there weren't any celebrities who were said to be the king of the Imperial Capital!'

'Wow, this is a tobacconist's shop, with a stack of fancy cigarettes. Aren't these the cigarettes I never got around to smoking?'

'Well, maybe they're just trying to get us to relax before we get into the real game?'

And then they realize that before they hide in the basement, they've been sprayed with limited-edition perfume and smoked fine tobacco.

The Hellhounds used their keen sense of smell to pinpoint the location of students wearing perfume, cigarettes, and cosmetics, and they were in hot pursuit.

Anyone who wore even a drop of hand cream was not immune from the hellhounds' pursuit.

Meanwhile.

“...That's what it's going to be like.”

“What, what? What did you just say?”

“Nothing.”

Vikir looked away, watching the goings-on at the grocery store in the distance.

Behind him, Granola looked terrified, and in front of him was a pack of hellhounds.

The other hellhounds, who had been chasing the runaways, had caught up to Vikir.

Granola despaired at the dead-end alley behind them.

“Ugh! That's why I told you to go to the dormitory wing, there's plenty of places to hide in the area where my room was! You ignored me and came this way, and now you've brought all the hellhounds from everywhere!”

The hellhounds currently surrounding Vikir and Granola accounted for most of the total number of summoned.

With most of the Hellhounds concentrated here, the survival rate of the other students is quite high.

However, it's hard not to feel like a broken man in this harsh situation.

'I'm crazy! I shouldn't have followed this guy! I shouldn't have been so weak after all the help I got earlier...!'

Granola regrets his choice.

“Don't worry. There's a way out.”

Vikir said simply.

Granola retorted in disbelief.

“There's no way, how are we going to run and hide from all these hellhounds!”

“...Hide? Why hide?”

“Huh?”

Granola gives Vikir a blank look in response.

But Vikir is completely unfazed and replies with a nonchalant expression.

“I'll get them all.”

The hellhounds here... No, all the chunks of experience.

Chapter 310

Hell Tree (6)

◆

[Grrrrr...]

Cerberus began to emit dark murderous energy.

“Long time no see.”

Vikir couldn't help but think of the long-ago confrontation on Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

His first monthly evaluation at the age of 8. His childhood in the wilds of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Back then, he'd caught them with chocolate obtained from beating the Baskervilles' triplets, a pit trap he'd spent days carving, and a combo move that utilized the venom of the Bloody Mamba he'd saved from its Cradle.

“Do you recognize this scent? It belongs to your kind.”

Vikir took out the hood of the picaresque mask he was wearing around his neck and took it out of his collar.

The hood was sewn from Cerberus's hide.

It had been tanned countless times, but the dog's scent had never completely disappeared.

Cerberus's face contorted even more frighteningly when he smelled his own kind.

[Kwaaagh!]

Vikir stumbled backwards, dodging the teeth and claws of the charging Cerberus.

Kurrrr! Pug!

Beelzebub, coated in a sticky liquid aura, slammed into Cerberus's side.

'I felt it.'

It didn't pierce the thick hide, but it did manage to drive the impact into it.

Probably cracked some bones.

But.

...Swash!

Cerberus swung its tail as soon as its side gave way, slamming into Vikir's body.

When people think of Cerberus, they think of its three heads, but its real weapon is its tail.

The sharp spear at the tip of its tail and the venom that coats it are enough to instantly kill a Danger Class A or higher creature with a single stab.

Vikir himself was poisoned by the tip of his tail.

Hororok-

A young madam crawled out from the side, sucking the poison from Vikir's wound.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

The basilisk's regenerative ability makes the wound on its side heal in an instant.

Kang! Kaang- Ttang! Chaang-

Cerberus' tail and Vikir's sword began to clash fiercely.

A spark from the clash caught the bangs of the stunned Granola.

“Ouch! Hot! What is it! Hic!”

Upon opening his eyes, he saw Vikir and Cerberus clashing with terrifying force.

Sssh.

A long line of blood drew across Vikir's cheek.

Seeing it, Granola exclaimed.

“That, look at that! How is he going to catch Cerberus with a body 100 times weaker...!”

But before he could finish his sentence.

Bam!

Vikir brought one of Cerberus's heads up with his knee.

Cerberus' middle head cackled, missing its lower jaw.

“...You caught it?”

Granola mumbles, looking dazed.

Even school professors fight on equal footing against a monster the size of a human, and with a body a hundred times weaker?

'Ho, how can a level 1 be able to fight like that, who the hell is he?'

Just to be sure, Granola punches the wall with his fist, and it's clear that his strength has been reduced by a hundredth.

Granola began to shudder at the thought of how strong Vikir's original fighting power must have been before he was trapped in the tower.

Meanwhile. Vikir was slowly falling back.

Cerberus, with its poisonous spirit, was a much more difficult opponent to deal with than expected.

What's more, the creature in front of him now, having been brought by the fairy straight from the depths of the Oil Fields, was much larger and more ferocious than the one he had faced on the Black Mountain.

Even if he somehow wins, this is still only the second level of the underground. At this rate, it would be a battle of attrition.

'One chance.'

Vikir leapt toward Cerberus once again.

Boom.

Cerberus's forepaws flew out.

It was a familiar demeanor, as if Cerberus had already figured out Vikir's strength and speed after a few engagements.

However.

'...Now!'

Just before Cerberus clashed with him, Vikir reached into his pocket and pulled out all of the strange candies that were inside.

Warglock-

The sensation of small, hard, round, sticky things in his grasp.

Red candies for strength, green candies for agility, and blue candies for stamina.

Vikir shoved them into his mouth and chewed.

Crunch, crunch, crunch!

A salty, bitter, astringent flavor that reached the root of his tongue.

'...I've heard that some people can't eat them because of the taste.'

Even Vikir, who had a strong stomach, feel nauseous.

At the same time, the status window began to change.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: 'Gutter Rat Hunter'

-Stats.

Strength: 178 (+52) = 230

?Agility: 203 (+16) = 219

?Stamina: 207 (+37) = 244

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

The stats have risen dramatically.

Cerberus was startled by the sudden surge in strength and speed of Vikir and tried to retreat, but it was already too late.

Pugg!

Vikir's sword pierced Cerberus' skull.

The sword sliced through the tough leather, pierced the eyeball, and stabbed the brain inside.

'But this won't kill it completely.'

Monsters with a Danger Rating of A+ or higher have an incredible amount of vitality.

This is especially true for a creature like Cerberus.

Pugg, Pugg, Pugg!

Vikir twisted the sword inserted into the crevice of the skull sharply from side to side.

Only then did the foreign sensation on the back of his hand completely dissipate.

The inner muscle fibers, nerve bundles, and brain had been completely crushed.

[Kaeng-grrrrrrrr...]

As one of the three skulls went limp, the other two went on a mad rampage.

Vikir stepped back and grabbed Granola by the scruff of the neck from the floor.

'This one still has use.'

Vikir said briefly to Granola, who looked on in horror.

“Enough of this. Let's get out of here.”

“Huh? Huh?”

“Grab your sack.”

Vikir gave Granola a swift kick on the butt and lunged forward.

“Wait! Aaaah! What did I do to get you so pissed off!”

Granola was running with a tearful face on his face, but remained clutching the sack containing ginkgo sabik fruit as Vikir had instructed.

Then Vikir ran into the ruins of a shop.

Cerberus followed him in, sulfurous fire blazing from all sides of its body.

A threat to burn down the entire ruined city.

“Sow the ginkgo.”

At Vikir's order, Granola closed his eyes and threw away the sack.

Whack- whack- whack- whack- whack-.

The foul-smelling sabik ginkgo berries scattered across the shop floor.

Unlike a hellhound, Cerberus merely wrinkled its nose and furrowed its brow, but didn't gag or drop to the floor in disgust.

“You've got a pretty nasty nose for a high-level monster.”

As Vikir admired, Cerberus bared his teeth and claws.

The spear at the tip of its tail was also aimed at Vikir.

Granola cried out in horror.

“Ugh, what's with the ginkgo? It doesn't work!”

The stench of the Sabik Ginkgo's fruit, though foul, appeared to be tolerable to Cerberus.

But.

“Let's see if this one holds up.”

Vikir held his breath and swung his sword.

Not at Cerberus, but at a dusty shelf.

A quick stroke sliced through the walls, cupboards, and shelves of the shop.

Crash, crash, crash, crash!

Glass bottles shattered everywhere.

Granola stared down in disbelief at the shattering glass and red, blue, and clear liquids before him.

The colorful liquids scattered into the air and landed on the ground where the sabik ginkgo fruits were scattered.

Cheolpuk- Cheolpuduk- Pompompompompomp...

A scent passing by the tip of his nose, and words written on a broken glass bottle

Granola stammered and read it.

“...Béatrice Newell. Brand new?”

They were perfumes of all kinds.

At the same time.

“Uh-weh-weh-weh!”

Granola vomited up everything in his stomach with a tearful snort.

What was this horrible smell!

'Nose, my nose feels like it's rotting, my brain feels like it's melting!'

One day, someone walked into the classroom after stepping on a ginkgo.

The smell of the ginkgo pressed into the soles of his shoes, combined with the scent of everyone else's perfume, made the room smell like it had been sprayed with poison gas, and even the stern Professor Banshee Morgue had to cancel class.

And now, without exaggeration, it smelled exactly 100 times worse than it did then.

A level of fierce scent that not even Granola from Leviathan had ever smelled before.

Even perfume is fragrant when it's subtle, but when it's mixed with so many concentrated liquids, it's a headache-inducing stench.

Even the foul-smelling sabic ginkgo berries.

To add insult to injury.

Patter-patter-patter-patter-

Outside, it began to rain.

[Gwe-Weeeeeeeek!]

The prey began to react.

Cerberus is the highest ranking member of the canine family of monsters.

Its acute sense of smell makes this series of scents much more recognizable.

[Guaagh! Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr! Weeegh!]

It shook its two remaining heads from side to side trying to figure out if it was getting a headache from trying to digest what was in its stomach.

And then.

“Well, I can't wait to see what the fairy has in store for me.”

In front of Cerberus, Vikir stood with an expressionless face, with cotton pads stuffed into both nostrils.

Completely prepared to kill the prey.

Chapter 314

Surplus Man (3)

◆

[Underground Level 3, “Familiar Ground (2)”]

Only then were the 68 survivors gathered here able to fully understand their situation.

“Shit. We need to worry about food, warmth, and survival tomorrow.”

“You all saw the video, it's impossible to fight back.”

“Then we need to decide who will be our food tomorrow....”

“Who are we going to sacrifice?”

Rather than looking for food and protection from the cold right now, they should quickly find a way to satisfy the cannibal flower's hunger tomorrow.

The Daylily of Blood Tree.

It is said that this dangerous creature will only go to sleep if it can feed on one human per day.

The more movement it takes to catch its prey, the more food it needs, so we had to make sure it could feed with minimal movement.

“That means... one of us has to be sacrificed.”

“Shit. You've just destroyed our unity and everything.”

“This is a demon's ploy to separate us!”

“So. If it's a ploy, what are we supposed to do, not go along with it?”

“...Who says? That's just the way it is.”

No one disputed the idea that one person should be chosen from the herd to make a human sacrifice.

The question then becomes who, how much, and how to organize the sacrifice.

“I don't suppose anyone... would volunteer to be a sacrifice?”

“How are we going to select the sacrifices in the first place? Are we going to nominate them, vote on them, or look for conditions that will benefit the community?”

“Shouldn't we first decide how many people to select?”

Food and water are limited here. Even then, most of it is rotten or contaminated.

They could probably survive for about two weeks if they persevered.

In order to shorten 68 days to about 14 days, more than 50 people are needed at most.

“Damn, 50 out of 68? That's almost it, then!”

“That's the bare minimum, we might need to make more sacrifices. I can't go hungry for more than three days.”

“What do you want me to do, you crazy person? Throw everyone but you into the feeding frenzy of that fucking flower!”

“Who said that! I'm just saying that different people have different hunger tolerances!”

“You fat bastard, you've been whining about being hungry since you were in school!”

The argument intensifies all around. And then one of them shouted in anger.

“I'm going to eat you!”

Suddenly, the atmosphere in the room turned cold.

The student who spoke up also stuttered, clearly flustered.

“Eh? Eh, what's with the atmosphere? I'm just saying this, guys... Of course it's not my intention. Just ... Just....”

But everyone had a hunch. What they had to do to survive two months in this place.

It's not just about deciding what to feed the Daylily of Blood.

They also had to decide what they would eat.

Cannibalism. An ancient taboo. But a way of survival once familiar enough to be taboo.

The demon's message was simple.

'Eat each other!'

Being reduced to mere prey in the presence of the Absolute was not the true bottom.

What lies beneath is the underground, the chamber of horrific cannibalism.

“....”

“....”

“....”

One by one, the students were realizing what the demon was up to.

No one was saying anything, but the silence, growing heavier and more murderous, showed it.

After a long silence, one man stepped forward.

It was 'Arthur Gordon Pym', a third-year student who was the leader of the aristocratic faction.

Gordon opened his mouth in a heavy tone.

“Boys, we're going to have to make some tough decisions.”

Everyone's heads snapped up at that.

Gordon continued.

“Harsh decisions will continue to be required in the future, ... but for now, let's focus on the problem at hand.”

All the students nodded in agreement.

Let's put aside the scary and horrifying thoughts of food, water, feeding, sacrifice, cannibalism, and kinsmen for a moment.

What was urgent right now was the 'food' that would calm the Daylily tomorrow.

Gordon swallowed hard and said.

“We need to decide on a sacrifice for the cannibal flower tomorrow, do you all agree?”

Everyone nodded. Gordon spoke again.

“Does anyone have any ideas on what criteria we should use to select the sacrifice?”

“How about a vote on ...?”

Someone raises their hand.

A vote. Good. It's a good idea. After all, students have always decided many things in school this way.

But voting is basically a process of saying yes or no to a specific agenda.

“In order to vote, the person or condition to be fed must first be presented, so that we can vote on whether or not to follow it.”

You could name a specific person and vote on whether or not to sacrifice them.

But that's too direct and aggressive for the average mind.

The students chose to 'turn around' and point out the target as a way to avoid guilt as much as possible.

“Hey, how about this...?”

The big man, his body packed with muscles, crossed his arms.

“Even in nature, the weak are eliminated and the strong survive, so... would be sacrificed from weakest to strongest, and even if it was a dog fight, the weaker ones would most likely be sacrificed anyway, so....”

“That's ridiculous!”

The rebuttal came straight from the other side.

A girl with neatly styled hair and glasses spoke up in a bubbly voice.

“We're human beings, we're civilized, we're intelligent, we're not like that, we're not like some wild animals with powers!”

“Then by what criteria do you want to pick tomorrow's sacrifice?”

“That... I said before. We're civilized people, we're intelligent people, right? So why don't we pick the sacrifices in order of stupidity, or school grades?”

The idea of sacrificing them in order of weakness or lack of studying came up.

The big boy who had shouted earlier, still with his arms crossed, shouted.

“We should sacrifice the weaker ones first, like that brat!”

Where he looked, there was a small, timid looking boy cowering.

However, where he would have cowered at the shouts of the larger boys in school, he no longer did.

“You say I'm weak, well, I don't know. I think I'm stronger than you are now.”

“What, what?”

The big boy flinched for a moment.

The timid-looking boy slowly stood up from his seat.

He looked at the big boy with bloodshot eyes.

“Why don't you relax your arms?”

“....”

The big boy could only break out in a cold sweat, unable to say anything.

...Puck!

The next moment, a timid-looking boy quickly charged at him.

The big boy was stunned, and his arms relaxed into a defensive stance.

The big boy's arms are untied, revealing a severed wrist, wrapped in a dirty cloth.

His wrist had been eaten by a Mimic from the random box given to him by the fairy earlier.

The timid-looking boy grabbed the larger boy's wrist and shook it, grinding his teeth.

“What do you think, maybe back in school, but here and now, I'm stronger than you. Do you still want to do this in order of strength?”

“Kwaaagh! Are you crazy! Don't you know that I'm a member of the aristocratic faction!? If I say one word to my father, I can put you out of business!”

“Try to fold it somewhere. To do that, you have to get out of this fucking tower, right? Try it! Huh?”

With their usual tantrums, the two boys began to argue and fight.

Actually, it wasn't really a fight, but more of a one-sided beating of the boy with the severed wrist.

Was it because he picked up a few red candies? The timid-looking boy was throwing some serious punches.

At that time, Gordon mediated between the two.

“Okay, that's enough, now is not the time for us to fight, if we don't stop it, the atmosphere can get out of control.”

When Gordon, a senior member of the aristocratic faction, said this, the timid-looking student stepped back with a grunt.

The big man with the severed wrist also hurriedly crawled back on three legs.

His groin was already yellow and wet.

There were many more to come.

“I think we should start with the weakest first.”

“Send out the ones who can't study first! Are you going to waste their brains?”

“Somewhere in the lower grades, people are fooling around! We need to make sacrifices starting with the lower grades!”

“It's not fair to pick by grade! I'm three years older than you! Do it by age! Shouldn't the elderly be favored?”

“Damn it! Age is a free pass, how do you expect me to treat you with it? I'm not kneeling down, but let's do it in order of class!”

“Money! Why don't we do it in order of money! It's simple!”

“How about friends? Let's sacrifice the friendless first! Friendship vote! Friendship vote!”

“Ba, you know we're a great family when we go outside, don't you? The world is all about connections~ Let's think about it when we leave the tower~ The guys who sacrifice for me, I'll make sure to remember their real faces so I don't forget them later....”

As the atmosphere heats up, the guilt evaporates faster and faster.

The students, who were initially glazed over with guilt, were now glaring and drooling, as if they were bargaining in a meat market.

“Do it like intelligent people, vote! Vote!”

“Fine! Let's do it democratically!”

“Majority rule!”

“Yes, Let's do this until there is unanimous agreement!”

Intellectually, democratically, and through discussion, like the students of the Colosseo Academy, the most prestigious university in the empire.

As a result. It was decided that one student would become daylily food tomorrow.

A first-year student whose face and name you can barely remember.

He can't study, he can't play sports, he's not particularly good-looking, and he has no friends to protest on his behalf.

He cried out a cry, or rather, a protest that was close to a scream.

“It's unfair that I was chosen!”

“Shut up! It was a majority vote! You were unanimously chosen!”

“You guys colluded amongst your friends! I'm an underdog, and I don't have any friends to back me up!”

The faces of the other students stiffened as the would-be 'prey' shouted desperately.

“Hey, are you bragging about having no friends?”

“Connections is a skill, don't you know?”

“What's the point of being alive if you're useless? What good can you do to the community?”

“...Shut up. If we trick you right here and now, make a fool out of you, and throw it to that flower tomorrow. What are you going to do?”

“Just go quietly since you were chosen. We can compensate your family later when we leave the tower. I'll tell them you were a hero. Huh?”

Threats and appeasement follow at every turn.

Those who weren't chosen desperately tried to build a wall to secure their safety.

“Ughhhh... no. I have parents at home... and siblings....”

The boy who was chosen to be fed began to sob.

And everyone who saw his tears looked away, if only for a moment.

They didn't want to admit it. That this boy, reduced to a mere “prey,” is also someone's precious child and brother.

But what can they do? If others don't die, I will die. This is a place like that.

...No, maybe the world outside the tower was actually like this, too.

Everyone was nauseated almost simultaneously.

In the midst of the great contradictions and confusion, the atmosphere was becoming increasingly distorted.

Just then.

“Enough.”

The bubbling madness was instantly quelled.

A hand grabbed the attention of all the students.

“...I will be the prey.”

The footsteps pushed their way through the crowd.

Black hair, red eyes, expressionless expression that makes it impossible to read what he's thinking.

It was Vikir.

Chapter 315

Surplus Man (4)

◆

“...I will be the prey.”

A hand grabbed everyone's attention.

Vikir stepped to the front of the class.

His nonchalant face looks like it belongs to someone who's volunteering to clean their room or wash the dishes for the day.

....

The room fell silent.

There was hardly anyone here who didn't recognize Vikir's face.

The talk of the town, the first-year super-rookie.

Whether it's his sports, his grades, his skills, or his looks, he's quite a celebrity in many ways.

The auction's simultaneous outbidding of the Aristocrat faction and the Baron faction was rumored among the professors.

Gordon, a third-year student in the aristocratic faction, asked in a nervous voice.

“Are you... going to be the sacrifice of that cannibalistic flower?”

“Yes.”

“Don't you know what a sacrifice is? I mean, aren't you a little out of it? Did you hit your head on something when you fell?”

They didn't see Vikir hunting Cerberus with a pack of hellhounds.

But they did know that Vikir was much stronger than most upperclassmen, so they found the situation puzzling.

But Vikir merely repeated the same words in an indifferent tone.

“I will be the prey. If you don't like it, find another volunteer.”

With that, Vikir turned his head to look at the students lined up on either side of Gordon.

Although they were covered in blood and sweat, they were all expensive clothes that clearly looked like they were luxury goods.

They were probably students of the aristocratic faction.

Everyone who caught Vikir's gaze cowered and hid behind.

“No members of this group, is that it?”

At Vikir's question, Gordon and the other students from the Aristocrats averted their gaze.

Vikir continued nonchalantly.

“You guys, weren't you planning to hunt down other students and use them as fertilizer for Daylily anyway?”

The eyes of all the students widened to the point of tearing.

Vikir was convinced that the Aristocratic students were plotting an evil plan because of what he heard behind the scenes.

'That cannibalistic flower, will it eat and sleep even if we throw a corpse at it?'

'I'm sure it will, it didn't say it only eats the living.'

'...That's good, then. It will make things easier.'

'I'm thinking the same thing, maybe even easier than the previous stage?'

However, the students of the baron faction turn white when they hear Vikir's words.

“What, what are you talking about, are you crazy! How could anyone think such a thing!”

“Isn't it?”

“Of course not!”

“....”

“It's true, believe me!”

Gordon exclaimed in frustration.

But it was too late.

The other students, who had heard Vikir's warning, slowly began to distance themselves from the aristocrats.

No longer could they dominate the atmosphere as they had before.

Gordon scratched his head as he watched the students slowly avoid him.

“Damn it! So what should I do! I came here because I wanted to say something, but you!”

“I told you at the beginning, I'm going to be the prey.”

“Then just get eaten! Do it!”

“It will still be like that ....But”

Vikir paused and looked back at everyone.

“I'm just trying to tell you how no one will die after me.”

With those words, everyone's eyes locked on Vikir again.

Every single one of them looked desperate.

Gordon shuffled toward Vikir, ready to drop to his knees at any moment.

“What? Well, is there a way to do that? What? If you changed your mind and decided to lie....”

But Vikir didn't let Gordon finish his sentence.

“Get it.”

“...What?”

Gordon said, and then looked blank for a moment.

Vikir spoke again.

“I will catch the Daylily of Blood Tree.”

The faces of the students around him went blank.

“What the hell, crazy...!”

“Didn't you see the video the fairy showed us earlier...!”

“Oh, no. We just wasted our time...!”

Just when the complaints were about to explode.

...Boom!

A terrifying blast of sound ripped through everyone's eardrums.

Vikir raised his fist and slammed it into the wall of the clock tower.

Crack, crack, crack! Rumble!

The diagonal crack stretched out and completely collapsed one of the stone pillars of the clock tower, causing the bridge piers beyond it to collapse one after another.

“....”

All the students' jaws dropped.

Vikir spoke again.

“The Daylily of Blood Tree will be caught by me alone tomorrow.”

“....”

There was nothing to say to that. The students just stood there, mouths agape, listening to his words.

Then Vikir crossed his arms.

“But there are some things that are essential to the process.”

“...What, what are they?”

Gordon asked, and Vikir answered him nonchalantly.

“Random boxes. Candy.”

“...!”

“I need all of yours.”

At that, the students looked at each other's faces.

Those who had opened their random boxes were looking at the candy and other assorted items inside, while the unopened ones hesitated, holding the random box itself.

Gordon was no different. As he held up the 15 strange candies from the random box, he thought to himself.

'If I had known, I would have eaten them all as soon as I got them.'

But Vikir knew what they were thinking.

“From now on, people who eat candy will be excluded from transactions. Even people who have nothing to offer.”

“What do you mean, exclude?”

“Think about it yourself. I have a plan.”

That made everyone bite their lips.

In truth, there wasn't much to think about.

In the first place, the random boxes and the items they contained were given to them in order to survive the Daylily of Blood Tree.

As long as they could save their lives by consuming them, they would stay in business.

But the human heart is a tricky thing.

It's not easy to give up what you have for the common good.

Gordon, the leader, is hesitant, but the other students are not.

Vikir turned to Gordon, who was hesitating, and to the aristocratic students beside him.

“Earlier, you looked at me like you could never lose your people. Was it a relationship so cheap that you couldn't even pay for the random box?”

“No, of course not! I'm not doing this because I feel like the random box is a waste! I'm doing this because I'm afraid you're going to run off with our random box and candy, and I'm wary of that!”

“You might think so, then, but don't give them to me yet, and keep them. Tomorrow, when the Daylily wakes up, I will go and stand in front of it, and stack them some distance away. You guys stand a little further away.”

It's a way for them to have a backup plan if it looks like the agreement is going to be broken.

If Vikir betrays, the students can run forward and retrieve the random box.

If they do, Vikir can use his quick feet and strength to run the other way.

“I will not betray you. As long as the number of random boxes and candies are kept.”

“...Hmm. But does it have to be random boxes and candy? Can't it be something like money for leaving the tower, or an unconditional offer of a good job?”

“No. It has to be random boxes and candy. All other items as well.”

Even the students here know that the promises outside the tower are empty.

Just when everyone was about to give up.

“Stay here, Vikir.”

Granola was the first to step forward.

His eyes were sparkling for some reason.

“If you ask for it, I'll give it to you. We're 'friends'. We trust each other!”

Vikir paused for a moment.

Then he took the random box from Granola's hand.

And when he opened it.

...Snap!

The random box didn't explode, but instead bit into Vikir's wrist.

Mimic. Granola's random box was a 'flop', but that's to be expected when you can't tell anything by looking at it.

The blood drained from Granola's face.

“Aaahhhhhhhh! Oh, my God! Are you okay, Vikir? Oh, no! I didn't know! Gee, I swear, I didn't know, uhh...! No, that's not what's important right now, the medicine, the medicine, now!”

But Vikir just smirked.

“Calm down.”

Vikir squeezed the arm that had been bitten by Mimic.

And then.

Pow!

With his other hand, he struck the Mimic's stomach and crushed it.

When the box-shaped exoskeleton breaks, tongues, intestines, and teeth pour out together with blood.

There was not a single wound on Vikir's wrist when he was taken out of the Mimic.

“I guess I'll just have to take your heart.”

“....”

Granola gives him a blank look, then a sparkling gaze.

“As expected, my friend!”

All the students in the room stuck out their tongues in disbelief.

They had just watched a pretty strong third-year student lose his wrist to Mimic so futilely just moments ago.

Besides, Vikir was still not finished with his demands.

“And one more thing. There's something I need you to hand over.”

“...What the hell is it?”

“This is the most important thing.”

Vikir opened his mouth to make his final demand.

“I need one human body.”

“...!”

Everyone's complexion changed drastically, including Gordon's.

This wasn't like the random boxes and candy he'd been asked for earlier.

“What, what are you talking about? Why do you want a human body? You're the one who's going to make sure there's no body in the first place.”

“The only time I need a human body is the beginning. Right now, the Daylily of Blood Tree is overly skinny and has very hard skin, it's slowed down because of that, but it's also difficult for me to attack.”

Granola had seen Vikir cut through the flesh of the Daylily of Blood Tree with painstaking precision.

The other students had also seen hellhounds annihilated by the vines of the Daylily of Blood Tree without leaving a single living soul, so they all had no choice but to agree with Vikir.

Finally, Gordon said bluntly.

“Shit. So, whose body are you going to sacrifice?”

In the end, it came down to the same old discussion.

Who would die?

The student who fails?

The student who doesn't have enough money?

The student who doesn't have many friends?

Or those who are simply powerless?

With all these questions in front of him, Vikir drew his sword once again.

“It's up to me to decide.”

At that moment.

...Whirr! Kwa-kwa-kwa-kwak!

The stone pillars that Vikir had just smashed with the force of his fist immediately collapsed.

Seeing this, the students realized once again that Vikir was a hundred times weaker inside the tower.

Several times they denied the reality of the situation, only to have the inevitable conclusion come out of their mouths.

“...Are you a swordmaster?”

Chapter 316

Surplus Man (5)

◆

Gi gig u geu geu geug –

A sound unpleasant to hear, as something hard and dried twisted.

Exactly 24 hours later, the giant cannibal flower awoke.

<Daylily of Blood Tree>

Danger Rating: S

Size: ?

Found in: Deep in the polar hell, 'Inaccessible Zone (Blood Swamp, Flesh-splattered Zone of Area 4)'

– Also known as 'Blood Swamp Daylily' or 'Blood Swamp Nightmare'

A mysterious plant that floats on the churning waters of the Bloodswamp, at the mouth of the 'Blood Lake' in the depths of Hell.

Even in the blood swamp, where everything sinks because there is no buoyancy, you can somehow see them floating.

It is the strongest and most ferocious of all the creatures that inhabit the Blood Lake, and its endless appetite and gluttony make it an object of fear even to fellow monsters.

It is said that a single Daylily, sprouting from a single seed of this plant, once grew so large that it brought humanity to the brink of destruction.

A Daylily of considerable size and weight. It would have to be at least several decades old to grow to this size.

[Oomph, oomph, oomph, oomph!]

The noise emanating from the Daylily's mouth resembled the sound of a rusty clockwork being forced to turn, but it was a much louder and more unpleasant groan.

Thud, thud, thud!

The ruins around him crumbled as the creature rose to its feet and slammed down on the clock tower.

All it took was for the sprawling vines and roots to shift slightly to the side.

[...Gigigigig!]

Daylily moved the vines and roots around hungrily, groping for the ground.

But there was nothing to touch.

It must have intentionally raised its body temperature in the cold field to attract prey, but nothing was caught in its trap.

Fumbling...

The Daylily stretched out its dried-up root tips and pawed at the ground.

But the prey had already fled into the distance.

They're probably hiding all over the ruins by now.

[Giggle- giggle-]

Daylily felt more and more hungry the more it moved.

It couldn't wait to get into the warm waters of its hometown's lake to warm up and quench its thirst.

It was so cold and thirsty here.

Just then.

...Pop!

Something touched the end of the dry root.

It wasn't cold concrete or rebar or anything like that.

Warm and soft leather, chewy and juicy meat inside, and savory and crunchy bones inside.

But most irresistible of all was the blood inside. Blood, that sweet, refreshing nectar!

Shaking...

After so much cold and thirst, Daylily had found the perfect treat for its taste buds.

It's a different texture than the cold, rotten food it had been reluctantly swallowing.

The Daylily groped for its prey by the tip of its roots, which trembled with excitement and thrill.

It felt the tiny sphere that must be the head, the dense brow, through the delicate root tip.

The roots trailed down the slender neckline that connected the head to the body, licking the smooth cleavage, and the waist and hip lines next to it.

It climbed back up the straight, outstretched legs and now came to the hands, the only part of the body that looked quite rugged compared to the rest of the smooth body.

And down past the hands was a long, hard... this?

Daylily was just about to decide what this was.

Tsk-.

The sensation was abruptly cut off.

A searing pain shot through the tip of the root.

[Kki-gigigigigig!]

Daylily suddenly realized.

The tip of the root had been cut off by a long, hard sword.

“If you're awake, you should be moving.”

Vikir muttered in dry tones.

The Daylily of Blood Tree in front of him casts down a flower that resembles a face.

The wrinkles of the flower were horribly distorted, and the gaping maw was filled with misshapen teeth that had sprouted out at will.

Vikir already knew a bit about this grotesque creature.

“Daylily of Blood Tree. It's a plant-type monster that lives in the depths of the oil fields. During the Age of Destruction, the lakes were overgrown with them, and we had a hard time finding water.”

How many of his friends and men had lost their lives trying to exterminate them.

So Vikir had a better sense of the situation.

'This is the degraded version.'

It wasn't just Vikir, but anyone who had lived through the Age of Destruction would have recognized it.

Daylily of Blood Tree are basically aquatic plants. Aquatic plants don't thrive in places without water.

Only a lake filled with nothing but blood, deep in the depths of hell, can sustain this terrifying plant to adulthood.

'...If not that, at least a place full of water.'

When the war began, the demons brought the seeds of this plant into the human world, and sowed them.

There were no lakes filled with blood in the human world, but there were many lakes filled with clear, clean water.

The Daylily of Blood Tree drank from the waters of these lakes and thrived.

Although they were smaller than the ones from the mainland of Hell that had been fed on blood, they were still large and fierce.

'However, this one in front of me has been suffering from hunger for a long time.'

It's small and dwarfed for a Daylily of Blood Tree. It looks slow and weak, like it hasn't had blood or water in a long time.

...Of course, this was not to be underestimated.

Qua-kwa-kwa-kwa-kwa-kwak!

Just like in the video the fairy had shown earlier, this monstrous creature could collapse buildings in a radius of a dozen or so meters with a single swing of its vines like a whip!

No amount of ducking and dodging will save you from being mortally wounded by that attack.

'It's much weaker now that it's out of the water, but it's still an impossible monster for students to deal with, which means that....'

Vikir's eyes sparkled.

'I didn't place it there to be captured!'

As far as Cerberus was concerned, it had been placed there for entertainment purposes, perhaps in the slim hope that someone would show up to catch it.

But this was no Daylily of Blood Tree.

The students who had just entered the tower, even if they were a thousand strong, would be no match for this single degraded version.

They have created an absolute being that cannot be caught at all and cannot be resisted.

In order to destroy all ethics and laws outside the tower and create a state of anomie through antagonism and discord among colleagues, and even cannibalism!

...Boom! Quack, quack, quack!

A gust of wind whipped through Vikir's back hair.

The vines of Daylily whipped up again, making the surrounding ruins even more chaotic.

Destructive enough to warp the entire terrain!

“Admit it. Give up. As you have deteriorated, so have I.”

Vikir held up his hands.

Then he turned and started running.

His destination the meeting place with the randomized boxes of the 68 survivors!

'...Anyone who isn't an idiot wouldn't break a promise.'

Vikir leapt over the rubble of the ruins, dodging the whipping vines.

Now, beneath the collapsed fountain, he could see a black line.

It was a long row of 67 random boxes.

The survivors, including Gordon, had left them behind.

(Not including Granola's Mimic.)

'I'm glad there aren't any idiots.'

If there had been any, he would have turned on his heel and run for the hills.

That way, at least thirty people would have died and we'd have gotten through the day unscathed.

[Gigig! Geugyagyagyag!]

Vikir doesn't have much time, as the enraged Daylily has already spread its roots and is moving toward him.

Vikir hurriedly opened all 67 random boxes.

Puff-puff-puff-puff-!

Random boxes spit out items with a loud explosion sound.

Among them, there were as many as five Mimics.

'There are a total of 68 random boxes and only 7 mimics, so the demon are still in bad taste.'

Vikir quickly scanned the items.

Most of them were junk, not even worth looking at.

Polished bronze swords, shiny beads, fake potions, shoes with holes in the soles, stinking armor....

Vikir sifted through the junk, quickly searching for anything worth taking.

The first thing he picked up were red, green, and blue candies.

<Vikir>

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: 'Gutter Rat Hunter', 'Hell's Dog'

-Stats.

Strength: 230 (+30) = 260

?Agility: 219 (+10) = 229

?Stamina: 244 (+25) = 269

?Physical Resistance: 1

??: (Locked)

??: (Locked)

By consuming 30 red candies, 10 green candies, and 25 blue candies, Vikir's strength, agility, and stamina stats have increased significantly.

'Definitely, I feel lighter.'

The power of the stats was amazing. His body suddenly felt like it was boiling over with energy.

After collecting all the candies, Vikir picked up the rest of the miscellaneous items.

'These two are useful.'

From the pile of junk, only two items stood out to Vikir.

-<Sunflower Seed Shrew's Tooth Hoe>/ Farming Tools / D

A hoe made from the teeth of a large shrew.

If nothing else, it's useful for digging up plant seeds.

-<Oil Paper Pouch>/ Pouch / D

A pouch that is quite tough and does not dissolve well in water.

It's good for holding things because it keeps moisture out.

Once Vikir had packed these, he looked into the pile one last time.

At first glance, there was nothing left to carry.

Vikir was just about to turn around.

“...Hmm?”

For a moment, Vikir thought he must be looking at the wrong thing.

However, the seasoned veteran knew well that if he ignore this type of sense in an urgent situation, he will end up hitting the ground and regretting it later.

Vikir looked through the junk once more.

...Shiny!

Something silvery and round was buried among the trash.

A candy. Silver glowing candy.

“...!”

Vikir's fingertips trembled for a moment.

He'd quickly dismissed all the other colored items, expecting to find only red, green, and blue candy, but... hadn't expected to find something like this.

Even as the Daylily, mad with hunger, rushed in from behind, destroying everything in its path, Vikir's gaze remained fixed on the silver candy in his palm.

“...Heh. I guess I used up all my luck early on.”

Before regression, the great heroes from the tower reminisced about this silver candy, filled with great regret, longing, and yearning.

A treasure that still captivates the hearts of so many heroes, even after so much time has passed since they left the tower.

-<Strange Candy>/ Reflexes / Silver

A candy that increases the Reflexes stat by 1.

Tastes fishy.

+1 Reflexes

Vikir never thought he'd find this hidden piece in a random box on the third floor of the tower, which was said not to fall out even after all the monsters in the depths of the tower were captured.

Chapter 319

Underdogma (1)

◆

-Ding!

[You have left the 3rd underground level 'Familiar Land']

[Entering the 'Island in the Black Sea' on the 4th underground level]

The Imperial Capital area on the third floor of the underground is getting darker and darker.

Even the huge tsunami that had drenched them up to their toes could no longer follow.

All 68 survivors scattered through the one-person gate.

...And Vikir opened his eyes to find himself on the fourth level of the underground world.

“Hmm. An ocean.”

Vikir swept the dry sand from his face.

A moist sea breeze blew in.

He was on an island in the middle of a vast, distant sea.

It looked like an earthen mound rising out of the sea.

Bare dead trees appear and disappear like bones in the gray fog.

With a splash-

Vikir went to the beach and dipped his hands in the water.

The water was a murky color throughout.

He submerges his hands up to his elbows and soon loses sight of the backs of his hands.

The water had almost no buoyancy, so even hair and the hem of his clothes didn't float to the surface.

Splash, splash, splash

He waves his hand around, and his movements become extremely sluggish.

The water itself also felt much heavier than normal water.

“...Is this what you call 'black water'?”

Vikir nods.

An ocean somewhere at the end of the world, a very distant ocean.

The waters there are said to be black and heavy and float nothing.

Anything that falls into this black water, thick and heavy as molten lead, will not float and will sink.

That's why it's a taboo area for sailors, a place they must never enter.

“Well. A ship that's sailing fine will suddenly sink for no reason.”

He looked up to see a fierce windstorm raging on the black horizon.

A storm that seemed to circle the island and trap it.

Vikir shook off the salt water and headed back to the beach.

He walked through the black sand and back into the forest of old growth trees, where he could now see white soil.

“This is mycelium.”

Between the grains and grains of dirt are white threads, sticky as blue cheese.

Half the island is black sand, the other half white.

It was a strange ecosystem. As if it had been plucked from a different world and stitched together.

“...The soil dries up, the trees die. The result of two different landscapes being forced together.”

It's obvious who created this bizarre world.

[Amdusias is a worldview absorber].

Decarabia on his chest opened his mouth.

[He wanders the world, plucking out bits and pieces of the world he likes and storing them in the Abyss, which leads to a variety of different raggedy spaces, this one among them].

It certainly made sense when I thought of the Colosseo Academy or the Imperial Capital from above.

“So what happens to the creatures that lived there when a part of the world is absorbed?”

[They are dragged along with it, to the position of challengers to the tower].

This means that there may be previous guests who entered this tower before Vikir.

Whether they were human or monster.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir spotted something strange near the center of the island.

It was a large tree, towering in the center of a black and white world where everything else had dried up.

“The roots of the Hell Tree.”

Rising from the ground, it was a giant twisted thing, with no branches, no trunk, no leaves.

Perhaps it had sprouted from the main body of the Hell Tree, lost its way, and sprouted here.

Vikir climbed up the roots of the tree.

After climbing up the black, hard bark for a while, he saw a hollow.

Blood-red sap oozed from it, forming a puddle.

Vikir dipped a finger into it and tasted it.

“This is edible.”

The taste was faintly sweet.

Though the sap was watery from the tip of the twig, and the quantity was small, it was enough to sustain a man.

In the memoirs of the great heroes he'd read before his regression, there were numerous references to survival by drinking the sap from the roots of the Hell Tree, so it was probably safe to consume.

Vikir stuck his head in the hole and sucked the sap down. He felt like a bug, but that doesn't matter when it comes to survival.

The liquid was just sweet and bland enough to moisten Vikir's parched throat.

His guts, which had been parched, were now moist and taut.

But.

“ ... Is all I need.”

Vikir drank enough and pulled his mouth away from the sap.

There was still quite a bit of fluid left in his muzzle, dripping, but Vikir didn't touch it anymore.

Decarabia said.

[Well thought out, human. There is only a certain amount of sap that can be drunk from a Hell Tree at a time, and to exceed it is to be turned into a demon].

“I know.”

Vikir was just coming down from the tree roots.

“Hey, what are you!”

A sharp cry came from below.

A few students were casting wary glances in the direction of the hill in the distance.

The faces he hadn't seen on the third floor of the underground.

But they were all students of the same Colosseo Academy, so they were all familiar.

They continued to shout at Vikir.

“You drank that sap on your own accord!”

“This time it was our turn!”

“He came from somewhere and stole ours!”

They seemed to have landed on this floor before Vikir.

Normally, Vikir should have landed here after spending more than 68 days, but the fairy's improvised end to the mission seemed to have blended in with the others.

'Hmph. That means they cleared the mission on the third underground floor before me.'

I guess that's possible, since the concept of time in the tower is different for each floor.

Vikir glanced back at the students below.

Of course, they weren't the only ones.

“What is it? What's going on?”

“Eh? There's a new guy here.”

“Who's here? Are they from the barons or the aristocracy?”

One by one, the students appeared over the hill.

All of them are skinny and have bloodshot eyes.

They must have been poisoned by the Daylily of Blood Tree on the third floor of the Tower.

Then, one of the students, who seems to be the leader, steps forward.

“I am Dogma, a third-year student in the Colosseo Academy Hot department. I'm the vice president of the student council. I'm sure you recognize my face.”

It was a line that felt oddly flattering.

Of course Vikir knew his face and name.

'Dogma. Commoner. From the underdog city. Third year in the Hot department, top of his class. The one who lost to Dolores in the finals.'

Vikir is a male student who has a significant inferiority complex about his commoner origins, and has a tremendous competitive spirit and admiration for Dolores, who is the student council president, class president, and comes from a prestigious family.

Dogma turned to Vikir and said.

“I know who you are. You're Vikir, a first-year in the Cold Department, and apparently you've joined 'our floor' late.”

He continued in a high-pressure tone, as if the entire floor belonged to them.

“There are rules here, and they are to be followed in a fixed time frame, as the sap in the gland is limited. You broke that rule.”

“...Who made that rule?”

Vikir asked, and Dogma spoke as if it were obvious.

“We, the Commoners.”

“...The Commoners?”

Vikir cocked his head.

There are three factions at Colosseo Academy.

The official one, the Student Council, and the unofficial ones, the Aristocrats and Barons.

But there was no organization called the Commoners. There's no way a faction could be formed on the subject of commoners in the first place.

'I see, it's a new idea in the tower.'

The world outside is ruled by the rich and powerful. The aristocracy, the royalty, the elite.

It's a system that has been in place for eons, and it's increasingly seen as impossible to move between classes.

Although there have been extreme cases, such as the 47 Riots, all such attempts have been brutally and completely suppressed.

In other words, beings from the lower tiers could never ascend to the upper tiers.

“...But this place is different.”

Dogma smirked.

The logic of the forces that governed the rest of the world, the system that seemed eternal, had no power here.

Nothing but zero base. A world where everything was perfectly fair.

Rich, beautiful, handsome, high status, educated, strong, powerful, all the criteria that gave you an edge in the world... revert to zero, a level starting point.

Total equality of opportunity. A world where anyone can rise to the top if they try hard enough.

The low status you've been carrying since birth, your ugly looks, your weak body, your lack of talent, your poor family... – all of these things can be overturned in an instant.

You have the first and last chance to rise above the things that have always looked down on you!

“We've been disadvantaged since birth by the original sin of having poor, powerless commoner parents. But what about now? It's all about levels and stats, and honest rewards for hard work, and now we commoners have a chance!”

Dogma spread his arms around him.

The twenty or so people gathered were all commoners.

Dogma held out his hand to Vikir, his voice strangely eager.

“You're a commoner, too, I know, and it's been a long time coming.”

“....”

“So was I. Aristocrats and Barons can't stand it when a commoner does something well. Even though I never got to be the valedictorian because of that bitch Dolores, I have never missed out on being the runner-up, and by my third year, I was vice president of the student council, and I've endured countless stares and humiliations along the way.”

“....”

“Yes. Even if you don't say it, I know everything. Are you the one who ruined the aristocracy and the barons faction at the auction? I've been paying attention to you since then. I always thought it was a pity that these idiots who only sat there because they had a good relationship with their parents were slandering you. I wanted to help in my own way, but at that time, it was too much for me to think about myself. But now it's different!”

“....”

“I can help you, Vikir. Let's hold hands. How long will you continue to bleed under the exploitative structures created by those before you?”

All the students around him nod, their eyes moisturized by Dogma's speech.

There was an unseasonably warm atmosphere on the island.

“...What about the rest of the survivors?”

Until Vikir splashed me with cold water.

At least 50 people must have survived the fall from the second floor to the third.

Those lucky enough to escape the hellhounds would have been faced with a Daylily of Blood Tree and forced to make a choice.

And the twenty or so commoners gathered here are those who survived that choice.

Vikir asked again.

“What did you do with your non-commoner classmates?”

Dogma replied.

“That's obvious, you too would have traveled through the third level of the underground. They all became prey.”

“Of whom?”

“....”

Dogma didn't answer Vikir's repeated questions, but merely smirked.

“Don't be too hard on yourself. This is a land of reversed hierarchies, and it's fitting for the fate of nobles who are no better than dogs and pigs.”

Soon, the students split into left and right, following Dogma's gesture.

Clink, clink, clink!

Several students dragged chains they had apparently picked up from the ruins.

Then, several humans appeared from beyond the pile of dried black fire.

Dog collars around their necks, long chain leashes, and signs of beatings and abuse all over their faces and bodies.

“....”

Vikir squinted.

The faces were all familiar.

Chapter 321

Underdogma (3)

◆

...Bang!

Vikir ripped the chains around the necks of Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro with his bare hands.

The Commoner students, who had been pushed in the chest, look dumbfounded.

Dogma, the leader of the Commoners, asked.

“...What are you doing?”

But Vikir didn't answer. Only.

“If you despise the powerful, why do you copy their behavior?”

“What?”

“Isn't it true that you didn't despise them, but rather admired them?”

Dogma's brow furrowed.

His gaze remained glued to the chains in Vikir's hands, even as his words hit home.

'You must have a pretty high Strength stat to be able to rip through that thick chain with your bare hands. What's it, four or five? No... I'd say ten, judging by the way you're acting.'

With a strength stat of 10, it would be difficult to subdue him even within the lines of Dogma.

Moreover, there are more than twenty Commoner Faction students on this side!

“Don't be stubborn. If you refuse to join hands, I'll have to cut off your hands.”

Dogma's words changed the mood of the commoner students.

Unlike the aristocrats and barons student who were only looking to take advantage of each other, the commoner students were quite quick and united.

It's like the grass roots of a weed are intricately intertwined.

“...Hmm.”

Seeing this, Vikir's thoughts were subtle.

'It's all in your power, and you're rewarded fairly for your efforts. You can get things you weren't born with. A land of reversal, a land of opportunity, a new world!'

Vikir gave a small sigh.

'...What are they thinking?'

He wasn't quite wrong. At least on the surface.

In fact, Vikir had met quite a few humans who had changed because they liked the world the demons had created before regression.

Surprisingly, quite a few people with great talent and potential for Great Heroics joined the Demon Army during the War of Destruction.

...However, of the humans who eventually joined the Demon side, there was not a single one who was okay with it.

The New World, the land of opportunity, the land of reversal, was hell.

Most of their bodies had been demonized, and they had lost their minds.

Those who managed to retain their human memories and reason were forced to spend a horrifying amount of time in loneliness, solitude, and pain.

“Demons are monolithic creatures, devoid of any sense of homogeneity or kinship between individuals. Humans can never understand the culture and way of thinking of this creature, which exists only as an individual before God.”

Demons basically live alone. No parents, no children, no friends. If they do, they're just mimicking them, for obvious reasons.

In other words, from the time they are born into the world, demons are monospecies, and they do not have intimate relationships with anyone else.

Diaspora.

As a tribal and social creature, humans can neither understand nor be understood by demons.

And a human being who becomes a demon with human memories, reason, and thinking is bound to spend the rest of his life in solitude and loneliness, belonging nowhere, without purpose and without hope, drowning in his own life.

'...I've seen a lot of great heroes on the demonized or demonized human side take their own lives in their later years, regretting their choices.'

There's a short period of time when you can hold on to what you've never had and rejoice.

After that, there's an eternity of nothingness, anguish, regret, and longing.

This is why Vikir is forced to take a complex look at Dogma, a short-sighted hegemony of opportunity and reversal.

Soon, Dogma and the commoners under his command surround Vikir.

All of them were armed with low-grade weapons that could have been picked out of a random box.

“Hey, you're Vikir, I recognize you, you're a commoner, join our side.”

“I don't care how great you are, you can't take on all of us.”

“How many stats do you have? I'll eat the candy that drops when I kill you.”

“Bullshit- the guy who kills him gets to eat it.”

When they're casually confident of victory.

“Raise your hand.”

Vikir said briefly.

All eyes turned to Vikir's half-raised hand.

“I am a third-generation reader.”

“...?”

“There is a single mother, a single father to take care of.”

“...?”

“I have an old lover or am getting married soon. Or I'm already a newlywed.”

“...?”

Everyone looked puzzled at Vikir's continued words.

Finally, Vikir said something short.

“If you want to do it, leave it to one side.”

Then, laughter erupted from the crowd of commoners.

Dogma chuckled and opened his mouth.

“Where have you been reading so many fantasy novels that you think you're cool now?”

“....”

“Are you a high level, do you have a big stat, or do you have some rare items? Just looking at your arm, it looks like you're just bluffing... What do you have the nerve to believe?”

At that moment, one of the commoner students who was wearing special glasses spoke up.

“He's level 1, I can see it through these 'level peeking glasses'! I can't see his stats, but....”

Dogma burst out laughing.

“....”

Vikir silently raised his fist, but no one paid it any mind.

“Ohhh, you're going to use your fist?”

“Akumusherra! Hehehehe-”

“Hey, little guy. My strength stat is over 5. Won't your fist just break for nothing?”

“Forget it. I know you were quite famous outside the tower, but not here.”

Just then.

...Boom!

A loud explosion erupted.

It was heard not from the ground, but from the roots of the Hell Tree.

“What, what!”

All the students looked up in unison.

There was an incredible sight.

Sap, the island's only food. A cloud of dirt was rising from the hole where it was coming from.

And emerging from the dust was a large creature, its entire body coated in a black exoskeleton.

“...Oh. That's the ship's owner Decarabia was talking about.”

Vikir stared at the creature, which was sticking its head into the pool of sap and sucking up everything inside.

It had the appearance of a human being, covered entirely in the shell of a rhinoceros beetle.

Insect King. A legendary race that once existed in the distant past.

However, due to their voracious appetite and warlike nature, they are said to be extinct now.

To think that such an ancient creature could be found here.

Meanwhile, there was a stir among the commoner students.

“Hey, that guy is over level 10! I don't know his stats, but....”

“If he's over level 10, that means he's got a ton of stats. Oh my God!”

“Ouch! That guy is draining all our sap!”

“Well, more than that, that... is trying to rip us apart, right?”

Then, Dogma, the leader, drew his sword.

“Let's defend our pool! Follow me, I'll lead the charge!”

He was quite impatient. It was the sap pool that allowed him to rule like a king on this tiny island.

With that, Dogma drew his sword and charged at Insectking.

Boom-

A sharp swinging slash.

But.

...Taaang!

The sword broke too easily against Insectking's back armor.

Ppajik-

A vein appeared on Insectking's forehead.

Pugh-

A heavy black fist flew out, knocking Dogma to the ground.

“Ugh! What kind of strength!”

“Huh! The sword won't penetrate! The skin is so hard!”

“Help, help! I'm dying!”

All of the commoner students who rushed in after them were cut down by the Insectking.

An out-of-size monster. Suddenly appearing from above the roots of the tree, Insectking beat the entire group of twenty students to a bloody pulp.

It was as if he wanted to remind them of the true owner of this sap pool.

Just then.

“Step aside. Let's talk.”

One man stepped forward.

It was Vikir.

Dogma gritted his teeth and shouted.

“You're crazy! You can't talk to a monster like that! You won't understand a word.”

“ ...I know the common language.”

Vikir's answer gave Dogma a blank look.

“Common language? Is there such a thing?”

“Was he... good at foreign languages?”

“No, there's no way he could talk to a humanoid monster in the first place....”

When all the students were looking at him in disbelief.

Tsk-.

Vikir stood in front of the Insectking.

“Let me ask you something.”

[....]

But the King has no answer.

He just stretched out his giant arms and tried to blow Vikir away.

'Look! It's just a dog's death!'

Dogma bit his lip tightly, knowing that he would soon see Vikir's limbs disintegrate before his eyes.

...However.

“I guess I'll need a translator after all.”

Vikir muttered something short, then pulled a great 'translator' out of his pocket.

It was his fist.

Boom!

A single, short punch.

The effect it created was quite shocking.

Wududududuk!

The black armor that had casually deflected the attacks of the commoner students crumbled like a soggy cookie.

The King's eyes widened, but he was unable to scream.

He fell upside down on the floor, spitting out everything in his stomach.

“Now, do you feel like talking?”

[...Yes].

Insectking replies in a very humble voice.

“Did you know how to speak human?”

“...That works.”

“No, but you caught that monster with a single punch?”

The commoner students all have a blank look on their faces.

Then they remembered what Vikir had said earlier.

'If you want to do it, leave it to one side.'

What would have happened if they had ignored him and charged in?

Creepy.

An unseasonable chill runs down everyone's spine.

Just then.

“You idiots, what are you freezing, That's the last hit!”

Dogma incited the other students.

“That bastard must have caught something we let slip, otherwise it doesn't make sense!”

One by one, the students nod in agreement.

“Yeah, right, we're in the same level 1!”

“Even if you ate a bunch of strange candies, it wouldn't make much of a difference.”

“You cowardly bastard, stealing the last hit!”

“Ooh, we're not too late, let's get it!”

At this point, all the students from the Commoner faction were in motion.

Insectking who had fallen to the ground, was crouching on the floor, trembling and being hit by numerous kicks.

Dogma stepped in front of Vikir and said.

“Hmph. This must have been the boss monster guarding the sap gland, and I suppose you're not unhappy with the way things turned out, since you stole the last hit from us too.”

The reply came from Vikir's side.

“You shameless bastard, you are trying to steal the last hit!”

“It is!”

“It is!”

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, they stood guard by Vikir's side, glaring at Dogma.

But.

“...I have no complaints.”

Vikir said briefly, dismissing the triplets.

Then he turned his gaze upward.

“...?”

Dogma looked up to where Vikir was staring.

“Huh?”

His complexion quickly turned pale.

And so did the other commoner students, who were assaulting the King on Dogma's orders.

Bung bung bung bung-

A loud flapping of wings.

It was the sound of countless armies of Insectking race descending from the roots of the Hell Tree.

“...It, it wasn't a boss mob?”

The blood drained from Dogma's face like a tide.

The commoner students began to tremble, not even daring to resist.

...And.

“Raise your hand.”

Vikir's voice came again.

“I am a third-generation reader.”

“....”

“There is a single mother, a single father to take care of.”

“....”

“I have an old lover, or I'm getting married soon. Or I'm already a newlywed.”

“....”

“Otherwise, there's a 'humanly' reason why people should not be killed in this place.”

“....”

“Outside to one side.”

No one snickered this time.

All of the commoner students began to slip away, looking away.

“...Is gone?”

Eventually, everyone left to one side, and Vikir ended briefly.

“Then let's begin.”

Chapter 322

Underdogma (4)

◆

...Woosh!

The joints snapped.

One of the creatures sprawled across the floor.

Vikir grabbed the horns of the lunging beetle-type King by the horns and put the joint back on.

...Crunch!

Even the toughest armor has weak joints.

A few taps revealed that the exoskeletons of the Kings were quite strong, and realizing this, Vikir stopped using the old, exhausting method of striking, and instead, conserved his strength and used articulation.

The result.

More than fifty Insectkings lay groaning on the sandy ground.

After pinning down a stag beetle-type Insectking with a long white beard by the middle arm, Vikir asked with a hint of irritation.

“Do you guys feel like having a conversation now?”

[Yes. Please, just look at the middle arm, it's a valuable part of the human body, too, please....]

The elderly rhinoceros beetle-type Insectking, who appears to be some sort of elder, bends down and begs the question.

When the old, gray-bearded Insectking bowed their heads, eventually all the Insectkings knelt before Vikir.

Vikir stared at them all.

Black exoskeletons, muscular bodies, subtly different faces depending on their gender....

Overall, they all looked similar, but there was a crucial difference.

It was the appearance of their horns.

Some had a single, thick horn that towered over them, while others had two horns that sprouted like pincers.

So to speak, it's the difference between a rhinoceros beetle and a stag beetle.

Apparently, these Insectkings didn't get along very well among themselves.

They didn't work as a team when attacking.

'...That made it easy to overpower them.'

Vikir sat down on a rotting log.

In front of him, stag beetle-type and rhinoceros beetle-type Insectking were sitting on their knees.

Naturally, the students of the commoners group were kneeling down with pale complexions and voluntarily paying their taxes(?).

'Did you see, 50 beetles that all of us couldn't do anything about.'

'We couldn't even handle one of them... but 50 of them....'

'He's a monster, he's a monster! What the hell is he?'

'Maybe he ate hundreds of candies from upstairs, but that doesn't explain it.'

Vikir can hear them all chattering away.

And to those guys.

“Why don't you shut up, you're making noise to my lord.”

“Noisy.”

“Noisy.”

The triplets Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro now made no attempt to hide their reverence for Vikir.

Meanwhile.

Vikir turned to the Insectkings.

“How did you guys end up here?”

Then Insectking, a rhinoceros beetle type with long white eyebrows and beards, and Insectking, a stag beetle type, bowed their heads and opened their mouths.

[We were living a very long time ago on an island called “Giant Beetle Island” beyond the harsh sea].

[Then we were fighting a demon that attacked us out of nowhere, and we ended up trapped inside this strange tree].

Amdusias had apparently carved off a portion of the island and turned it into a world within a tree.

However, by forcibly stitching the disparate terrain together, all of the island's vegetation dried up, leaving only a single root of the Hell Tree.

[Since then, we have fought a long battle for the sap of the Hell Tree. There were other ship owners, but as time passed, they all died and we were the only ones left.]

“...I see.”

Vikir nodded.

The Insectking explanation was that the demon Amdusias was mimicking a god.

Decarabia interjected.

[I assume you are aware that Lun, whom you consider your creator, is also a 'worldview collector' who likes to squeeze many worlds into one place?]

“I didn't know that. What is that?”

[It's nothing. A sheep has its own world, and a wolf has its own world. But sheep and wolves obviously coexist in reality, don't they? That's the work of Lun].

The Beginning. In the great world that originally existed, sheep, wolves, and humans lived together.

But a being called Lun took some from the world of the sheep, some from the world of the wolves, and some from the world of the humans, and put them together, and that is the real world.

[You call the needle that stitched those worlds together the 'ecological pyramid' and the thread the 'food chain'].

“Wasn't that just an old Bible verse, something that was real?”

[ Well, I don't know, not even I can figure that out. What I do know is that Amdusias has been gathering worlds in his Hell Tree to mimic Lun. It's been a longstanding hobby of his].

Of course, the worlds in the Hell Tree that Amdusias has created and the real worlds that the Lun Gods have created are far different in their sophistication.

It's like comparing rags to riches.

“...I'm not interested in complicated theological theories. I need to get out of here and go to the bottom floor.”

Vikir tucked Decarabia into his chest pocket and turned back to the Insectking.

“There will be no more arguing over sap. I will get you out of here.”

[What? Is that even possible?]

All the Insectking, including the elders, opened their eyes wide.

Vikir nodded and asserted.

“Of course it is possible, but I need your help.”

[Whether it is possible! Anything as long as I can clear the mission on this floor and get out...!]

But the Elders didn't finish their sentence.

“We need a ship. If it's you guys, you'll be able to get it, right?”

At that, the complexions of all the Insectking stiffened.

....

Silence. The awkward silence continued for a while.

Eventually, the Insectking race who did not know lies brought out their inner thoughts.

[In fact, the reason why the rhinoceros beetle tribe and the stag beetle tribe have been at odds for a long time is because of 'ships.']

“Why?”

[Because, well, there's a ship... that's a bit of a problem...]

When Vikir and the Insectking were in the middle of a conversation.

“Uh! My lord, over there!”

Highbro exclaims in a panicked tone.

Vikir turns his head to see what it is, and his eyes catch an unexpected sight.

Dogma. The leader of the Commoners' faction was climbing the roots of the Hell Tree at breakneck speed.

“Hahahaha- you stupid bastards, do you think I'm going to hand out sap to you!”

His bloodshot eyes told them that he had already lost his mind.

...With a plop! Gulp- Gulp- Gulp- Gulp-

Dogma dropped his head into the puddle of sap and began to gulp it down.

Despite his already bloated belly, Dogma sucked down the sap with all the strength he could muster.

He was desperate, as if he couldn't give another drop.

“Do, Dogma, give us some too!”

“You're the only one who drinks it, you disgusting bastard!”

“The sap is for us!”

Several of Dogma's followers followed at his heels.

They too were just about to dunk their heads in the puddle.

...Pow!

One student's head was crushed.

Dogma's hand. It had grown many times larger and thicker, and now it squeezed the man's skull and crushed it.

Gulp-gulp-gulp-gulp!

Despite the blood, brain fluid, and strange candies dropped by the dying man into a puddle of sap, Dogma did not remove its head from the sap gland.

Seeing it, Vikir hissed low.

“You shouldn't drink that much.”

The sap of the Hell Tree belongs only to demons. No human could drink too much of it.

And Dogma was a case in point that proved it to be true.

“K-Uuuuuuh!?”

He grabbed at his face with his hands, his stomach bulging from the amount of sap he had consumed.

But it was too late.

The sap of the Hell Tree had spread through his veins and seeped into his marrow, and it had begun to transform Dogma's entire body.

Pppudeudeug- kkudeudeug- ppadeug- ujijig!

The students following Dogma cowered in fear.

But they couldn't escape under the roots.

...Quack!

Dogma opened his mouth wide and chewed through their entire upper bodies with his razor-sharp teeth, swallowing them whole.

[Ggah-aaaah...]

Dogma chewing on flesh and candy.

His appearance was already no longer that of a human.

Majin (魔人).

A creature classified as a demon, but neither demon nor monster.

A wandering diaspora between the human and demon worlds for all eternity.

As soon as Vikir saw it, he sighed once more.

“It's not going to be easy for someone that size....”

Just then.

[ Surp rise miss ion ? ]

A grotesque fleshy fairy appeared above everyone's heads.

It wiggled its obnoxiously fat ass from side to side and chirped excitedly.

[Wow ? Is the re an excell ent chall enger who has al ready be come a Majin ? Is it a hap py occa sion ? Th en of cour se I shou ld gi ve you a miss ion, rig ht ? ]

With that, the fairy dangled the mission in front of everyone's eyes except for the Insectkings.

-Ring!

<Mission>– Let's kill a Majin!

-Majin (0/1)

※ Your precious friend has lost his temper, oh no~ Let's quickly put him at ease! The only way is... you know?

...The problem is.

-Ring!

<Mission>– Let's kill all the living things!

-Survivor (0/77)

※ Even though you've become Majin, it's meaningless if you don't run wild, right? Let me prove how strong you've become! By the way, the rewards will be quite generous, right?

Dogma got a mission too.

Chapter 324

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea (1)

◆

<Vikir>

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: 'Gutter Rat Hunter', 'Hell's Dog', 'Daylily Lumberjack', 'Majin Executioner' (NEW)

-Stats

Strength: 300

?Agility: 270 (+10) = 280

?Stamina: 300

?Physical resistance: 1

?Magic resistance: 0 (+1) = 1

?Reflexes: 1

Vikir's status bar has changed once more.

The title “Majin Executioner” adds a deep karma to Vikir's soul.

Vikir's body will be faster and his sword will be a sharper when dealing with Majin in the future.

After feeding the little madam, I ate all the remaining Agility Candies.

It's the most difficult of the three primary stats to get, so you have to be diligent about eating it whenever you get a chance.

'...But that's not the point right now.'

No matter how valuable the Agility stat is, is that all there is to it?

Vikir took note of a new stat, Magic Resistance.

This is in line with the Physical Resistance stat, which bends the laws of reality to create unusual force distortions.

In the case of Mana Resistance, it makes you more aware of the flow of mana in the real world, and resists mana flowing in the opposite direction.

In other words, it rejects aggressive mana that flies at you from an opponent and forces mana that flows backwards through your body to be repelled in its original direction.

'To put it simply, it halves the enemy's magic attacks and suppresses the mana surge that occurs within my body.'

This is the ultimate stat for anyone practicing mana, especially mages.

It halved your opponent's magical attacks, but being able to control the mana surges within your own body was an incredible perk.

Mana surges are usually the last thing a swordsman or mage wants to see when they step up to a higher level.

Just as a worm emerging from its cocoon or a crustacean breaking out of its shell is at its weakest, those who practice mana also become weakest at the very moment they transcend their limits.

Having a high Mana Resistance stat will help protect you from one of the worst dangers of all: Mana Surge.

'...Before regression, Camus invested everything in her Magic Resistance stat in the tower, and used that overwhelming resistance to learn all of the high-risk spells that would definitely result in Mana Surge if practiced.'

In High Risk, High Return, she's cramming all of her risk into her stats and then taking all of her return.

It's a very ignorant thing to do, but it's something you can't do without absolute confidence in your skills, talent, and future.

“...Alright, now I have all six stats.”

The stats you'll never get in the early stages, or even see until the end of the tower in the later stages, are Physical Resistance, Magic Resistance, and Reflexes.

These three special stats are the Tower's most secret hidden prizes and are progressive perks that grow with their owner, and now that Vikir has succeeded in flowering all of them, he just needs to level them up.

As you level up, all of your stats will naturally increase, so you don't need to get any weird candy to grow all three base stats and three special stats.

When Vikir was lost in thought.

“My lord, with all due respect,... I have a question.”

Highbro spoke up from beside him.

“When you got 10 level candies earlier, why didn't you use them to level up? At level 10, wouldn't you be able to find 10% of your power outside the tower? It seems like that would be much more beneficial than just raising your stats a bit right now....”

“Hmm. It's to bloom all six stats.”

Vikir explained the stats to the Baskerville triplets.

When the triplets realized that in addition to the three primary stats of strength, agility, and stamina, there were three special stats, they were motivated.

“We'll try to find them, too! Then, my lord, you have collected all 6 major stats, so you can now level up!”

“You're going to get a huge level!”

“You're going to get a huge level!”

But Vikir shook his head.

“I won't be leveling up as much as I can for a while. If you get level candy, sell it to the candy store and exchange it for stat candy, and when you get to the second half of the game, don't use the level candy, but save it in your pockets.”

The Baskerville triplets look puzzled at this.

Vikir explains the reward structure inside the tower.

“As you level up, you regain some of your power outside the tower, which allows you to grow quickly in the beginning. However, the increasing difficulty of the tower's missions and the decreasingly small rewards in the later stages of the tower can put people off.”

While newcomers to the Tower may be all-in on collecting stat candy and converting it to level candy, experienced players don't do that.

The rule of the tower is that the lower the level, the better the rewards.

Great feats by the strong are rewarded with mediocre rewards.

Even when the weak achieve minor achievements, they also receive modest rewards.

When the strong perform a small feat, they receive almost no reward.

...But when a weak person does something great.

In these cases, the rewards are vastly different from what you'd expect!

That's why Vikir, in his Level 1 existence, has slain a Gutter Rat, Hellhound, Cerberus, a Daylily of Blood Tree, a number of Insectking, and the Majin from earlier.

The rewards of these missions have been labeled “rare,” “difficult,” “epic,” and “awesome”.

But even with all these missions and rewards, Vikir is still treated as an underdog.

That's because of the system in the tower, which uses level as a measure of strength.

'I've grown tired of playing weak.'

He sighs. All the time he had spent in Colosseo Academy as a nerd who hid his strength had been a long wait for this day.

“...Anyway. This is why you don't need to level up at the beginning.”

The triplets nodded eagerly at Vikir's words.

To the triplets, who gave him a look of blind loyalty, Vikir added another word.

“And one more thing, leveling up is a waste because....”

Hearing Vikir's whispered words, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro's eyes widened for a moment, before returning to their normal size.

“Hmph, so all those fairy things that keep encouraging us to eat level candy are a scam....”

“Indeed. I guess I should never eat level candy at the beginning, then.”

“I guess I should just focus on increasing my stats for now.”

There was no reason to rush to level up, as the stat candies that were collected without eating them could be exchanged for level candies at the candy store later.

Vikir repeated the advice to the triplets one more time.

Then.

...Kurrrr!

A small anomaly occurred at the spot where Dogma, who had become a Majin, had died.

A single flame, black and glowing, danced across the surface of the water.

Vikir leapt to his feet and grasped the flame in his hand.

It was hot enough to boil the water around it, but surprisingly, Vikir's hand didn't feel the slightest bit hot.

-<Fire of Inferiority 'Fire'>/ Flint / A+

A stone that allows you to get hot embers anytime, anywhere.

It burns with the inferiority complex deep within you as firewood.

-Hotness +1,000

*Temperature may be higher or lower depending on the level of inferiority complex.

“...So, you use inferiority complexes as firewood, then I'm not going anywhere.”

Vikir, too, was once a victim of inferiority complexes.

His lowly origins, his family's alienation, his deformed appearance, his former life filled with nothing but shame and hatred.

With such bitter memories, Vikir has virtually unlimited power.

...Crunch!

Vikir carefully tucked the flames of inferiority burning within his grasp into his arms.

No longer would he freeze to death or be unable to cook his food, no matter where he was.

Then.

[O-our savior, get us off this island!]

Vikir had to listen to the shouts of the Insectking again.

It was annoying, but it served their purpose.

Vikir needed to get off the island and down to the deeper levels, so it couldn't hurt to play along.

“Right. You said you had a ship, right?”

It was said that a ship was the reason why the two races of Insectking, rhinoceros beetles and stag beetles, have been at odds for so long is because of one ship.

Apparently, it was a dispute over which of the two races would take possession of the ship.

They nodded in a sullen tone.

[Yes, there is one ship].

“Where is it?”

Vikir asked, and the two elders stretched out their index fingers and pointed in unison.

[It's anchored over there].

“...?”

Vikir scratched his head. There was nothing where the two Elders pointed.

Nothing but a distant horizon.

“...What?”

Vikir turned his head, and the two elders nodded with a heavy expression.

[Yes, it is sinking].

The ship, the only means of escape from this island.

It is sunk at the bottom of the Black Sea right now.

Chapter 328

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea (5)

◆

The Trident of Baskerville.

The triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, who had sworn allegiance to their half-brother Vikir, now stood dazed on the beach.

While holding the Baby Madam who was whimpering while looking for Vikir.

“Master's level... 1, right?”

“That's right. He's a hundred times weaker.”

“And he can fight like that?”

Vikir is a god of battle, his feet moving over the bodies of ghost ships and jellyfish, sometimes even breaking the surface of the water.

It was like watching a fighting dog born solely for battle.

An aura that was at least a Graduator Intermediate or higher, and a sword skill that was clearly Baskerville, but whose level of mastery was unknown.

Those who don't know Vikir would be puzzled if they saw him.

Why is Vikir not weaker than he was outside the tower, but stronger?

But the three Baskerville brothers knew.

Vikir had already reached that level four years ago.

'I'll buy you some time. You go.'

The Hound was left alone to face the Nightmare of the Depth, Madame of the Eight Legs.

How could they forget the sun-like aura that rose from the tip of the hero's sword at that time?

That light changed everything. The triplets' way of thinking, their behavior, and their fate.

From that night on, the triplets became tridents. Moving solely at Vikir's command.

Highbro spoke with conviction.

“Indeed. My lord, he was a master.”

“He was a Master.”

“He was a Master.”

What is a Sword Master? According to official records, there are fewer than ten of them in the entire Empire.

In Iron Blooded Swordsman Baskerville, it is assumed that Hugo Le Baskerville, Cane Corso, one of the Seven Counts who disappeared a long time ago, and Osiris, the young patriarch of the Family, will soon become Masters, but it is not yet certain.

In such a situation, the fact that Vikir was promoted to Sword Master was a fact that would have shocked the entire empire.

Not to mention he's not even twenty yet.

The triplets' gaze shifted to the side.

There, they saw a group of Commoner students gathered together, shivering.

Their stats were pretty low from all the stats they'd been feeding Dogma, and none of them dared to look the triplets in the eye, especially since they'd just been feeding Vikir candy.

Highbro spoke up.

“...I'll see you guys later.”

“Huh?”

The commoner students began to tremble.

They had a history of treating triplets like dogs and mistreating them.

But that didn't mean they couldn't do something about it.

For the commoner students, even if Vikir wins the fight against that giant jellyfish, it is despair, and even if he loses, it is despair.

'No matter what, I'd rather Vikir win....'

The commoner students remembered what Vikir had said when he first appeared.

'Raise your hand. I am the third generation reader. I have a single mother and a single father to support. You have an old lover or are about to get married. Or are you already newlyweds? There is a 'humanly' reason why people should not be killed in this place. Outside to one side.'

The fact that he said this means that he at least has warmth.

'Now that things are like this, I have no choice but to beg for my life from Vikir.'

'There's no way the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro will forgive us.'

'They'll kill us, and even if they make a thousand concessions and let us live, they'll cripple us.'

'...Let's go to Vikir and beg as much as we can.'

While the commoner students were thinking about this and that.

...Kwakwakwakwakwang!

A pillar of fire of immense height and thickness rose from the sea surface.

It signaled the end of the battle and the victory.

◆

The Black Sea Shadowless King was still as large and powerful as ever when it rose to the surface.

Beodungbeodung-

Its tentacles flailed, churning the water.

It looked like it wanted to go back down to the heart of the sea again.

Kuguk- Kugigik...

It was impossible, as a powerful buoyancy enveloped its body, the opposite of anything it had ever experienced since its birth in the Black Water.

Shurororok-

It stretched out its tentacles and tried to cut the air sacs and stems, but even the Daylily of Blood Tree is not as easily broken as a Dangerous S-ranked monster.

The roots, which had already burrowed deep into the jellyfish's shapeless body, were impossible to pull out without tearing off flesh.

“It may be a freshly germinated seed, but its durability cannot be ignored.”

Vikir sliced off a few of the lunging tentacles and dried them, then stepped onto the King's lampshade.

The body was so soft that it sunk into your thighs when you stepped on it, but Vikir managed to maintain his balance even on top of it.

Snap.

Vikir pulled at the Daylily's stem with a strong grip.

The blossoms all over Shadowless King body were pulled down like balloons on a string.

Snap, snap, snap!

Vikir tied the Daylily's tough stems together.

In an instant, a knot the size of a human head appeared.

The knotting techniques he'd learned in the field could be used to bind even the strongest ropes tightly in an instant.

Vikir stepped on the knot, jumped to the other side of the trunk, and used his weight to pull it across the slick ground.

He then gathers up the thicker stems on the other side, ties them together, and knots them.

Soon, the stems were tightly tied together, and it looked as if Shadowless King of the Black Sea had been bound with rope.

“That's it. At this point, if one explodes, the others won't be blown away.”

Vikir zigzagged to avoid the flying tentacles.

The many stalks tangled and knotted together like a honeycomb, so the tentacles could not reach him if he slid under them.

Thwack! Whirrrrrr!

A flying tentacle is caught in a web of # shaped Daylily stems.

Due to its mushy nature, the tentacle is unable to untangle itself.

From then on, Vikir didn't cut off the flying tentacles.

Instead, they were caught in the netting made from the Daylily's stems, causing them to tangle even more.

Eventually, Vikir arrived at the end of the cap and jumped onto the surface of the water, holding a small air sac in his hand.

...Blast!

At the same time, Vikir kicked as hard as he could against the jellyfish's body wall.

Splash- splash- splash-

He must get as far away from the Black Sea Shadowless King as possible.

“Let's pull! Ugh!”

“Ugh!”

“Ugh!”

The Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro catch Vikir's call just in time to tug on the threads extending from the madame cub's tail.

It had been attached to Vikir's waist all along.

Chwaaaag-

Vikir cuts through the water, putting distance between him and the Black Sea King.

Soon, the embers that Vikir had placed in the center of the Black Sea Shadowless King's body have finally caught fire in the far end of the air sac.

Crackle!

The flames that had been sizzling on the surface of the air sac soon engulfed the entire air sac.

...Pow! ...Pow! ...Pow! ...Pow!

Eventually, the air sacs swallowed by the fire shrunk and began to react.

Ka-Boom!

The Daylily's air sacs were filled with toxic gas, a dangerous gas that exploded uncontrollably when ignited.

When the first air sac explodes, the other air sacs all flutter around in the strong wind in the aftermath.

However, because the stems were already tightly knotted, the air sacs did not fly away.

The air sacs that moved for a moment are soon dragged by the knotted stem and cling to Shadowless King of the Black Sea.

Once again, they became the fuel for the gas and firestorms in the atmosphere.

...Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom!

A chain of explosions and flames, it followed the knotted air sacs and began to burn the Shadowless King of the Black Sea in earnest.

A red-hot flower burning on the black sea surface.

The Shadowless King of the Black Sea wants to go down to the bottom of the sea, but it is impossible to do so because of the air sacs that still remain.

As a result, it's a fate that leaves itself open to the poisonous gases and flames that float to the surface, where it will slowly cook to death.

And Vikir watches from a little distance away, on the surface of the water, in a small airbag.

'The scale is different from the Daylily I met on the previous stage.'

The Daylily we met on the 3th floor had been starved to death and hadn't been able to grow its air sacs properly.

So instead of looking like a balloon, its stamens were spread out like leaves, and no one realized that it contained a deadly poisonous gas.

But of course, Vikir had already realized this.

'There was a person who organized the Daylily of Blood Tree like this before my regression.'

Vikir once worked as a special task force member of the Demon Subjugation Task Force.

There had been a time when a group of soldiers in danger had been forced to flee in secret from a demon army, and these Daylily happened to be blocking their escape route.

Leading the group was Bianca, the eldest daughter of the Usher family.

Using her archery skills, she unleashed a powerful bolt of flame that exploded all of the monstrous plants.

This cleared the way, saving Vikir's life and the lives of many others.

“...I owe you, Bianca.”

Vikir nodded, watching the tidal wave of flames swirl around it.

And then.

-Ding!

A loud notification sounded in his ears.

['Level 1 Warrior' Vikir has successfully hunted an 'A+ Ranked Majin' for the first time!]

['Awesome' achievement reward will be distributed!]

['Level 1 Warrior' Vikir has successfully hunted the first 'S-ranked Monster, Black Sea Shadowless King']!

[The reward for the 'Impossible' achievement will be distributed!]

“...I'm done.”

Vikir breathed a sigh of relief.

At the same time.

...Boom!

A chunk of rotting flesh appeared in front of Vikir's eyes.

The fairy who was always characterized by splitting with a bizarre smile.

...But for some reason, this time was different.

It looked at Vikir, almost sobbing.

[ Wh at are you, why are you do ing th is to me? ]

Chapter 333

The Mating Room (3)

◆

Darkness has fallen in the mating room.

Judging by the lack of light beyond the translucent walls, it was either night or the lights had been turned off.

As a result, the temperature inside the cage began to drop rapidly.

White frost formed on the walls.

Furthermore.

[Enters mating environment]

[1st timeout 00:00:00]]

[2nd timeout 10:00:00] .

.

.

A light rain began to fall from the darkness of the ceiling.

It was just enough to moisten the surface of the sawdust, but with the freezing cold around them, it was quite threatening.

Vikir ducked out of the pouring rain and into the sawdust at the bottom of the hill.

'...I wonder if this is primary.'

The blue mist that had brought the giant mantis to heat earlier was definitely round two.

Apparently it happens when the time limit for the first round is up.

'It was hot and sweaty earlier, but now it's raining and frosty. What a crazy day.'

As Vikir was thinking to himself, Sinclaire, who was squatting next to him, spoke up.

“Do they want us to freeze to death out here? They're going to make us sweat and then leave us out in the rain.”

It had been hot in the kennel just moments before, and Sinclaire was wearing only a black sleeveless t-shirt on his upper body.

But even if it had gotten colder, she couldn't bring herself to put the cloak back on.

It was already damp from sweat and drizzle.

...Phut! ... phut!

When Vikir turned around after vigorously shaking off the water from his clothes, Sinclaire was just breathing quietly with her head buried between her knees.

As her breathing gradually became quieter, her physical condition seemed to be not that good.

'She's hypothermic, and she's going to die if I don't keep her awake.'

Vikir moved to Sinclaire's side and sat down.

He spoke to her to keep her awake.

“What were the missions on the previous floor?”

“....”

“Sinclaire, what were the missions on the previous floor?”

Vikir asked, shaking her shoulder, and Sinclaire snapped out of it.

She shuddered once, then opened her mouth to speak.

“Ah, on the magic train... to fight each other.”

Sinclaire said she survived a swarm of hellhounds on the 3rd floor, and made it to the 5th floor after experiencing a Daylily attack on the 4th floor.

The intervening time was a long one, but it wasn't particularly odd, as different floors had different notions of time inside the tower.

“Hellhound and blood daylily, I went through those too.”

“Really? How many days did you endure them?”

“I didn't. I caught the Daylily.”

“What, you caught it? Was that something you could catch?”

Sinclaire looked genuinely surprised.

Then she spoke in a hushed voice.

“We fought it, actually. We couldn't make the sacrifice... and then the Daylily ate most of the survivors, so the mission was automatically cleared.”

“Maybe that was the best thing that could have happened. Realistically.”

The chances of the Colosseo Academy students catching a Daylily of Blood are slim to none.

It's just that Vikir was off-the-charts strong.

Sinclaire then turned to the next floor, the 5th.

“The fifth floor was ... hell, much worse than the 3rd and 4th.”

“What was it?”

“....”

Sinclaire paused for a long moment before answering in a low voice.

“A killing spree.”

Sinclaire's next words were quite shocking.

“The location was a compartment of the magic train. When I came to, everyone was in their seats on the train.”

And then, in front of everyone's eyes, the mission.

<Mission>– A group task of strong friendship! Let's make our group the best group!

※ From now on, the 5 closest people will form one group!

※ If any of the 5 people in a group die, the group will be automatically eliminated and everyone will die!

※If you have a weaker friend, be sure to help and protect him or her! The outcome is important, but the process is also important! Cooperation is also a criterion for evaluation!

※ The stats of the dead are automatically absorbed into the stats of the killer!

※ Try to eliminate all other groups and be the last one standing!

※ P.S-I intentionally formed groups with people who seemed close to each other^^

It was a “struggle of all against all” between the survivors.

Five people in a group. And if you lose even one of them, everyone dies.

Also, if you kill a member of another group, you can take away all their stats.

As soon as the mission was announced, several students sprang into action.

In the blink of an eye, a female student swung an awl and pierced the neck of a large, burly male student next to her.

He died without so much as a scream, and all of his stats went to her.

She began attacking other students, using her stats to become as strong as one of the muscular men.

The train compartment quickly turned into chaos.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire, who happened to be in a group, worked together to deflect all the incoming attacks.

Once they'd managed to fend off everyone, another mission popped up.

<Special Mission>– Even the best groups have their best members, but who is the MVP player?

※It's a bit futile to win by holding out, right? Don't make the game too boring.

※Congratulations to the five challengers who seem to be getting along so well!

※But unfortunately, only one of you can make it through this stage!!!

※From now on, we'll be sending all but one of you to the Daylily Colony on the 4th floor!

It was the fairy's stench that made the five close friends into a group in the first place.

The five survivors had already bonded over the hellish chatter.

What's more, not only were they close to begin with, but they had saved each other's lives many times over.

Of the five of them, only one can survive.

The remaining four will descend into a hell of off-size monsters.

Sinclaire smiled bitterly, avoiding Vikir's gaze.

“I was the one who made the first move.”

“I understand.”

“ ...You find that contemptible, don't you?”

“No. No one can blame you.”

Vikir spoke in a dry voice.

Then he spoke.

“In that situation, it's right to let the one most capable of surviving live. That's what I would have done.”

In reality, Vikir had been in situations like this countless times.

He'd been on the losing end, and he'd survived.

Sinclaire stared at Vikir with a puzzled expression on her face.

Then, in a small voice, she asked.

“ ... If my brother joined, would you have done the same?”

“Of course.”

“Then you would have survived. You are stronger and wiser than me.”

“That is also true.”

Vikir nodded nonchalantly, and Sinclaire could only smile in response.

“It's a strange feeling, like being comforted and a little bit hurt....”

Sinclaire hesitated for a moment before continuing.

“I guess I'll never be as strong-minded as my brother, no matter how hard I try.”

Sinclaire finished telling the rest of the story.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire.

Of the five, only one would survive.

And it was Sinclaire who made the first move.

Sinclaire had been working hard to distance herself from her friends in anticipation of dropping out of the Academy.

So, once again, she closed her eyes tightly and cast a powerful spell.

...No, she tried.

But Sinclaire couldn't make it work.

Guilt. Friendship. A tidal wave of unspeakable emotions washed over her, sapping her mana.

“...So what happened?”

Vikir continued.

He couldn't stay still, or he'd fall asleep, and then he'd really freeze to death.

Sinclaire answered with a half-open, half-dazed gaze.

“Then Tudor spoke.”

In Sinclaire's recollection, Tudor had said exactly what Vikir had expected.

'In a situation like this, I think it's only right to let the one with the best chance of survival live.'

Suddenly, the eyes of Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca all turned to Sinclaire.

'You're the most brilliant of us all, Sinclaire, so I think you should go.'

'You will get revenge on those demons. With your skills and talent, you can do it.'

'I thought of course I should get out. Make sure you survive to get my share!'

'...Heh. You realize how you've been treating me lately? Really reflect on yourself. Where can I find such a good friend?'

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca unanimously voted to save Sinclaire.

Hearing this, Vikir nodded.

'Of course, you're right, my thoughts are also influenced by the Tudors before the regression.'

Tudor, the great hero of the Age of Destruction, always made rational choices.

However, he sometimes acted irrationally, always sacrificing himself to save others if it involved himself.

Vikir's life was once saved by Tudor's sacrifice in a life-or-death situation.

Tudor was dying for the first time. Bianca cried out. The warriors of the Humanity Alliance who had survived, but had been grieving for a long time afterward.

Vikir wondered over and over again why the great hero Tudor had sacrificed himself for the sake of a lowly warrior.

And then, in the present day, Vikir heard the answer.

“He said... 'cause that's what heroes do,' that idiot.”

Sinclaire's eyes narrowed.

Tudor gave Sinclaire a thumbs-up with a smirk as he stood there trying not to leave.

'Don't worry. If any circumstances arise, we will use a return scroll.'

The penalty for which, instead of returning to the tutorial safe zone, all levels would be reset to 1.

At that, Vikir nodded.

'Good thing they all have their scrolls.'

Scrolls can save your life once in a crisis.

Resetting your level to 1 is a pain in the ass, but there's nothing more precious than a life.

“Yeah. Using a return scroll is a wise choice. Instead of resetting your level, you'll have the foundation to become stronger. Your stats will remain the same, and you'll have information about the missions you'll face, which will make it much easier to become stronger. Of course, once you've use the scroll, you'll be classified as the tower's pre-existing creature, so you'll be destined to create many more victims...hmm?”

Vikir had to stop mid-sentence.

“....”

He turned to the side and saw Sinclaire curled up in a ball, head bowed, saying nothing.

Apparently, she had fallen asleep from her tears.

Hic-hic-

Her breathing has become so soft that it is barely audible anymore.

Thud.

Sinclaire's head rests on Vikir's shoulder.

Her breath, faintly warm, tickled the nape of Vikir's neck.

But.

“Wake up. If you sleep, you die.”

Vikir slapped Sinclaire across the cheeks, relentlessly.

“Huh, did I fall asleep?”

Sinclaire jerked awake and sat up.

“Thanks, brother, I could've frozen to death if I'd messed up. I've been feeling warm and sleepy for a while now... But why does my cheek hurt like this?”

“It's your mood.”

Sinclaire nodded at Vikir's words.

But once the temperature dropped, there was nothing she could do about it mentally.

Next, Sinclaire leaned in and whispered in Vikir's ear.

“I'm sorry, brother... I... I think that's it....”

There was no more mana to draw. Her body and mind were already exhausted.

“If only one of us can get out... you... I'll be fine... I can count on you....”

But Vikir had already stopped listening to Sinclaire.

'What should I do?'

Vikir decided to look at the other room on the other side of the wall.

It was drizzling and frosty in the other room, too.

“...!”

Vikir looked over to see what the creatures in the other room were doing.

They were burrowing deep into the wet sawdust on the outside, then burrowing into the dry sawdust on the inside, and sticking together.

The creatures, who were basking in each other's warmth, also huddle together to share their body heat in the face of the cold.

'...I wonder if this was the intention of the watering. It's extremely dark and damp.'

I could see what the owner of the room was expecting.

Stripped of rain- and sweat-soaked clothing, Vikir made his way to Sinclaire's side.

As he approached, Sinclaire's eyes narrowed and her voice trembled.

“Bro, brother, what are you going to do....?”

Vikir answered briefly.

“I guess I'll have to live up to expectations.”

Chapter 334

The Mating Room (4)

◆

Sinclaire J Bourgeois.

She was still a child. Long hair flowing like the Milky Way down to her waist.

She looked up at the tall man in front of her and asked,

'Father, why do I have to go out?'

The little girl asked while hugging her teddy bear.

But the tall man didn't answer.

Instead, it was the old butler standing next to him who answered.

'When you grow up and come back, everything will be yours.'

With those words, the little girl left the family home.

After cutting her long, flowing hair short, she looked back at the back door of the house.

Everything was still in its place. Nothing would change even if she left.

Then. A small shadow flickered high above the family's building.

Was it an illusion? Or just a shadow? The hem of a curtain that swayed in the wind?

No, it wasn't. It was a tall man. He's standing there to look down on her final journey.

That's what the girl thought.

'Why did you abandon me?'

'Did you love me?'

'Is that why you abandoned me?'

'Can I go back to you?'

'...Then can you love me again?'

So many questions, so many footprints in the snow, so many doubts.

And. At the end of it all, the answer was not a pleasant one.

[It wouldn't be a bad idea to weed out useless relationships at this point. As of this time, all plays have ended.]

The tall man's face as an adult was much different from what she remembered as a child.

He was so tall it was hard to see, but still, the glimpses of gentleness in the center of his bluntness were gone.

A hideously contorted expression. The bloodshot eyes. And that fierce, demon-like rampage.

The grown child reverted to the child she had been.

The child who had been forced to leave her family on the day of the heavy snowfall.

'I understand,'

'I know you did it because you loved me.'

And the truth is, you never abandoned me.

'I'm back.'

'Please love me again.'

The answer the little girl had been preparing for so long boiled down to one.

'...I wanted to see you.'

But she couldn't bring herself to say it.

'The demon kills.'

A hound tore through the nightmare, leaping from the depths of the underworld.

Its gaping mouth and sharp teeth tore at everything before the girl's eyes.

'It's over. You worthless one.'

That was the last of the tall man.

The girl had lost her only family.

And with that, the only source of record of her existence in the world was completely lost.

She was left alone in the world without any ties.

Now who will testify to her existence?

By what means should a person who has lost her source reveal herself to the world.

Esse, Non Videri. 'To exist, but not to be seen'

From that day forward, the girl became one who exists, but is not seen.

King of the Bourgeois.

The girl made up her mind.

She was determined to see that vicious hound from that day, that nightmare-like mouth and teeth, and those eyes that shined with ominousness.

◆

“...Huh!?”

Sinclaire gasped, her body jerking awake.

She must have had a terrible nightmare, but she couldn't quite remember. Her mind and body were dazed.

The next thing she knew, she realized she was completely naked.

“Kkyaaahh!”

She quickly covered her hands up and down.

Then a nonchalant voice came from the back of her neck.

“You're awake.”

Sinclaire turned her head quickly.

Vikir, also shirtless, was hugging her from behind.

“Bro, bro, bro, bro, brother? Wh, wh, What is this...?”

“Maintaining body temperature.”

The voice, still flat.

Sinclaire could finally take in her surroundings.

There was sawdust all around Vikir and Sinclaire, who were naked and close together.

A burrow dug so deep that the sawdust around them hadn't been soaked by the rain at all. They weren't cold because they were buried in the dry sawdust.

The moisture that had soaked their bodies was long gone.

Vikir had spread Cerberus's hide across the center of the wide den and built a small fire.

Firewood turned to sawdust, and smoke escaped through a vent dug into the den's ceiling.

Cerberus's hide was fireproof, so the fire didn't spread to the sawdust.

Vikir had made a small fire in a pouch of Cerberus's hide, and was tossing dry sawdust into it, little by little.

He made sure to spread the damp sawdust around to prevent sparks from flying.

“...Ah.”

Sinclaire suddenly realized what had kept her awake.

Vikir had done the best he could.

A cold, dark world. Yet so bright and warm, even with only a single matchstick of fire.

So was Vikir's hard body against his back and his tickling breath.

“Did you have a nightmare?”

Somehow, the voice that usually sounded so hard and dry in his voice now sounded so soft and sweet.

Vikir's words brought Sinclaire to tears.

“...Night Hound killed ...my father.”

The more time that passes, the more clearly she remembers the details of the nightmare.

No, she couldn't forget it because it had happened to her in the first place.

“...I woke up and my father was there. ...He was turned into a demon. ...He used a strange power. ...I wanted to stop him, but I couldn't because I didn't have the strength. ...So the Night Hounds killed him. ...Why, why did this happen. Why.”

Sinclaire is still babbling, having just woken up.

But Vikir could make out everything she wanted to say.

'I don't know how to explain it.'

The families of the demon-possessed are always difficult to deal with.

A dead man, just a shell of a demon?

That would only confuse Sinclaire.

'Maybe it's better to hate me, to loathe me.'

It might give her a little more motivation to live.

After all, revenge is a good motivator for humans.

Wordlessly, Vikir strengthened his arms and pulled Sinclaire into a tight embrace.

Bare skin rubbed against bare skin, warmth rising from the friction.

Sinclaire shivered and cried.

A moment.

A whimper.

She turned her head to the side.

Sinclaire's lips touched Vikir's neck.

Vikir quickly turned his head to the side to avoid it.

But Sinclaire didn't let go, and she began to run her tongue along his neck.

It was creeping up.

'...Holy shit, is it time already?'

Vikir was momentarily distracted by the status bar.

Vikir quickly opened the status window in the corner of his vision.

[Creating mating environment]

[2nd timeout 00:03:21]

.

.

The air entering his nostrils had become quite sweet for some reason.

A blue mist that permeates every inch of the sawdust den.

The time between tending to the fire and pumping mana into Sinclaire's body had already passed like this.

Vikir began to hold his breath.

'It's like a fog that can't hurt to breathe in....'

There was nothing particularly harmful about the mist.

The problem was that it stimulated various bodily functions too vigorously.

No wonder it was used as an estrus fog to promote mating between males and females.

-Ding!

[Human 2 (♀) is ready to mate]

[Human 1 (♂) is still not ready to mate]

The sound of humans being treated strictly as livestock.

This is exactly what happens in a Ryumajin's mating room.

Sinclaire turned towards Vikir.

Then, blowing out a breath of hot air, she said.

“Brother, I have no family anymore. I'm all alone in the world.”

“....”

“So I want to make a family, if it's you... if it's you.”

The world is cold and dark. It is inherently lonely and solitary.

But just like in this sawdust hole, if you have a little bit of warmth, even if it's just a single match, it can give you the strength and warmth to get through the world.

Sinclaire buried her face in Vikir's chest as if she could stand it no longer.

But even then, Vikir's gaze remained cold.

“....”

Of course, there's no way to be a family with Sinclaire.

It was Vikir himself who had destroyed Sinclaire's only family.

'...I have to admit it.'

When dealing with Bartolomeo, he didn't risk his life like he did with Camus.

He avoided risk as much as possible and took the safest route to kill Belial.

No regrets. If he had it to do over again, he would make the same choice.

But guilt and innocence are two different things.

To kill Sinclaire's only family, to be her only family, was a deception within a deception.

Vikir grabbed both of Sinclaire's shoulders as she burrowed deeper into his arms and lifted her up.

Sinclaire's head, bowed deeply, lifted to meet his eyes, which were already dazed.

“Listen, Sinclaire, I'm....”

Just when Vikir was about to open his mouth to say something.

-Ding!

[Entering mating environment]

[Begins third attempt]

.

.

The time limit was up.

As soon as Vikir stopped talking and gritted his teeth, he began to show signs.

...Thump!

The entire room shook once and loudly.

External intervention. A biofactory-style forced breeding.

The same evil hands that had forced the giant mantis creatures to mate in the past had entered the mating room to do the same thing this time.

Chapter 335

The Mating Room (5)

◆

Vikir pushed Sinclaire back.

“ ...How much of the mist did you drink?”

Sinclaire was too disoriented to answer even the most basic of questions.

'Anyway, your body temperature has recovered reasonably well. If I leave her alone, she'll wake up.'

Vikir laid Sinclaire on the ground, turned off the lights, and walked out of the den.

As he stepped out of the sawdust den, he saw two giant grasping hands piercing the darkness of the ceiling.

Hands covered in blue scales. They must belong to the owner of this mating room.

-Ding!

[The owner of the farm would like to check the condition of the collected items]

[Target: human 1 (♂)]

[Target: human 2 (♀)]

.

.

Simultaneously with an unpleasant beeping sound.

Koo-koo-koo-koo...

The shadow cast by a blue hand looms over Vikir.

The other hand was merely hovering over the sawdust, presumably searching for Sinclaire, who was probably hiding somewhere beneath the layer of sawdust.

'I can't let that happen.'

Vikir drew his sword.

A crimson aura dripped from the surface of the magic sword Beelzebub's hilt, sticky and dripping.

...Flash!

A sharp stab flew out like an arrow and struck the blue hand.

Thud-!

The aura on the blue scales produced countless sparks, as if iron and steel had collided.

However, as expected, the blue hand only flinched slightly and didn't seem to have suffered any fatal wounds.

Koo-koo-koo-koo.

Now, even the hands that were looking for Sinclaire have joined in capturing Vikir.

The two hands were quickly surrounding Vikir and pulling him to one side.

At this point, Vikir pulled out all the candy in his pockets.

<Vikir>

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: “Gutter Rat Hunter”, “Hell's Dog”, “Daylily Lumberjack”, “Majin Executioner”, “Black Sea King Slayer” (NEW)

-Stats

Strength: 300

?Agility: 284 (+16) = 300

?Stamina: 300

?Physical Resistance: 1

?Magic resistance: 1

?Reflexes: 1

Having eaten all of the Agility candies he had been saving up for, he now has all three stats at 300.

...Boom!

Vikir moves much faster than before.

There was a moment of confusion between the two hands that had anticipated Vikir's speed.

And Vikir was taking advantage of the gap.

“Now, it's your turn.”

[Hack-hack-]

Vikir stretched out his left hand, and the madam cub that had been waiting on his wrist spewed out a web from its mouth.

It shot out quickly and clung to the back of the approaching blue grasp.

Flick!

Vikir pulled on the web and soared into the air.

The giant, hovering hand was getting closer and closer.

Then Decarabia clinging to his chest spoke with concern.

[Human. Are you sure you'll be okay? The scales of a Ryumajin are thick and hard. It's most likely too much for you with your current strength... Didn't you fail to slash it before?]

“It's fine. I'm not after the hand.”

Vikir pulled on the web and climbed up.

He stepped on the back of its hand as it panicked and tried to pull back.

Tuck.

Landing on the blue scales, Vikir tapped them lightly with his hand.

As a result of slightly injecting mana, the blue scales covering the back of the Ryumajin's hand were not only much lighter and harder than ordinary metal, but also had good elasticity.

'Clearly, any attack, whether sword or magic, won't be able to make a scratch on it.'

Not even with a Graduator's level of skill. Head-to-head combat is a losing proposition.

Vikir made his decision in a split second.

...Flash!

The blow erupted once more.

The crimson aura coursed through the blue scales, traveling down the back of the hand, up the forearm, and into the darkness beyond.

Koo-koo-koo-koo-koo-koo...

Then, a loud vibration began.

The two grasping hands disappeared through the ceiling at breakneck speed.

By now, Vikir's web had been severed.

Decarabia said urgently.

[Oh, no! We lost them! The web is broken! This is bad news! How are we going to escape this cage?]

“Wait and see.”

[What do you mean wait for? You'll die and that's it, but I might have to spend the rest of my life in Amdusias's tower! Ugh! And it's a Ryumajin's laboratory!]

Decarabia bustles about in all sorts of fussiness.

But Vikir remains nonchalant.

Despite losing his grip on the Ryumajin and having his webs cut, he doesn't show the slightest sign of agitation.

Vikir's eyes are fixed on the ceiling. Where the Ryumajin's grip appeared and disappeared.

[...? Human. It's too late. Staring at the arm won't change anything...]

While Decarabia is showing a puzzled expression.

...Click!

The ceiling soon responded.

...Tinkle! ...tinkle! ...tinkle!

Raindrops falling, little by little.

It was like the drizzle that had been falling before to take away the body heat.

..., Except this time, it was different.

Sswaaaaaa-

It was suddenly pouring like crazy.

[What, what? Why is the water suddenly like this?]

Decarabia looked at him in disbelief.

But Vikir nodded, as if he'd seen it all coming.

“That was not an attack on the Ryumajin.”

[...Then?]

“It was an attack on the precipitation device above.”

Vikir could clearly see the grip coming in and out.

A sight that was revealed whenever the darkness lifted.

It was an odd-looking device, apparently serving as an intake for rain from above.

“I don't know if it is a device that extinguishes fires inside the mating room or if it is simply a device that makes it rain to lower body temperature. But....”

Vikir looked around as the rain fell like mad.

“It's the only way we can get out of here, that's for sure.”

The sawdust swells as it absorbs the water.

But there was far more water pouring down than the sawdust could absorb.

Kuleuleuleuleug... cheolsseog-

Naturally, the room gradually began to fill with water.

The chat wheel, water bucket, rice bowl, etc. were also gradually floating on the water.

“Now that our grip is gone, it's time to get Sinclaire out.”

Vikir launched himself toward the sawdust hole he had dug in the high ground.

At that moment.

...Thud!

Vikir felt a terrifying impact that crushed his entire body.

From above, pressing down with a weight that seemed to crush his entire body, was a blue hand, It was the fist of the Ryumajin who was thought to have disappeared!

It was a fist, not a grasp, and it was clear that it no longer had any affection for the collected items.

'Well, I've wounded you, albeit stingingly, so you won't see it.'

Vikir gritted his teeth and pushed himself to his feet.

Kkugugugugug...

The Ryumajin's fist slid upward, inch by inch.

But.

BANG!

A second hand appeared and grabbed his wrist, just above his fist.

This time, even Vikir doesn't last long.

Ujijijijiji!

A loud cracking and breaking sound erupted from Vikir's knees.

Fortunately, the floor was made up of water and sawdust, so he was able to avoid becoming a blood clot.

[Human. What would you have done if it weren't for me?]

Decarabia, who is blocking the fist, boasts in an arrogant tone.

“....”

But Vikir had no time to respond.

Every muscle fiber and blood vessel in his lower body is popping and breaking, then joining and rejoining under the basilisk's power, over and over again.

And since it was Decarabia, which consumed a lot of mana, he wasn't sure how long he could maintain this inverted pentagram shield.

'...Maybe I should have invested the rest of my stats into strength instead of agility?'

But then he wouldn't have had this chance in the first place. He wouldn't have been able to dodge the double grasp in the first place.

So Vikir gritted his teeth and pushed up against Decarabia's shield with all his might.

The Ryumajin, in turn, was pressing down on Vikir with both hands, intent on killing him.

'I have no choice.'

Vikir decided to use his last resort.

A picaresque mask. Using it, he transforms into a dog and runs back to the den to retrieve Sinclaire from the Ryumajin.

He uses the water to escape from the cage.

To do so, he must first dodge the Ryumajin's fists, which threaten to crush his entire body.

He also has to save Sinclaire, who might be drowning in the burrow....

Vikir was just about to slip the mask over his face.

“...?”

A voice that shouldn't have been heard at this moment.

Sinclaire poked her head out of the sawdust den in front of her, her eyes wide.

Not archery, but swordsmanship.

A red-hot aura that seems to be on fire.

A plague doctor's mask covering his face.

A spider on his shoulder. A shield shaped like an inverted star.

The unique black energy of the River Styx rising from the body.

Sinclaire's body began to tremble again. This was not a phenomenon caused by body temperature.

“...Ah, no, no, brother, no?”

“....”

Sinclaire desperately denies reality, but Vikir doesn't answer.

Koo-koo-koo-koo-koo-koo!

Pouring rain, flooding waters, and the Ryumajin's fists crushing his body.

Vikir has a choice to make.

To tell the truth or not to tell the truth.

And in the face of such crossroads, Vikir has always pursued only a single-minded answer.

“...Yes.”

Vikir's dry voice echoes in the damp air.

A word that made Sinclaire's pupils tremble mercilessly finally came out of Vikir's mouth.

“I am Night Hound.”

Chapter 336

The Mating Room (6)

◆

Sswaaaaa-

The rain was pouring down like a torrent.

A raging flood that seemed intent on destroying the world with water.

Sawdust, bowls, wheels, and buckets of water were swept away in the torrent.

Everything in the kennel began to swirl violently.

...And in the middle of it all stood Vikir.

Truth and lies. Revelation and silence.

At the crossroads, Vikir made his usual dry judgment.

“I am Night Hound.”

Those words were the beginning of everything. It was a statement that would change many things.

The first change was the look on Sinclaire's face.

Horror. Disbelief. Confusion. Doubt.

All of these complex emotions stormed across her otherwise lake-clear retinas.

And then.

...Quack!

Vikir flipped his picaresque mask completely over, transforming into a dog, and used the difference in size to escape the Ryumajin's fist.

Whirriik-

The madam cub riding on Vikir's back spewed out a spider web and snatched Decarabia.

Pas-

Back in his human form, Vikir wrapped his arms around Sinclaire's waist in the blink of an eye and leaped into the air.

Just like before against Belial.

Hanging from Vikir's waist, Sinclaire mumbled through empty pupils.

“Why, why, brother, why.”

“....”

“Then why did you save me, then... and now....”

Sinclaire's voice began to tremble more and more.

All alone in the world. The one person she desperately wanted to get rid of, but couldn't.

“Why were you so good to me....”

Drops of water finally fall from Sinclaire's eyes, which are filled with rainwater.

But Vikir can't stand to watch Sinclaire's condition.

The rain is pouring down, the rapids are rushing, and everything is being swept away!

'One last chance to escape.'

Soon, the rising waters were overflowing the middle of the kennel.

With a splash! Paas-

Vikir jumped onto the floating wheel.

With all his might, he slammed down on the wheel and yanked at the spider web around his left wrist.

With a plop! Kkoleuleug-

The wheel that had served as Vikir's foothold shattered and sank to the bottom of the water.

A high wave rose up and swallowed the pile of sawdust completely.

Narrowly avoiding the wave, Vikir tugged with all his might at the spiderwebs tied to his wrists and ran vertically up the translucent wall.

And then he jumped again.

...BANG!

His knee slammed into the corner of the cage, but it was only enough to shatter his kneecap.

Feeling the searing pain and the sensation of it healing, Vikir did a backflip and landed on the outside of the cage.

Thud!

Vikir landed on the ground with Sinclaire in his arms.

At the same time, a status window popped up in front of him.

<Mission Complete>– Escape from the Ryumajin's Kennel!

※ It's surprisingly comfortable inside the Ryumajin's kennel. Water, food, and a partner to love are provided. Is there any reason to get out of here and return to the harsh world?

※ A world with everything but freedom, or a world with freedom and nothing. It's up to the challenger to decide which one to choose~?

Finally, the mission is complete, and it's been a harrowing escape.

Vikir dropped Sinclaire from his waist onto the black stone floor.

Vikir and Sinclaire's gazes met.

“....”

“....”

After a moment of silence, Sinclaire spoke first.

“That's a familiar gaze.”

“....”

“You have a goal, and you'll do whatever it takes to get there.”

For a moment, Vikir paused.

He'd had this conversation with Sinclaire once before.

'I've only ever seen one person with eyes like yours, and that's my father.'

'....'

'He's the kind of man who pushes forward with goals that ordinary people like me can't even fathom. I can see it in your eyes. Brother, you're the same kind of man my father is.'

Rainwater from Sinclaire's eyes trickles down her cheeks.

Vikir didn't know whether to wipe the tears away or let them fall.

But.

A status window popped up in front of Vikir's eyes, putting all of that to rest.

<Special Mission>– Pursuit of the Angry Ryumajin

※ If you think that escaping is the end of the story, you're looking at the world from the wrong angle.

※ If a bug you usually keep escapes, you try to catch it again, right?

※ If the bug manages to hide in a crevice somewhere... ugh!

※ Now let's run and run until the gate opens ... Good luck!

At the same time. Something huge fell down from above.

...Rumble!

The fist of a Ryumajin, falling like a bolt of blue lightning.

There was no way he was going to let the forage he'd fed to them escape with a sting in his hand.

Quack! Ujijig!

He had to use his bare hands to deflect the heavy lightning strike.

“...Keug!?”

An overwhelming weight. An unimaginable shock.

The fist of a dragon, once the most powerful ruling species, with demonic power in its body.

It was definitely too much for Vikir, who was unable to unleash his original strength.

U-deudeudeudeudeug!

Hides burst, muscles tear, and bones break. Every hair on his body seemed to be on fire, and every internal organ seemed to be melting away.

The pressure inside his body was exploding.

The veins of mana that connected his body to the rest of his body were broken, and the lost mana stretched out in all directions.

If it weren't for the Basilisk's regenerative powers, the mana surge would have come sooner.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes narrowed.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Behind Sinclaire, he could see the gate to the lower level opening.

A black oval-shaped gate. Judging by its size, it was a one-person gate that led to different places.

-Ding!

[You've found the 10th floor of 'Lost Paradise'].

An escape route to the lower level.

It told Vikir and Sinclaire that the plateau was close, that it was right in front of them, that they were only one step away.

However, Vikir was unable to enter the gate because he was currently holding up Ryumajin's fist.

“Bro, brother!”

Sinclaire scrambled to her feet.

Sinclaire grabbed her last bit of mana and drew a magic circle.

...Flash! Kkudeudeudeudeudeug-

A golden hand protruded from Sinclaire's hat and began to support the ground and the Ryumajin's fist.

The pressure on Vikir's entire body decreased ever so slightly.

As the veins in his eyes subsided, Vikir's vision also returned to some extent.

The moment.

“....”

“....”

Vikir and Sinclaire's gazes met again.

For a split second, Sinclaire saw.

Vikir's eyes were shaking.

And those eyes are soon obscured by the large soles of the feet.

'...?'

Sinclaire's head spun as the mysterious sole filled her vision for a moment.

Pugh-

The next moment, Vikir's sole was in Sinclaire's face.

“...!?”

Sinclaire threw her head back with a lone scream.

But there was nothing Vikir could do about it.

With both hands cradling the Ryumajin's fist, there wasn't much Vikir could do.

He could only kick, sending Sinclaire flying through the gate on the other side.

“...! ...! ...! ...!”

Sinclaire was sent flying backwards and landed in the gate at the bottom.

The darkness inside the gate gradually engulfed Sinclaire's body.

But all the while, Sinclaire desperately struggled and flailed her hands.

Once again, Vikir's gaze met Sinclaire's.

It was only for a fraction of a second, a split second, but the conversation between the two eyes was much faster than that.

'The demon is an absolute evil, you can't be too stupid to know that, can you?'

'You're treating me like a child... There's not much difference in our ages....'

'Being the opposite of absolute evil doesn't necessarily make you good, but at least you know which side you'll be on when it comes down to it.'

'....'

'What you choose to see, what you choose to believe, and what you choose to do is entirely a matter of personal choice.'

These words were spoken by Night Hound on the night of Bartolomeo's death.

The conversation of that day becomes complicated in Sinclaire's mind.

And then there was Vikir's last words, which summarized it all, loud and clear.

“Decide for yourself. What you will see, what you will hear, what you will believe.”

You decide what you believe.

It was Vikir's advice to Sinclaire as much as it was to himself.

The fist of a Ryumajin.

An irresistible force.

And Vikir's choice to risk his life at the last moment to keep Sinclaire alive.

And the responsibility that came with it.

“A, no... no, no...!”

Sinclaire squirms as she tries to force her way through the neck.

...Thud!

In front of her, the Ryumajin's fist slammed into the ground.

Of course, everything that was underneath didn't even leave a proper shape.

Pis.

This happened almost at the same time that Sinclaire's vision went black after she fell through the gate.

Chapter 340

Private Life (2)

◆

....

Silence.

Silence hung in the bathroom for what seemed like an eternity.

Dolores stared down at Choco, or rather, Vikir, with a blank expression.

“...Choco, did you just say that?”

She tugged at Vikir's body.

Seueug-

Vikir closed his mouth and avoided eye contact, but it was already too late.

“Choco? Are you Choco? Yes, you are, with the mole on the bottom of your foot and the scar on the bridge of your nose... Has the demon transformed? But I can't feel any magic at all... No, but I thought you just said it clearly.”

Dolores began to examine every inch of Vikir's body.

From his lips to his gums to his eyelids to his eyeballs.

Vikir's mind was barely able to comprehend after the battle with the Ryumajin.

He had no choice but to speak, if only to avoid suspicion.

“...Meong.”

But the crisp, careful pronunciation, which made the line feel all the more awkward and unnatural, only served to heighten Dolores's alarm.

“You, who are you, who are you?”

Dolores was now more than a little frightened.

If he left it at this, things could get out of hand, so Vikir simply told her the truth.

“Calm down.”

The moment Vikir spoke, the warm bath water seemed to freeze.

Dolores stiffened as if she were an ice sculpture.

“....”

“....”

There was another infinite silence.

“Hmm. I think there's a misunderstanding....”

“Kkyaaaaah!”

Unable to bear the weight of the silence, Vikir opened his mouth once more, only to be met with Dolores' screams.

There was nothing he could do about it now.

Vikir put on his mask and transformed into Night Hound.

A human body with a face covered by a mask would somehow explain it.

It would be much faster and more intuitive than trying to communicate with words.

...Pop!

The effect of the picaresque mask reveals Vikir's human body.

Splash! -Slosh!

The water ripples as Vikir's body drapes over Dolores' half-laying body in the bathtub.

A look of horror on her face, clearly visible even through the steam.

Facing Dolores like that, Vikir twisted his voice as low as he could.

“It is me. Night Hound. Van....”

However.

“Split in half!”

It was Dolores' fist that returned.

...Pow!

Dolores was so embarrassed that she performed the miracle of splitting the bath water in half.

She lashed out with a fist strengthened by divine power and defeated the pervert in front of her.

Jukbang.

The fist shot out with a tremendous aura, reminiscent of Dolores in her prime, when she was known as the Saint of Steel.

And the moment that fist met Vikir's chin.

...Tug!

Of course, Vikir's thinly held consciousness was cut off.

◆

Vikir slept soundly for the first time in a while. It was a good night's sleep without a single nightmare.

“...!”

Vikir jerked out of bed.

His wounds were almost healed.

But the mask on his face and his clothes were still off.

Pulling back the covers, Vikir stood up and locked eyes with Dolores, who was sitting on his bedside table.

“....”

“....”

The silence was eerily thick.

So thick you could hear cells dividing.

After a long moment of silence, Dolores was the first to speak.

“Hey, are you awake? Night Houn... no Van... no Vikir....”

She spoke with her head bowed, her face bright red.

“I wasn't going to take that... mask off, but it's full of water and you can't breathe....”

Vikir nodded. What can he do?

“I owe you.”

It was a conversation starter.

But it only made Dolores' face turn even redder.

Earlier, Dolores wondered if she could get any redder in here, but apparently she had plenty of energy left to do so.

Dolores remained silent, her head bowed, so Vikir turned his attention elsewhere.

Then he saw Madame cub and Decarabia sitting somewhat uneasily on the couch beyond.

“...Where have you been?”

[Sorry, human, I tried to hide, but I got caught].

[Hack-hack-]

There's no point in disguise or pretense now that he's been spotted with his bare face, his distinctive mask and voice, and now the cub and Decarabia.

Vikir sighed and opened his mouth.

“This is....”

“I know.”

But before Vikir could say anything, Dolores spoke up.

“I'm sure you meant it all.”

“....”

“Don't be so hard on yourself. We're colleagues.”

Dolores echoed Vikir's words from before.

'Don't be too hard on yourself. We're colleagues.'

She'd been trying to get those words back to Night Hound, to Vikir.

'I can finally tell him this!'

The timing was a little odd, but who cares!

She knew the identity of her 'soul mate', Night Hound, the one she had missed and wondered about so much!

Dolores examined Vikir's form carefully.

She was checking him for wounds, but then her face turned bright red again.

“Oh, you need to get dressed....”

Dolores said in a hushed voice as she handed him a bathrobe.

In all her years of treating patients, she had seen men naked countless times.

But she was surprised that her heart was beating so fast right now.

Finally, Dolores spoke again, unable to bear the awkward silence.

“By the way, how did you get the ability to turn into a dog and why...?”

“It's an ability I gained after hunting down Dantalian many years ago.”

“Aha....”

Dolores then asked, her voice even more hushed than before.

“Well, then, were you the one who bathed with me last time...?”

“That was me, too.”

At the same time.

...Hwaag!

Dolores's face was now flushed to bursting.

The first thing she remembers is kissing the soles of Vikir's feet and hands.

After that, stroking his hair, pressing his cheeks, touching his chin, rubbing his belly, rubbing their noses together.

And then...

'Dogs are supposed to kiss.'

'....'

'You don't give me choco? It's a pity.'

'....'

'Are you sure you're not a dog? This is suspicious.'

Vikir's tongue licked Dolores's cheek.

And Dolores kissed Vikir's mouth, nose, and the rest of his face.

Dolores clamping her mouth shut and swallowing the screams that came out.

Trying to lighten the mood, Vikir cracks a joke of his own.

“ ...I'm lucky I didn't get neutered.”

“Kkyaaaaaah!”

Of course, that only irritated Dolores even more.

◆

Two more days passed.

Dolores was able to wipe the slate clean of all of her previous thoughts.

“The more painful the reality, the more deeply you should think about the meaning of life and religion. Only then will it lead you to a better realm of greater goodness... So you meant that there is meaning in the process itself, not in the outcome of your agonizing and torturing. Thank you, Vikir.”

Her expression was more determined than ever, as if she had realized something.

Vikir nodded, not knowing much about theology.

'Before the regression, this was the floor where Dolores spent most of her time, but this time is different.'

In the past, Dolores had wasted months on this floor.

She'd spent months on this floor, until a desperate Tudor convinced her that she needed to find Bianca, and she'd finally left.

This time, however, Dolores shook herself out of her thoughts very quickly.

Whether it was because of the realization, or the traumatic event in the bathroom, or both, he wasn't sure.

“ ...If we go out of this gate, will we be separated again?”

“I suppose.”

At Dolores' question, tinged with regret, Vikir nodded nonchalantly.

But even if we are separated now, we will meet again someday. That's what towers are for.

If only Dolores had come to her senses a little sooner, a lot of lives could have been saved.

Step-

Vikir took a step forward.

Dolores hesitated behind him, gripping the cuffs of Vikir's robe for a moment.

Then released.

Step-

She, too, took a large step forward to stand beside Vikir.

<※A small perk for all the trouble you took to get here, send a message to the figure outside the tower who will be anxiously awaiting my arrival!>

“I'm not fooled by your fake answers.”

<※ The 'Letter Item', originally worth one golden candy, will be given away for free once a month to residents of this floor only!>

“We don't have time to wait a month, because there are probably tons of people suffering on other floors right now.”

<※ Your chances of being in this room are less than 0.0001%, you're the lucky one who's been chosen!>

“I decide whether what is in front of me is luck or not.”

<※ From the very next floor onwards, the difficulty will increase by at least ten times compared to the floors you've been through so far!>

“It doesn't matter what penance awaits me, I'm not afraid.”

<※ Please rest here to rejuvenate your body and mind so that you can challenge the tower again!>.

“...Are you ready?”

“Of course.”

Vikir and Dolores stood side by side at the starting line.

“It's going to be a tough road from here on out.”

“With you, I can handle anything.”

“Are you sure you want to abandon this place of comfort?”

“My heart will never change, no matter what.”

At Dolores' confident answer, Vikir nodded.

And with that, they began to walk away, looking in the same direction, heading in the same direction, with the same stride.

Companions.

Their gazes were unwavering, shining straight ahead.

As if they were not afraid of the 11th floor of the Abyss, the core of darkness they were about to encounter.

Chapter 341

Ballak (1)

◆

-Ding!

[You have exited the 10th underground level, 'Lost Paradise']

[Entering the 11th underground level 'River of Flow']

.

.

Vikir felt his vision slowly brighten.

When he looked up, he was alone, seemingly separated from Dolores, who was beside him.

“I've fallen into a bad place.”

Vikir looked around at his surroundings.

Razor-sharp leaves and thorny bushes.

The climate hot and humid.

In the distance, a large, gently winding river circled the forest.

At first glance, it looked like an ordinary jungle, but there was one crucial difference.

Daylily of Blood.

These grotesque aquatic plants cover the surface of the river.

A colony. Vikir had fallen into the center of a colony of blood daylilies.

“ ...Are they surrounding this jungle? It will be difficult to go out like this.”

The blood daylilies covered every inch of the river that circled the jungle.

They were so numerous that it was hard to see them all at a glance.

Vikir pulled a picaresque mask over his face in case the daylilies gave off poisonous gas.

“Looks like a normal jungle, except for the daylilies.”

Vikir turned his gaze back to the forest.

A moment.

“...!”

Vikir realized something was wrong.

He hadn't realized it until he was distracted by the daylilies that filled the vast river.

The jungle looked the same now as it had when Vikir first looked at it earlier.

The basic landscape remained the same, with large boulders and giant trees, but everything else was changing in real time.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Leaves sprouted from the dainty branches, then blossomed into flowers and fruits.

The fruit then falls back to the ground, sprouting seeds, and the original branch shrivels up and dies.

Everything in the forest is born and dies at an incredible rate.

It was as if time was being rewind dozens of times.

Vikir looked at the standing water in the muddy puddle.

The water was evaporating at a noticeable rate, shrinking.

The tiny eggs in the puddle hatched in the blink of an eye and turned into tiny flying insects.

They flew up into the sky, fluttered around a few times, and then fell to their deaths.

“...Is that a mayfly?”

Something is definitely wrong if a mayfly, which usually lives for about seventeen hours after two days, can die so quickly.

'Time passes quickly.'

Vikir once again paid attention to the name of this floor.

<Level 11, 'River of Flow'>

Time flows like a river.

Perhaps the name of this floor refers not to the surrounding river, but to the swift passage of time.

“A jungle where time flows quickly. Another strange place.”

To be precise, it's a place where only the time of organisms passes quickly.

The breeze on his nose, the speed of the river's flow, these things were no different from the normal world.

Vikir noted his body.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The marks of his deep wounds were noticeably fading.

This was a speed that even a Basilisk's regenerative powers could not match.

'...The passage of time is even faster than I thought.'

Vikir's expression hardened.

Considering that recovery was so rapid, it was highly likely that time was passing at a much faster rate than 2 or 3 times.

“We'd better hurry.”

Vikir tapped his foot quickly, feeling the time running out.

◆

Vikir paused and looked around the jungle.

As he moved away from the river and into the center of the forest, he frowned as the sunlight filtered through the leaves.

'It's not going to be easy to spot the enemy in this.'

Blue and red, blue and purple.

The trees around them were changing color every few seconds, casting a brilliant glow over the jungle.

The splendor is incomparable to the huge stained glass on Quovadis Street.

“....”

Vikir decided to change his method of searching the jungle.

The scariest thing in a jungle battlefield is not the enemy, but nature itself.

Vikir understood this well, having lived in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

If you don't know the ecology of a jungle, don't tread near it.

That was the rule of Ballak's rangers.

Still, the good news was that it was only the plants that had changed.

Perhaps the only thing that has adapted in this great river is the plants.

For them, aging is a natural and familiar concept.

“We'll have to climb a tree for now.”

Vikir quickly decided on his next move.

It's better to get out of a place like this quickly than anything else.

Staring at it would only make his head hurt.

He grabbed the vines around him,

Sreuk-

The tree vines fell helplessly.

In the meantime, the vines have dried up and grown new ones from their roots.

Tub-

Vikir grabbed the tree trunk for good.

He'd had enough of tree climbing when he was in the military.

It was an abnormally large tree, but with Vikir's tree-climbing skills and his current physical abilities, he should be able to climb it without difficulty.

“For now, we'll go to higher ground....”

Vikir stroked his chin and muttered.

...Ping!

A strange sound sounded in his ears.

Ssshhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.

An arrow flying with such incredible speed that even Vikir could barely react.

Luckily, Vikir is an expert in archery and ducked his head to avoid the flying arrow.

However, one of his earlobes is torn off.

Puff-puff!

Arrow after arrow flew from an unseen angle.

The attacker seemed to be well-adapted to these woods.

It was only in the area of surprise that Vikir found it difficult to react.

Reading the approximate direction of the arrows, Vikir was dodging them with ease.

'About 74 meters.'

The arrows were clearly coming from a single person.

They all have their own unique heaviness.

While Imperial archery was usually sharp, this archery felt more like a cannon, as if the arrows were being fired with real force.

It's also different from Ballak's archery.

Something about this archery is very familiar.

'This is....'

And with that, Vikir tries to deduce information about the attackers,

Shae'ek-!

A flying arrow pierces the rocks behind him.

Flash!

A dull iron light sprayed in front of him.

An extremely small dot shoots out in front of him.

It was a spear.

Since it is stretched out in a straight line, only the front view is visible, and the side view is not visible.

As fast as an arrow, the spear was like a bolt of lightning striking horizontally.

It was aimed directly at Vikir's eyes.

...Tada!

Next, two monsters appeared in front of Vikir's eyes.

A man in his mid-twenties and a woman in her mid-twenties.

Both were nearly naked, their bodies covered in animal skins and leaves.

The man was covered in mud and grass, so it was clear that he was probably hiding in the ground. The woman, on the other hand, had already dried the mud on her body.

'A combination of ranged and melee.'

The man was carrying a long spear and the woman was carrying a large bow, which seemed like a good match.

Swoosh-pass!

The man swings his spear to create a gap, and the arrow from the woman fires right through it.

This was a coordinated draw attack, where the arrow didn't fill in the gap left by the spear, but rather the arrow finished off the path that the spear had deliberately created.

A high-level combination that would be impossible to pull off except between partners who had been practicing together for a very long time.

...But Vikir was a seasoned veteran who had rolled on the battlefield dozens, perhaps hundreds, of times the amount of time they would have combined.

Kkilig- kwagig!

Vikir grabbed the spear that was digging into the solar plexus with his hand and spun it around to break it.

...Thud!

The man tries to hold on to the spear, but he's outmatched in strength stats.

Seeing the spearman's wrist snap, Vikir immediately pulled the spear away.

Hwaeg- kwaag!

Reaching for the spearman's throat like a snake, Vikir tightened his grip.

“...Kuhg!”

Vikir grabbed the man by the throat and slammed him right into the ground.

The woman behind him jumped back in horror.

Puff-puff-puff!

With the man in danger, she used her superhuman strength to fire four arrows at once.

All while running!

But Vikir took a step back and at the same time stretched out his other hand forward.

The arrows are visible in real time as they slip through his five outstretched fingers.

'It's helping that I raised my Reflexes stat.'

Even though it was only a 1 increase, the effect was amazing, as it was like having a stat that didn't exist at all.

...Charak!

Vikir caught all four of the flying arrows with a single movement of his hand.

“No, no way!”

The woman muttered in disbelief.

Just then, the man who had been grabbed by the throat by Vikir's hand cried out with all his might.

“Don't come!”

The man was warning the woman.

His voice was so desperate that even as Vikir pressed down with his knees, his entire body shook.

“Run away, you're in danger!”

“...But you've been caught, how can I leave!”

“Go! Go and call for backup!”

“No! I can't go!”

The woman ignored the man's words. She gritted her teeth and drew the dagger she wore on her thigh.

She was about to charge at Vikir, even if it meant giving up her life.

Then. Vikir opened his mouth with a light sigh.

“That's enough. Donquixote, Usher.”

For a moment, the struggling man and woman stopped moving.

“...!?”

“...!?”

Through the leaves, I see a pair of eyes wide open.

Donquixote of the spear. Usher of the bow.

It wasn't every day that two people came from such prestigious families.

Then, their mouths opened at the same time.

“...Vikir!”

They scrambled to their feet, wiping the dirt and leaves from their faces.

They were Tudor and Bianca!

They were both surprised and delighted to see their friends for the first time since entering the tower.

But Tudor and Bianca weren't the only ones who were surprised.

Vikir was also stunned as he jumped out of his seat.

“...!”

The two of them removed their leaf masks and muddy makeup to reveal their bare faces.

They looked at least ten years older.

Chapter 343

Ballak (3)

◆

The jungle on the 11th floor of the basement was a horrible place, reminiscent of the floods of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Venomous scarabs, bone-sucking mosquitoes, vines armed with spikes like awls, berries as heavy as maces, narrow, deep cliffs cleverly covered in rotting leaves...

A normal person would not have been able to survive half a day in this forest, let alone make it through.

Moreover, it is now night, and the darkness has descended to an unbearable depth.

It was an ambitious time to be wandering around, even for the ship's owners, who were the original inhabitants of this jungle.

But.

Pasasak.

Vikir moved freely through the forest as if it were his own home.

He carried Cerberus' fur against the wind to keep other beasts at bay, found cliffs hidden by fallen leaves and scaled them, and cut open the air sacs of overgrown daylilies to release gas to scare away poisonous insects.

The spiderweb on his left hand, spun by the cub, bridged the gap between cliff and cliff so effortlessly that it would have taken hours to climb.

It was all done with such skill and familiarity, as if he'd been doing this for decades.

Naturally, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, who were following Vikir, couldn't help but be speechless.

“This is even more amazing than when we realized Vikir was actually Night Hound. How does he move so well?”

“I don't think even Basilios, the mercenary king of the North, could do this...”

“What, are you saying that Vikir is Night Hound? No, what does that mean?”

“When I saw him earlier, he was wearing the mask of Night Hound. I'll ask him what happened later.”

Meanwhile, Vikir was having a flashback.

'It's like old times.'

Two memories come to mind.

The age of destruction, before the regression.

A harsh time when survival depended not just on swordsmanship, but on herbal gathering, scouting, searching, stealth, ambush, assassination, pharmacy, healing, cooking, and everything else.

Another memory was the two years he spent in the depth of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

...Spot!

Vikir sliced through the rotting log that stood in his way, halfway across the room.

The aura of the Graduator, vibrating and spinning at the tip of the sword at lightning speed, sliced through everything in an instant.

And Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, seeing its power, must once again be horrified.

“Vi, Vikir. What level are you?”

“Oh my god, how many stats have you raised?”

“You've been strong since you were outside the tower?”

“...He's a guy with a lot of secrets.”

And then.

...Stop!

Vikir, who had been walking ahead, stopped.

Looking at the footprints in the mud on the ground, Vikir checked the direction of the wind, then crouched low and circled behind a bush.

To hide his scent.

Beyond the thick darkness, he could see a faint beam of light.

A dozen or so people gathered around a small campfire.

Pow!

Tudor gritted his teeth.

“That's them, shipowners. The ones who stole our food.”

The tower's challengers had been on this floor before Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

They were all middle-aged warriors with sturdy builds.

Their faces were smeared with mud and their bodies covered in animal skins and leaves.

Their bodies, covered with copper-colored muscles, were tattooed with intricate designs, but strangely, the colors were quite pale and blurry.

Beside him, Tudor whispered in a low voice.

“They laid something like dry gravel near the campground. If you step on it, it makes a loud noise and breaks.”

“I know. Let's get closer while clearing away the scoundrels.”

Vikir approached carefully, avoiding the dry gravel on the ground.

After a slow crawl that covered only a few meters in an hour, Vikir was able to close in on the food thieves.

...Ppagag!

Vikir trampled all the trees and bushes and appeared right in front of the bonfire.

“Give me the food.”

The raiders were startled by Vikir's appearance, who had approached this far without sound or sign, and grabbed the bows and arrows beside them.

Ping-!

The arrows flew.

Each of the raiders was sending arrows flying with an all-too-familiar motion, as if they were masters of the bow.

And as the arrows flew, Vikir was certain.

'Warriors of Ballak.'

He had heard of their mysterious disappearance before entering the tower, from Cindywendy's report.

He was worried about their whereabouts, but he never thought they'd be trapped in the abyss of Amdusias.

'At least they're still alive.'

Vikir thought to himself that this was going to be surprisingly easy.

Next, Vikir removed the mask from his face, revealing the tattoo on his shoulder.

It was a tattoo of Ballak's hunting grounds.

“Enough. It's me.”

There was no way Ballak, or any of the warriors of the native tribes of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, would not recognize Vikir.

Vikir was the hero who had saved all their tribes from the dreaded plague of the Red Death, as well as a massive flood.

...However.

Things had taken an unexpected turn.

“...What is that guy?”

“Why does he have a tattoo of the hunting grounds?”

“Does anyone know him?”

“I don't know him. Beat him up!”

Ballak's warriors didn't seem to recognize Vikir at all.

They were old enough to be Ballak's warriors, judging by the tattoos on their shoulders, their archery, the black ash that painted their faces, and the language they spoke.

But somehow they didn't remember Vikir at all.

Pow!

Vikir was forced to take a few steps backwards to avoid a full-blown arrow.

'Warriors this old don't recognize me?'

Vikir sheathed his sword with some doubt.

“Can't you tell?”

A Baskerville-style swordplay unfolded.

It was something the warriors of Ballak, who had spent their lives fighting against the Baskervilles, could not fail to recognize.

But.

“This guy uses a strange sword technique!”

“Hmph! A tooth-shaped slash?”

“I've never seen anything like that!”

“Do not engage, fight at a distance!”

Ballak's warriors still didn't recognize Vikir.

They just stood there, strangely confused.

'I don't think my memory is failing me, but something is wrong.'

Vikir furrowed his brow.

Surely the people in front of him were Ballak's warriors.

But for some reason, they were acting as if they had no memory of Vikir at all.

They showed no signs of having been affected by mind magic.

Vikir shrugged it off.

“If you've forgotten, I'll have to remind you, how I went from being a foreign slave to being your hunting ground.”

At the same time, Vikir pulled out an item.

It was the one hidden piece that Vikir, who had so far claimed no need for items and accepted all of his rewards as candy, only wanted.

-<Scale of Forced Equality>/ Scales / S

The values ??of other stats also change depending on the value of the highest stat you have.

The values of all stats will gradually and slowly increase in line with the value of the highest stat, and this change will continue until all stats are equal.

Vikir opens a status window with a golden scale in hand.

<Vikir>.

-LV: 1 (%)

-Title: “Gutter Rat Hunter”, “Hell Dog”, “Daylily Lumberjack”, “Majin Executioner”, “Black Sea King's Executioner”, “Ryumajin's Favorite Enemy” (NEW)

-Stats

Strength: 798

?Agility: 92

?Stamina: 100

?Physical Resistance: 1

?Magic resistance: 1

?Reflexes: 1

Vikir's three primary stats, Strength, Agility, and Stamina, were originally set at 300 each, for a total of 900.

But now, Vikir's three stats total 990.

Almost all of it was in Strength.

That was because Vikir had exchanged the stats he had gained on the previous floor, Lost Paradise, for candy, and then absorbed and redistributed them again.

<This is the largest candy store in the tower>.

<Challengers can exchange their items for candy here>

<Even candy that has already been eaten and become stats can be vomited out and turned into candy, especially for residents of this floor!>

<If you vomit out candy that was consumed before entering this floor, you will receive an additional 1 candy for every 10 candies you vomit out!>

Vikir wasn't planning on using the shop, but he turned his stats into candy and got an extra 1 candy for every 10.

And then he ate it all again.

'...I've just taken the bait in a trap laid by demons.'

I'm sure Amdusias and his minions would be wailing and gnashing their teeth if they found out.

Vikir was rewarded with the most red candy, the most common candy, based on probability.

Green candies for agility and blue candies for stamina were rare, but this was all the better for Vikir.

That's because Vikir was in possession of the aforementioned Scales of Forced Equality.

It's a temporary item that gradually raises all of your stats to match your highest stat, and it disappears when all of your stats are equalized.

'It was originally an item I obtained to increase the special 3 stats by at least 1, not the basic 3 stats....'

The rate at which stats are increased by these scales is extremely slow, so there's not much of a benefit to challengers anyway.

In order to utilize this item to its full potential, you'll need to spend a very long time in the tower, until all of your youth is gone.

By the time you get strong enough to do so, you'll be an old man, so what's the point?

...However.

“Good, because in this jungle time flows like water.”

Vikir was getting older by the hour.

His hair was growing at a rapid rate, his bones and muscles thickening.

His voice grew thicker, and the lines on his face began to darken.

And naturally, Vikir's stats began to change accordingly.

-Ding!

[The item 'Scales of Forced Equality' is starting to forcefully balance stats!]

[The 'Strength' stat is out of balance with the other stats!]

[Other stats are being forced to adjust to the 'Strength' stat's value of '798'!]

[The 'Agility' stat will be increased by '1' from '92' to become '93'!]

[This change will continue until the 'Agility' stat reads '798'!]

[The 'Stamina' stat increases by '1' from '100' to become '101'!]

[This change will last until the value of your 'Stamina' stat reaches '798'!]

[The 'Physical Resistance' stat increases by '1' from '1' to become '2'!]

[This change will last until the value of your 'Physical Resistance' stat is '798'!]

[The 'Magic Resistance' stat is increased by '1' from '1' to become '2'!]

[This change will last until the 'Magic Resistance' stat reaches a value of '798'!]

[The 'Reflexes' stat is increased by '1' from '1' to become '2'!]

[This change lasts until the value of your 'Reflexes' stat reaches '798'!]

[The 'Agility' stat increases by '1', from '93', to become '94'...]

[The 'Stamina' stat increased by '1' from '101' to become '102'...]

[Physical resistance stat increased by '1' from '2' to become '3'...]

[Magic Resistance' stat increased by '1' from '2' to become...]

['Reflexes' stat increased by '1' from '2'...]

.

.

The highest stat, Strength, is now 798.

And all six of Vikir's blooming stats were increasing by 1 to match this 798 number.

<11th floor underground. 'River of Flow'>

A wave of time flowing like a river.

It was entirely on Vikir's side.

Chapter 346

Key man (1)

◆

In the darkness.

In the middle of an endless void, Pigi stood alone.

'Get out.'

A middle-aged man's voice shouted.

The moment he heard the voice, Pigi realized.

'Another dream.'

The vision he had when he was nearly crushed to death by a pile of golems during the midterms.

The nightmare he'd barely escaped with Vikir's help.

'This trash is not my blood.'

His voice was bitterly cold.

Followed by his mother's sad sobs.

'You lowly thing, you don't even know what subject you're talking about.'

'Get him out of here now.'

'...Get rid of him.'

The whispers around him follow the whimpers, swirling around.

After that it was the same again.

A fleeing mother, forests and mountains, pursuers, steep cliffs, raging rivers, hungry wolves, and the surprised faces of passing merchants and mercenaries; a mother who gradually regained her smile; a stepfather who was always kind; a difficult but rewarding exam period; a school dormitory life that was difficult and hard, but made bearable by friends.

The fantasy continues as time flows like a river.

Next thing Pigi knew, his body was covered in some sort of sticky thread.

“...Hugh!?”

His surroundings, which had been nothing but darkness and emptiness, were now filled with uncomfortable walls of flesh.

The unpleasant sensation of being trapped in the esophagus of a giant monster.

Pigi pushed forward, flailing desperately.

The muscle fibers in his limbs were snapping.

Then, up ahead, he saw a door.

A large, circular gate, with searing flames blazing around it.

<Gates of Destruction, “Serpent's Tongue”>.

The tip of the searing pillar of fire split into two, like the tongue of a snake.

Countless pillars of flame, each ominously shaped, hovered incessantly around the gate.

A moment. Pigi felt an intense desire.

A great, fundamental desire to enter the gate, a desire he dared not resist.

'Why am I like this?'

A normal person wouldn't even dare to walk towards the gate.

But Pigi was walking toward it, not even knowing why, even to himself.

And then.

“Hey, Pigi.”

A familiar voice called out from behind him. It was Tudor's.

“You can't go in there. We're human.”

Tudor's words gave Pigi pause.

Then he heard Sancho's voice right behind him.

“That gate is for demons. We can't go through it.”

“Are you crazy? Get back here now!”

Bianca called out to Pigi.

Other familiar voices called out behind them.

“Come back, Pigi.”

“It's safer this way.”

“You can't go there!”

“Over here! Over here!”

“Look this way! Turn your head!”

His mother, his stepfather, his friends back home... all the people he missed called out to him.

Pigi finally stopped walking and stood, his eyes glazed over.

And then.

Slurp-

The head slowly turns back.

Pigi was about to turn his back on the gate.

...Just then.

'Never look back.'

The voice sounded like it was speaking to his heart.

The beat restarted his heart and cleared his foggy mind.

“Huh!”

Even as Pigi snapped out of his reverie, he could still hear the shout from behind him.

“Pigi! Look over here, please!”

“Behind you! Look behind you!”

“Dodge! Run now!”

“Come on, Pigi! You have to come this way!”

The voices of family and friends demanding that he turn around.

But. Every time Pigi unconsciously tried to turn his head, a voice echoed in his chest, hot and harsh, almost the panting of a fierce animal.

'Never look back, keep moving forward.'

The voice sounded like a stubborn old man moaning and speaking.

Pigi took a step forward with his eyes tightly closed.

“Pigi! Are you crazy! Come back!”

“Why are you ignoring us!”

“Get back here now!”

“Look here, Pigi! It's your mom!”

“You ungrateful brat, if you don't look over here right now...!”

And Pigi's face fell, too.

How could he not turn around when the people he had missed so much and cherished so much were shouting at him in such desperate tones?

“Ughhhh....”

Pigi stopped in his tracks, drooling.

He closed his eyes and tried to turn his head away.

And then.

...Boom!

A hand grabbed Pigi's face.

“Huh!?”

Pigi opened his eyes in surprise.

But before he could look back, the hands on either side of his cheeks jerked his head back to the front.

Pigi looked down at the hand holding his face.

A rough hand, wrinkled, scarred, and covered in sticky blood.

The hand's owner was clearly at his side.

'Walk forward.'

It was the same harsh, hoarse voice from earlier.

Pigi shuddered, but took a step forward.

When he glanced sideways to follow the hand, he saw a taller man walking beside him.

A middle-aged man.

It was hard to make out his features from the edge of his vision, but Pigi could see that his hands and face were covered in burns and slash marks.

He was limping, but he was carrying Pigi forward as if to support him.

Hands around his neck, shoulders, and chin to make sure he never looked back.

And then. Pigi came face to face with a huge gate.

Searing fire and heavy steel. It was the kind of gate that intimidates the onlooker.

But for some reason, Pigi wasn't afraid of the door at all.

The only thing that bothered him was the shouting behind him.

However, Pigi had made it this far thanks to the mysterious man walking beside him.

There was a strange sense of accomplishment and pride. For some reason, it felt like he had to walk through the gate.

Pigi had just opened his mouth to say thank you.

The man next to him took his hand off Pigi's body.

'Don't look back, you're on your own from now on.'

At the same time, his figure and voice disappeared from Pigi's sight.

Pigi knew without looking.

That he wasn't supposed to be here in the first place, and that he had just gone one last time, to a very far away place, forever.

“...He's a good person.”

Pigi pushed the gate in front of him with all his might.

And threw himself out into the darkness beyond.

Kkiiiiiiiig-

With only the dull sound of the gate closing behind him.

◆

“Huh!?”

Pigi jerked his sweaty body to his feet.

The first thing he saw when he lifted his head was his own reflection in a puddle of water.

“Oh, you're back?”

Pigi touched his face and realized he still had the skin of a teenager.

All the years he'd lost in the river had been reset.

Finally, Pigi lifted his head and looked up.

“Huh!?”

There was something even more astonishing than before.

Plant roots sprouted from the ceiling, black as the night sky.

The roots of the deep roots that extended from the main body of the Hell Tree were passing through it.

And at the base of the many tiny roots that sprouted from the main root hung a slender fruit.

There was a human figure sleeping inside the outer shell of the fruit, and only the face was sticking out of the shell, so everyone could tell who was who.

Tudor, Sancho, Bianca, and all of Ballak's warriors hung there, wrapped in cocoons.

Each with their eyes closed and in a deep sleep.

Pigi sensed that the massive root was the main body that sustained the Hell Tree's power.

Looking down at the main root, he could see that the veins within it drew steadily from the waters and fires of the underworld.

From there, the seeds of various aquatic plants, such as the blood daylilies, and jellyfish, such as the Black Sea Shadowless King, were brought forth.

“...Yes, using the emotions we unleashed as fuel to connect the human world to Hell.”

Pigi opened his mouth, his voice trembling.

Right now, Pigi's power alone is not enough to deal with the giant root in front of him.

...But there was something he could do with his powers right now.

Sereung-

Pigi drew the sword hanging from his waist.

The levels and stats he had accumulated while training in the great river were still the same.

His age had returned to normal, but the experience he'd gained in those years was still in his hands.

“Eis!”

Pigi swung his sword with all his might.

The strike sent his friends tumbling to the ground, one by one, as they clung to the roots of the tree.

Pigi went to Tudor, the first to fall, and peeled off the fruit.

Then he began to slap the sleeping Tudor across the cheeks.

“Tudor, wake up! Sancho! Bianca!”

Pigi slapped with such fervor and sincerity that one by one, Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca began to wake up.

“Huh? What is it, I thought I heard my father call me and turned around?”

“Hmm? Sis, where did you go... huck? Where am I?”

“Ew, my head hurts. What is it, my face is back to its normal age?”

The first to open their eyes was the first to die.

Pigi pulled down the rest of the fruits.

One by one, the natives of Ballak who had been trapped inside also began to open their eyes.

All of them were alive, both those who had died and those who had been killed.

“Huh? Look at that! Isn't that Ballak's hunting ground?”

“What? How can a little kid like that....”

“Heck, no, that's the face, and they're all babies!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca were horrified to see the pale-faced girl in front of them.

She was Aheul.

They were all stunned to realize that the woman warrior, with her overwhelming power, level, and the presence of mind of a seasoned old woman, was actually such a young girl.

Indeed, the majority of Ballak's warriors who have awakened from the Fruit since then have been young children, leaving Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca feeling somewhat helpless.

However, they still had the experience, levels, and stats they had gained in the great river, so they couldn't be underestimated just because they were children.

They are Ballak warriors who have already lived for several decades.

It's a fact that Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, who have spent seven years on the flowing river, know well.

Meanwhile. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca muttered a few words to each other as they saw the roots of the Hell Tree.

“...Yes. The hatred, murder, insecurity, anxiety, nervousness, inferiority complex, and lust for life that we spew is the nutrient that sustains this Hell Tree.”

“I suppose this is the source of power for demons. It is the nutrient conduit between Hell and the human world.”

“Is this what you've been drawing the flames and waters of Hell from, to power the tower?”

“All of the unfortunate creatures I've encountered have crawled up these roots.”

Just then.

“Hey, over there!”

Aheul shouted in poor imperial language.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca turned their heads in the direction Aheul was pointing.

“Huh!”

There, hanging from the tree, was a large fruit.

A fruit that looked much larger and heavier than the others.

Trapped inside was Vikir.

“We'll get him out!”

Pigi cautiously raised his sword and swung.

Immediately, the gaseous aura characteristic of an Expert emanated from the tip of Pigi's sword and shot out in the shape of a crescent moon.

...Slash!

The fruit Vikir was trapped in fell to the ground.

Everyone rushed to Vikir.

“Vikir, wake up!”

“Open your eyes, Vikir!”

“He's breathing!”

“He's just in a deep sleep.”

No matter how many times they slapped him and shook him, he wouldn't wake up.

Obviously, Vikir was the only one who survived the final beheading.

But none of the men in the room doubted Vikir's sincerity.

“Vikir knew, that the first to die wakes up the fastest from the illusion.”

“I see. I guess this was one of those missions where the early deaths were an advantage.”

“If they made it this far, they must have been strong and skilled enough to not die easily.”

“They must have gotten used to being the last man standing, and they probably wouldn't have died easily, so they'd be stuck in their hallucinations longer....”

Eventually it all became clear.

<Mission>– Die and Kill!

※ Don't let your guard down! Latecomers become increasingly stronger as time goes by! If you don't want to be caught up, even if you're a ship owner, you have to work hard, right?

※Recognized only when everyone has cleared the mission!

Mission “Die”, “Kill”. It wasn't just about killing others.

It ended when you had to 'die' yourself.

Moreover, this mission was a last man standing.

It meant that if you inevitably become vicious and live with the habits of betraying and hurting someone, you will have to bear the full consequences.

The first to die would be the first to exit the illusion, and the first to be abandoned, the first to be betrayed, would not leave their competitors still sleeping.

Add to that the restriction that everyone has to complete the mission, and the difficulty level is truly unimaginable.

It's a diabolical idea, indeed, to switch sides in the blink of an eye and create new ones.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir opened his eyes.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Aheul, and the rest of the Ballak warriors rushed to check on him.

“Vikir! Are you okay!?”

“Are you hurt anywhere?”

“How many fingers do you see here, Vikir?”

“No, what on earth were you doing all alone in the flowing river?”

Vikir's eyes narrowed for a moment.

Then he looked down at his hands.

“ ...The wrinkles and age spots are gone, and when I wake up, I'll be back to my normal age.”

Everyone who heard him was stunned.

If his hands had wrinkles and age spots..., how long had Vikir managed to survive in the flowing river?

Vikir didn't have much of an answer to that question.

Only.

<Vikir>

-LV: 1 (%)

-Titles: “Gutter Rat Hunter,” “Hell Dog,” “Daylily Lumberjack,” “Majin Executioner,” “King of Black Sea Executioner,” “Demonic Dragon Great Rival,” “Renowned Boatman”

-Stats

Strength: 798

?Agility: 798

?Stamina: 798

?Physical Resistance: 798

?Magic Resistance: 798

?Reflexes: 798

Level 1. Total of 6 major stats: 4,788.

The fact that he'd blossomed all three of his special stats and had 798 each only confirmed the ridiculousness of his record.

After a moment of silence, Vikir turned his head to look at Pigi next to him.

He gave a short laugh.

“ ...You did a great job.”

Was it because he was deep in thought? Vikir's voice was very hoarse and rough.

It returned to normal quickly, but for a moment it really sounded like an old man's voice.

Then.

Pigi's expression changed.

“This, this voice!”

At everyone's puzzled looks, Pigi spoke again.

“It's the voice that saved me from the hallucination! It's the voice!”

Pigi was certain that the voice that had led him to the gate, that had helped him not to look back, belonged to Vikir.

He knew it, too, because the scars on Vikir's hands were exactly the same as his, the position of the moles, the shape of the nails.

'Never look back. You're on your own from now on.'

Pigi remembered the voice and squeezed Vikir's hand.

“Vikir. If I had looked back then, I wouldn't have woken up, and I wouldn't have been able to wake up my friends.”

Vikir paused for a moment at Pigi's genuine gratitude.

'What? I don't remember doing that.'

Vikir thought for a moment, and then came up with a hypothesis.

'The old comrades I encountered when I reached the 10th Floor Lost Paradise.'

Could it be that something similar had happened this time?

Perhaps his pre-regression self, a residual thought in his memory, had materialized in some way and helped his friends, Vikir thought.

Just then.

<Mission End>– Die and Kill!

※ The deathmatch is finally over!

※ How did you feel once you died?

※ As soon as the late comer clears the mission, the ship owner will be reverse summoned out of the tower.

※ Ship owners eligible for reverse summons are limited to those who have cleared the mission.

A loud notification sounded and the rewards began to pour in.

Whirr-!

Piles of golden candies fell in front of everyone.

At the same time, the gate to the deeper levels of the Abyss appeared.

...And the sound that Vikir had been most wary of.

<Reverse summons of ship owners will be carried out>

<Do you agree to the reverse summons?>

As Vikir had warned, Aheul refused to be recalled.

“Well thought out.”

Vikir stroked Aheul's head and nodded.

Since he did not know exactly what outcome the Insectking race he met in the Black Sea had met, he decided that it would be better to remain in the tower.

“I will clear the tower. You will then leave the tower and return to the jungle. We must rebuild Ballak.”

At Vikir's words, Aheul and the rest of the children of Ballak nodded with determination.

In the tower, their incredible talents blossomed, and they would become great warriors and restore their clan.

Then.

“Vikir.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca spoke almost simultaneously.

Turning to Vikir, his friends asked.

“Do you know why only Pigi was able to wake up?”

Their questions were legitimate.

To be honest, Pigi's physical strength was the lowest of the four, and so was his mental strength.

When it came to strength, energy, persistence, and hardness of heart, Pigi was also last.

But somehow, it was Pigi who was the first of the four to wake up and save them all.

“....”

Vikir stroked his chin silently.

His gaze remained fixed on Pigi's forearm, a small wound with black blood caked on it.

“Listen, Pigi.”

It was the result of Vikir, who had lived in the flowing river for decades, constantly thinking and worrying.

“Perhaps you are the key to bringing down the Amdusias Abyss.”

Chapter 347

Key man (2)

◆

<Underground Level 11, 'River of Flow'>

Countless corpses of demonic beasts are floating on the boiling river water.

Geuleuleuleug...

Daylily of the Blood Tree. Among them, the largest one raised its huge head and revealed its teeth.

However.

Peo-peong! Ujijijijig!

Eight giant thunderbolts struck down, tearing the daylily's head off.

Hududug- hududug- hududug- pungdeong! Pungdeong! Pungdeong!

Fluid and flesh fell like rain, pounding on the surface of the water.

Seven large teeth and an eighth that was small in comparison.

A massive aura rises around it, like the body of a hound.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

A concentration of aura that boils and evaporates the surrounding river water just by existing.

There was an existence that emitted a huge aura in the shape of a hound.

An old man sat with his eyes closed on a pile of daylily corpses.

Despite the wrinkles and age spots, his straight waist was like a well-forged long sword.

Vikir.

He opened his eyes, stroking his graying hair and long beard.

“...It is time to go.”

The years passed like water.

After what seemed like an eternity, Vikir looked at his stats and saw that they were all at 798.

...Pow!

The scale of forced equality has done its job and shattered.

“That's enough.”

Vikir stepped down onto the corpse of the last daylily he had just killed.

The reward for killing all of the daylilies that had formed a colony on the river was piled high in Vikir's hand.

Golden candies. A huge number of candies in Vikir's hands.

Vikir had converted the rewards into level candies.

[Hack-hack-]

Vikir turned his head at the sound of breathing behind him.

There was a Baby Madam, or rather a girl madam, who had grown so big that she had to raise her head to look up.

[...Has time already gone this far? Time flies so fast].

Decarabia squinted through Vikir's white beard.

Vikir had killed Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and all of Ballak's warriors, and yet he had remained here, in this flowing river.

Then.

[ Are you still out there? ]

A voice came from the air.

Vikir turned to see a familiar figure hovering in the air.

It was a fairy.

[ Is there really no such thing as a progression?]

The fairy grumbled, as if tired of seeing Vikir.

After all, as a store owner, how can you look kindly at a customer who is proudly refusing to leave the floor while continuing to hunt the daylilies that have been made so that they cannot be caught?

The fairy said, as if dying of headache.

[ Could you please leave now ? You ate enough to pluck, right? ]

It was crying like a baby.

Then.

Vikir opened his mouth.

“Okay. It's time to get out.”

[ ! ]

For a moment, the fairy's eyes flashed open.

Vikir, who had always kept his eyes closed and remained silent when asked to leave the floor, had somehow responded to the conversation today.

[ Were you thinking well, when are you going to leave ? ]

Vikir waved a hand in the air at the fairy.

“When I leave depends on your attitude. Come closer. Let's talk.”

[ What ? What do you want to talk about ? ]

The fairy looked frightened for a moment at being asked to come closer.

However, as if it wanted Vikir to get out of this floor quickly, the creature was hesitantly approaching.

Keeping its distance as far as it could.

But.

What the fairy considered a safe distance was meaningless to Vikir.

...Hwaag!

Reaching out in an instant, Vikir grabbed the fairy by the nape of the neck before it had time to react.

“What are you so wary of, just because I want to talk to you?”

[ What what what are you doing ? ]

But the fairy didn't finish the sentence.

Vikir pressed down on both of its cheeks, forcing it to open its mouth, and shoved something into it.

It was a black liquid in a leather sack.

Gulp- Gulp- Gulp- Gulp-

The fairy had to drink the liquid that Vikir poured into its mouth without knowing why.

And soon enough, the response came.

[ K h u a a a a a a a g h ? ]

Along with a terrible scream, black smoke began to billow from the fairy's mouth.

The sensation as if the five internal organs were melting was tormenting the fairy.

“...Hmm.”

Vikir stomped on the struggling creature and looked down at it.

Fairies were essentially indestructible, the product of magic engineering created from the essence of the Hell Tree, and therefore indestructible except by their creator, the Demon.

But the fairy in front of him now was dying, slowly but surely.

It was slowly dying in terrible pain.

[ Uh huh huh why? ]

The fairy itself doesn't seem to know what has caused it to suffer.

“Well. Maybe it's revenge for all the humans who have suffered in this tower.”

Vikir replied in a dry voice, but the fairy didn't seem to hear him.

Puswiiiiiig-

In the end, the fairy burned with a terrifying momentum, and then vanished.

“...Well, that worked.”

Vikir flicked the black liquid in the leather hilt in his hand.

It was Pigi's blood.

Blood that had been there for a very long time, unevaporated and unrotten, still pooling in the sack.

It was certainly no ordinary human blood.

Vikir had collected it after killing Pigi and stored it in a leather sack.

'There is definitely a strange blood in Pigi's body. It's deadly to demons.

When Vikir first noticed the small wound on Pigi's forearm, he felt a sense of strangeness that only a seasoned demon hunter could.

'Pigi. Is your blood naturally black?'

'Huh? Aaah, it's always been this way, huh? I'm not demonized or anything, I've been like this since I was a kid! The doctors said it's because I have a lot of iron in my blood... but it seems like it's gotten a little darker since I've been in the Hell Tree?'

Vikir nodded, looking at the fairy that had turned into a handful of blood and spread before his eyes.

“If my judgment is correct....”

◆

“...You may be the key to bringing down Amdusias's Abyss..”

Vikir spoke up.

Now that they had cleared the 11th level of the Flowing River, the younger Vikir stood before Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Aheul, and the rest of Ballak's warriors, all of whom looked nervous.

“Huh? Me?”

Pigi looked surprised, as if he felt overwhelmed by all the attention on him.

But Vikir was serious.

“I've been studying you for a while now, during my years in the Flowing River. It seems that your blood has strange properties.”

Pigi's blood reacted not only to demons, but also to fairies, monsters, and others.

Although it didn't cause a violent reaction by itself, it could be used to great effect when applied to a sword or mixed into an aura and wielded.

“I'm going to use this to clear the tower once and for all.”

It was a question that Vikir had pondered over and over again during the decades he'd lived on the river.

In the timeline he lived in before his regression, the tower would be captured a little later.

But even then, most of the heroes had fallen by now, and only one had cleared the tower.

Camus Morgue, a genius among geniuses.

'At that time, I didn't even know that the appearance of this tower was the work of the demon.'

This is a glimpse into the genius of Camus, who cleared the tower despite the uncertainty of the situation.

But now, Camus is not in the tower.

Someone else has to clear the tower.

'...Plus, Pigi wasn't at the Academy at that time.'

Maybe it wasn't just bullying that caused Pigi to drop out of school before the regression.

Maybe his blood was telling him something was wrong and he was scared that he wasn't like everyone else.

Vikir stared at Pigi once more.

“....”

“...?”

A being that bends the laws of causality within the tower. Perhaps the greatest variable in the future.

Vikir put a hand on Pigi's shoulder.

“The reason you woke up first is because there was something you had to do first.”

“...What I had to do.”

Pigi dropped his gaze and looked at his hands.

Then.

“Vikir.”

Tudor called to Vikir.

Vikir turned his head, and Tudor thrust a tightly curled fist in front of him.

“Take this.”

The thing in Tudor's palm opened wide.

It was a candy, sprinkled with glittering gold.

“Why are you giving me this?”

“I don't know why.”

It was not Tudor who answered Vikir's question, but Bianca, who stood beside him.

Sancho, Pigi, Aheul, and the rest of the Ballak warriors also handed Vikir golden candies.

“This is the reward for completing the mission. But I think it would be better for you to eat it than for me to eat it.”

“Please, please, Vikir, I can do nothing but share my blood!”

“Hunting ground. Please....”

Everyone stares at him.

Vikir is silent for a moment, then nods.

“I will not waste them.”

The golden candies fell into Vikir's hands.

Jjalgeulag-

Combined with the rewards for completing the mission and all the candies they had collected while killing demons, there were quite a few.

Tudor's eyes widened in anticipation.

“So, are you going to eat them all in one sitting and then go meet the core of the tower?”

“No. There's something I need to do first.”

Vikir shook his head once, then pulled an item from his pocket.

“...!”

The one that made everyone's eyes widen.

-<Return Scroll>/ Scrolls / Rank: ?

A scroll that allows you to return to the Tutorial Zone for one time only.

The answer to the question 'Lord, where are you going?' is written.

※Level will be reset when used

It was a return scroll that sent you back to the very beginning of the stage.

Chapter 349

Outside the Tower (1)

◆

[...How could a human even reach this place!?]

Amdusias's mouth dropped open in astonishment.

Without another word, Vikir flicked his sword once.

Then, fragments of crimson aura fall to the floor.

Amdusias's expression changed in an instant.

[That blood is...? Why is that here...?]

The energy of twisting the causality of the Hell Tree was clearly felt in Vikir's sword.

But Vikir did not answer any of Amdusias's questions.

Only.

“Demons kill.”

Twice, or even now, he has struck the river that flows through the abyss, and over the course of his three lives, he has only shown a conviction that has become more and more solid.

...Pakang!

The tip of Amdusias' horn collided with the edge of Vikir's sword, rupturing the atmosphere.

The void shattered like a pane of glass, sparks falling through the myriad of tiny cracks.

Pajig! Pajijig!

Amdusias sensed a different ominousness in Vikir's sword.

Unlike when they had clashed before, Vikir's sword had become much faster and more precise, and now it held an eerie aura of some unknown nature.

[Assuming it was the stats from the tower that made it faster and stronger, but... is this eerie feeling also due to its blood?]

Amdusias shouted as he stepped back.

[You! What have you coated your sword with, and where did you get it?]

“Be gone.”

Vikir was still dancing.

...Pakang!

Once again, eight strikes flew out to cut Amdusias down.

Amdusias lifted up the unicorn's unique, gigantic horn and struck them all away.

Jiiing-!

However, it was not possible to block all the slashes.

As the crescent-shaped strikes shattered and their fragments scattered, they inevitably left tiny cuts all over Amdusias's body.

And the shards of aura dug into the wounds.

[Huh?]

Amdusias felt his vision blur for a moment.

For a moment, a strange vision flashed before Amdusias eyes.

A swamp of blood and flesh, a mountain of bones, an atmosphere drained of mana, a giant mushroom cloud rising over the distant horizon.

...And an endless, barren desert.

...A huge tower rising in the middle of the desert.

...An old man in black walking lonely and alone toward the tower.

Each vision pierces Amdusias's mind, fragmented and broken.

[What, what is this?]

Even the mighty Amdusias was bewildered.

Strange things kept popping into his mind as the unknown substance that bent the laws of cause and effect seeped through his wounds.

Seeing it, Vikir was convinced.

'...There is something in Pigi's blood.'

I don't know what Amdusias is hallucinating, but I do know this.

Pigi's blood is poison to demons, and it's enough to distract a Demon King once.

It's unclear how the causal chain is twisted and the demons are struck, but it's enough that it happens.

Vikir gathered his strength once more and prepared to strike.

However.

[Oooh! You think I can suffer any more?]

Amdusias began to counterattack as well.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

The nightmares in the Hell Tree turned into black energy and began to be absorbed by Amdusias.

He glared at Vikir as he sucked the black energy into his mouth.

[You see, all the negative emotions exuded by the challengers of this tower become the nourishment for me, this is Hell Tree].

All the negative energy emitted by those who have been forced into the tower.

Emotions such as sadness, grief, anger, screams, feelings of betrayal, hatred, and inferiority will all be fed to Amdusias.

[I'll eat your emotions too].

“Emotions. Do I have any of those left?”

[As one who has stepped into the realm of the Supreme, I can see clearly into even the deepest unconsciousness. Bluffing doesn't work].

Amdusias's eyes glowed, and he raised his horns, pointing them at Vikir's chest.

[Your fear, your anger, your sadness, all of your negative energy will become my strength].

At the same time, Amdusias began to gallop.

The gallop of a ghost horse. It laid a straight black path on the ground.

It galloped directly into Vikir's mental world.

◆

...Thud!

Amdusias stamped his hooves on the ground.

Amdusias is as adept at entering the minds of others as he is at drawing them into his own.

Amdusias looked around.

His vision was obscured by parched black soil, tiny dead trees, scorched earth, and smoky plumes of fire.

[Hmm. For a human, you've got quite the interior].

Amdusias walked forward through the smoke and fog for a while.

Finally, he saw a vague shadow through the thick atmosphere.

It was a large stone statue, weathered by the passage of time and no longer in perfect shape.

It was chipped here and there, but its face was still recognizable.

[Hugo and Osiris... The Iron-Blooded Swordsmen are the Patriarchs and Young Patriarchs of Baskerville. Hmm, for a statue of this size to have such a large presence in its mind, it must have some family feelings of its own].

Amdusias was judging the presence or absence of emotion by the size of the statue, which was quite large.

The bigger the wound, the bigger the emotion, the bigger the representation.

...Thud!

Amdusias stomped his massive feet, crushing all the giant trees and boulders in his path.

[It seems to be quite large for a mere mortal's mental world. I can see some pretty big beings...]

With all the smoke and fog, it's hard to tell exactly how big this place is or where you are.

But in the end, it's the mental world of a boy not even twenty years old.

If it's that big, how big can it be, and if it's that desolate, how desolate can it be?

[Laughs].

Amdusias snorted and stepped forward.

Suddenly, Amdusias saw a very steep uphill slope ahead of him.

The terrain looked like a mountain, but the smoke and fog made it impossible to determine its exact height.

[High, at least, in the insignificant human inner world].

Still, if they got high enough, they might be able to see their surroundings.

Amdusias began to walk up the slope of the mountain that appeared before him.

...Thud! ... thud! ... thud! ... thud!

Amdusias's hooves pounded the ground.

Parched, crumbling earth rushed down, causing landslides, but Amdusias used his massive frame to crush them all.

Amdusias continued to climb the mountain that must be somewhere in Vikir's inner world.

[...This mountain is probably the highest mountain in the world.].

Amdusias felt beads of sweat forming on his forehead.

A mountain where the leaves of every tree had been burnt to a crisp, the soil had dried up, the insects had died, and the beasts had been reduced to bones.

The mountain was unexpectedly high. So high that even the mighty Amdusias was momentarily exhausted after climbing it.

[A mountain in the mental world is usually a deposit of emotions, such as responsibility, burden, or debt, but... how much emotion is this human piling up?]

Amdusias muttered in incomprehension.

No matter how much power he has, he's barely a teenage boy, isn't he?

Does he carry these feelings inside of him because of how much he's lived, or how much he's suffered?

Amdusias continued to climb the mountain of emotions as he questioned himself.

He could not see the peak because it was shrouded in smoke and fog, but he could intuitively feel that the summit was just around the corner.

Amdusias continued to climb.

...He couldn't tell how much time had passed.

Soon, Amdusias was at the top of the mountain.

The end of the mountain, pointed like an awl. There was nothing there, just nothing.

Amdusias lifted his head and looked down the mountain, but there, too, he could see nothing, shrouded in smoke and fog.

Just an empty summit.

Amdusias measured the height he had climbed and opened his mouth in disbelief.

[I don't know how a single human could have accumulated this much negative emotion, even a centurion who's crossed the line of fire hundreds of times wouldn't have this much...]

Amdusias had to admit, Vikir was right.

To be able to build a mountain this high in your mind is usually a sign that you're not human.

[But even then, a human would be no match for the power of me, Amdusias].

Amdusias snorted and looked down the mountain.

He would find Vikir's mouse-sized self hiding somewhere and destroy it.

Then.

Kugung-.

The entire mountain trembled lightly.

A storm from nowhere began to sweep the smoke and mist around the summit.

And in that moment, Amdusias saw.

[...!]

The land stretched endlessly beneath the mountain.

The vast horizon stretched out so far that even Amdusias dared not guess its end.

But it wasn't just the vastness of the land that took Amdusias' breath away.

It was the bloodshed.

Swamps of blood and flesh. Mountains of bones. Rivers, lakes, and oceans of blood.

Demon and human corpses tangled together to form hills and valleys, ravines and canyons, and everywhere boiling lava and sulfur erupted in fountains.

Vast numbers of demonic beasts swarmed and devoured the corpses, and everywhere there were wails and cries of anguish, and endless, endless streams of demons.

Amdusias shuddered at the sight of this vast chain of chaos, this vortex of hatred.

[How can this be in the minds of humans!]

A terrifying battlefield, the likes of which even Amdusias, a Demon King, had never experienced.

The world of human and demons. The horror and cruelty of this place have gone beyond the limit.

A scene even more brutal and terrifying than hell unfolded here.

[A human will never see such a scene in their lifetime! Even I, a Demon King, have never seen such a battlefield, and yet here it is, in the mind of this child, a child who has barely lived a moment!]

It was unbelievable to see it so clearly, so vividly.

Just then.

...Kugung!

The mountain vibrated once more.

[...?]

Amdusias looked up in surprise.

And then, something even more devastating came into view.

Gooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo...

A mountain.

Flanked by mountains even bigger and taller than the one Amdusias had just climbed.

Like, there were four more!

The mountain Amdusias had climbed with his energy was only the smallest of them all.

Awe. Shivering. Amdusias froze in place, unable to speak.

As mentioned before, the mountains of the mental world represent the burdens of the heart, such as debts, responsibilities, and missions.

How can a human being, a young boy in his teens, have five of these mountains?

And in such a terrible, terrifying world!

Amdusias stammered.

[No, no, no...]

But he could barely finish his sentence.

Kung!

The five mountains shook violently, then suddenly began to surge upward.

[???]

Amdusias soared upward without even knowing what was happening.

And soon, he realized a terrifying truth.

Ku-gugugugu...

This great mountain range, five peaks, was coming toward Amdusias now.

It was carved with a swirling pattern at the end.

Amdusias muttered in despair as he looked at the five gigantic mountain peaks, filled with smoke, fog, and fire, gathering in one place.

[...Fingers?]

That's right.

A large body revealed beneath five huge mountain peaks. The source and core of the mental world.

The age of destruction. A returner who holds a piece of the terrible universe in his heart.

Vikir's own self had risen.

Chapter 351

Outside the Tower (3)

◆

...Thud!

Vikir landed on the ground.

The tip of his sword was still emitting a stream of aura, and at the tip of it was a giant sun.

A concentration of aura, a black sun.

It shone in full view of every student, every parent, and every professor at Colosseo Academy, illuminating the depths of the abyss where the Hell Tree had sunk.

....

A collective silence. Everyone was at a loss for words in the face of something so unreal and unbelievable.

The person who finally opened his mouth was Professor Banshee Morgue, the interim principal of Colosseo Academy.

“Vi, Vikir-kun, is that you? Uh, how did you get such power...?”

Professor Banshee's fingers trembled as he pointed to the solid aura of a Swordmaster.

But Professor Banshee never got to finish his question or hear the answer.

Kwakwakwakwakwakwang!

The fragments of the Hell Tree that had shot up into the sky came crashing down to ground.

And then the huge thing carrying the debris cast a dark shadow over everyone's heads.

Amdusias!

A unicorn with two eyes burning red was waving its fiery mane.

Winston's body had long since burst into flames.

Turning to Amdusias, who was now in the body of his former self, Vikir asked in a dry voice.

“It would be too much of a burden to incarnate without a host, wouldn't it? Do you intend to destroy yourself?”

[I don't care, as long as I can get rid of you!]

Amdusias glared at Vikir and said.

[You are someone who should never be allowed to live, especially now that we are about to embark on the Great Quest].

“You mean the gate?”

[...If you know that much, I can't let you live any longer!]

Amdusias steadied his crumbling body and channeled his magic power into the tip of his horn.

Peo-eong!

The aura shoots out in the shape of a huge horn.

It threatened to sweep away not only Vikir, but all those behind him at once.

“Oh no! Everyone back up!”

“Everyone on the ground!”

Spear King Cervantes and Archon Roderick were the first to react.

Two absolute powerhouses in the realm of the Supreme, they had gathered their magic power and raised it to stop Amdusias.

But.

There was an earlier, faster, more powerful action.

...Flash!

Vikir cast a long aura from his magic sword, Beelzebub.

Then, like a tidal wave, the massive strike rose to meet Amdusias' attack.

Boom!

[...!?]

Amdusias was stunned by Vikir's power, which was now much stronger than before.

But that was to be expected.

Vikir had leveled up to 100 in the tower and gained additional stats.

He had a talent he wasn't born with, and he honed it to the extreme until he became an old man in a flowing river.

Upon exiting the tower, he regained his original strength, and all the power he had built up inside the tower was added to it, doubling his strength at least twice.

The trajectory of Vikir's sword's movements began to take on a complex number.

One tooth. Two teeth. Three teeth, four teeth....

Slowly, the number of teeth grew to seven.

And finally, an eighth tooth.

Kwa-gigigigigig!

It was much bigger than any of the seven teeth that had appeared so far.

The Baskerville 8th Form. That too is completely extreme.

It took the breath away from everyone who saw it.

The expressions on the faces of Spear King Cervantes, Archon Roderick, and Osiris, the young patriarch of the Baskervilles, were particularly stunned.

“Oh, my God, the swordsmanship of an iron-blooded swordsman! That's also 8th Forms”

“It's not just 8th Form, it's the Ultimate of 8th Form, Master!”

“...This is surprising.”

It was now officially known that Hugo Le Baskerville, Patriarch of the Baskerville family, had mastered the 7th Form, and that Osiris, a young patriarch, had just reached the beginning of the 7th Form.

But now, here was a user of the 8th Form who was completely flawless.

This is a boy who has never made a name for himself in the world and who has only just turned 19!

Ujijijijijig! Kkwadeudeudeudeug!

A total of eight strikes, led by the most powerful 8th tooth, slowly carved away at Amdusias's horns, sending them into a spiraling trajectory.

And then.

...POP!

With a loud crash, the horn broke and snapped in two.

Earth Shattering (驚天動地).

The clouds in the sky were blown away by the wind pressure, and the ground shook like crazy.

Vikir was single-handedly blocking a Demon King runaway dive.

That too, against the demon Amdusias, who is optimized for one-on-one combat among the Ten Corpses, and there is no one who can beat him in a 1:1 match!

[Ku-aaaaaghh!]

Amdusias roared in pain, humiliation, and anger at having his horns broken.

Kwakwakwakwakwang-

Rocks and trees were shattered in all directions by the rampaging hooves.

“Damn it! Protect the citizens first!”

“Protect the students!”

Cervantes the Spear King, Roderick the Archon, Professor Banshee, and other heroes and heroines were fending off the falling rocks and other debris.

Meanwhile, Amdusias sprinted, his body crumbling.

He ran so fast that his body caught fire.

At the end of it, Vikir stood.

[I do not lose to humans, not even in one-on-one combat!]

Amdusias had always prided himself on his combat prowess as a single entity.

So he couldn't admit defeat anymore.

Is that why?

Amdusias drained his life force. He was unleashing his full power.

His body burned like a shooting star, fading away.

But despite this, Amdusias continues to run in a straight line, with only one goal in mind, to kill Vikir.

...However.

“I already know that you are strong in one-on-one combat.”

Vikir pulled back lightly.

Even though he had mastered the 8th Form, it would be a burden to go one-on-one with an Amdusias who would fight for his life.

Vikir chose a slightly more certain method.

“There is no need to match the other person's strengths.”

'If Amdusias is a land-based demon that specializes in 1v1s, there's no need to fight him 1v1.'

...Vikir barely finished speaking.

“Well said, husband!”

A voice came from beside him.

Vikir turned to see a familiar-looking girl running towards him, her face bright with excitement.

Camus Morgue. She looked quite tired, as if she had been staying here for just a few days.

“We met quickly this time? I was prepared for another few years!”

As soon as she entered the battlefield, Camus summoned a wall of fire and iron skewers to block Amdusias' path.

...Teoeong!

Amdusias gritted his teeth as his charge was stopped.

[Seere! How dare you betray me!?]

“Look at me straight. Who is Seere, to say the least?”

[Ha, but I can definitely feel Seere aura...?]

“If you mix 99.99% water with 0.01% beer, do you call it beer?”

Camus snorted as if she were full of energy.

Indeed, the power she was exuding was clearly something that had once belonged to Seere, but now it was nothing to sneeze at.

Seere had shrunk to a very, very small size, even smaller than a fairy, and was hanging from Camus's shoulder.

The feeling of seeing a Thumbmaiden, not a Thumbelina

Decarabia, clinging to Vikir's chest, chuckled.

[Hahaha! What is the appearance of Seere, the world's scum!]

[You're laughing at a subject that's no better than a cheap necklace from the road shop...]

[Still, I'm better than you, we're equal partners, not master and slave, khahahahaha!]

While Decarabia and Seere were snapping, Camus completely blocked Amdusias' charge with a grid of flaming iron skewers.

Just then.

“Vikir-nim! Let me help you!”

Another voice interjected.

Dolores stood at Vikir's side with a determined look on her face, her holy power radiating from her.

The scars on Vikir's body faded away, and his mana began to flow again.

Meanwhile, sparks flew from Camus's eyes.

“Hey, who are you, and why have you been hanging out near my husband since last time?”

“What, what? Who are you and what are you talking about?”

“I don't have a name to give you, so get the hell out of my way and don't play tricks on someone else's fiance!”

“How rude, when did you see me...!”

“I saw you at the festival!”

“ ...At the festival?”

Dolores's pupils twitched slightly.

Suddenly, that voice sounds familiar.

Dolores's expression turns to one of disbelief.

“You mean the black mage who invaded the festival, the Corpse Queen?”

“....Ugh. Oops-”

Camus realized her mistake and shut up for a moment.

Dolores glanced back at Vikir, too, as if demanding an explanation.

However.

“...I don't think this is the time for that.”

A voice floats over Camus and Dolores' heads, landing lightly at Vikir's side.

Osiris.

He, waving his black robe, faced Amdusias with his red sword hanging down.

He, who had just recently reached the level of master, lightly struck the rising solid aura with the tip of his sword.

Then he looked back at Vikir and spoke in a calm voice.

“...Acting Patriarch. Your orders.”

Camus and Dolores, as well as everyone behind them, were astonished by Osiris' actions of bowing his head in a light but extremely polite manner.

What kind of shocking behavior would this be for a boy from a commoner background, from a person who was no less than the young patriarch of the iron-blooded swordsman Baskerville?

...And an acting patriarch?

And yet.

Vikir received Osiris' greeting in a very natural manner.

Teobeog-

With that, Vikir took a step toward Amdusias.

Camus's skewer bars creaked as if they wouldn't last much longer.

Amdusias' body is about to rush towards them and explode.

Toward the red-hot body of the unicorn, Vikir spoke briefly.

“Hounds assemble.”

At the same time, an object emerged from Vikir's arms.

A dark red whistle shaped like teeth.

It makes a quiet yet heavy beating sound.

The moment it rings once.

Chills...

Everyone in the hall shivered at the unknown chill.

Flutter.

The sound of a cloak fluttering can be heard from somewhere.

Flutter- Flutter- Flutter- Flutter- Flutter- Flutter- Flutter-

It wasn't just one or two.

One by one, shadows in black bloody robes began to emerge from the Academy's walls.

Strange people with red auras dripping stickily like honey from the tip of their long swords.

A hundred people in a group, all Graduators. And seven such groups.

Pit bulls. Mastiffs. Dobermans. Shepherds. Rottweiler. Wolfhound....

Seven Hundred in total.

And six senators to lead them.

The Seven Counts.

The strongest of the iron-blooded swordsmen, who spend their lives in battle.

All six are here, except for Cane Corso, who guards the Grave of Swords.

A red whistle that symbolizes all military authority of the Iron Blood Swordsman.

The proof of the patriarch, once given to Vikir by Hugo himself to bring the Wraith Tree to Pomeranian.

All the Baskerville hounds, attracted by that sound, have gathered here.

Chapter 352

Outside the Tower (4)

◆

'I don't know what it is, but bring it to me, son.'

'....'

'I would like to go in person, but I cannot leave because of the current tension with the Morgue Family. I'll give you the entire Knights Order if you need it.'

While Hugo was busy analyzing the newly installed Morgue's delegates, he left Vikir with a mission.

To retrieve a Wraith Tree in the middle of the salt desert.

In the process, Vikir had taken over full military control of Baskerville from Hugo.

Even though it was only a power that was effective for half a day, allowing the army to stand by within a certain distance at the right time to blow the whistle, it was actually an enormous power as it could summon all seven knights, including the Seven Counts of the Iron Blood Swordman Family

In other words, Vikir became the de facto military commander of the Baskervilles for half a day from the time he blew the whistle.

“...Order.”

Young patriarch Osiris bowed respectfully, and the Six Counts behind him did the same.

Vikir gave a short command.

“Bite him to death.”

The hunter unleashed the hounds.

No sooner had Vikir's command been uttered than the shadows behind him shot forward.

The prey had just escaped the cage... Amdusias!

...Papapat!

The first to attack Amdusias were the triplets at the front, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

The Three Swords. Swords that multiply in power when wielded in unison.

Together, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro breathed aura into their swords with all their might and then slashed.

Taaang!

However, the triplets' combined auras were unable to pierce Amdusias's iron-like hide.

[Aah! It just tickles...!]

Amdusias was just about to snort.

“Puppies stay back.”

“Let's see if this one tickles, too.”

Two huge shadows loomed over the triplets' backs.

Boston Terrier Le Baskerville, leader of the Pit Bull Knights.

Great Dane Le Baskerville, leader of the Mastiff Knights.

The most fiercely competitive of the Seven, they bared their teeth at the same prey.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwang!

The strikes from Boston Terrier and Great Dane weren't as smooth as those from Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

The extremely concentrated auras drew six teeth, piercing through Amdusias's hide.

[Ohhhhhhhhhhhh!]

Amdusias screamed in agony.

The total number of teeth embedded in his body was twelve. Boston Terrier and Great Dane had not only sunk their teeth into the hide of their prey, they had ripped it to shreds.

After that, four other Seven Counts joined.

'Isabella' La Baskerville, leader of the Doberman Knights.

'German' Le Baskerville, leader of the Shepherd Knights.

'Metzgerhund' Le Baskerville, leader of the Rottweiler Knights.

'Cu-Chulainn' Le Baskerville, leader of the Wolfhound Knights.

It was quite unusual to see all the Knights Leaders in one place, save for the currently vacant position of Cane Corso.

“Hehehe... I see your face often these days. It seems like it was just yesterday when we executed Seth.”

Count Boston Terrier chuckled lowly.

But neither Great Dane nor any of the other Seven Counts had any particular response to that comment.

Each took a hundred Graduators under their command to intercept Amdusias.

Meanwhile.

“Break his horns first, then his neck. Then the hind legs. Then the lungs and liver.”

Vikir was giving orders, step by step.

The Six Counts and the Osiris dutifully followed his orders.

Everyone who watched eventually realized.

“Vikir, was that guy... from Baskerville?”

“I never heard of a guy like that in the Ironbloods Swordman?”

“Yes, dude, I've heard of him, the supernova that appeared on Baskerville Family!”

Some of the more gossipy of the group spoke up.

“It is written that at the age of 15, he rescued a woman from another noble family and died heroically!”

“That he even received a letter of commendation from His Majesty the Emperor?”

“I heard there was even a golden statue of him in a city somewhere.”

“What? Wasn't that a rumor?”

“I thought that was a rumor started by the Baskervilles to raise the family's stock price...”

“Now that I think about it, I wonder what the Baskervilles are upset about that would do such a thing. That closed family.”

“I can't believe he was a real person in the first place... and that I went to school with him all these years.”

The public is shocked.

But Vikir couldn't care less.

“What are you doing? A demon who almost dragged your sons, daughters, and disciples into the abyss.”

Vikir's words brought everyone to their senses.

The first to step forward was Professor Banshee Morgue.

“Professors, listen up! Our first priority from now on is to protect our students!”

At the same time, Professor Banshee unleashed his full power.

Six magic circles were drawn, and within them, magic from the elements of earth, fire, wind, water, iron, and wood poured forth and began to envelop Amdusias.

The other professors awoke and drew their own swords and magic.

“Hehe- I was distracted for a moment, shame on me.”

“You will pay dearly for touching my daughter!”

The spear king Cervantes and the Archon Roderick also unleashed their sharp momentum.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwang!

A large number of people united to attack Amdusias.

Even a land-based demon with a 1:1 strength ratio would be no match for such a large number.

Especially after the destruction of the Hell Tree, his secret weapon.

[...!]

But Amdusias did not give up.

Despite the nineteen piercing holes in his body, he stood up on all fours.

He raised his broken horn and pointed it at Vikir.

[I cannot fail in my duty, and you must die here].

An uncanny amount of determination. It had a solidity that could never be matched by Vikir's.

Even when his body is torn apart and his soul torn to shreds, Amdusias rises.

Somehow, on all fours, on all four hooves, it stands tall.

...Kwakwang!

Amdusias begins to move.

Even in the midst of the cascading storm of auras, he was running straight for Vikir.

A demon ready to throw away his life. His final dive was one that even the power of the many gathered here could not prevent.

“Vikir! Get back!”

“Vikir! Dodge!”

Camus shouted, throwing a fireball at Amdusias' body.

Dolores shouted as well, imbuing Vikir's body with holy power.

But Vikir remained where he was.

“....”

He was merely looking for a momentary gap in Amdusias's strength.

[O-oooooo!]

Amdusias ran. It lunged. His crumbling body pushed forward, unafraid of death.

To eliminate the hated enemy in front of him, the variable that might be the greatest obstacle to his future endeavors.

But.

...Boom!

Something massive crashed down on Amdusias' head.

It was a metal object, heavy and solid enough to be indestructible even by Amdusias' charge.

[...A vault?]

Amdusias's charge was interrupted by the sudden appearance of a vault in the middle of the wall, dented by the impact.

The massive vault, made of adamantium and orharcone, was one that Amdusias was surely familiar with.

[This is Belial's...?]

Suddenly, something loomed in Amdusias's vision as he turned his head.

Damian. And the white-haired girl next to him.

Sinclaire stood there with an expressionless face.

Charak-

Sinclaire placed one hand on his hat and chanted an incantation.

The vault above Amdusias's head seemed to melt for a moment, then began to transform.

A rabbit with a pocket watch.

Looking like it was in a hurry to get somewhere, the rabbit struck Amdusias with a watch made of a mixture of adamantium and orharcone.

...Kwakwang!

Amdusias' legs snapped.

Above him, Camus black fireballs rained down with terrifying force.

[He-aaaaaghh!]

Amdusias screams.

The barrage of heroes pouring in from all over was gradually sinking Amdusias.

And then.

...Bam!

Vikir took a step toward Amdusias.

His hands glowed brightly with Dolores' blessing.

Vikir slowly stroked Beelzebub's sword.

A crimson aura blazed, and it stretched out to form a massive greatsword.

“Demon...”

With that, the tip of Vikir's sword exploded with layers and layers of aura.

Boom, boom, boom!

The sun rose and filled the sky above the Academy.

The giant Black Sun was the result of eight teeth snapping together to form a sphere.

It was the ultimate manifestation of Vikir's power after leaving the tower and reaching the 8th Form, mid-Swordmaster rank.

“Kill.”

No exceptions.

From the first blow, to the last. There was no room for second thoughts.

The demon must be struck down.

...Flash!

With a blinding burst of light, the Black Sun fell.

Woo-duddeuddeuk!

It sucked the slowly crumbling body of Amdusias into the center of the sphere, where it was swallowed up in an endless chain of crushing.

[...! ......! ...!]

An end without even a final word, let alone a will.

A Eternal Annihilation.

It was the end of Amdusias, the 'Unicorn of the Abyss', the 5th of the Ten Corpses.

Chapter 353

Outside the Tower (5)

◆

Could this be the end of the wooden horse that took down the impregnable castle in legend?

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

The giant horse's form slowly began to crumble.

From the tip of its broken horns to the tips of its hooves, it crumbled to ash and scattered, letting everyone know that there was an end to this long nightmare.

Amdusias of 5th Corpse. It was the moment when the 'Unicorn of the Abyss' was completely destroyed.

“...It, it's over!”

“The demon is dead!”

“The Hell Tree is collapsing!”

Excited exclamations came from all directions.

Parents reunited with children they thought were dead, children reunited with parents they thought they would never see again, teachers who had lost and gained disciples they loved, disciples who had returned to the arms of their revered teachers.

All of them shed tears of joy and cheered.

Their gazes fell upon the center of the crater, where the Hell Tree had disappeared.

The seven knights of the Baskerville Family stood there.

The Seven Chariots, who intervened on the battlefield at the crucial moment and led the last stand.

If it weren't for them, the crowd gathered at the Colosseo Academy would have suffered far more damage.

“Thank you, thank you, Baskerville! If it weren't for you...”

“I will never forget this favor for the rest of my life!”

“But why are the knights of Baskerville Family here?”

“Isn't the Ironblood Swordman Family an extremely closed family?”

“Surely that boy has summoned the knights, I saw him blow his whistle!”

The crowd began to roar.

Suddenly, all eyes were on one place.

The hero who had broken through the Abyss Tower.

The Swordmaster who had formed a pillar of aura that seemed to reach the heavens.

A freshman who once attended the Colosseo Academy.

...And the one who brought all the hounds of the Ironbloods swordman to this place.

Vikir. Vikir Van Baskerville!

Vikir unleashed all that he had been hiding.

And the seven hounds bowed respectfully before him.

“Your orders have been fulfilled.”

Osiris, the young patriarch of Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman, followed by Isabella, the leader of the Doberman, German, the leader of the Shepherd, Metzgerhund, the leader of the Rottweiler, Cu-Chulainn, the leader of the Wolfhound, Boston Terrier, the leader of the Pit Bull, and Great Dane, the leader of the Mastiff, all bowed their heads.

Everyone who saw it was shocked.

This is Baskerville, not the other families.

The men gathered here represent the entirety of Baskerville's power. Even the next patriarch, Osiris, is among them.

The sight of them all bowing their heads toward a nameless boy was more than shocking, it was unreal.

And then a few sharp-eyed tycoons spoke up.

“ ..., You mean Vikir Van Baskerville?”

“Underdog's Deputy Magistrate! A legend of the Baskerville family, even commended by the Emperor!”

“Huh, wasn't that a rumor? I thought he was a fictional character because of his outrageous exploits!”

“I was right, a golden statue with a face exactly like his stood at Morgue's Red Fang Castle!”

“You mean the hero who opened the way for peaceful trade between the Baskervilles and the barbarians was a real person, my God!”

“Are you sure you're not the same student who recovered the Wraith Tree in the second round of the University League?”

He wasn't the only one.

Several students emerged from the Hell Tree and began to praise the heroic deities Vikir had seen inside the tower.

“Dad, he's the reason I was able to escape from that pack of hellhounds!”

“He saved me from the daylilies! Oh, Vikir, my friend, how can I ever repay this favor!”

“Thank you for forgiving us, and what the hell is your vessel...! Damn it, you are a true hero!”

Everyone, aristocrats and barons and commoners alike, were looking at Vikir with respect, admiration, longing, and gratitude.

That's because he's always been at the forefront, making all the sacrifices.

No one noticed, of course, that it was all so he could reap the rewards within the tower.

“Mr. Vikir, look over here, I'm taking a mana screenshot!”

“I know you've done a great job solving this Hell Tree situation, what do you think...!”

“Is it true that you're the hidden power behind the Baskervilles!”

“Why have you been hiding your identity for all this time!?”

The reporters, realizing they had the scoop of the story, the jackpot, swarmed around Vikir like bees.

He didn't see them coming, and he wondered how they'd managed to gather in such large numbers.

“Husband! Aah! Get out of the way! I can't see him!”

“Van-nim, I'll just pass by for a moment-!”

Camus and Dolores tried to get closer to Vikir, but it was impossible to move forward because the crowd had swelled so much in an instant.

Meanwhile, their gazes met, and neither woman backed down an inch.

Meanwhile. Vikir's normally tight-knit group of friends shrugged.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca waved at Vikir.

Luckily, they'd been around him from the beginning, so it wasn't hard to get close.

“Vikir, you finally did it, you bastard! You can't pretend we don't know you're a superhero!”

“Great job, buddy! I didn't realize you were a descendant of the Baskervilles, by the way, keeping such a secret. I'll bet you're going to have a good night's drinking.”

“Aaahhhh! Vikir, I'm so glad you're okay! I'm most glad you're okay!”

“Whew. Anyway, he's a guy that makes me nervous.”

“....”

Sinclaire, who was standing in the back, was also walking towards them with a complicated expression.

....

But.

Vikir was just looking at all these situations calmly.

Unmoved, in fact, with a cold stare.

With his back to the cheering crowd, Vikir silently stretched his left hand to the ground.

He whispered in a low voice.

“Follow Aheul, and for now, we part ways.”

He spoke to the madam cub attached to his left wrist.

[Hack-hack-hack...]

The cub whined as if it didn't want to go, but at Vikir's urging, it jumped to the ground.

Sasasak.

The madam cub crawled after Aheul as they faded into a distant dot.

Looking back a few times.

“....”

Then, once the madam cub was completely out of sight, Vikir turned to face the crowd.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca came to his side.

“Now, reporters, please be respectful, our Vikir is tired! Now, I know you're excited to meet the superhero of the century~”

“Vikir. Are you feeling okay? You seemed to be giving off all your aura earlier, I wonder if you need some pills or potions.”

“Don't you think you're doing too many interviews? Maybe you should rest first...”

“Ugh, where did all these reporters come from? I didn't even see them during the battle. What should I tell my dad to do to get them to leave?”

A tribute to a friend who crossed countless lines of fire and accomplished a great task that no one thought possible.

It showed in their demeanor.

...But.

Vikir's response to this pure and unconditional favor from his friends was short.

“Get lost.”

The words froze his friends in their tracks.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca tilted their heads as if they had misheard.

“Huh? Vikir, who were you talking to?”

“Who else?”

“Whoa! Who's bothering Vikir!”

“You should tell your professors first, so they can bite some reporters...”

Then Vikir spoke up again, this time more sharply.

“I told you to fuck off. Scum.”

At this point, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca realized something.

That Vikir was now glaring at them with the eyes of an enemy.

“Hey, hey, hey... what's the matter with you, why are you suddenly so...?”

“Ugh. Did you think we were trying to take your honor? You're wrong. We had no such intention...”

“Oh, that's right, Vikir! I was just purely worried about you...”

“Did you hit your head somewhere? What's wrong with you all of a sudden?”

His friends reacted to his unexpected attitude with confusion.

But Vikir cut them off.

“I don't have weaklings like you as friends. Know your fractions and get your heads out of your asses.”

Ending symbol.

It was the line that cut off all the bonds, ties, and relationships.

Shock. A major shock. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca froze in their seats, mouths half open.

Tudor was the first to come to his senses, stammering with a pained expression.

“What? What's wrong, Vikir? Is it because you made the order in the last stage? Ha, but at that time neither of us had order...”

But Tudor didn't finish his sentence.

Vikir pushed him in the chest and walked to the center of the crowd.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca felt an unbridgeable line in Vikir's gaze as he stared down at them like bugs.

A line drawn in stone. A distance that could never be closed.

Tudor sprawled on the floor, unable to speak a word, and Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca beside him.

They weren't the only ones who didn't feel comfortable with Vikir's cold gaze.

Camus, Dolores, Sinclaire, and everyone else whose lives had been saved by Vikir in the tower froze in place.

Vikir had drawn a line in the sand with everyone he'd ever met and befriended at Colosseo Academy.

No, everyone he had ever made a connection with.

He stepped up to the front of the crowd of reporters and said.

“I am ....”

It was so unexpected that few people in the front row understood what Vikir was saying.

As the reporters in the back of the room furrowed their brows and pricked up their ears, Vikir pulled something out of his pocket instead of answering.

And.

...!

Everyone who saw what came out of Vikir's arms had to take a step back in horror.

A crimson sword. Inverted pentagram necklace. And the plague doctor mask.

What these symbols meant was all too obvious.

As the room fell silent for a moment, Vikir spoke in a low, but clear voice.

“I am Night Hound.”

Chapter 356

Crime and Punishment (3)

◆

Even the most notorious prison in the Imperial Capital seemed unable to handle the notoriety of Night Hound.

Ahead of his transfer to Nouvelle Vague, the most remote and worst prison on the continent, Vikir was temporarily housed in a holding facility on the Imperial Capital.

“Tomorrow at dawn.”

Vikir closed his eyes, remembering his journey to Nouvelle Vague.

3,021 life sentences and imprisonment in Nouvelle Vague.

A sentence that would be executed just six hours after the verdict.

“ ...I'm glad I escaped the death penalty, but Hugo's plea was a surprise.”

After analyzing numerous precedents, he was confident that a summary execution would not be granted.

However, even if an unusual result occurred and he was summarily executed, there were several secret plans in place.

“It's going well.”

Vikir accepted the verdict without complaint.

This verdict, too, was part of the original plan.

There were some variables, but it was well within the margin of error he'd anticipated.

Then.

-Execute the criminal! Execute the criminal!

-Execute him!

-Burn him!

-Apologize! Apologize!

Small noises came from beyond the bars and walls.

Apparently, the protesters had gathered and were causing a ruckus.

The anger and grief of those who had lost family, friends, and lovers to Night Hound was immense.

They had been protesting outside nonstop since the verdict was handed down.

[...Isn't that sad?]

Decarabia asked suddenly.

Decarabia had shrunk in size to a tiny dot, wedged between Vikir's collarbones.

That's why it was impossible to detect it during the pre-incarceration search of his belongings.

[Everything you did was for the good of humanity, and if it weren't for you, the gates would have been opened and countless people would have died, and those who died were unforgivable when they made their pact with the demon in the first place, so they should be thanking you instead].

Decarabia rolls its one eye, wondering if it's more embarrassing.

Vikir, however, has not lost his dignified demeanor.

“There is no way for them to know that the dead are all beings who have made a contract with the demon and will commit great sins against all mankind in the future. Even if I tell them, they won't believe me.”

Humans are animals that don't believe in anything unless they see it with their own eyes.

Even if Vikir explained it, it wouldn't work, and he wasn't sure he could convince all those people in the first place.

“So it would be easier for me to be the one to kill.”

[Human. Do you dream of being a hero or a saint?]

“No. I just want to save as many people as I can.”

He's not interested in concepts like absolutes.

There is no desire to make a noble sacrifice for the sake of humanity as a whole.

He just wants to hold on to the few warmths that made his previous life bearable, and the precious connections he's made in this one.

So Vikir spent some time in silent meditation with his eyes closed.

Feeling the cold sensation of the restraints around his wrists and ankles.

'...And these restraints?'

Vikir ran his fingers over the cuffs on his wrists, the shackles on his ankles, and the chains that connected them.

Cold metal, but unusually heavy and solid.

Not only were they more frightening and harder than any other metal of the same volume and mass, but they even had the ability to drain and neutralize the restraints' mana.

Vikir was suddenly intrigued by this restraint.

'Let's study it a bit, maybe it'll give me some interesting variables.'

Just as Vikir was fiddling with the restraints.

Kkiig-

The door to the dungeon opened and a guard's voice came through.

“Visitation.”

Prisoners on death row, or those being transferred to Nouvelle Vague, are only allowed three visits.

But Vikir had already turned down one request from the Baskervilles and two from students at the Colosseo Academy.

The guards thought that Vikir would deny them another visit and tried to close the door.

But.

“Let them in.”

Vikir accepted the third visitation request.

The guard looked a little surprised and turned around.

Soon, the visitors began to descend toward the dungeon's grate.

Four men in black hoods and robes.

They walked up to Vikir and removed their hoods to reveal their bare faces.

“Hello, it's been a while.”

The first to speak was Cindywendy.

She was followed by a worried-looking Chihuahua, MiniPin, and finally Aheul.

“Young Master, what's going on, oh my God!”

“Boss, Your face has become half-faced!”

“...Hunting leader.”

They were all currently using Baskerville's last name.

That was because Vikir had appointed them as his aides upon his promotion to Senator within the family.

“Unexpected.”

Vikir stared at Cindywendy's face in front of him.

“I thought you wouldn't take the surname Baskerville.”

She shrugged.

“Well, I'm getting older, and I think I need to lean on something, because sometimes I get too tired.”

“You don't lean on a sword when you're tired. Alliances are only temporary. Wasn't your ultimate goal to get revenge on the Baskervilles?”

“Yes, but I've decided to think a little differently.”

Cindywendy smiled and raised her left hand.

Sparkle-.

Surprisingly, a small ring was shining on the ring finger of her left hand.

It was obviously a wedding ring, a token of love, or a pledge of love between lovers.

“If I become the mistress of the Baskervilles, wouldn't that also be revenge in some sense? It's like swallowing up the Baskervilles from the inside.”

“...?”

For a moment, Vikir's eyes, which had never wavered, twitched slightly.

Suddenly, a line from Hugo that he'd heard many years ago popped into his head.

'I think Osiris has a girlfriend, but she's never stepped on his tail, and when I ask, he never answers.'

Hugo had said this to Vikir when he visited Baskerville for the second round of the University League.

Vikir was surprised.

Before his regression, Osiris had been an emotionless killer doll, and now he was dating a woman.

Vikir had thought that Hugo and Osiris' demeanor had changed a bit since the arrival of Pomeranian.

But he never thought it would have this kind of butterfly effect.

'I don't know if this is good or bad.'

It was a difficult phenomenon to discern, even for the ever-understanding Vikir.

“...Since when?”

“Since I was brokering and supporting Baskerville's trade with the natives on the Western Front. I met him a few times on bodyguard duty. Well, we knew each other as children.”

As it turned out, it was Osiris who had gotten to the bottom of everything that had happened to Andromalius after the death of his host, Seth, and had cleaned up his mess.

After Vikir left for the Academy, Osiris cleared the name of the Messinadnaro family, which had been unfairly exterminated, and acknowledged the Baskerville family's responsibility for this.

'There were procedures for compensation for damage and appointment of personnel to oust old elders. Did you get hit in the eye during that time?'

Moreover, she was a childhood friend of his, so it's not surprising.

The encounter between Cindywendy and Osiris was big news, enough to make even the usually dull Vikir pick his butt up off the floor.

Meanwhile, Cindywendy said that her feelings were renewed.

“ ...I'm the opposite of what I was then.”

When they first met and talked to Cindywendy, she was in jail and Vikir was out of jail.

But now, Vikir is in prison and Cindywendy is out of prison.

Vikir's response to this is short.

“I expected it.”

Vikir turned his head.

Chihuahua, MiniPin, and Aheul were looking at him with concern.

But instead, Vikir was worried about those outside the cage.

“There are things you need to do.”

Vikir took Chihuahua, MiniPin, and Aheul aside and whispered something to them.

“ ...To stock up on food, ...to fortify the highlands, ...to move the human race, ...to the last fortress, ...Tochka.”

Each one had a slightly different keyword, but there were several common ones.

Finally, when it was Cindywendy's turn, Vikir rose from his seat and approached the grate.

Swoosh.

And then. The leather of Vikir's face suddenly peeled away.

A picaresque mask.

The strange mask, which merged with the user's flesh the moment it was overwritten, fell into Cindywendy's hands.

“Oh my God, why are you giving this to me?”

“It's not yours. Give it to Camus.”

An artifact left behind by Dantalian upon his death. Imbued with demonic power.

A mask that Vikir has worn on countless hunts of demons and their followers, a symbol of Night Hound.

“I'm sure she'll understand what I mean.”

Camus is accompanied by Seere. So surely she will understand what it means to be handed this mask.

After being handed the picaresque mask, Cindywendy shook her head in disgust.

“I wonder how much that tomboy will turn the world upside down again... The entire Morgue family was turned upside down during the Wraith Tree.”

“The world will turn upside down naturally.”

“...?”

Vikir's face fell at Cindywendy's rhetorical comment.

Cindywendy, Chihuahua, MiniPin, and Aheul all looked at Vikir with wide eyes.

Vikir then addressed them all.

“There will be a great flood soon.”

It was the first code of conduct for survival in the age of destruction.

The only way to save humanity.

“Prepare the ark.”

Those were Vikir's last words to his henchmen.

Chapter 359

Voluntary Escort (3)

◆

[Our masters are Donquixote Passamonte, Usher Madeline, and Hobbes Leviathan!]

[Their real names are Cimeries! Andrealphus! Flauros!]

[Well, anything! I'll tell you anything! Please stop! What more do you want to know!?]

Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas shouted at the top of their lungs.

Their desperate cries sent chills down the spine of anyone who heard them, but Vikir's face remained unmoved.

“I don't want to know anything. I'm just having fun.”

With his grotesquely twisted iron, Vikir slowly carved away at the bodies of Pedro, Isolde, and Thomas.

And with each stroke, they wailed miserably.

[Aaahhhhhh! Just kill me!]

Vikir's torture techniques, which could make even demons cry and beg, were an advanced artifact learned in the Age of Destruction.

“....”

“....”

“....”

“....”

Naturally, it was far beyond the reach of any modern-day Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, or Lovebad.

Even Mozgus, the Inquisitor, was speechless at Vikir's torture methods and skills.

Soon, Vikir washed away the black blood that had splattered on his face from the foam that crashed into the player.

Tsk.

The disgusting flavor of the demon's blood washed away in the cool waters.

'That was good.'

He said it, but of course he wasn't just torturing himself to relieve stress.

Pedro, Isolde, and Tomas are the entourage of the Ten, and naturally have a lot of information to share.

And Vikir had gotten most of what he wanted from them through his brutal torture techniques.

The information the demons spilled will surely prove valuable in the future.

...Bam!

Vikir tossed the three mangled minions onto the deck.

“Salt them and put them in the fishbowl. I don't want them to die, so feed them every week or so. A few drops of human blood mixed with liquor will suffice.”

Clear orders.

But none of the men on the deck complained.

“....”

“....”

“....”

“....”

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad were in a cold sweat.

A prisoner destined for Nouvelle Vague had escaped, in the midst of a convoy for transfer.

It was an event that would turn the entire Empire upside down.

Even a demon showed up in the middle of it, so the aftermath is hard to imagine.

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad are the main characters in this story, and their feelings are understandably mixed.

Isabella asked in a small voice.

“...Where are we going now?”

Now that Night Hound has been freed from his restraints and cage, the answer is obvious.

It would flee to a faraway place where it could never be caught.

...The problem was how to get away.

On land, that would be one thing, but here, on the sea, he would need a ship to get away.

If Vikir, who is clearly the Swordmaster, is determined to take the ship, the situation becomes bleak.

No matter how much she thought about it, she was no match for the sunlike aura Vikir had displayed earlier when he subdued the three demons.

Even if he were outnumbered, it would be pointless; everyone on board would have to risk their lives.

...But Vikir's answer was unexpected.

“That's not a question for a convoy leader.”

“...?”

“To prison, of course. To the Nouvelle Vague.”

With that, Vikir turned and walked nonchalantly back to the cage he had just broken through and sat down.

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad couldn't help but gape at the sight of him.

Isabella asked, puzzled.

“Didn't you mean to steal this ship and run away?”

“Of course not, we have no intention of causing trouble for others.”

Vikir's answer was both common sense and nonsensical.

The situation was taking an unexpected turn.

◆

Vikir was true to his word.

He waited until Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad's mana was fully restored, and then he let the ship reach its destination.

And so the ship made it through the raging storm and waves to the coordinates they had initially set out for.

Kuoooooooo...

Maelstr?m. A giant whirlpool, called the “navel of the sea,” was gaping open.

At the tip of the bow, you can see the color of the sea turning black.

This is because the water is deepening rapidly.

...Kung!

The ship finally stopped after setting dozens of anchors on the surrounding reefs.

“It's a whirlpool that only opens at midnight. This is the middle gate to Nouvelle Vague.”

Vikir nodded at Isabella's words.

The Nouvelle Vague, the Great Prison of the Deep, is a long way down this vortex.

Naturally, prisoners are thrown here alone to sink.

During the 10,000-meter descent to the depths of the Nouvelle Vague, most prisoners are crushed to death by the pressure and claustrophobia, and only a few survive to be imprisoned in the Nouvelle Vague.

Vikir obediently stepped into the coffin attached to the tip of the boat.

Iron Maiden.

A human-shaped coffin embossed with the face of a gentle, smiling woman with closed eyes.

This fearsome coffin is riddled with nails made of an orthoharcone alloy that, when the prisoner is placed inside and the lid is closed, punctures the prisoner's body with numerous holes.

The nails are placed to avoid the prisoner's vital organs and are designed to maximize pain.

The blood that fills the coffin then flows out through the cracks in the maiden's eyes, creating the illusion that the maiden is weeping tears of blood over the prisoner's death.

Kugugugugukuk...

Vikir walked into the coffin, wearing the new BDISSEM handcuffs, shackles, and chains.

He turned to Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad, who were standing outside.

“Would you mind closing the door?”

His calm tone was out of character and extremely out of place.

Isabella, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad had to shudder at the chills that ran down their spines, even though they had been in charge of countless convoys.

Then.

Professor Banshee, the Morgue's escort, stepped forward.

“...Vikir-kun.”

“Something.”

Banshee flinched slightly at the nonchalant tone of Vikir's voice.

But then he gathered his courage and spoke up.

“I am a professor at Colosseo Academy, and you are a student at Colosseo Academy.”

“....”

“No matter what your current situation is, no matter what your identity is, you are my student.”

Banshee took a deep breath.

He took a deep breath and spoke in the same snarky, stubborn tone he had come to expect from the Colosseo Academy.

“I speak not as an escort, not as an official, but as your teacher.”

The words that came out of the Banshee's mouth surprised everyone. Even Vikir.

“Run away.”

Isabella, Mozgus, and Lovebad look back at Banshee in surprise.

But Banshee's demeanor didn't change.

“Honestly, I'm still not good at judging good and evil. I'm not sure what the demon or the Hell Tree is. I never imagined that I would experience such confusion at an age when everything is slowly becoming clear, but... Still, I always saw you during my time at the Academy. You are not a villain. That much is certain.”

“....”

“The Nouvelle Vague is a living hell. Those who enter never return, and I cannot send a good and brave young man to such a place.”

At that moment, someone stepped forward, glaring at Banshee.

It was Mozgus, a member of the Quovadis family convoy.

“I, too, have heard the whole story from St. Dolores.”

“....”

“To be honest, I didn't fully believe her when she told me that you were a demon hunter. As a cleric, I couldn't believe that so many demons were integrated into the human world. But now that I've seen the realities of the demons that have slipped right under my nose, I see it all clearly. You must live, and I don't know why I've only realized this now!”

Mozgus slammed his fist down on his head in self-pity.

Beside him, Lovebad, a member of the Bourgeois family convoy, stepped forward.

“Do you remember my second cousin? Merelini Lovegood? She fell in love with you in the University Leagues, and now she's stoping to eat and drink after learning that you're Night Hound and are to be imprisoned in Nouvelle Vague.”

“....”

“As soon as I return, I will show the demons as evidence and request a retrial. So please run away from here. And although it may be difficult while on the run, I would really appreciate it if you could meet my brother secretly. I will take responsibility and erase your tracks. If it's money, don't worry.”

Banshee of Morgue, Mozgus of Quovadis, and Lovebad of Bourgeois have made their shocking declarations of defection.

All that remained was Isabella of Baskerville.

“....”

After a moment of silence, she looked up.

The dreary gaze was spreading red in the air.

“...Truth be told. I've been assigned one other task in addition to the Imperial convoy.”

Isabella's next words were a surprise.

“The orders came from the Baskervilles in great secrecy. To kill everyone on the convoy and break you out.”

At that, Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad swallowed hard.

They had wondered why a magnate of the Seven Counts' rank had bothered to come to them, especially one who had retired from the Imperial Prison Service, but now they knew.

Isabella even had a dozen of the Doberman Knights' core strength disguised as lowly sailors waiting in the dock.

“I have instructions from my lord to break you out, Vikir, even if it means sinking the ship.”

In other words, the Baskervilles were going to keep Vikir, even if it meant turning the other six families of the empire and the imperial family against them.

Banshee, Mozgus, and Lovebad muttered in disbelief.

“I almost got killed by accident.”

“For some reason, there was a reason I wasn't too embarrassed by the appearance of the demons.”

“Damn, it's Baskerville again, those crazy people.”

Vikir said, sounding surprised as well.

“Didn't you tell me before that it would be better to commit suicide?”

“That was in the public eye. You're not really a great person to commit suicide in the first place.”

Everyone, including Isabella, was urging Vikir to run away.

The gale had driven all the sailors back to the dock.

The minions are all salted and locked in the hold, so the only ones who can see the last of Vikir are the four escorts here.

If all four of them are correct in their testimony, Vikir will be able to return to the surface without being trapped in Nouvelle Vague.

But.

“I refuse.”

Vikir dismissed the invitation to run away so casually, so matter-of-factly.

Banshee asked in disbelief.

“Do you not know what the Nouvelle Vague is like? To be trapped there is worse than death!”

Isabella, Mozgus, and Lovebad shake their heads in disbelief.

But Vikir's voice was still unmoved.

“I could have done anything to escape. What do you think I was tried for?”

Nouvelle Vague. And Vikir, who silently accepted more than 3,000 life sentences.

He smiles dryly at his escort, who seem unable to comprehend the situation.

“I am a person who has been waiting to go to Nouvelle Vague for the past 19 years.”

Chapter 361

Ghost Castle of the Ultra-Deep Sea (1)

◆

It is the coldest, hottest, roughest, foulest, and harshest place in the world.

God cut it off from the rest of the world, separating it from the sunlight forever.

It is a hell that no one can imagine.

No words or illustrations can fully convey the horrors of Nouvelle Vague, and its unique and grotesque atmosphere can only be felt by breathing its air.

People of the world, please do not sin. If you have already committed it, find a way to repent as soon as possible.

For Nouvelle Vague, the Great Prison of the Deep, awaits you at the bottom of the abyss of unknown depths with its mouth open!

◆

At the bottom of a deep, deep trench in the ultra-deep sea.

A castle rises high above a thick forest of black seaweed.

A yellowish-blue light glows eerily like the luminescence of a deep-sea fish on the peak of an extinct volcano.

It was the very nature of the Nouvelle Vague, a dilapidated old castle made of giant cube-shaped bricks stacked on top of each other.

...Teoeong! Kung!

The coffin containing Vikir was dropped onto the very top of the main castle, onto a huge circular iron gate.

A ghost castle of the Ultra Deep Sea, Its interior is dug deep into the social mountain.

Vikir surveyed the landscape outside through the eyes of Decarabia.

'...This is the Gate of Good and Evil.'

The huge circular iron gate was tens of meters in diameter.

The material seemed to be an alloy of adamantium and orthoharcon, like the vaults of the Bourgeois he had seen before, and he dared not imagine its thickness and weight.

White on the left, black on the right. There is only one meaning to this antithetical placement of colors.

'The Gate of Good and Evil'. The final boundary between good and evil.

It was the main gate and symbol of the Nouvelle Vague.

And now.

Rl-gigigigigi!

The door slowly began to rotate 180 degrees.

Like the lid of a manhole, the open door slowly flipped up and down, sucking the coffin containing Vikir into the castle's interior along with the seawater.

Beneath the gates of good and evil, an unidentifiable sticky, mucousy membrane could be seen, which appeared to be blocking the influx of seawater.

The windows throughout the castle were also covered with the same clear slime.

Kwakwang! ...cheolsseog!

The coffin containing Vikir fell to the hard ground with a heavy splash.

By this time, the coffin had been molded to Vikir's size like a suit of iron.

Next, Vikir felt sinister hands twist the lid open.

“....We have arrived.”

Vikir stuck his head out as soon as the coffin lid opened.

The interior of the Nouvelle Vague's true nature came into view.

The floors, walls, and ceiling are pitch-black. The atmosphere was cold, dank, and dreary, as befits a castle built in the depths of the sea.

Guards in black uniforms peeked out from under the brims of their hats.

“...'Night Hound'. Is this the last resident?”

He heard the burly guard in front of him mutter.

He had a large burn scar on his face and a nameplate on his chest that read 'Garam Nord'.

His rank appeared to be Lieutenant, judging by the single diamond on his shoulder epaulettes.

'Lieutenant Garam Nord', he said, looking down at Vikir.

“The entrance ceremony will be held shortly. Make sure you're ready when it does.”

At those words, Vikir looked up.

Sure enough, there were several more prisoners gathered in the waiting room in front of him.

They were all dressed in black and white striped prison uniforms, with BDISSEM shackles on their wrists and ankles.

Then, in front of Vikir and the others who had changed into their uniforms, Lieutenant Garam spoke.

“I'm going to give you all a brief introduction to the system here, as I'm sure you already know.”

Nouvelle Vague looks like a castle atop an extinct volcano, but its interior is actually much more expansive.

A huge, vertical underground chamber carved out of the base of the volcano.

“It's divided into nine parts.”

Lieutenant Garam prefaced his explanation with a simple drawing.

The 1st floor. Aka 'Level 1'.

This is where the guards live and where all events, except executions, are held, such as entrance ceremonies and promotions.

It is also a space where criminals with the lowest sentences, those with sentences of three years or less, are imprisoned.

The 2nd floor. Aka 'Level 2'.

This is where prisoners with sentences of 5 years or less are held.

One year in Nouvelle Vague is equivalent to 10 years in any other prison on earth, so in a normal prison, prisoners who would have been sentenced to at least 30 years and no more than 50 years in prison would be held here.

The 3rd floor. Aka “Level 3”.

This is where criminals with a sentence of 10 years or less are held.

In a normal prison on the ground, this is where felons would be sentenced to 100 years in prison.

The 4th floor. Aka 'Level 4'.

This is where criminals with sentences of 15 years or less are held.

You won't find any common criminals on this level.

War criminals and other heinous criminals involved in at least city-scale terrorism and genocide are locked up here.

The 5th floor. Aka 'Level 5'.

Criminals with sentences of 20 years or less are held here.

This is where those who have caused great damage to the country through state terrorism, civil unrest, or conspiracy are held.

It is also a place where the quarters of high-ranking officials at the guard level are located, and several special facilities such as a 'breeding house' and an 'execution house' are also located there.

The 6th floor. Aka 'Level 6'.

This is where criminals sentenced to life imprisonment in Nouvelle Vague are held.

The purpose of this level is to keep dangerous people who could overthrow the state away from the world forever, and prisoners here are treated more like monsters than human beings.

The 7th floor. Aka 'Level 7'.

Even the same life sentence is divided into grades and weights.

Under Imperial law, a judge may impose multiple life sentences if it is deemed that a mere sentence of life imprisonment is not enough to absolve the offense, and this level contains prisoners who have served at least 100 life sentences.

The 8th floor. Aka 'Level 8'.

Prisoners with 1,000 or fewer life sentences are held here.

The 9th floor. Aka 'Level 9'.

....

Lieutenant Garam finished his explanation, tapping the picture with the three-stage baton he wore around his waist.

The prisoners about to be admitted giggled and murmured among themselves.

“I was sentenced to eight years in this place, this is awful.”

“Shit, I got a 13-year sentence, this means that if you live on earth, you will have to rot in bread for 130 years! I'd rather serve my sentence here short and sweet.”

“Tsk tsk tsk... I'm a life sentence. Fuck, you want me to live in this shitty place for the rest of my life?”

“They are young chicks, you do realize that life imprisonment has a count, right? I've served three life sentences.”

The prisoners were engaged in a nerve-wracking battle, matching each other's strength and brutality.

One in particular drew all the attention.

He was huge, with black spots covering his body, and facial features like a demon.

There was no one among them who did not know him.

'Sakkuth De Leviathan'. His earthly nickname was 'Plague Leper'.

An extremely evil criminal who was expelled from the Leviathan family for his outrageous human experimentation, the bounty on his head once reaching 11 figures.

He grinned, baring sharp teeth.

“Have you ever heard of a plague called the Red Death, child? It was created by this very body.”

Recognized as a danger by the Empire, Sakkuth was sentenced to life imprisonment, 666 times over, and imprisoned here in Nouvelle Vague.

He now resides on Level 1 to wait for the news of admission, but he is not the person who was originally supposed to be here.

When he opens his mouth to speak, the mouths of the prisoners around him shut in unison.

As if enjoying the heavy silence, Sakkuth continued.

“We even completed clinical trials on the indigenous people of the jungle. Out of nowhere, Quovadis intervened and messed things up. Ugh... It's a shame. It was an opportunity to see the pandemic, an infectious disease spreading at an all-time high. Uhuk-uhuk-uhuk.”

Clean. There was one more unique thing about him besides his appearance and biography.

He'd come in as a self-declared prisoner.

“Grrrr! I came here of my own volition to meet 'Him', So, we are on a different level from minnows like you who were forcibly brought in.”

Sakkuth was ignoring not only the prisoners who were to share in the ceremony, but even the guards.

However, the momentum he was giving off was so vicious that not one of the guards came forward.

They kept their distance for fear of the plague he might carry.

Meanwhile.

Lieutenant Garam was briefly explaining the procedures for the upcoming entrance ceremony.

“There will be a total of three steps in the process. First, an inspection of belongings. Second, a medical examination. Third, bathing.”

The prisoners looked surprised.

“We don't need to be searched or have our weapons removed, do we? We can't bring them here in the first place.”

“They're going to do a physical and then a health check? That's like a medical service, not a prison welfare center.”

“They also disinfect and bathe you! Haha, the Nouvelle Vague is more comfortable than I thought.”

“Ugh, I can't wait to get cleaned up, the saltiness of the sea water made me sticky all the way here!”

Contrary to the rumors, the Nouvelle Vague was quite comfortable.

The prisoners seemed to be relaxing into the idea that the news that would soon follow would be no big deal.

...But.

'It's begun.'

Vikir knew.

The entrance ceremony mentioned here does not really mean simply the entrance ceremony.

And how terrifying this series of events, wrapped up in ordinary words like 'belongings check', 'medical examination', and 'bathing', was.

Chapter 362

Ghost Castle of the Ultra-Deep Sea (2)

◆

#1st entrance ceremony:<Belongings inspection>

The induction ceremony consists of three procedures.

Until it started, the prisoners didn't realize the seriousness of the situation.

The belongings inspection was a matter of course, and the second and third health checks and baths were unexpected luxuries.

As a result, the prisoners were generally happy.

“What kind of an idiot would bring a weapon into a place like this?”

“I'm not hiding anything, so I'll be fine.”

“Oh, I just want to take a bath.”

But Vikir didn't believe a word of what was written in the protocol.

'For those who were dragged to the Nouvelle Vague, they are naive.'

The prisoners do not lose their smiles even as they are dragged away tied up in rows next to them. How long can their expressions be maintained?

Soon, the prisoners, including Vikir, were led by the guards out into the open square.

Only then did their faces change.

“...?”

“What, you said you were going to check our belongings?”

“Then why are you taking us to this cliff...?”

The scene in front of them was quite a sight.

Sheer cliffs. And then, far off in the distance, almost a dot, another cliff.

And sharply sharpened blades were connected between cliffs.

...And there was more.

On top of the giant blade bridge connecting cliff to cliff, giant iron balls that could have been used for demolition in a construction site were swinging from side to side like clockwork.

“What the hell is this? You don't want me to cross this, do you?”

“We're on a ridge!”

“What are those iron balls!”

The prisoners' faces turned white at the horrific sight before them.

'I see.'

Vikir nodded.

The Nouvelle Vague's word of mouth is no ordinary thing.

It would be disguised in everyday words, but the reality would be horrific and brutal.

...Just like right now.

Sereung-

Finally, the guards showed their true colors.

They stabbed the prisoners in the back with knives, clubs, spears, and tridents.

They were going to kill them if they didn't get on the blade bridge.

In the end, the prisoners cried and put their feet on the blade.

They had to walk barefoot over hundreds of meters of blades.

If they lost their balance for even a moment, they would fall to the bottom of an unknown cliff.

One of the prisoners shakily asked.

“What happens if I fall off that cliff?”

“...I'll leave it to your imagination.”

Lieutenant Garam, who was leading the prisoners, replied in a bureaucratic tone.

Next, the prisoners stood in a line and began to walk on the sharp blade.

The razor-sharp blades dug into their bare feet with each step.

Each cut would be deeper and deeper under the weight of their bodies.

The cold blade cut and cut at the soles of the prisoners' feet.

“Kkeuaaaagh!”

The prisoner, who was spewing out blood and falling to his knees, fell straight in front of the blade and his entire body was broken into pieces.

Hududug- hududug- hududug-

Red blood and flesh rained down.

Seeing the prisoner in front of them fall to his death in an instant, the other prisoners became even more nervous and stood on their toes.

They strained their big and little toes, holding on to the blade with their toes and walking slowly.

That was how the prisoners were able to move.

..., But it was really just a way to get around.

Buung-

A giant iron ball passed in front of the prisoner's eyes.

The balls traveled across the bridge in sections, each with a tremendous amount of weight and speed.

If you were hit even once, your entire body would be crushed like fish meat and you would be thrown off the cliff.

“Haha- idiots, there's no way we're going to get hit by these balls!”

A prisoner was crawling like a cockroach, holding onto the blade with both hands and feet.

His hands and feet were already covered in blood, but he was still crawling quite steadily on his legs.

The giant iron ball was passing over his head, so he was in no danger.

...At first glance, that was the case.

But there was something the prisoner didn't realize, and that was the ball's material.

Buung-

The iron ball flew by and then came back.

As it approached, the prisoner ducked his head.

The idea was to let it pass safely over his head.

But.

“...Huh?”

The prisoner suddenly felt his right hand fly up of its own accord.

Snap!

His right hand was suddenly snatched out of thin air and caught on the swinging iron ball.

“Hii!? Magnet!”

That's right. Each of the iron balls passing over the blade bridge had a powerful magnetic force.

The prisoner, whose fingers were embedded with iron cores, felt his right hand being held in place by a powerful magnet.

And then.

...Ppuug! Udeudeug!

The prisoner saw the iron core in his finger tear through the flesh, pull out, and attach itself to the iron ball.

“Aaaah!”

The prisoner screamed as his fingers were ripped from his body and he lost his balance.

The toes and fingers that had been gripping the blade's legs gave way, and he fell backwards onto the blade, splitting his body vertically and sending him falling down the cliff.

Similar things were happening one after another on the blade bridge.

The swinging iron ball sucked everything in.

Poof!

A prisoner with a file knife hidden in his anus was torn apart in a horrific mauling.

Another prisoner, with shards of the blade embedded in old wounds, fell to the ground beneath the blade's bridge, grievously wounded.

The same was generally true of those who wore prosthetic arms or legs.

There were also quite a few prisoners who had fallen off the cliff in agony as the iron ball, with its powerful magnetic force, snapped like a rope with each swing.

Those who hadn't yet made it onto the bridge could only shudder in terror.

“What the hell, what is this, what is the word of mouth, this is just a dog's death, isn't it a de facto execution?”

Lieutenant Garam next to him shook his head.

“No, it's not. There's a 'Nouvelle Vague' execution, and it's a lot worse than this, and there's a prisoner over there who's doing just fine.”

“...What?”

At those words, all the prisoners turned their heads.

The blade bridge, precarious, and the magnetic iron balls running over it.

In the middle of it all, there was a man walking casually.

It was Vikir.

'It's a good thing Beelzebub and Decarabia didn't get caught in the magnets.'

Vikir was simply walking barefoot on the ridge.

His calluses, hardened by years of training, could push back a blade of this size without the need for mana.

It wasn't too difficult to make it to the other cliff, as long as he kept out of the way of the occasional iron ball.

“...What's that monster?”

“Yay! I'm going too!”

“Even a little kid like that is going, so you can't be scared!”

The other prisoners were also encouraged by Vikir's propaganda and started to ride the small bridge.

#2nd entrance ceremony:<Medical Examination>

After the first round of checking their belongings, the number of candidates had decreased.

However, they were not wiped out as they had traveled to the deep sea.

However, there were quite a few people whose bodies were covered in bruises and blood.

“Okay, next up is the medical examination.”

Lieutenant Garam opened his mouth, but none of the prisoners now believed him.

And sure enough, the prisoners were trapped like lab mice in a narrow valley.

“What the hell are we supposed to do here?”

“Huh? Uh-huh! Up there! Up there!”

“Something's falling!”

One by one, the prisoners looked up.

One by one, they looked up and saw something like black snow falling down.

Up close, they were spheres that looked like rubber balls, a little smaller than an adult fist and bouncy to the touch.

As soon as they hit the ground, they revealed themselves.

The rounded body stretched out to reveal an elongated oval shape.

The all-black body twitched, and sharp, nail-like teeth protruded from what appeared to be a head.

“Ew!? Leeches!”

Screams erupted from the prisoners.

Countless leeches were raining down on the prisoners' heads.

These tiny little vampires were clinging to the prisoners' bodies, sucking out whatever they could, and it didn't look like they were just drawing blood.

“Huh? This isn't blood....”

“It's bones, it's bones!”

“They suck skin, these bastards!”

Screams of horror erupted from among the prisoners.

What the leeches sucked varied.

Some leeches sucked blood, as they were supposed to, some sucked bones, and some sucked skin.

As the prisoners languished in the leech swamp, the guards scribbled on charts.

“Number 12, bone density normal...”

“Number 36, low blood volume, we're going to have to speed this up.”

“No. 43, skin condition good, no impairment to work.”

“Report to Lieutenant Colonel 'Black Tongue'.”

Health checks are what leeches are made of.

The fact that leeches are aggressively attacking means that there is no major problem with the prey's body.

Just like that.

Swiiiiig-

The leeches clinging to one of the prisoners suddenly became paralyzed and started screaming in pain.

“Kkeuleug! Kkeuleug! Kkeuleug!”

Sakkuth De Leviathan.

A wicked man whom even the poisonous Leviathan had banished for having a mental problem.

The leeches that clung to his body, sucking blood, bone, and skin, stiffened and fell away.

Perhaps the blood or marrow contained poison.

'...That's a lot of trouble.'

Vikir thought to himself as he stood quietly by the leeches, giving them what they had to give, and watched Sakkuth laugh nonchalantly in the distance.

'It's a good thing he's a troublemaker.'

If Vikir was careful, he might be able to use Sakkuth to his advantage.

#3rd entrance ceremony:<Bath>

The prisoners, who had crawled out of the leeches' swamp, lay exhausted on the floor.

Their bone density, muscle density, and blood reserves had decreased, and they were hanging on for dear life.

...The only thing left to do is to take a bath.

But none of the men had the look of anticipation on their faces.

The survivors were dragged into an empty, circular plaza, where they found something unpleasant.

It was a mass of skeletons.

The skeletal remains of human beings were rolling around, and upon closer inspection, there were many strange features.

“Are those little holes in the bones caved in?”

“Burned or melted.”

“What the hell... are they going to do again.”

The prisoners looked around anxiously.

And then, once again, a terrible surprise struck them.

Chwaaaaaag-

Boiling, yellowish groundwater burst from the ceiling.

The acrid smell seemed to contain a lot of sulfur.

“Kyaaghh!”

The prisoners scrambled to avoid the sulfur raining down from above.

But the bubbling sulfur soaked everywhere, fairly evenly.

Pushishishisik-

With tiny holes piercing all over his body, the prisoner finally collapsed to the ground.

The prisoners, who had been lying around a moment before, quickly rush over and crawl under the dead man's body.

This was to avoid a shower of sulfur.

“Hey, give me my umbrella!”

“Shut up! He's been my friend since we were on earth!”

“Give it to me! It's mine!”

The prisoners fiercely argued with each other, tearing at the dead prisoner's body.

In the meantime, the dead prisoner's body was torn apart and turned into countless umbrellas.

Finally, the hours-long shower of sulfurous water ended.

Through the thick cloud of stale steam, gas masked guards entered the room.

Lieutenant Garam Nord looked around and nodded.

“All prisoners are disinfected, we will proceed with floor assignments now.”

Chapter 367

The Servant (1)

◆

Vikir lifted his head and looked over the cliff.

A large man with black skin and searing golden eyes.

D'Ordume D D'Orcdile.

Colonel by rank. One of the five wardens of Nouvelle Vague, and with the exception of Warden Orca, there is virtually no one higher than him.

“A riot?”

Colonel D'Ordume's voice was like a slow boil from a low temperature.

Lieutenant-Colonel Bastille, below him, answered hastily.

“Yes! One of the inmates of Level Nine refused to do his labor and injured the guards! We were just about to subdue him!”

“...Hmm.”

D'Ordume's gaze shifted to Vikir.

Suddenly, Vikir felt as if countless axe blades hanging from chains were stabbing at his entire body.

'This is dangerous.'

His reflexes, maxed out in the Hell Tree, alerted him to the danger by making every hair on his body stand on end.

It was a sensation he hadn't felt in quite some time.

Vikir was willing to trust the warnings of his instincts, and he immediately stomped the ground and stepped back.

Kwakwakwak!

The ground where Vikir had stood just moments before exploded with a loud crack.

D'Ordume had fallen there.

A slight earthquake occurred when a large figure measuring 298cm tall and weighing 220kg fell.

D'Ordume landed with one hand on the ground and slowly pulled himself up to face Vikir.

D'Ordume's yellow-blazing eyes emitted a strange glow beyond the searing sulfur fire.

He wore metal gauntlets and a bandana on his forearms, from which sprouted axe blades in a swirling, twisting spiral pattern.

Kiiiiiiing-

With that, an aura appeared on D'Ordume's axe blade.

It began to spin at high speed, following the swirling lines of the blade.

It was as if he was wrapping a vortex of blades around the forearms of both hands.

'...As expected, he uses an unusual weapon.'

Vikir nodded, remembering a time before the regression.

Among the heroes who once roamed the battlefields of the Frontier, there were two who were rumored to have unusual methods of attack: Mozgus, Archbishop of Quovadis Family, and D'Ordume, a Warden from Nouvelle Vague.

Mozgus's attack consisted of wrapping an aura around a thick scripture, splitting it open at each page and sending it flying, while D'Ordume's used an attack method of extending his fist with aura loaded onto the strange arm straps and torsos wrapped around both forearms.

'He's quite intimidating in person.'

Aside from his massive size and immense aura, there was something about D'Ordume that intimidated his opponents.

A human zookeeper, a man who had spent his entire life imprisoning, torturing, enslaving, harassing, and killing others.

Like a dog curling its tail around a dogcatcher, a human being would naturally shrink in the presence of this man named D'Ordume.

But Vikir is a demon hunter, a man who can make even demons curl their tails.

He is a veteran of the battlefield, having spent more time on the battlefield than D'Ordume has lived in his entire life.

The momentum that Vikir exuded was not only neutralizing D'Ordume's momentum, it was overwhelming it.

“...!”

D'Ordume flinched at the sharpness of Vikir's aura.

“Is it true that you can't use mana? If the power of pure flesh is this great... is amazing.”

Seeing the groaning bodies of the Major and Lieutenant Colonel level guards lying around, D'Ordume spoke up.

“I'm going to have to uproot you from here.”

In this state, D'Ordume had an overwhelming advantage, as his opponent was still wearing BDISSEM handcuffs and shackles, unless he had access to mana.

...Srug!

D'Ordume raised the axe blade on his forearm and said.

“I warn you, this may be a summary execution. Because of an 'unsavory incident' between a guard and a prisoner 19 years ago, the lower levels are strictly controlled and punished.”

“....”

“There is no judgment. Farewell.”

With that, D'Ordume clenched his thick square jaw tightly.

And soon, he ran forward with snake-like veins on his forearms as thick as logs.

...Thump, thump, thump!

It was as if a giant water buffalo was charging at him.

At the same time, D'Ordume's two forearms crossed horizontally and vertically.

Ppeoeog-

Vikir blocked D'Ordume's two fists with his BDISSEM cuffs.

But D'Ordume's real attack came from behind his fists, from his forearms.

Kiiiiiiing.

Wind whipped along the sharp lines of the spiral axe blade on his forearm, spinning shards of sharp aura.

Vikir felt a chill run down his spine.

He could feel it in his gut. If he continued to struggle with D'Ordume in this position, he would be pulverized like fish meat.

Pow!

Vikir quickly ducked his head and rolled to the side, out of the wind's reach.

And then.

Kwa-gigigigigigi!

A whirlwind of aura that must have been more than a dozen meters in diameter flew out like a snake and swept in front of him.

Patter-patter-patter-patter-

It sucked in the surrounding rocks with a tremendous sucking force, crushing them into sand.

It was obvious that if a person was sucked into such a place, they would be turned into a handful of blood in less than a second.

“Ew, wah! D'Ordume is unleashing his power!”

“Everyone dodge, you'll get caught!”

“Co, Colonel D'Ordume, even the guards are getting affected...!”

In front of D'Ordume's power, which minced and crushed everything without distinction, everyone in the sweatshop began to flee in terror.

Vikir, meanwhile, was slightly impressed.

'This is the power of one of the Five Warden's.'

Before the regression, the heroes from Nouvelle Vague had mostly fought on the front lines in terrain that even Vikir had never encountered, so he had never seen their skill and prowess with his own eyes.

But now, in front of him, their power was truly untold, and the rumors had not been told in vain.

Kwadeudeudeudeudeudeudeug!

Mountains are being chipped away before his eyes, and rocks are being turned into grains of sand and scattered in all directions.

The swirling air currents mix with the sulfurous gas, creating a maelstrom of flames that soon explodes into a violent explosion.

...Boom, boom, boom, boom!

And the whirlwind of strikes created by D'Ordume shredded even the explosions and flames, rushing towards Vikir.

'Such a monster has been lurking in Nouvelle Vague, but I doubt he will fight the demons in the future.'

In the pre-Regression world, D'Ordume had also participated in the war against demons.

But that was due to complicated circumstances, and his participation involved the sacrifice of many innocents.

In this life, Vikir had already changed so many things on earth that it was unlikely that things would go as predicted.

'True. Many of my allies have been harmed by this man. Perhaps it's better to be safe than sorry.'

Vikir shook his head as he saw the screaming prisoners and guards caught in the maelstrom of fire in the distance.

And when D'Ordume saw this, veins like a viper rose up on D'Ordume's forehead.

“How dare you slack off?”

D'Ordume drew in a deep breath to summon his strength.

Then he doubled the number of rotations per second of the aura spinning from his forearms.

Kiyuuuuuuuuuung-

The boulders that had been sucked into the vortex of the attack were no longer grains of sand, but instead turned into numerical dust and began to whirl.

'This is going to be hard to dodge, isn't it?'

Vikir ducked his head out of the way of the swirling blades.

Every nerve in his body was screaming like crazy from earlier.

Vikir had to keep his wits about him, because if he reacted any slower, his entire body would be torn to shreds.

'...No mana should be used at this time, so I must use my reflexes, which have blossomed to the extreme, to completely control and maneuver my body. Above all else, I must focus on the original principle.'

Vikir utilized his spatial perception and reflexes to the fullest.

To know the exact size and position of his own body, so that he could pass through a shower of flying strikes.

It was even harder than walking through raindrops falling from the sky without getting wet.

The slightest miscalculation in the size and position of the body would tear flesh and shred bone.

'But on the other hand, if I calculate the size and position of my body perfectly, it means I won't get hurt at all.'

Vikir moved like a ghost in the opposite direction of the twitching hairs.

Wajijijijig!

One step, and the place where he had just stepped is ripped apart.

Pfft.

Tilting his head, a fine line of stitches burst through the shoulder of his prison uniform.

Vikir continued to dig into D'Ordume's arms.

And then.

Peoeog-

A fist wrapped in BDISSEM chains shattered D'Ordume's aura and drove deep into his abdomen.

'It went in.'

Vikir thought to himself.

[...Human! Danger! Back!]

He heard the tiny voice of Decarabia shouting in his chest.

Almost at the same time.

“...!”

Vikir felt an uneasy sensation like never before.

No matter how much humans trained their bodies, there was a limit to how strong muscles could be when they were basically made of bone, flesh, blood, and skin.

But there was something different about D'Ordume.

His fist doesn't feel quite right at the end.

There's a hard, heavy semi-elasticity that comes back along the back of the hand after a clear hit to the abdomen.

It wasn't the kind of thing that would be felt when hitting a human body.

It's like....

“...Dragon body?”

Vikir furrowed his brow.

Whoosh!

The thick sulfurous gas and the fragments of the aura caused by the vortex were cleared away, revealing D'Ordume's body.

...BANG!

It was clearly not a human body as it ferociously stamped on Vikir's body.

Chapter 370

Solitary Confinement (2)

◆

The old man who gave his name as Angajumang continued to talk to Vikir, apparently bored.

“It feels like it's been several years since I was locked in this solitary confinement. Let's see, I make a stroke in my mind every time I count 60 seconds, and that's already over three million strokes....”

Hearing Angajumang's words, Vikir couldn't help but click his tongue.

Even for Vikir, who had gone through many hardships, the 100 days in solitary confinement were difficult and daunting.

'And you've been locked up here for so many years? I can't believe it.'

These are the words of a man he has never met and will never see again, but they are also the words of a prisoner he met in solitary confinement, not anywhere else.

“How did you not starve to death after being locked up for so many years?”

“Pushishishi – they put black bread crumbs into the bowl every two days, right?.”

“The amount of water I can take in must be insufficient.”

“No. You just have to suck in the dew in the air.”

Vikir was silent for a moment. Dew? In this hot space?

But Old Man Angajumang was nonchalantly telling him how to survive here.

“Well, actually, you can live longer without eating breadcrumbs. You just have to slow down your metabolism extremely slowly and slowly break down the nutrients you've stored up.”

“....”

“Pushishishi – Young people these days tend to try to live too hard, and too much passion is a poison. It's good to slow down and take a look at life once in a while, instead of rushing through it all. Be like stone, be like water.”

It sounds like the ramblings of an old man in a back room, but the location is too important to ignore.

The solitary confinement of the Nouvelle Vague.

This is a man who claims to have been locked up for several years in a place worse than Level 9.

'If he hasn't already gone insane from being locked up here,... he must be a big-time criminal.'

Or maybe he was already insane.

Angajumang then said to Vikir.

“By the sound of your voice, you're still a young man. What has brought you to this place?”

“Where can there be old and young in sin?”

“Pushishishi- that's true. So, what were you imprisoned for? Please answer the old man's question.”

“Assassination of a political enemy.”

Vikir answered briefly.

Then Old Man Angajumang chuckled.

“Why were you imprisoned after doing such a good deed? Have you been rejected by your family?”

“Well, you could look at it that way.”

“Well, well. It was like a hunting dog. When a rabbit falls in the mountains, it's only natural that the hunting dog is boiled and eaten.”

Old Man Angajumang naturally added an afterthought.

“For some reason, I think I know where you're from, you're from Baskerville, right?”

Vikir was a bit stingy.

The old man Angajumang sensed Vikir's agitation like a ghost, and let out his usual eerie laugh.

“Pushishishi- you're right, few families are heartless enough to send a hound that has worked so hard for the family to a place like this. At best, it would be an Ironblood Swordman family or an Extreme Poisonous family.”

“I take it you're familiar with the Baskervilles.”

“I know. Our family was once called the Iron Blood Swordsman.”

The old Angajumang man's words caused Vikir to rack his brain for a moment.

Nowadays, the Baskerville family is considered the greatest sword family, but it wasn't like that in the past.

Before the Empire was united, there were at least four other swordsman families across the continent that were more prestigious than the Baskerville.

Bahamut. Jiz. Sade. Nibelungen.

The Baskerville were somewhat of an inferior brand compared to these four.

In fact, until then, they were just a family-type mercenary group that wandered around the continent without even a small territory.

Anyway. There was a time when the Baskerville family was added to the four families above and they were called the 5th Ironblood Swordman Family.

Old Man Angajumang chuckled nostalgically.

“At that time, our family was also considered a prestigious swordsman family. However, since I gave up the sword at the time, the sword's legacy would have been lost from then on ...Hmm, no. Perhaps the family itself has ceased to exist?”

“Are there no descendants?”

“Hmm~ There was a granddaughter, but I don't know if she's dead or alive. If she's alive, she's probably older than you. Not as far as your mom.... More like your youngest aunt or oldest sister.”

“You must have lived a long time, huh?”

“Yes. I've lived a long time. I've spent a lifetime on the battlefield.”

The old man Angajumang chuckled bitterly.

“To expect an old man like me to suddenly adapt to a peaceful world is unreasonable. Fighting and war have been my life.”

“And you still live fiercely in your solitary confinement in Nouvelle Vague. It's a consistent life.”

“Pushishishi – Fierce? Here? You're welcome. This place is like a resort. Right now, I am taking a leisurely rest to relieve the fatigue I suffered in the past... I plan to go out as soon as I feel better.”

This was no ordinary old man who had the nerve to use Nouvelle Vague's cell as a resort.

Vikir wondered a little bit how long the old man next to him had been alive, and what a hard life he had lived.

Apparently, Old Man Angajumang was thinking the same thing.

“You seem to be able to talk to me. Do you know how to use a non-sword bimu?”

Non-sword Bimu. Just as accomplished Go players play verbally with their eyes closed, accomplished swordsmen can duel verbally with their eyes closed.

This is impossible unless they know each other's sword paths and moves.

Vikir readily accepted the elder Angajumang's request for a non-sword bimu.

“Do you know the swordsmanship of the Baskerville?”

“I know the basics, so let's get started.”

Old Man Angajumang opened his mouth to begin his opening move.

Vikir did the same, unleashing his powers as he went along, creating an imaginary duel.

Baskerville 1st Form. Teeth that stab deeply into the opponent's body.

Baskerville 2nd Form. Another deep, immobilizing bite into the opponent's body.

Baskerville 3rd Form. A tooth that bites into the opponent's body and weighs them down.

Baskerville 4th Form. Slice through the opponent's body.

.

.

Vikir warmed up and proceeded to perform Baskerville Forms 1 through 4.

To his surprise, Old Man Angajumang saw through Vikir's mastery of the four forms.

“It's amazing, a young man who hasn't even reached the age of majority has mastered the Four Forms. It's like watching a middle-aged man who has spent his entire life rolling on the battlefield!”

However, after he finished speaking, he added in a laughing tone.

“ ...Well, compared to this old man, you're still a greenhorn.”

With that, Old Man Angajumang proceeded to make his first form.

Vikir knew nothing of the old man's swordsmanship, but Angajumang used Vikir's theories of swordsmanship to build upon his own.

Although he did not know Old Man Angajumang's swordsmanship, but knew his own, could naturally see how old Angajumang was destroying his own swordsmanship.

It was a sight to behold.

Vikir's first form was consumed by the gentle stroke of Angajumang's sword.

And the second one that followed was merely a reminder of where his main body was.

The third and fourth forms, which hadn't even gotten off the ground yet, were quickly consumed by Angajumang's attack, and soon Vikir's body was in danger of being torn to pieces.

'...What's that? It's not a normal snake?'

Vikir had to stop himself from stealing a glance.

At this point, the full extent of Vikir's power is revealed.

Baskerville 5th Form. Teeth that tear the body apart.

Baskerville 6th Form. Teeth that crush the opponent's body.

Baskerville 7th Form. Teeth that mince the opponent's body.

Baskerville 8th Form. Teeth that brings all the teeth together and holds them in place.

The ultimate in swordsmanship that Baskerville can reach. The limit of the living.

It struck back at Old Man Angajumang with tremendous momentum.

The Black Sun.

The same ultimate that had cut off the life force of 5th Corpse Amdusias had shaken the entire virtual world of Non-Sword Bimu.

However.

“Pushishishi- this really surprises me, I can't believe it, how is it possible for you to be at such a peak at such a young age?”

Old Man Angajumang was only surprised, not frightened or intimidated.

Eventually, the power of old man Angajumang clashes with that of Vikir.

There was a ferocity and aggression in the old man that one would never expect from a dying old man, a youthful madness in his brash counterattack.

A madman, a warmonger who has spent his entire life fighting and waging war.

Even Vikir had no choice but to give in to his ferocity.

'...I never knew such a madman existed in the world.'

Even Vikir had to admit that his duel with the old man Angajumang had left him in a state of shock.

A creature brought into the world solely to fight, kill, and conflict.

The very definition of a war madman.

Every breath he takes, every step he takes, every hand he stretches out, is filled with nothing but the desire to kill and destroy.

An aura that is eager to torment others. These misaligned dramatizations. This perverse virtue.

He could see now why the old man had been kept away from humanity, locked away in solitary confinement here in Nouvelle Vague, in the deepest and most inhospitable of all places.

[He's a madman, the type that should never be mixed with, regardless of species, demon or human].

Even the once-demonic Decarabia had said this.

At that moment, Old Man Angajumang laughed bitterly and said.

“Playing with you like this, I feel a little motivated. I feel a little younger.”

“I'm glad to hear it helps.”

“A great help. Ah! I don't know how long it's been since I've felt this way. Not since Winston and Orca. Hmm, and before that, of course, when I was fighting the Seven Counts of Baskerville.”

“The Seven Counts? You mean like the Boston Terriers and the Great Dane and Isabella?”

“Who? I don't know about that. Not the current Seven Counts, but the Seven Counts of previous eras.”

Well, judging by Old Man Angajumang's age, it would have to be at least two generations back.

Old Man Angajumang asked Vikir.

“Who is the current patriarch of the Baskerville family?”

“Hugo Le Baskerville.”

“Hugo... Hugo... who is that? Some unheard-of rascal is running the place, and Why didn't that old Cane Corso inherit the position of patriarch?”

“ ...Do you know Cane Corso?”

“I know. He was a strict and picky man. When I was young, I got into trouble a lot because I was fussy without knowing anything.”

The old man Angajumang murmured in a wistful tone, as if recalling childhood games.

“I still shudder when I think of the devastation he inflicted. Pushishishi – Is he supposed to be dead now? Well, it's only natural that so much time has passed. Perhaps he was possessed by something and chased after a vision of that sword grave or something. Like an idiot with lesser strength.”

“....”

Vikir fell silent.

He didn't need to be told that the Grave of Swords existed, or that Cane Corso had become a Death Knight and attained the 9th Form.

...And apart from that, Vikir thought he knew the identity of the old man Angajumang.

Before the regression, the guards of Nouvelle Vague had declared that they would not participate in the war between demons and humans.

But that was only in the early days of the war.

In the latter stages of the war, the guards of Nouvelle Vague began to fight demons on the surface, and not just to defend humanity.

The collapse of Nouvelle Vague.

As Nouvelle Vague itself disappeared, the guards and prisoners were forced to come to the surface.

'It was Orca himself, the warden, who brought down the Nouvelle Vague.'

Why would he, the symbol of Nouvelle Vague, take such an action?

There were many different theories on the subject.

But one theory is quite compelling.

It was the result of a prisoner trying to get to the surface, and Orca taking extreme measures to stop him.

It's hard to imagine how dangerous he must have been to bring down an entire Nouvelle Vague prison just to prevent one man from escaping.

As for who that escapee was, the opinions of the experts were divided...

'Perhaps it was him.'

If so, Vikir knew exactly who old man Angajumang was and what his true name was.

And given his knowledge of the long history of the Baskerville from Non-sword Bimu from earlier, he was even more certain.

Vikir was confident in his guess.

He concluded.

'...A person who should not be involved as much as possible.'

Here was a human being, even more terrible and frightening than a demon, right next to him.

Chapter 374

Poseidon (2)

◆

“What's going on?”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille, who had primary jurisdiction over the entire labor camp, rushed over.

A guard with the rank of captain pointed down into the depths of the pit.

“There's been a mysterious explosion in the center of the Level Nine sector.”

“It's different in scale from the previous incidents. It seems to be a sign of something bad.”

“We are not yet able to investigate because of the lava and gas, which could cause further collapse.”

After receiving his subordinates' report, Lieutenant Colonel Bastille said coldly.

“Send a few prisoners to investigate.”

“What? Ha, but if we go down there now, there's room for us to get caught up in a further collapse....”

“That's why I say send some prisoners. If you promise to exempt them from a day's labor and throw in a few crusts of bread, they'll volunteer.”

The guards fell silent at Bastille's words.

No prisoner would sell their lives for a day's rest and a few crusts of bread.

But there was a surprising volunteer.

“I'll go.”

Vikir took a step forward.

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille flinched.

“You? What do you have up your sleeve?”

“Nothing much. I just want some bread.”

“...Hmm.”

Lieutenant Colonel Bastille thought for a moment.

But Vikir had been a model prisoner for the past two years, with no incidents since he first arrived.

Bastille finally nodded.

“Good. Do you think you can make it down through that fire and gas?”

“Only if you can get me out of my BDISSEM restraints.”

“Don't play games with me....”

“Just kidding. Bye.”

Vikir stepped into the pit with a dry joke.

Gurgling!

The gas storms, flames, and lava that erupted from within the surface were more than even Vikir could handle.

It was at times like this that the physical and magical resistance stats he had maxed out in the Hell Tree came in handy.

“Hey, Decarabia, can you put up a shield?”

[I'm out of mana, so I can only do a little].

“That should be enough.”

At Vikir's words, Decarabia raised a small barrier, covering a few meters around him.

Vikir, hiding behind a curtain of fire and gas, moved forward, shaking off lava that was up to his knees.

'...I can't hold out much longer.'

If he stayed in this place with no mana, his legs would burn without a trace.

Vikir paced, eager to find the cause of the explosion as quickly as possible.

Suddenly, beyond the thick cloud of sulfurous gas, the roaring flames, and the brilliant red aurora of lava, a giant shadow loomed.

“...!”

Vikir knew at once that this was what he had been searching for.

“This is the first time I've seen it with the naked eye.”

But there was no doubt nonetheless.

In the heart of Nouvelle Vague, in the deepest reaches of Level Nine.

Is this the only 'sphere of blue lava' that exists here?

Vikir quietly raised his head to take in the sight before him.

An oval-shaped sphere, about five meters in diameter, covered in blue flames and roiling, it looked like the 'egg' of something.

“I found it. Poseidon.”

Vikir reached out and stroked its surface once.

Underneath the sphere, roots made of aura extended out from beneath the ground, and they resisted violently at the slightest impact.

Kwakwang! Kuleuleung! Uleung!

Because of that resistance, it seemed like explosions were occurring all around.

...Peog!

Vikir stretched out his fist and punched Poseidon's outer surface.

Then, something amazing happened.

Swoosh!

Poseidon absorbed the impact from Vikir's fist.

Wriggle!

The blue flames that had been roaring grew ever so slightly larger.

The surrounding light also seemed to grow a little brighter.

“I see. It grows by absorbing external shocks.”

Vikir nodded.

Finding this Poseidon is not the end of the story. In the future, we need to provide numerous shocks to grow.

'...They don't call it “synchronized” for nothing.'

Vikir stroked his chin.

Just like discovering Poseidon, making this thing work was not a solo effort.

'But once you've discovered it, 90% of the work has been accomplished. The rest is just a matter of time.'

Vikir, of course, had a plan for the future.

...Cheolpeog! ...cheolpeog! ...cheolpeog! ...cheolpeog!

Vikir turned and ran back through the lava swamp.

Eventually, everyone who saw Vikir rising above the rocky area was frightened.

“Oh, you're not dead?”

“How did you get all the way inside that hell?”

“Didn't you just come back from the entrance?”

The others chattered, but Vikir didn't care.

“There's a strange mass of lava inside. It seems to absorb shock.”

“...Absorb shock?”

Lt. Colonel Bastille looked impressed.

It might be better if it was something that exploded, but materials that absorb shock are not very pleasant.

This is true from the perspective of having to dig down a tunnel.

Then, as the gas and oil vapor cleared, the blue orb Vikir had spoken of became more clearly visible.

Searing flames, roots of auras reaching beneath the ground, and a mysterious entity that explodes with a loud bang at the slightest touch.

Lt. Colonel Bastille raised his greatsword and struck.

Kwa-kwakwakwakwakwang!

The blue sphere absorbed even the aura of a Graduator Superior without difficulty.

“It's true! It absorbed all of Lt. Colonel Bastille's attacks!”

“Huh? Doesn't that lump... seem to have gotten a little bigger than before?”

“It looks like an egg or something.”

Even the guards were agitated.

Now that the mysterious sphere was stuck in the middle of the labor camp, it was difficult to do their work.

Even if they wanted to dig around it, they couldn't because it absorbed all the impacts from pickaxes, shovels, and other tools.

Even worse, the veins of the aura, which were laid down like roots, would explode in a massive explosion if they were disturbed.

Lt. Colonel Bastille grunted.

“If an explosion of this magnitude can be caused by merely touching one of those twig-like veins,... it's going to be a mess if the main body of that lump explodes.”

At best, the entire Nouvelle Vague fortress would be blown away.

Worst of all, it could reawaken an extinct volcano that was thought to be dead and begin to erupt again.

“Damn it. Nouvelle Vague is not a fully extinct volcano.”

But the veins of aura around Bastille, the sulfurous gas, steam, and bubbling magma that were erupting in real time, were more than a glance away.

Until now, he had assumed that it was an eruption of old geothermal heat trapped in the ground, but he might have to revise his thinking.

“Call in the geologists. We need to do a full survey to see if Nouvelle Vague is really an extinct volcano....”

But Lt. Colonel Bastille's order was unfinished.

“What nonsense.”

From behind him, a large man in a dark uniform walked out.

Colonel D'Ordume. The moment he appeared, Lt. Colonel Bastille straightened up and saluted.

D'Ordume returned the salute with a wave of his hand and got straight to the point.

“Tell me again what you said earlier. You're going to do the whole survey again?”

“Yes! It's none other than the unidentified object found in the labor camp on Level 9....”

D'Ordume frowned at Lt. Colonel Bastille's words.

“Let me take a look.”

D'Ordume followed Bastille's lead down to the blue sphere.

“If you hit it, it absorbs the impact, and if you touch the veins of the aura underneath, you get a loud explosion, which is also absorbed by the sphere. If you mess with it too much, the sphere might release all the shock it's accumulated at once. If Nouvelle Vague is a dormant volcano, not an extinct one, then....”

“Nonsense. Nouvelle Vague is definitely an extinct volcano.”

D'Ordume dismissed Bastille's words.

Then he spoke again.

“Don't prolong the construction period over something you're not even sure of. Do you have any idea how long it will take to conduct a full survey again? At least a decade.”

“Ha, but....”

“What about the astronomical budget that will be incurred if the construction period is extended? Will you be responsible for that?”

“....”

When Bastille shut up, D'Ordume drove a wedge.

“Labor will proceed as scheduled. You will meet the construction deadline at all costs.”

“....”

“This is all for your own good. The sooner Level Ten is finished, the sooner I'll be ahead of that Souaré, that bitch, if I become the head of the prison, and the sooner you'll be promoted to warden.”

At D'Ordume's words, Bastille nodded.

“You're right, Colonel.”

“Yeah. If there's going to be an explosion, it's going to be a bunch of scumbag prisoners dying anyway. If you're really worried, tell the guards to stay away from that area if they can.”

As he spoke, D'Ordume's eyes glowed.

“Personnel evaluation season is coming soon.”

“....”

“Souaré, that bitch is keeping the old man Angajumang in solitary confinement, and she's always getting near perfect personnel scores for that alone.”

“....”

“Me, on the other hand, I'm the one who takes the initiative to put down the prisoners' riots, I go out and fetch food, and I always do my job as the warden's closest confidante.”

“....”

“If I and that Souaré bitch have similar quarterly personnel scores, Why should I be a candidate for the next prison director along with that bitch?”

It was the first time Lt. Colonel Bastille had ever heard D'Ordume talk this much.

With a click and a grinding of teeth, he finished.

“So the Level Ten project I've been entrusted with must be completed on time, no matter what. It's the only way we can stay ahead of Souaré, and when I'm the next warden director, you're the next warden. Do you understand what I mean?”

“I only accept it.”

D'Ordume nodded in satisfaction at Bastille's polite reply, then disappeared down the hallway.

Behind him, Bastille sighed in unease.

'I have a bad feeling about this. Once that thing goes off, it won't just blow up the Nouvelle Vague, it might even affect the climate on the ground....'

Lt. Colonel Bastille thought to himself for a long time.

But then he shook his head.

'I know. Worrying too much is my weakness.'

Lt. Colonel Bastille decided to resume his labor the next day.

He had no time to worry about it now that he was involved in a political battle between D'Ordume and Souaré, the next in line for the head of the five wardens.

...And.

'This is good for me in many ways.'

Standing behind a stone pillar, listening to their conversation, Vikir quietly melted into the darkness.

With a bag of bread in his hand as a reward.

Chapter 375

The Hounds of Nouvelle Vague (1)

◆

Nouvelle Vague, a place the world has abandoned.

In this remote area 10,000 meters below the sea, there is only one day warm.

It was Christmas Day at the end of the year. Lun's birthday. It's the only day of the year when prisoners are allowed a holiday.

The meals were different.

Instead of the usual pickled sardines and brick-hard black bread, they are served pork jerky and soft white bread.

For the first time in a long time, the prisoners eat in a proper dining room, not on the floor of the labor camp. Candles burn on leaden candlesticks, and meat and bread are served in a gloomy, shadowy stone room.

For once, the guards do not interfere, standing at a distance with their weapons slung behind their backs.

The prisoners are happy with the chewy, savory pork jerky and half-dried white bread, as if they had everything in the world.

“I survived a year looking forward to this day.”

“It's a good thing I'm alive.”

“The most pitiful are those who died yesterday. Cough, cough-”

Then.

“Kurukuru... get the fuck out of here.”

A level 8 prisoner shouted.

When he thrusted his huge body at them, the prisoners scrambled to their feet and out of the way.

They were afraid of his poison, which hadn't been disinfected by the three sulfur showers they'd undergone during the entry.

“Did you hear? That bastard can't control his plague.”

“That's right. Anyone who comes in contact with his saliva, blood, or other bodily fluids gets the plague.”

“Look at those spots on his skin. Whether it's poison or plague, it's really nasty.”

But their rant didn't go unnoticed by the other prisoner.

“Kurukuru, you stupid bastards. I walked in here on my own two feet, and I'm going to get out one day, I am saying that my Queen will take such action!”

He's been saying this for two years now.

At first, it was a sincere belittling of others, but as time went on, there was a hint of madness in his words.

Now it sounded like some sort of sinister incantation.

Some of the prisoners frowned at his salivating rantings, others were horrified. But they all agreed that they didn't want to be around him.

Soon, there was an empty circle around him in the dining hall.

With a satisfied smile on his face, he sat down and chewed on his pork jerky and white bread.

...But?

Suddenly, he felt someone behind him.

Just one. Only one prisoner hadn't moved from his seat.

It was Vikir.

Sakkuth asked in disbelief.

“Kid, aren't you afraid of my plague?”

“....”

Vikir didn't bother to answer.

Sakkuth would probably faint if he knew that Madame's poison, far more terrifying than the plague, was coursing through the veins of Vikir's body.

Dalgeulag- dalkkag-

Vikir finished his meal in silence.

It was a much different meal than the one he would have at the Colosseo Academy.

Then, at the table in front of him, he heard a group of prisoners talking amongst themselves.

“ ... Is this real?”

“It's real, though the guards have seen it all and it's tattered.”

“Wow- you really got that?”

“Hehehe – you can pick up a lot of stuff when you're cleaning out the restroom septic tanks. More good stuff than you think.”

It turns out that the prisoner who was cleaning the septic tank had picked up something good.

Assuming it was, at best, a cigarette, a watch, gambling paraphernalia, or cheap drugs, Vikir tried to ignore it.

However, his ears perked up.

“Holy shit. You picked up a 'newspaper'.”

A newspaper. The only way to get news of the world here in Nouvelle Vague!

Newspapers are incredibly valuable in Nouvelle Vague.

Common sense dictates that these few pieces of paper must have traveled an incredibly long journey to reach the Nouvelle Vague.

Unless it is brought in by one of the guards on an extremely rare occasions when they go out on the ground, receiving a newspaper on a regular basis is a luxury that can only be dreamed of.

But apart from the guards, there are always prisoners who long for news from the outside world.

Vikir was one of them.

Drat-

Pulling back his chair, Vikir walked over to the conversing prisoners.

“Hey.”

Vikir's voice startled the prisoners, who were busy talking amongst themselves.

“Yes, yes!”

They were Level One prisoners, low-level prisoners who could get out of this hellish place three years later.

However, they were so weak and frail that most of them lived for less than a year before dying.

Worst of all, if Vikir, a Level Nine prisoner, were to stir up a ruckus, they would die.

But Vikir didn't raise his voice.

“Newspapers and such will only cause trouble if you have them. Treasure you can't handle is a curse.”

“....”

“Why don't you trade it for this?”

Vikir held out a bag of black bread, a prize he'd won not long ago.

The prisoners' eyes widened at the sight of it.

Vikir teased in a low voice.

“I'm sure you've all read the newspaper anyway.”

“Oh, I haven't seen it yet... because I'm blind.”

“Then why don't you let me read it and then I'll tell you what it says?”

That was a deal not to be refused.

The prisoner frowned, and then pulled from his pocket a finely folded piece of yellow paper.

“It's a little smelly because I picked it out of the shit, hehe-”

Vikir handed over the bread and took the newspaper.

At first glance, the newspaper was not in pristine condition.

Most of it was torn, so the only intact parts were the first and second pages, and even then, only the headlines were recognizable due to smudged or torn text in the middle.

Worst of all, it was dated six months earlier.

'I used to look at newspapers before they were even published.'

Looking at the newspapers that he used to tirelessly create during his time at Colosseo Academy's newspaper department, Ryukeion, and that he used to have access to even before they were published, it was refreshing to see them being treated with such respect (even six months old!).

Parak.

Vikir scrutinized the paper.

[Inside...] ... palace guard, raiding...

-The Usher family... a mysterious attack... heavy damage... authorities have identified one suspect... the victim, Madeline... seriously injured, but not life-threatening...

The [sole] victim of a series of attacks on...

-Donquixote Family... another mystery... attack... Count Pasamonte... minor injuries... authorities have identified one suspect... believed to be the same...

[Exclusive] Suspected assassin arrested...

-Leviathan Family... Attack on Patriarch Hobbs... Blamed on the recent surge in demonic activity... Mysterious gates and strange dungeons popping up all over the Leviathan Family estate... An empire-wide investigation has been launched... The Night Hounds... A suspicious organization... A citywide scare...

It's a short list, but it gives you an idea.

The first and second pages usually contain the biggest events in society, so here's a glimpse of what's going on on the ground.

'The Usher family, Donquixote, and the Leviathan family have been attacked, one after the other. One attacker? Who?'

As Vikir scrolled through the article, his attention was drawn to one place.

'...A series of unexplained gates and strange dungeons.'

There were other odd keywords, like the Night Hounds, but the first one caught Vikir's attention.

'The Ten Corpses have begun in earnest.'

The gates of destruction were already showing signs of opening.

No, considering this was already six months old....

'We'd better hurry.'

The time of destruction would be hastened.

Perhaps it was the butterfly effect of Vikir's elimination of the Ten Corpse so far, and the messages he'd left to Cindywendy, Isabella, and others before his imprisonment in Nouvelle Vague.

-'I have always seen you during my time at the academy. You are not a villain. That much is certain.'

-'Seeing the reality of the demons that were under my nose just a moment ago, I now know everything for sure. You must live. Why have I only realized this now?'

-'As soon as I get back, I'll show them the evidence and ask for a retrial.'

-'I have orders from my lord to break you out of prison, Vikir, even if it means sinking the ship.'

The strict Banshee Professor, the single-minded Archbishop Mozgus, Lovebad whom he had never met, and even the Baskerville Hound, Countess Isabella.

Given the attitudes of the Morgue, Quovadis, Bourgeois, and Baskerville escorts at the end, it was easy to imagine what must have happened between the Seven Families after Vikir's trip to Nouvelle Vague.

'I can see why they would be so rash to open the gates of destruction.'

It's probably a political and strategic decision. They operate with demonic common sense, not human common sense.

...Thud!

Vikir closed the newspaper and washed his hands in the falling water from the ceiling.

'I need more information from the outside world.'

There's no point in searching for a newspaper when you don't know when you'll get one.

There is only one surefire way to get information from the outside world.

'You have to go out there yourself.'

He's already found his core purpose of coming to Nouvelle Vague, Poseidon.

That alone is more than 90% of the way there.

Vikir was starting to get tired of the heavy restraints on his wrists and ankles.

'...There's no need to wear this prison uniform anymore.'

The dawn of the prison break was dawning in earnest.

Chapter 376

The Hounds of Nouvelle Vague (2)

◆

The dreamlike Christmas was over in the blink of an eye.

And then they were back to the same old hellish labor.

...Ttang! ...kkaang! ...ttang!

Everywhere, prisoners were breaking stones and digging up soil. The sounds of sulfurous gas, steam, and lava were erupting.

Since the discovery of the mysterious explosives in the labor camp on Level Nine, the work had changed a bit.

Where the guards had previously formed a panopticon-like formation to keep an eye on the prisoners, this time the guards have moved to the perimeter instead of the center.

This was due to Colonel D'Ordume's orders to keep the guards as far away from the explosives as possible.

It was also a strategic move to take advantage of the temporary chaos to make it easier to subdue rioting prisoners with concentrated firepower.

However, it is inevitable that there would be errors, large and small, in the process of changing the original system.

The response of the guards, who would normally be able to intervene immediately in the event of laziness or disputes among the inmates, was slowed down even slightly as they adjusted to the change.

“....”

Vikir, who had noticed the change, had his eye on a figure since earlier.

“...Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.”

Sakkuth. He'd been acting a little out of sorts since they'd met at the diner on Christmas Day yesterday.

His gaze, which usually darts from top to bottom in a condescending manner, is now directed from bottom to top.

His bloodshot eyes, the corner of his tmouth twitching, the profanity he recited like a mantra and his obsession with “him” made him look like a definite maniac.

And before anyone knew it, it was lunchtime.

While all the prisoners were enjoying their ten-minute break, Sakkuth walked into a canyon between the red rock mountains and pulled at his hair.

“What happened? How did this happen....?”

He was biting down his fingers beyond his nails.

“Queen, boss, master, what's going on, you said you'd get me out, why haven't I heard from you for two years, you told me to go into Nouvelle Vague and serve 'Him', you said you'd make sure I go out. Of course, I didn't make it into Level Nine because I wasn't good enough, but that doesn't mean you're going to leave me like this. Why aren't you coming to rescue me? When am I going to get out of here, from this hellish servitude, please....”

The mumbling didn't stop, despite the fact that the first word was nearly torn from his fingers and covered in blood.

Vikir, meanwhile, was listening to the mutterings from a distance.

'...It tastes good.'

He was always a bit of a weirdo, but not that weird.

Apparently, like Vikir, he had infiltrated this place with a purpose.

But there was a crucial difference between Vikir and Sakkuth.

Vikir doesn't count on others to help him achieve his goals. He does everything by himself and in silence.

Sakkuth, on the other hand, is desperately waiting for someone else to help him achieve his goals.

This created a huge difference between the two.

'This is what separates the predator from the prey.'

Vikir leaned against the wall and watched Sakkuth in silence.

Meanwhile, Sakkuth was becoming increasingly unstable.

“If it's been a while and I haven't heard from you, that means you've abandoned me. You've abandoned me. No news from the outside world, that's it. It's because I didn't make it to Level Nine. That's why the Boss, the Queen, abandoned me.”

Just then.

TOOOOOO-!

A horn blared, signaling the resumption of labor.

He could hear the guards shouting.

“Here we go!”

“Hurry up and get to work, scum!”

“Do you want to get fucked! Get moving!”

The shouts further stirred up the already unsteady state of Sakkuth.

“....”

With his lips pressed tightly together, his eyes were bloodshot.

One of the guards, a lieutenant, walked by and said.

“Hey, what are you doing there, get to work!”

And the words hit the nail on the head.

“Kkeuaaaaaaaagh!”

A sudden, screaming seizure.

He turned his head, rolling his bulging eyeballs, and bared his teeth at the terrified guard.

Wadeug- puhwaag!

He bit down on the tip of his own tongue, and a huge fountain of blood began to spew from his mouth.

A stench that stung the nose. A reddish mist filled with plague aura scattered around.

“Uh-uh!”

The first guard to shout at Sakkuth, shocked and took a step back, not knowing what was going on.

Only then did Vikir take his back off the rock wall.

'It has begun.'

It was time for the first step of the Nouvelle Vague prison break.

◆

A riot by an inmate on the 8th floor of Level 8 was a big enough deal.

It would be hard enough to deal with the guards, let alone the lower ranking guards, the so-called lieutenants.

But the guards were not in a good position right now.

Colonel D'Ordume's orders had reversed the guard ranks in the Panopticon structure, and the guards hadn't yet fully adjusted to the new system.

As a result, most of the guards stationed around Sakkuth were junior officers.

At most, there was a captain, a dozen or so lieutenants, and all the rest were ensigns.

“It's Level 8 Sakkuth! He's started a riot!”

“We're way out of our league!”

“Damn it, we should at least have Lieutenant Colonel Bastille here!”

Sakkuth's strength was one thing, but the fountain of plague blood he spewed was another.

Moreover, his beastly roar, glowing madly in the red mist, was perfect for creating an atmosphere of fear.

“Uh, what do we do?” naked shakily one of the guards, who had just earned the rank of captain.

But there was not a single guard here with a higher rank than him.

For the first time, he had to realize that a higher rank wasn't always better.

Right then.

“We need to buy time.”

Someone bravely stepped forward.

Kirko. Lieutenant Kirko Grimm.

Promoted from Ensign to Lieutenant due to her dazzling performance, she glared at those who outranked her.

“While someone stays behind to deal with that prisoner, let's all disperse and call for the higher ranking guards, that's the only way.”

“Ha, but who's going to stay here to deal with that monster, he looks like he's going to go crazy right now.”

No matter how much he's wearing BDISSEM handcuffs and shackles, the plague aura he emits is still intimidating.

No one would rush to fight him, not knowing what kind of plague he might catch.

Then.

“I'll stay.”

Kirko said firmly.

She drew a long sword from her belt and slung it over her shoulder.

“I'll buy as much time as I can, and you, seniors, bring in someone capable of resolving this situation as soon as possible.”

At Kirko's words, the other guards began to look at each other.

“Uh, yeah. If it's Kirko, then....”

“She's only a lieutenant, but she's better than most of the captains.”

“That's right, she's as good as a senior officer.”

“Good, Kirko, I want you to stay behind. We'll go get some reinforcements!”

“Your brave sacrifice will not be forgotten! It will be reflected in your performance review at the end of the month!”

With that, everyone runs off, not sure who's first.

Kirko, alone, with no juniors or subordinates, stood watching his seniors and comrades leave.

And then.

Huug- hug-

The sound of ragged, anxious breathing came from behind her.

Swallowing hard, Kirko slowly turned her head.

Behind her stood a plague monster, probably crazy.

And for Kirko, with her skills, it would be impossible to fully subdue him.

'But it must be done.'

It's better for one of us to venture out than for all of us to die.

She would rather perish violently here than engage in collusion among those who care about each other's interests.

Having her mind made up, Kirko looked back with a fierce glare.

Then, through the red mist, she saw a blurry shadow approaching.

At the same time, Kirko's eyes widened.

“...?”

Yes.

Shaky legs, anxious breathing.

It was Garam Nord, a.k.a. “Stupid Garam,” who remained behind Kirko.

“You, why didn't you go?”

“How can I give up my courage and go on...?”

The words themselves weren't bad, but his voice was as shaky as his legs, which didn't make him sound very cool.

Kirko let out a heavy sigh.

“Kurururururu.......”

A twisted, maniacal laugh came from somewhere.

Kirko and Garam turned in surprise, and there stood Sakkuth, tears streaming from his eyes.

His eyes were so wide that they were torn open. His mouth was torn open to the base of both ears and dirty drool was dripping from it.

“That's it. Just kill them all and get out of here. Kurururu-”

He looked like he'd gone completely insane.

Chapter 377

The Hounds of Nouvelle Vague (3)

◆

“Kururururu....”

There was no focus in Sakkuth's pupils.

His face was turned to the side, like an owl's, and froth and drool were dripping from the corners of his mouth.

“I don't need any of this. I'm going to kill you, and then I'm going to Level 9, so the 'boss' will have to look at me again.”

The targets of his insane gaze were Kirko and Garam.

Thwack.

Kirko held her long sword horizontally, prepared to jump out at a moment's notice. But Garam was still shaking and sulking.

“Ki-Kirko. Don't you think we should run away now?”

“Then the damage will also affect the guards in other districts. I don't know if it's other prisoners, but if it's him, he might spread a plague throughout the region.”

“Well, but....”

“If you're scared, you go alone, idiot, I'll fight.”

Kirko glanced at Garam in a pathetic way, then fixed her gaze back on the scene before her eyes.

The gaseous aura of the Expert was at the tip of her sword.

It was so dense that it looked like it could turn into liquid at any moment.

Seeing it, Sakkuth laughed with his mouth open.

“Kurururu- not bad for a bitch born and bred in Nouvelle Vague.”

Instantly, Kirko's expression changed.

A tiny crack appeared in her eyes, which had been tense but now radiated nothing but cold, merciless energy.

And Sakkuth didn't miss it.

“About twenty years ago, I believe, there was an incident where a prisoner forcefully degraded a guard, which is why the guards at Nouvelle Vague are so sensitive to the lower pole.”

“....”

“Kuru-kuru-kuru- I heard that a child was born and was like a by-product of that unpleasant process.”

The voice was touching a trauma hidden deep within Kirko's mind.

It backfired, and Kirko's anger exploded.

“Don't talk nonsense about prisoners.”

With that, Kirko's longsword shot out like an arrow.

The aura, which has the properties of a gas, spreads widely in front and cuts and stabs as wide an area as possible.

It was an effective method for a large prisoner like Sakkuth.

However, it was merely a form of corporal punishment that used wide, shallow cuts to create fear by drawing bleeding and cuts over as wide an area as possible, and that was not a good way to quell the riot of a prisoner prepared to die.

“Kururururu!”

Sakkuth leaned forward, unperturbed by the multitude of strikes that dug into his entire body.

“You're like a frog born and raised in a well, you've never seen the outside world, right? After all, what right does a bitch born of rape have to walk on this earth? You're useless to everyone, so you're stuck in this deep sea!”

Sakkuth chuckled and reached out a thick arm to grab Kirko by the scruff of the neck.

“...Ouch!”

Kirko tried to pull back, but Sakkuth grabbed her by the collar.

His teeth, sharp as nails, turned toward Kirko.

Kirko closed her eyes tightly for a moment.

...At that time.

“Take back that statement!”

A baton was shot from the other side.

Pug!

It snapped, breaking Sakkuth's teeth with a loud crack.

“Huh?”

Sakkuth staggered backward, clutching his mouth with both hands.

On the floor, Kirko looked up, dazed.

There, unexpectedly, was the back of Garam's head.

In a moment of confusion, Garam bravely stepped forward and swung his triple baton as if to protect Kirko.

It would have been more impressive if his arms and legs hadn't been shaking like aspens.

But Garam's voice was not trembling.

“Kirko is a worthy and honorable fellow, not someone a scumbag like you would dare to insult!”

“...What!”

For a moment, Kirko's earlobes turned red.

However, Garam didn't notice as he was too focused on Sakkuth, who was standing up in front of him.

“Kurururu....”

Sakkuth spat out his broken teeth and laughed.

Then he glared at Garam through his chapped lips.

“'Stupid Garam, you're feeling especially brave today for a stupid dog, is it because I messed with your crush?”

“...No, that's not it!”

“You've got a lot of nerve on the subject of stupid guards buying prisoners lunch, don't you? Does your crush know that you're a weak, cowardly, unqualified piece of shit of guard?”

“No, no, no!”

“Kuru-kuru-kuru- Nope. You and that bitch have a lot in common when it comes to giving something to a prisoner. Be it bread or a body. Kurururu!”

“...I, ig!”

Garam raised his triple baton and infused it with mana.

The mana, overheated by his anger, was shaking unsteadily.

Then.

“Stop.”

There was a hand on Garam's shoulder.

It was Kirko, standing beside him with a calm demeanor.

“Don't get caught up in the mind games. He can't use mana. He's just trying to shake our composure.”

“Ugh! Is that what he's doing?”

“Yeah. Let's do something about it, just the two of us.”

Garam's face instantly brightened at Kirko's calm tone.

“Yes! I will. You're amazing, Kirko!”

“Ugh, you idiot....”

However, looking at the rare smile on Kirko's usually grumbling lips, she didn't seem to be in a very bad mood.

...However.

This wasn't the kind of frenzied battle that usually happens in heroic novels or shonen comics.

Peoeog!

With a loud sweep of his arm, Sakkuth sent the BDISSEM chain flying. It cracked like a whip.

Kirko's face, which had been showing a slight smile just a moment ago, turned sideways.

Quack!

Unable to even scream on the spot, Kirko fell out of the way, hitting her head on a rock, her neck twisting in a strange direction.

Chiiiiig...

Red blood spurted out of her head, pressed against the hot ground.

“...?”

Garam looked dumbfounded, as if he hadn't yet understood what had just happened.

Sakkuth walked in front of her, giggling brightly.

“Oh? What is it, she's alive, what a great woman.”

He pursed his lips as he watched Kirko squirm intermittently.

“It's a quality with a promising future. If she survives that blow, she'll be quite the hero when she's older.”

At this point, a sinister and unholy glow of lust emanated from Sakkuth's eyes.

“It would be a good idea to trample on such a hero-level bud in advance. It seems that you've got a pretty good face and body too....”

But Sakkuth didn't go any further.

Chaang!

Garam. He was standing in front of the fallen Kirko with a baton.

“You will never lay a hand on Kirko.”

“Kurururu-”

“I will defend her with my life, for she is someone I admire and respect....”

But Garam was cut off mid-sentence.

This is because Sakkuth threw his fist and blew away the man as if he was annoyed.

Splat!

Garam crashed into the rocks and laid there like a marionette with a broken string.

Sakkuth chuckled loudly.

“You talk a lot for a scum who hasn't even become a lieutenant yet. I've already risked my life. I need to get to Level 9 and get my boss to trust me again.”

He stalked toward Kirko, his eyes bloodshot.

But.

Pfft.

An unexpected triple baton hit Sakkuth's shoulder from behind.

It was a blow that was clearly wielded by Garam.

“...?”

Sakkuth turned his head to look at Garam in disbelief.

A cracking sound escaped Garam's throat.

“Kirko, don't... touch... her....”

Viper-like veins sprouted on Sakkuth's forehead.

“You troublesome bastard.”

Sakkuth raised his elbow and smashed it into Garam's jaw.

Thud.

All the bones in the jaw shattered, teeth popping out.

Droplets of blood scattered in all directions.

But.

Thud!

Garam collapsed, still clinging to Sakkuth's ankles.

“Kir...ko...don't....”

“Ah~ You're so persistent. I was just trying to have some fun with a girl for a change....”

Garam squirmed on the floor, but Sakkuth looked down at the man that was spewing killing intent to him as if it were insignificant.

He bared his bloodied teeth and smirked.

“Sweetheart, when you spew out killing intent towards someone, you really have to have a strong, focused intention to kill them and stab them in one place. That way, at least my skin will feel itchy. You can't do anything with that kind of dirty dog ??mentality. Do you understand?”

With those words, Sakkuth turned away, shrugging off Garam's hand. It wasn't even worth stomping on.

“Kurururu, now-”

Sakkuth stretched out his hands toward Kirko, who had fallen to the ground.

...No, he tried to stretch.

Kuoooooo!

If only it hadn't been for the explosion from behind him and for the killing intent that looked like it was going to rip his throat out at any moment.

“...Hugh!?”

Without realizing it, he covered his throat with his hand.

The killing intent that had just been blasted from his back was beyond his imagination, it was something that would not only shred his throat and heart, but would pierce his entire body dozens or hundreds of times.

He turned his sweaty face to stare at the place where it had come from.

Stupid dog, stupid Garam. Behind the fallen lowly guard stood another prisoner of similar size.

“Is this really a way to radiate killing intent?”

A terrifying burst of killing intent was emanating from him.

Vikir. The Night Hound.

He was watching everything from behind.

Chapter 380

Kennel (1)

◆

Vikir, a low-ranking guard with no name or affiliation.

No one knew the identity or intentions of this hound that melted into the darkness of Nouvelle Vague.

'Did I give the picaresque mask to Camus for no reason? Maybe I should have kept it a little longer.'

Vikir thought as he moved forward, his eyes fixed on the ceiling.

It's easier to be a little smaller to avoid the prying eyes of the guards.

Vikir briefly wondered if turning into a puppy would make it easier to hide.

...But Vikir soon had to change his mind.

There wasn't a single dog or cat in the Nouvelle Vague.

If he were to change into a dog, he would be very noticeable.

The guards occasionally had pets, but they were usually crayfish, crabs, and octopuses, and occasionally there were seals, fish, and water buffalo.

'If you're going to have pets, you're going to need an aquarium.'

This is the deep ocean, after all.

Vikir dropped to the floor, realizing that all the people around him were gone.

5th floor. Vikir's primary destination for his escape.

In front of him was a vast sea.

The vast plaza had large circular pools in each section, with narrow, steep passageways between them.

An aquarium, or fish farm.

This was the only aquarium in Nouvelle Vague.

“Let's see what they're keeping.”

Vikir pulled up a bundle of ropes stacked in the corner of the aquarium.

Then, he threaded the pickled sea bass onto a hook as big as the anchor of a decent ship attached to the end and threw it into the pool.

Pungdeong-

The bait sank into the salt water of the pool.

Then, there was a reaction.

Swoosh.

It was visible above the surface. A long, gigantic shadow approaching the bait.

...Snap!

The rope pulled taut.

Vikir clenched his hands together and yanked on the rope.

Chwaaaaaag-

A huge peak of water rose above the surface, and what was beneath the water was soon impaled on the hook.

It was a giant eel.

“...Hmm. So this is a Gulper eel.”

The appearance of the 'Gulper eel' was indeed bizarre.

Its head and belly were enormous, with a skinny, tiny tail.

Meanwhile, its mouth, which takes up more than 90% of its head, is as large and wide as the main entrance to a great temple.

Despite its grotesque appearance, it was surprisingly not a monster from the Demon World, but an endemic species that originally lived in the deep sea.

It is also known by nicknames such as One-bite eel, Gulping eel, Elevator eel, etc.

[Geu-ooooo!]

This giant deep-sea creature was immediately irritated when it was dragged to the surface.

When the huge mouth opens wide, one can see gums protruding from the teeth, each one shaped like a fish hook.

Behind each tooth was a row of razor-sharp barbs, as if to say, once bitten, never let go.

...Of course.

“It's a spoiled eel.”

It posed no threat to Vikir.

Bam!

With a single slap, Vikir broke most of the eel's teeth and dragged the limp, dripping eel all the way back to the surface.

“That's a lot of them. Is this the biggest?”

Vikir looked over at the countless eels swimming in circles in the aquarium's pool.

The one he had just caught happened to be the largest.

This Gulper Eel is a species of eel that is bred in captivity at Nouvelle Vague.

It's characterized by having a body that's too large and fins and tail that are too small to swim well, but its bulk and light weight allow it to float in the currents and roam the depths of the ocean.

Most of their bodies are made up of water, and the rest are bones and skin, so there's no meat to be had.

What's more, they're so fishy and foul-smelling that they're hardly edible.

As you can see, they're not even cute enough to keep as pets.

...So why is this seemingly useless species being farmed in Nouvelle Vague?

“Because this is the only 'elevator' to the surface.”

Vikir stared at the Gulper Eel gasping in front of him.

Getting down to the Nouvelle Vague from the surface is simple.

It's a long, long way to sail through the harsh waters.

At 12 midnight, the vortex that serves as the primary gateway opens, and a prisoner is placed inside an orthoharcon alloy coffin and allowed to sink.

The coffin slowly sinks with the current and eventually arrives at Nouvelle Vague, 10,000 meters below the surface.

...But how do you get from the Nouvelle Vague to the surface?

You can use a Gulper Eel.

It has a big mouth and an even bigger stomach. It can hold any number of people.

Its flesh is soft and its skin is tough, allowing it to survive the crushing pressure of the deep sea.

Gulper Eels with these biological characteristics are bred to an appropriate size according to the body size of the occupants.

In the rare event that it is necessary to go to the surface, a Gulper eel of the right size is selected and the rider opens its mouth and enters its stomach.

Gulper eels are built to withstand water pressure, but they have little ability to swim on their own, so they ride a “specific current” to the surface and are slowly swept up to the surface.

Hence the nickname “elevator eel”.

“ ... I just need to break through that one bubble and I'll be out of here.”

At the end of the tanks, the passageways look out onto the vast depths of the ocean.

However, there is actually a transparent mucus barrier separating the two spaces.

This sticky, transparent wall of mucus, which looks like a soap bubble, is called “Flubber” by the Nouvelle Vague guards.

BDISSEM and Flubber are the two key substances that keep Nouvelle Vague alive.

BDISSEM creates order by binding the prisoners' mana and strength, while Flubber keeps water from flowing into the castle from the outside, allowing the prison itself to be maintained.

Both have one thing in common: they are mysterious substances whose identities have yet to be determined.

Sticky...

Vikir frowned at the mysterious mucus that covered the windows, and indeed the entire castle of Nouvelle Vague.

Flubber was a substance that was responsible for Nouvelle Vague's security alongside the BDISSEM, but it was nowhere near as strong as the BDISSEM.

Now that he was free of his restraints, there was no reason why Vikir, with his mana, shouldn't be able to penetrate this Flubber.

Squirm.

Vikir tugged on the eel's tail and approached the window.

The eel didn't want to move from its spot, but it didn't matter.

Their bodies are too slimy to fit through the narrow window, and they don't have the ability to swim, so they just follow the current.

“Is this for the purpose of restraining a giant? Why is it so big?”

Vikir looked at the eel he'd just caught.

It was a large eel so large that it could be considered a restraining weapon for the giants.

There were only a few of these in the aquarium, while other aquariums were full of smaller ones.

Kugugug-

Vikir attached the reins to the eel's tongue, and soon the line was stretched across its stomach.

Even if the eel didn't have the ability to swim, he'd at least be able to control the direction of its fins.

And then.

...Poof!

Vikir kicked the eel out of the water.

Splash!

The flubber mucus ripped away, and the eel slipped into the darkness of the deep.

The eel's stomach was empty.

Since then, Vikir has reeled in several more eels, using rope, hooks, and a pile of perch in the corner as bait.

Three small ones, just big enough for him, and two bigger than the last one.

Vikir did the same to them, tying a halter to their tongues and fins, and shoved them out the window.

The flubber window, once torn, healed quickly, so he didn't have to worry about the seawater continuing to rush in.

Then, as Vikir was pushing the sixth eel out of the water, Decarabia asked.

[Human, why do you keep throwing these eels into the sea? I'm not even going to ride it.].

“To distract them. It would take a lot of manpower to chase them all down, and it would take a long time.”

[Aha. That's a good idea.]

“It's always a good idea to have a distraction when you can afford one. Especially if you're going to break out.”

[So now we're on our seventh eel, huh? But why did we only catch six eels, don't we have to catch one more?]

Decarabia questioned Vikir, who threw all the eels out the window.

Vikir's answer was short.

“I'm not going out.”

[...What?]

Decarabia asked in disbelief.

[No, if you're not going to, why did you untie the eel in the first place?]

“I told you, distraction.”

Vikir smiled thinly.

“Riding the eel is a little later. The jailbreak is not yet finalized.”

If we go out now, we'll be caught, no matter how many eels we untie. The currents are too slow.

Also, since there was no drinking water or food stored up, it was impossible to go on a voyage without knowing how long it would take.

There was also the risk that the eels would be eaten by larger deep-sea creatures along the way, or that they would run aground on reefs or rough currents.

So Vikir wanted to go into the escape prepared.

This is because it is right to exclude uncertain factors as much as possible.

...Just then.

“What is it, an escaped prisoner?”

An unfamiliar voice came from behind.

“...!”

Vikir instinctively sensed danger and wiped the burn marks from his face, returning to his bare skin.

Slowly turning around, Vikir hears footsteps approaching.

“I thought you were a guard because of your uniform, but I guess not.”

The voice turns to face Vikir, an admiring note of interest in its voice.

“Hmph- this is what you look like, the face of the man who broke my handcuffs.”

The being was admiring Vikir's face, not Garam's.

A young girl with green hair, lazy eyes, and a pale face that still looks to be in her early teens.

But the layers of restraints on her wrists and ankles were unmistakably familiar.

Despite wearing the uniform of a guard, the mysterious girl in the restraints wore a shiny rank on her chest patch.

<★>

One Star. The mark of a brigadier general, the rank above a colonel.

Vikir's eyes narrowed as he recognized her identity.

“...I see. You made that.”

One of Vikir's oldest questions was finally answered.

Chapter 381

Kennel (2)

◆

BDISSEM.

A mysterious substance that binds the mana and power of the prisoners in Nouvelle Vague.

Vikir had once vaguely speculated that it was made of plants.

-Title: 'Daylily Lumberjack'

Inflicts massive additional damage against creatures in plant form.

Taunt, Confuse, Blind, Bleed, Burn, Poison, and other status ailments last slightly longer.

Vikir's suspicions were confirmed, as he realized that the restraints, which he could not break no matter what, could be destroyed by the power of the Daylily Lumberjack, a title he had earned in the Hell Tree.

And Vikir realized that his guess was correct.

The girl before him was higher in rank than any of the guards he had ever met.

A brigadier general, even higher than the colonel's rank on Souaré and D'Ordume, where the warden was a colonel.

Brigadier General BDISSEM.

Although she looked like a young girl, her true self was completely different.

A being with the power and cunning of an old tree.

Her race was called the Ents, or Dryads.

If the beings between animals and humans are called the Beastman, then the beings between plants and humans are the Ent.

'...So, it makes perfect sense that all five wardens are non-human beings.'

Vikir was right.

D'Ordume was a sea crocodile, Souaré was an elf-dwarf hybrid, and the one in front of him, BDISSEM, was an Ent.

Meanwhile, BDISSEM stared at Vikir in wonder.

“I'm here to find out who broke my handcuffs. It was you, wasn't it?”

Apparently, BDISSEM can feel when the handcuffs she made are destroyed.

Shhhhhh.

The five fingers on the end of BDISSEM's arm elongated like vines, then turned black and turned into chains.

“How did you break it? Do it again.”

As soon as BDISSEM finished speaking, a chain of vines erupted from her body and rushed towards Vikir like a snake.

Chakang! Chakang! Chakang!

At the end of the chains, handcuffs and shackles were interlocked like the jaws of a snake.

One bite from that thing would instantly cause the bindings to be filled and the mana and power to be sealed.

Of course, Vikir had the power to destroy it.

But the thought of having his mana flow interrupted, even for a fraction of a second, was disturbing, so he simply stepped back and dodged all of her attacks.

BDISSEM pulled out more vines as enthusiastic.

“Fight me properly! You're letting me off the hook!”

She was quite angry for some reason.

She seemed to misunderstand why Vikir was only dodging and not fighting head-on.

Grrttt.

The sound of tree bark rubbing came out of BDISSEM's mouth.

The vines, hard and resilient like extremely concentrated rubber, flew out like whips, aimed at Vikir.

The blow was a blow, but what followed was even more annoying.

“This is all because of Warden Orca! That old man is making everyone overprotective and treating me like a child! Why am I being treated so differently from Flubber!”

Although Vikir didn't know what she was talking about, he had a vague idea of what had caused all the complaining.

Vikir had plenty of opportunities to fight back, but he kept backing away from BDISSEM's attacks.

He gently scratched her nerves.

“Go get a guardian. You're too young to fight.”

“What! I'm a hundred years older than you!”

“I do not fight with the opposite sex. Back off.”

“I have both male and female genders!”

“....”

So why the hell is this girl overprotected?

Vikir thought for a moment and then spoke.

“You are a valuable resource to the Nouvelle Vague, so take care of yourself. I don't want any disruption to the production and maintenance of the BDISSEM restraints.”

“...!”

“What if you die and the rest of the restraints lose their power?”

“...! ...! ...! ...!”

Judging by the look of surprise on BDISSEM's face with each of Vikir's words, that was the answer.

Then, her expression turned to one of uncontrollable irritation.

“So what? Stop telling me to save my body, I'm sick of it! I have freedom!”

Apparently, BDISSEM was living a life of confinement in an alley because of the production and maintenance of restraints.

And she seems to be under a lot of stress because of it.

'Well, I know it because I lived as a prisoner. The frustration of Nouvelle Vague.'

Vikir dodged a whip and did a backflip, landing on the other side of the aquarium.

Suddenly curious, Vikir turned to BDISSEM and asked.

“So, if you're so overprotected, how did you get here?”

“Hmm. That's because Orca, the old man, was away.”

Orca, the warden of Nouvelle Vague.

Come to think of it, Vikir hadn't seen his face since entering Nouvelle Vague.

“I heard the ground has been devastated these days? There were so many felons to send to the Nouvelle Vague that the old man was sent on a long-term mission to the ground? We have to face some kind of huge 'event' or something..... We don't know what that means.”

BDISSEM was quite a talkative individual, perhaps because she spent so much time alone.

Even against the less talkative Vikir, it was obvious by the way she kept talking to herself.

“I hear there's been a lot of talk about demons and gates lately. Hmm~ Things are complicated on the surface.”

“...!”

Vikir, who has a quiet personality, gained a lot of information from BDISSEM's chatter, which spouted things without being asked.

Vikir barely suppressed the slight impatience in his heart.

'Demons and Gates. The age of destruction is upon us.'

He saw it coming, and he can't save them all anyway.

Only those who cannot be left to die can be saved.

...The rising of the Great Demons.

...Gates of Destruction.

...The Rainy Season of Fear.

...Poseidon.

...And the Nouvelle Vague.

Vikir strung together the keywords in his mind.

Then he began to act.

“First, the immediate enemy.”

When things are overwhelming, it's best to tackle them head on.

...Flash!

Vikir awoke and summoned Beelzebub, the magic sword.

Having not breathed fresh air for so long, Beelzebub's strength was surging and he was radiating a crimson aura.

There was no need to use the solid aura of the Swordmaster.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

A gaseous aura that only an Expert could produce.

Vikir converted all of his aura into a gaseous form and scattered it.

“Heh, what is it? Are you an expert? With just an attack like this... huh!”

BDISSEM, who had been looking down on the gaseous aura that was spreading like a whirlwind, swallowed the wind in vain.

Gases were just gases, flickering and weak.

But its scale was a problem.

The gaseous aura that Vikir unleashed began to envelop an enormous area, as watery fog envelop an entire mountain.

An ordinary Expert-level swordsman couldn't even dream of it.

Jjeojeojeong! Jjeojeojeojeong!

The sound of anchors and ropes breaking or snapping could be heard throughout the aquarium.

Each molecule of Vikir's fog of strikes was a sharp, lethal weapon.

'The Swordmaster's solid aura is good for one-on-one combat, but the Expert's gaseous aura is more effective for wiping out large areas.'

Vikir had no intention of killing BDISSEM.

Now that he knew who she was and what she was capable of, there were endless ways to use her.

'...I'll keep her alive for now.'

He'd seen her power firsthand, and it was more than enough for him to handle.

So Vikir enveloped the area in a fog of strikes to subdue, not kill, BDISSEM.

It was the foundation of the Hound, the art of slowly cornering a prey.

“Ugh!”

BDISSEM was left with no room to move back as the entire space around her was covered in Vikir's strikes and aura.

There was only one path she could take now.

The aquarium. Into that pool of saltwater where the balloon eels were being bred.

...And finally.

Pung Pung!

BDISSEM dived deep into the pool.

Vikir realized that the plan had worked.

'Plants don't like salt.'

Normally, plants exposed to too much salt would burn the tips off their leaves and eventually die.

The Ent or Dryads, as beings who owe their life to plants, were no different.

What's more, the water here is ultra-deep, 10,000 meters below the surface.

It was extremely salty and concentrated, making the water feel sticky.

Pung!

Vikir dove into the saltwater pool to capture the weakened BDISSEM alive.

Several balloon eels approached, assuming they had run out of food, but were quickly cut to pieces by Vikir's charge.

'...Where are you?'

Vikir looked around, searching for BDISSEM, who must be sinking and weakening somewhere.

Just then.

“Hohoho- are you looking for me?”

A seductive female voice called out from somewhere.

“...!”

Vikir's head whipped around.

Churrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!

BDISSEM vines, much thicker and tougher than before, flew out and enveloped Vikir's entire body.

It was a speed that couldn't even be compared to fighting on land.

Vikir's eyes widened at the unexpectedness of the situation, and BDISSEM appeared before him.

With her hair flying in the extremely salty brine, she looked quite different than before.

Her body had matured, and her face was no longer that of a child.

Seeing the vast increase in BDISSEM's power, Vikir had to admit that he had made a mistake.

“ ...Was it a seaweed entity?”

He hadn't realized that the thing he'd dragged into the water was actually a bad hand.